TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice	O
Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
27th	O
and	O
28th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
1st	O
and	O
2d	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Ninth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
GERARD	B-pers
CONYERS	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Powis	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Denton	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
,	O
Esquire	O
,	O
Deputy-Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
JURORS	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
The	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Stirrup	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Bull	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Hartland	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Brookhouse	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hodgson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Belcher	I-pers
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Stanton	I-pers
,	O
Valentine	B-pers
Grimstead	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bowles	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Chandler	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Forster	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Chad	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Forth	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Dowdswell	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barnet	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mildred	I-place
Poultry	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
Shilling	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jewson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
passing	O
along	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
about	O
Seven	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
passing	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
perceived	O
him	O
to	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
:	O
he	O
missing	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
down	O
about	O
Ten	O
or	O
a	O
Dozen	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
which	O
a	O
Woman	O
came	O
and	O
catch	O
'd	O
up	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
laying	O
hold	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
got	O
four	O
of	O
them	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mildred	I-place
Poultry	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Shargol	I-pers
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
Poultry	B-place
,	O
he	O
missed	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
laying	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
found	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Prince	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
her	O
Male	O
Bastard	O
Infant	O
,	O
by	O
throwing	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
Vault	O
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
given	O
her	O
her	O
Linnen	O
to	O
wash	O
,	O
she	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
some	O
Tokens	O
on	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
made	O
her	O
suspect	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
whereupon	O
she	O
went	O
and	O
acquainted	O
her	O
Mistress	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Domville	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Information	O
of	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
,	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Midwife	O
,	O
that	O
upon	O
being	O
examin	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Vault	O
.	O
The	O
Midwife	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Child	O
after	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Vault	O
,	O
but	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
no	O
Marks	O
of	O
Violence	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
readily	O
confest	O
her	O
having	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
ill	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Fit	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Child	O
came	O
from	O
her	O
the	O
mean	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
kept	O
it	O
three	O
Days	O
in	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
design	O
'd	O
to	O
have	O
carried	O
it	O
and	O
left	O
it	O
in	O
some	O
Church-Yard	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
bring	O
it	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Family	O
coming	O
home	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
prevented	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
threw	O
it	O
down	O
the	O
Vault	O
.	O
The	O
Midwife	O
likewise	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
spoke	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
lay	O
her	O
four	O
Months	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
spoken	O
to	O
her	O
again	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
Months	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
about	O
ten	O
Days	O
before	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
believe	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
still	O
born	O
,	O
because	O
what	O
should	O
have	O
come	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
came	O
not	O
away	O
till	O
the	O
Night	O
after	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
sickly	O
,	O
weakly	O
Creature	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
made	O
some	O
Provision	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Child	O
,	O
when	O
born	O
,	O
by	O
her	O
Desire	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
pleaded	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Purpose	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Midwife	O
had	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
adding	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Fall	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
thought	O
occasion	O
'd	O
her	O
hasty	O
Delivery	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
,	O
upon	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Levy	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Katherine	I-place
Creed-Church	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
six	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
and	O
Fork	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
value	O
38	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Henriques	I-pers
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
Moses	B-pers
Henriques	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
to	O
see	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
who	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
was	O
her	O
Cousin	O
;	O
that	O
his	O
Mother	O
found	O
her	O
Desk	O
opened	O
and	O
several	O
Things	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
afterwards	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
apprehended	O
selling	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
and	O
Fork	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
his	O
Mother	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Mark	O
was	O
scratched	O
out	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
was	O
to	O
prevent	O
Disgrace	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
House	O
Maid	O
,	O
to	O
sell	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
knew	O
not	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
stole	O
.	O
Upon	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Craydon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
George	I-place
Buttolph	I-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Tatam	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Day	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
12	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Mother	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
Service	O
,	O
lay	O
with	O
her	O
Mother	O
;	O
that	O
sending	O
his	O
Maid	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
told	O
him	O
his	O
Chamber	O
Door	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
,	O
upon	O
examining	O
his	O
Drawers	O
,	O
he	O
missed	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
that	O
upon	O
his	O
making	O
some	O
Stir	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Westminster	O
.	O
The	O
Maid	O
Servant	O
depos	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
adding	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
in	O
her	O
Mother	O
's	O
Room	O
under	O
a	O
seeming	O
Surprize	O
at	O
her	O
coming	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
She	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lay	O
out	O
11	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
Half	O
,	O
in	O
Cloths	O
a	O
Day	O
or	O
two	O
after	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Tatam	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
ill	O
one	O
Day	O
,	O
she	O
lay	O
longer	O
a	O
Bed	O
than	O
ordinary	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
coming	O
in	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
asking	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
wanted	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
nothing	O
,	O
and	O
telling	O
her	O
Husband	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
lock	O
'd	O
,	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Husband	O
had	O
the	O
Key	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
coming	O
up	O
to	O
a	O
clear	O
Proof	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Cole-Church	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Pickard	I-pers
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
been	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
drinking	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
the	O
Spoon	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
found	O
at	O
Mr	O
.	O
Port	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Port	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
Spoon	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
broken	O
in	O
three	O
Pieces	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
stopp	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
advertis	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
own	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Spoon	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
Woodstreet	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchre	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bay	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Godfrey	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
ride	O
the	O
Horse	O
home	O
to	O
his	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
,	O
without	O
his	O
Leave	O
,	O
or	O
Knowledge	O
,	O
he	O
sold	O
him	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bennet	O
,	O
at	O
Edmunton	B-place
.	O
But	O
he	O
having	O
entrusted	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquited	O
him	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Abrams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Katherine	I-place
Creed-Church	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
an	O
Emerald	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Gold	O
Chain	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Henriques	I-pers
.	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
Evidence	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Mary	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Velvet	O
furbelow	O
'd	O
Scarf	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
four	O
Tea	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
February	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Tunny	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
being	O
cleaning	O
Knives	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
suspecting	O
her	O
,	O
follow	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Scarf	O
under	O
her	O
Riding-Hood	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
laid	O
down	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
threw	O
the	O
Spoons	O
on	O
the	O
Tea	O
Table	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
down	O
on	O
her	O
Knees	O
,	O
desiring	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
some	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
positive	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Bowes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
two	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
The	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Holloway	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
stolen	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
went	O
away	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
her	O
at	O
Gravesend	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
:	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
bought	O
the	O
Ring	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Summerfield	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
at	I-place
Bow	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Thomas	B-pers
George	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
his	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
Shirt	O
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Bow	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
near	O
Bow	O
Church	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
yes	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
bear	O
him	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
he	O
Knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
about	O
his	O
Neck	O
,	O
and	O
drag	O
'd	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Path	O
,	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
and	O
threaten	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
made	O
any	O
Noise	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
shoot	O
him	O
through	O
the	O
Head	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
off	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
Shirt	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Shilling	O
,	O
his	O
Knife	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
cut	O
his	O
Wrist	O
with	O
his	O
Knife	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
off	O
his	O
Shirt	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
with	O
him	O
a	O
brindle	O
Dog	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
white	O
Breast	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
bid	O
look	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
the	O
Dog	O
would	O
sieze	O
the	O
first	O
Man	O
he	O
met	O
,	O
and	O
hold	O
him	O
while	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Robinson	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Servant	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
Bow	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Day	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
between	O
Mile	O
End	O
and	O
Bow	O
,	O
met	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
carried	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
three	O
Cups	O
in	O
Bow	O
,	O
where	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
Description	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
afterwards	O
apprehended	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wrist	O
was	O
cut	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
another	O
Cut	O
under	O
his	O
right	O
Eye	O
:	O
This	O
was	O
confirmed	O
by	O
his	O
Servant	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Crane	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
describ	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
Dog	O
exactly	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Remnant	O
confirm	O
'd	O
what	O
Mr.	O
Crane	O
had	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
also	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
loose	O
Fellow	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Amy	B-pers
Scriven	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Wall	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Kerby	B-pers
,	O
and	O
George	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Holt	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Day	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
15	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
two	O
Gowns	O
,	O
two	O
Salts	O
,	O
four	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
Value	O
;	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
James	O
Holt	O
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
while	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
were	O
at	O
Church	O
,	O
a	O
Couple	O
of	O
Panes	O
of	O
Glass	O
were	O
broken	O
,	O
his	O
Room	O
enter	O
'd	O
,	O
his	O
Drawers	O
opened	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Goods	O
stolen	O
;	O
that	O
Amy	O
Scriven	O
going	O
away	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
he	O
suspected	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
getting	O
a	O
Warrant	O
,	O
apprehended	O
her	O
with	O
9	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
25	O
l.	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Isabella	B-pers
Hobbs	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
claim	O
'd	O
them	O
there	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
also	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
another	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Amy	O
Scriven	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
but	O
acquitted	O
her	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
Evidence	O
sufficient	O
,	O
against	O
George	O
Bennet	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	O
Wall	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Broughton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Hester	B-pers
Stream	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Riding-hood	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Cross	B-place
Street	I-place
,	O
with	O
her	O
Riding-hood	O
under	O
her	O
Arm	O
;	O
that	O
a	O
Person	O
came	O
behind	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
snatch	O
'd	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
pursued	O
and	O
taken	O
;	O
another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
upon	O
the	O
Woman	O
's	O
Out-cry	O
,	O
he	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
thrown	O
down	O
by	O
a	O
Dog	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
siez	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Riding-hood	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
by	O
him	O
;	O
another	O
Evidence	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
Riding-hood	O
's	O
being	O
taken	O
up	O
hard	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Man	O
ran	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
thrown	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
with	O
the	O
Riding-hood	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Frances	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Totty	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Curtains	O
,	O
a	O
Rug	O
,	O
Blankets	O
,	O
Sheets	O
,	O
Looking-glass	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
a	O
Lodging	O
of	O
him	O
for	O
20	O
d.	O
a	O
Week	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
about	O
8	O
a	O
Clock	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
them	O
good	O
Morrow	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Things	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Bigs	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
asking	O
her	O
for	O
the	O
Key	O
,	O
to	O
straiten	O
a	O
Curtain	O
Rod	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
all	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
Other	O
Evidences	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Purpose	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Sister	O
very	O
much	O
like	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
her	O
for	O
her	O
Sister	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
an	O
unfortunate	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
transported	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
hard	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
her	O
Sister	O
did	O
ill	O
Things	O
in	O
her	O
Name	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
should	O
suffer	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Frances	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Thompson	B-pers
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Blankets	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
another	O
Person	O
,	O
whom	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
Sister	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
Lodging	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
about	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
Possession	O
of	O
the	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
under	O
Presence	O
of	O
fetching	O
their	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
no	O
more	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
afterwards	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Things	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
It	O
was	O
her	O
Sister	O
.	O
But	O
all	O
the	O
Evidences	O
being	O
positive	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Persons	O
that	O
took	O
the	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
both	O
away	O
together	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
a	O
third	O
Time	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Cole	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
China	O
Curtains	O
,	O
Vallants	O
,	O
Sheets	O
,	O
Looking	O
Glass	O
,	O
Blankets	O
,	O
a	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Spelman	I-pers
,	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Spelman	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
another	O
Woman	O
,	O
whom	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
Sister	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
Lodging	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
under	O
a	O
pretence	O
of	O
being	O
Country	O
Gentlewomen	O
,	O
with	O
Country	O
Dirt	O
on	O
their	O
Riding-Hoods	O
.	O
She	O
desiring	O
a	O
Character	O
,	O
they	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
should	O
have	O
a	O
Character	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
from	O
the	O
Carrier	O
.	O
And	O
having	O
lain	O
there	O
but	O
one	O
Night	O
went	O
away	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Room	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
saw	O
her	O
no	O
more	O
till	O
she	O
saw	O
her	O
in	O
Newgate	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
nothing	O
material	O
to	O
offer	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
bare	O
Denial	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Frances	O
Allen	O
,	O
alias	O
Thompson	O
,	O
was	O
again	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
fourth	O
Time	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
like	O
Fact	O
,	O
in	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Frances	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
Joseph	O
Allen	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Quilt	O
,	O
Counterpane	O
,	O
Sheets	O
,	O
Curtains	O
,	O
Etc	O
.	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Paul	I-pers
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
took	O
the	O
Lodging	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
lay	O
not	O
there	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Monday	O
Morning	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Paul	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Joseph	O
Allen	O
,	O
after	O
his	O
Apprehension	O
,	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
sold	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Knolles	O
,	O
at	O
Horsly-Down	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
but	O
Frances	O
Allen	O
being	O
suppos	O
'd	O
to	O
act	O
under	O
the	O
Direction	O
of	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Frances	O
Allen	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
again	O
with	O
Joseph	O
Allen	O
,	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
like	O
Fact	O
,	O
in	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Paul	B-pers
Hyron	I-pers
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
Joseph	O
Allen	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
But	O
acquitted	O
Frances	O
Allen	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Biggs	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
four	O
China	O
Curtains	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rudkins	I-pers
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
another	O
,	O
took	O
Lodgings	O
of	O
her	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
be	O
Sons	O
of	O
a	O
Country	O
Malster	O
that	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
about	O
an	O
Estate	O
of	O
60	O
l.	O
per	O
Annum	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Morning	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
look	O
'd	O
something	O
bulky	O
.	O
Upon	O
missing	O
the	O
Goods	O
she	O
apply	O
'd	O
her	O
self	O
to	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
,	O
and	O
he	O
procur	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
apprehended	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
Goods	O
for	O
42	O
s.	O
to	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Knolls	I-pers
,	O
at	O
Horsly	O
Down	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
sent	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
however	O
,	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
or	O
his	O
ever	O
having	O
made	O
any	O
Acknowledgment	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
third	O
Time	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Curtains	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Blackham	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
lodge	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
appear	O
'd	O
very	O
bulky	O
;	O
and	O
not	O
coming	O
home	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
she	O
looking	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Key-hole	O
,	O
and	O
missing	O
the	O
Curtains	O
,	O
she	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Things	O
to	O
be	O
missing	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Person	O
like	O
him	O
that	O
does	O
such	O
Crimes	O
,	O
whose	O
Sister	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Misfortune	O
to	O
marry	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
for	O
that	O
Person	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Merryday	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Suits	O
of	O
lac	O
'd	O
Head-Cloths	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Grace	B-pers
Dorney	I-pers
.	O
And	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Meredith	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Grace	O
Dorney	O
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
February	O
.	O
Grace	O
Dorney	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
her	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Drawer	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Stays	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
said	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
her	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
Mistress	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
some	O
Words	O
,	O
being	O
of	O
different	O
Religions	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
;	O
but	O
her	O
Mistress	O
not	O
giving	O
her	O
leave	O
to	O
go	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
without	O
leave	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
coming	O
home	O
,	O
she	O
charg	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
own	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
swore	O
positively	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
not	O
hers	O
but	O
theirs	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Paul	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bone	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
February	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Duncomb	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Owen	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Duncomb	O
being	O
a	O
Lodger	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
She	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Isaak	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Drew	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Edward	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Robins	B-pers
,	O
since	O
deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Ryman	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
Eighteen	O
Holland	O
Smocks	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
Value	O
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Servant	O
Maid	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Doors	O
and	O
Windows	O
were	O
made	O
fast	O
when	O
the	O
Family	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
up	O
about	O
six	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
the	O
Street	O
Door	O
was	O
unlock	O
'd	O
,	O
unbolted	O
,	O
and	O
unbarr	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
was	O
cut	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shutter	O
of	O
a	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Casement	O
open	O
'd	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Inon	I-pers
being	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
into	O
the	O
Round	O
House	O
,	O
before	O
Colonel	O
Carpenter	O
,	O
tax	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
Lewis	O
,	O
deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
as	O
being	O
Accomplices	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
Henry	O
Inon	O
being	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
examin	O
'd	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Nature	O
of	O
an	O
Oath	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
order	O
'd	O
by	O
he	O
Court	O
to	O
be	O
indicted	O
upon	O
his	O
own	O
Confession	O
.	O
But	O
their	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Isaak	O
Baker	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Bisset	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Godfrey	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
own	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
Gown	O
for	O
9	O
s.	O
but	O
she	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Pleasant	B-pers
Bateman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Uxbridge	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
her	O
Male	O
Instant	O
Bastard	O
Child	O
,	O
by	O
suffocating	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
Close-stool-pan	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Fact	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Grey	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
sitting	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
complaining	O
of	O
what	O
great	O
Pain	O
she	O
had	O
gone	O
through	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
answer	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
more	O
to	O
go	O
through	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
she	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
sitting	O
upon	O
the	O
Close-stool	O
something	O
stopp	O
'd	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
thereupon	O
she	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Child	O
in	O
the	O
Close-stool-pan	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Pan	O
was	O
pretty	O
full	O
of	O
Urine	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
She	O
did	O
believe	O
the	O
Child	O
might	O
be	O
born	O
alive	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Head	O
of	O
it	O
being	O
under	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Pan	O
was	O
sufficient	O
to	O
suffocate	O
it	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Glede	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Grey	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
see	O
the	O
Child	O
in	O
the	O
Close-stool-pan	O
.	O
She	O
believes	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
its	O
full	O
Time	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
fine	O
Child	O
,	O
the	O
Hands	O
were	O
shut	O
when	O
its	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
appear	O
'd	O
no	O
Marks	O
of	O
Violence	O
.	O
The	O
Child	O
's	O
Head	O
lay	O
downwards	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
Water	O
sufficient	O
to	O
strangle	O
it	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
She	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Pan	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
its	O
full	O
Growth	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
believe	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
Still-Born	O
.	O
These	O
Evidences	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
perceiving	O
her	O
bigger	O
than	O
ordinary	O
,	O
and	O
often	O
taking	O
Physick	O
,	O
they	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
tell	O
her	O
,	O
they	O
believ	O
'd	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
Child	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
own	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
wore	O
a	O
thick	O
Coat	O
.	O
The	O
Midwife	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
being	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
Child	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Pan	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
laid	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
did	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
born	O
alive	O
.	O
That	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Soil	O
,	O
and	O
enough	O
to	O
suffocate	O
the	O
Child	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
had	O
lain	O
there	O
,	O
she	O
supposes	O
,	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
believ	O
'd	O
she	O
might	O
have	O
taken	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
second	O
Birth	O
was	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
separated	O
it	O
from	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Fit	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
deliver	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
her	O
Senses	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
made	O
Provision	O
for	O
the	O
Child	O
;	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Evidences	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
who	O
did	O
depose	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
Months	O
before	O
,	O
seen	O
several	O
Things	O
proper	O
for	O
a	O
Child	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
several	O
Fits	O
but	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
help	O
her	O
self	O
in	O
an	O
Hour	O
's	O
Time	O
after	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
having	O
heard	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
,	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Griffith	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Haynes	I-pers
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
Side	O
of	O
his	O
Body	O
under	O
the	O
right	O
Pap	O
,	O
the	O
Breadth	O
of	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
five	O
Inches	O
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Blew	O
Boar	O
's	O
Head	O
in	O
Exeter	O
Street	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
were	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
some	O
Words	O
arose	O
betwixt	O
them	O
about	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Names	O
were	O
call	O
'd	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Lie	O
given	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
You	O
are	O
not	O
worth	O
a	O
Man	O
's	O
Anger	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
was	O
his	O
Man	O
at	O
any	O
Thing	O
,	O
let	O
him	O
Name	O
Time	O
and	O
Place	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
answered	O
,	O
No	O
Time	O
like	O
the	O
present	O
.	O
And	O
soon	O
after	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hatch	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
crossing	O
the	O
Fields	O
from	O
St.	O
Gile	O
's	O
to	O
Clerkewell	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
two	O
Soldiers	O
walking	O
before	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
Field	O
beyond	O
the	O
Lay-Stall	O
,	O
near	O
Tottenham	B-place
Court	I-place
,	O
they	O
both	O
stripp	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
drew	O
their	O
Swords	O
;	O
the	O
deceased	O
drawing	O
first	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
he	O
follow	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
pretty	O
high	O
them	O
,	O
He	O
bid	O
them	O
consider	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
about	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
made	O
several	O
Passes	O
at	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
half	O
Swords	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
at	O
one	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
Wounds	O
given	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
retreated	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
went	O
to	O
pushing	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
some	O
Blood	O
upon	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Shirt	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
Charles	O
leave	O
off	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
have	O
enough	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
push	O
'd	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
receiv	O
'd	O
the	O
Wound	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
suppos	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
he	O
dropp	O
'd	O
the	O
Point	O
of	O
his	O
Sword	O
.	O
They	O
both	O
shook	O
Hands	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
their	O
Cloths	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
about	O
twelve	O
Yards	O
off	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
deceased	O
's	O
Knees	O
then	O
began	O
to	O
fail	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
fell	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
rais	O
'd	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
He	O
believed	O
he	O
was	O
only	O
sick	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
dy	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
Spot	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
he	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
made	O
no	O
Resistance	O
,	O
and	O
beckoning	O
to	O
some	O
Bricklayers	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
sight	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
being	O
a	O
drinking	O
with	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Ale-house	O
,	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
Scoundrel	O
and	O
Blockhead	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
He	O
would	O
strip	O
off	O
his	O
Skin	O
alive	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
quiet	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
followed	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
call	O
'd	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
their	O
Serjeant	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
Blew	O
Boar	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Serjeant	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
How	O
could	O
you	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
spent	O
8	O
d.	O
to	O
beg	O
such	O
a	O
Man	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Savoy	O
?	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
said	O
no	O
such	O
Thing	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
the	O
Serjeant	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
There	O
's	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
says	O
it	O
,	O
meaning	O
the	O
Deceased	O
.	O
That	O
upon	O
this	O
some	O
Words	O
arose	O
between	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
apprehend	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
sight	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
quiet	O
,	O
peaceable	O
Person	O
,	O
and	O
among	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
his	O
Captain	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Murder	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Clerkewell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Broad	O
Piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
23	O
s.	O
2	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Abbot	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Trunk	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
not	O
amounting	O
to	O
a	O
clear	O
Proof	O
of	O
her	O
committing	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Burk	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstans	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Fitzer	I-pers
,	O
near	O
the	O
High-Way	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Jacket	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
2	O
Tobacco	O
Box	O
,	O
Knife	O
and	O
Fork	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Mile	O
End	O
,	O
and	O
stopp	O
'd	O
at	O
Stepney	B-place
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
was	O
met	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
Field	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
back	O
Lane	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
hedging	O
Bill	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
he	O
cut	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
he	O
wanted	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
must	O
have	O
his	O
Jacket	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
over	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
Bill	O
while	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
it	O
off	O
,	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
bid	O
him	O
be	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
speak	O
a	O
Word	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
five	O
Accomplices	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
made	O
any	O
Stir	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Apprehension	O
,	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Constable	O
had	O
taken	O
his	O
Knife	O
and	O
Fork	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Pocket	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
sworn	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Father	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
were	O
going	O
home	O
,	O
the	O
13th	O
Day	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
at	O
Work	O
,	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Langerwood	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
Rope	O
Maker	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
home	O
,	O
between	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
second	O
Field	O
,	O
next	O
the	O
back	O
Lane	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
half	O
Way-house	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
his	O
Bill	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
swearing	O
,	O
damn	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
them	O
stand	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
the	O
Bill	O
,	O
chopt	O
his	O
Father	O
down	O
;	O
he	O
thinking	O
his	O
Father	O
to	O
be	O
murder	O
'd	O
,	O
made	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
catching	O
up	O
his	O
Father	O
's	O
Stick	O
,	O
attack	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
cut	O
several	O
Times	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Wound	O
in	O
the	O
Arm	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
clos	O
'd	O
in	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
got	O
him	O
up	O
against	O
a	O
Bank	O
,	O
and	O
over	O
powering	O
him	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Hedging	O
Bill	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
his	O
Father	O
getting	O
up	O
to	O
his	O
Assistance	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
young	O
Man	O
coming	O
by	O
,	O
they	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Constable	O
;	O
John	O
Andrews	O
,	O
the	O
Father	O
confirm	O
'd	O
what	O
his	O
Son	O
had	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
shew	O
'd	O
the	O
Wound	O
in	O
his	O
Head	O
.	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Parkins	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
assisted	O
the	O
former	O
Evidences	O
,	O
in	O
apprehending	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
adding	O
,	O
He	O
saw	O
the	O
Constable	O
take	O
a	O
Knife	O
and	O
Fork	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Pocket	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
sworn	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
by	O
William	O
Fitzer	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
rob	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
Day	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
for	O
assaulting	O
James	B-pers
Westwood	I-pers
,	O
near	O
the	O
High-Way	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
Rule	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
Shilling	O
,	O
and	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
home	O
from	O
Work	O
about	O
seven	O
a	O
Clock	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
he	O
was	O
met	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Bill	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Collar	O
,	O
and	O
holding	O
his	O
Bill	O
over	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
that	O
was	O
all	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
,	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
bid	O
him	O
take	O
off	O
his	O
Frock	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
holding	O
the	O
Bill	O
over	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
hastened	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
thought	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
cut	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
before	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
it	O
off	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
hard	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
Frock	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
poor	O
Man	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
knew	O
him	O
,	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
dare	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
if	O
he	O
made	O
any	O
Stir	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
five	O
Accomplices	O
in	O
the	O
Field	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
.	O
That	O
going	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
his	O
Frock	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
again	O
another	O
Day	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
might	O
do	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
likewise	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Map	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Van	I-pers
Blake	I-pers
;	O
and	O
three	O
other	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Cary	I-pers
;	O
and	O
also	O
three	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Seephens	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	O
Price	O
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Price	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
confess	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
after	O
his	O
Apprehension	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Top	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Shirts	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
depos	O
'd	O
likewise	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fryer	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Shirts	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Back	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
going	O
along	O
Clerkenwell	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
ease	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Shirts	O
in	O
a	O
Bag	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
Head-cloths	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Linnen	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Man	O
came	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
penneyworth	O
of	O
Aniseed	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Friend	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Crown	O
Piece	O
to	O
change	O
and	O
while	O
his	O
Back	O
was	O
turn	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Things	O
were	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
Evidence	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
cheating	O
Sampson	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Shilling	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
another	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Dram	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
five	O
Shilling	O
Piece	O
to	O
change	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
having	O
given	O
the	O
other	O
Person	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Crown	O
,	O
he	O
wanted	O
a	O
half	O
Crown	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
not	O
having	O
an	O
half	O
Crown	O
,	O
he	O
swept	O
some	O
Money	O
into	O
the	O
Drawer	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
her	O
give	O
him	O
his	O
Crown	O
Piece	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
three	O
half	O
Pence	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
counting	O
her	O
Money	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
put	O
in	O
all	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
miss	O
'd	O
2	O
s.	O
he	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Shilling	O
for	O
a	O
Shilling	O
she	O
miss	O
'd	O
at	O
first	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
sufficiently	O
affecting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Roger	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Field	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Coach	O
Glasses	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Drelincourt	I-pers
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Glasses	O
were	O
stolen	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
the	O
Glasses	O
were	O
given	O
him	O
by	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pierce	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Lady	O
Philippa	B-pers
Walton	I-pers
's	O
Coachman	O
,	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
The	O
Coachman	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
upon	O
Oath	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
found	O
in	O
several	O
Stories	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Williams	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
the	O
Night	O
Time	O
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
24	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
about	O
eight	O
a	O
Clock	O
the	O
Key	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Pin	O
of	O
his	O
Window	O
,	O
the	O
Shutter	O
was	O
taken	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Shoes	O
taken	O
,	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shoes	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Lodging	O
of	O
Mill	O
's	O
Mother	O
,	O
and	O
Mills	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
one	O
Pair	O
to	O
Gibson	O
,	O
which	O
Gibson	O
sold	O
to	O
Edward	B-pers
Predom	I-pers
,	O
and	O
were	O
own	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Mills	O
pleaded	O
he	O
found	O
three	O
Pair	O
of	O
old	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Slippers	O
,	O
upon	O
a	O
Bulk	O
.	O
Mills	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
which	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Darvel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstan	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sheet	O
a	O
Bolster	O
and	O
Cap	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Arundel	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
depos	O
'd	O
She	O
hir	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
fill	O
Quills	O
,	O
for	O
3	O
s.	O
per	O
Week	O
,	O
she	O
gave	O
her	O
her	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
the	O
Sheet	O
,	O
Bolster	O
,	O
and	O
Cap	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
her	O
Mistress	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Cap	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Catherine	I-place
Creed	I-place
Church	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
50	O
l.	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fellows	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Holditch	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Eannerson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
being	O
carrying	O
Sugar	O
Loaves	O
,	O
at	O
two	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
Watch	O
apprehended	O
them	O
upon	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
and	O
examining	O
them	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
They	O
bought	O
them	O
in	O
Goodmans	O
Fields	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Celler	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
before	O
mentioned	O
had	O
been	O
broken	O
open	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Sugar	O
Loaves	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Sugar	O
was	O
mark	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Mark	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
pleaded	O
,	O
They	O
bought	O
the	O
Sugar	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
produce	O
that	O
Man	O
,	O
nor	O
prove	O
their	O
buying	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Keatly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.Bernard	I-place
Pauls	I-place
Wharf	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
a	O
House-man	O
's	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
How	I-pers
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
Her	O
Confession	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fryer	I-pers
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
but	O
however	O
,	O
she	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
;	O
saying	O
,	O
They	O
were	O
given	O
her	O
by	O
a	O
Man	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Davenport	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bernard	I-place
Pauls	I-place
Wharf	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
34	O
Boards	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Tobias	B-pers
Priest	I-pers
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
One	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
That	O
he	O
bought	O
Boards	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
own	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
:	O
Two	O
other	O
Evidences	O
swore	O
,	O
the	O
one	O
to	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
to	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
Mr.	O
Priests	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
He	O
bought	O
the	O
boards	O
of	O
a	O
Stranger	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
Temple	O
Gate	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
paid	O
him	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
a	O
Receipt	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Priest	O
;	O
which	O
Receipt	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Hands	O
of	O
one	O
Plat	O
,	O
at	O
Putney	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
not	O
yet	O
come	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Ford	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchre	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
6	O
Shifts	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
Moidone	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
Guinea	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
February	O
.	O
Winifred	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
She	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
Shift	O
of	O
hers	O
,	O
under	O
her	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
Moidore	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
false	O
Key	O
to	O
her	O
Husband	O
's	O
Drawers	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Mony	O
was	O
,	O
the	O
Moidore	O
had	O
a	O
Mark	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
swore	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
She	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
bought	O
the	O
Key	O
in	O
Forestreet	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
made	O
Use	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
Drawers	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
She	O
found	O
the	O
Key	O
and	O
the	O
Moidore	O
,	O
ty	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Rag	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
for	O
the	O
Shift	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
given	O
her	O
by	O
her	O
Mistress	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Phillip	B-pers
Large	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Paul	I-place
Covent-Gardens	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rone	I-pers
,	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
February	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
Play-house	O
,	O
going	O
into	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
.	O
Another	O
Gentleman	O
depos	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
many	O
Times	O
seen	O
him	O
picking	O
Pockets	O
about	O
the	O
Playhouse	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Handkerchief	O
and	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
Crowd	O
he	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
threw	O
away	O
one	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
three	O
more	O
,	O
when	O
carried	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Olave	I-place
Hart-Street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
French	I-pers
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Breeches	O
were	O
missing	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Turmer	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Messenger	O
,	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Breches	O
in	O
his	O
Lodging	O
,	O
hid	O
in	O
a	O
Private	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
wear	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
lent	O
him	O
these	O
Breeches	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Richard	B-pers
Henley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Black	I-place
Fryers	I-place
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Elmhurst	O
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
recommended	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
as	O
a	O
Customer	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Barber	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
borrow	O
'd	O
a	O
Wig	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
before	O
the	O
Commissioners	O
of	O
the	O
Customs	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
the	O
Barber	O
's	O
Wife	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
Wig	O
ty	O
'd	O
up	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
another	O
Wig	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Body	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
but	O
him	O
and	O
his	O
Friend	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
borrowing	O
of	O
the	O
Wig	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Wig	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
stolen	O
,	O
he	O
deny	O
'd	O
he	O
knew	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
not	O
thinking	O
the	O
Evidence	O
sufficient	O
to	O
charge	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
as	O
to	O
this	O
,	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stanes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Flitches	O
of	O
Bacon	O
,	O
two	O
Blankets	O
,	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
coming	O
up	O
to	O
a	O
Proof	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Wills	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
Jaunary	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
upon	O
his	O
being	O
apprehended	O
.	O
He	O
pleaded	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
drinking	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
drunk	O
,	O
put	O
on	O
the	O
Gown	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Frolick	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
home	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Rutt	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tailor	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
d.	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
going	O
along	O
Drury	B-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
thrown	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
pretty	O
much	O
in	O
Liquor	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
Rutt	O
called	O
some	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Dubart	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Linnen	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Magdalen	B-pers
Dessessey	I-pers
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Matter	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Linnen	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Simon	B-pers
Clifton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
liv	O
'd	O
when	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
stolen	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
The	O
Things	O
were	O
given	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
lie	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
consent	O
,	O
therefore	O
he	O
indicted	O
her	O
for	O
stealing	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Solomon	B-pers
Barlow	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Sheep	O
Skins	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Coleburn	I-pers
;	O
and	O
three	O
Sheep	O
Skins	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Arthur	B-pers
Elborough	I-pers
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Facts	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Eslic	I-pers
,	O
jun	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pestle	O
and	O
Mortar	O
,	O
Linnen	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
His	O
Father	O
was	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
took	O
such	O
ill	O
Courses	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
so	O
irreclaimable	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
take	O
this	O
Method	O
to	O
save	O
him	O
from	O
the	O
Gallows	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Isabel	B-pers
Carr	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Wig	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Bland	I-pers
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstans	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lambert	I-pers
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Blackford	I-pers
,	O
with	B-pers
Jane	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
with	O
Jane	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
;	O
3	O
half	O
Firkins	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
Barrel	O
of	O
Soap	O
,	O
2	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Oil	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cleeve	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Proof	O
to	O
convict	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Sammon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sack	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tovey	I-pers
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
from	O
James	B-pers
Orms	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
And	O
this	O
Fact	O
being	O
also	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Buttolp	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Fabian	I-pers
,	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
entertain	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
Charity	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Fabian	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
some	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
others	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Capers	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Worrel	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Agate	O
handled	O
Knives	O
and	O
Forks	O
,	O
2	O
Snuff	O
Boxes	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Valentine	B-pers
Henry	I-pers
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Katherine	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Fustain	O
Frock	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Nodes	I-pers
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Indictment	O
being	O
laid	O
Thomas	O
Nodes	O
,	O
instead	O
of	O
John	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Hester	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Rug	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
from	O
Katherine	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Rug	O
and	O
Pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
To	O
be	O
whipp	O
'd	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Whitehall	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Whitehall	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
19	O
Yards	O
of	O
blue	O
and	O
white	O
Linnen	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Goodman	I-pers
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
latter	O
for	O
receiving	O
it	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Mother	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
Linnen	O
in	O
Hounsditch	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Shears	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
He	O
found	O
the	O
Linnen	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Gravel	O
Lane	O
.	O
The	O
Mother	O
pleaded	O
,	O
It	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
her	O
by	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Douglass	I-pers
,	O
as	O
his	O
Wife	O
's	O
,	O
he	O
desiring	O
her	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
her	O
Son	O
being	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
not	O
it	O
was	O
stolen	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
John	O
Whitehall	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Swan	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Taff	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
Former	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Wig	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
7	O
flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Gregory	O
Swinney	O
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
Sarah	O
Swan	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
that	O
Jane	O
Taff	O
sold	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
,	O
that	O
Taff	O
knew	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
wherefore	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
Jane	O
Taff	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
Sarah	O
Swan	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Waller	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Humphreys	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Hassel	B-pers
Short	I-pers
the	O
6th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Linney	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Barns	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Blanket	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Clavering	I-pers
,	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Body	O
appearing	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
February	O
.	O
Several	O
Persons	O
appear	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
was	O
so	O
silly	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
rather	O
have	O
a	O
Half-penny	O
than	O
a	O
Shilling	O
;	O
and	O
gave	O
several	O
Instances	O
of	O
his	O
want	O
of	O
Reason	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
But	O
some	O
Persons	O
deposing	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
would	O
have	O
taken	O
Money	O
to	O
compound	O
for	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
insisted	O
upon	O
12	O
or	O
14	O
l.	O
the	O
Court	O
ordered	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
give	O
Security	O
for	O
his	O
Appearance	O
the	O
next	O
Sessions	O
,	O
and	O
oblig	O
'd	O
the	O
Persons	O
who	O
so	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
enter	O
into	O
a	O
Recognizance	O
then	O
to	O
prosecute	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Inon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
Reverend	O
Mr.	O
William	B-pers
Ryman	I-pers
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elisabeth	B-pers
Staughton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Linnen	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Burch	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
malicious	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
her	O
Indictment	O
granted	O
her	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Frost	I-pers
,	O
of	O
,	O
Lalam	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
black	O
Mare	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
l	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
plead	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
House	O
on	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Reeves	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
Money	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Stock	I-pers
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
saying	O
nothing	O
Material	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Burgess	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Katherine	I-place
Creed	I-place
Church	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
7	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
a	O
Penknife	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buttons	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Mortier	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
making	O
but	O
a	O
trifling	O
Defence	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
called	O
some	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Meers	I-pers
alias	O
Webster	B-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Ralph	B-pers
Keate	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
being	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
drink	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
into	O
their	O
Room	O
,	O
they	O
being	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
he	O
sat	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Bed-side	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
laid	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
either	O
on	O
a	O
Chair	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Bed	O
side	O
.	O
and	O
,	O
that	O
falling	O
asleep	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
awaked	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
taxed	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
since	O
offer	O
'd	O
either	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
or	O
give	O
him	O
another	O
in	O
lieu	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
several	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bennet	I-place
Grace	I-place
Church	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
17	O
Rabbets	O
,	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Knapton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Ann	B-pers
Knapper	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
divers	O
Linnen	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Leather	O
Clog	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Pig	B-place
Hill	I-place
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
behind	O
her	O
,	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
pull	O
her	O
Handkerchief	O
off	O
from	O
her	O
Neck	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
coming	O
off	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
her	O
down	O
,	O
drew	O
the	O
Bundle	O
of	O
Clothes	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
Arm	O
,	O
rolled	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Mud	O
,	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
strangle	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
his	O
Knees	O
bore	O
her	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Ground	O
;	O
that	O
thereupon	O
she	O
fell	O
into	O
Fits	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
was	O
done	O
afterward	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
feeling	O
about	O
her	O
Clothes	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
putting	O
on	O
her	O
Clog	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
that	O
pretending	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
call	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Evidence	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Bundle	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Clog	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
One	O
Evidence	O
swearing	O
positively	O
to	O
his	O
apprehending	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
going	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Assault	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Thornton	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Black	B-pers
Jenny	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Morris	B-pers
Prosser	I-pers
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Robinson	O
met	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
her	O
Lodging	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
refus	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
then	O
she	O
offering	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
Dram	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
a	O
Brandy	O
Shop	O
in	O
Chick	O
Lane	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
not	O
liking	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
was	O
for	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
offering	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
left	O
his	O
Watch	O
with	O
the	O
Man	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
refused	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
put	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
took	O
him	O
hold	O
one	O
by	O
one	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
by	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Watch	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Robinson	O
confes	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
Black	O
Jenny	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
10s	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Judd	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
taking	O
three	O
Hundred	O
Weight	O
of	O
Lead	O
off	O
from	O
the	O
Freehold	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ketteredge	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
had	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
empty	O
House	O
,	O
enquiring	O
for	O
the	O
Landlord	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
Friend	O
that	O
would	O
buy	O
the	O
Estate	O
.	O
That	O
some	O
Time	O
after	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
Key	O
again	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
His	O
Friend	O
had	O
bought	O
,	O
or	O
taken	O
a	O
Lease	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Workman	O
,	O
or	O
Bricklayer	O
,	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
work	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
that	O
hiring	O
two	O
Labourers	O
,	O
he	O
immediately	O
set	O
them	O
to	O
work	O
to	O
take	O
off	O
the	O
Tiles	O
,	O
and	O
strip	O
off	O
the	O
Lead	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
had	O
done	O
by	O
Breakfast	O
Time	O
.	O
That	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
to	O
Breakfast	O
he	O
brought	O
a	O
Plummer	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
told	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Friend	O
had	O
bought	O
the	O
Premises	O
,	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
pull	O
down	O
that	O
and	O
five	O
Houses	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
build	O
as	O
many	O
New	O
ones	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
recommended	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
the	O
Plummer	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Lead	O
for	O
29	O
s.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
fin	O
'd	O
him	O
twenty	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
begg	O
'd	O
the	O
Liberty	O
to	O
transport	O
himself	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
left	O
to	O
the	O
Consideration	O
of	O
the	O
Sheriff	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Pitchard	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
defrauding	O
Charles	B-pers
Greenwood	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Firkin	O
of	O
Butter	O
,	O
in	O
pretending	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
by	O
one	O
Tho	B-pers
Follows	I-pers
,	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
was	O
Servant	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
sentenc	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
three	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
pay	O
10	O
Marks	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Batt	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
rob	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
second	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
of	O
the	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
between	O
Mile	B-place
End	I-place
and	O
Bow	B-place
,	O
he	O
met	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
who	O
pass	O
'd	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
then	O
turn	O
'd	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
stand	O
and	O
deliver	O
,	O
threatening	O
to	O
fire	O
at	O
him	O
immediately	O
,	O
shewing	O
him	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Fellow	O
to	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Bosom	O
,	O
and	O
opening	O
it	O
,	O
did	O
shew	O
him	O
something	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Truncheon	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
it	O
hit	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Forehead	O
,	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
fell	O
on	O
his	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Head	O
against	O
a	O
Bank	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
very	O
Moon-light	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
full	O
View	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
on	O
a	O
black	O
Coat	O
,	O
so	O
short	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
be	O
five	O
or	O
for	O
inches	O
above	O
his	O
Knees	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
took	O
nothing	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
He	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
He	O
had	O
nothing	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
damn	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
You	O
Dog	O
,	O
where	O
do	O
you	O
work	O
?	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
about	O
?	O
He	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
He	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
begging	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
with	O
a	O
Course	O
,	O
Then	O
get	O
up	O
and	O
beg	O
again	O
.	O
And	O
so	O
he	O
came	O
away	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
afterwards	O
going	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Boswel	O
's	O
at	O
Bow	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
taking	O
Notice	O
of	O
the	O
Wound	O
in	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
describ	O
'd	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
three	O
Tuns	O
in	O
Bow	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
see	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
answer	O
'd	O
the	O
Description	O
.	O
That	O
accordingly	O
he	O
went	O
,	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
positive	O
in	O
Court	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
his	O
having	O
ever	O
seen	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
labouring	O
Work	O
for	O
Sir	O
Charles	B-pers
Peers	I-pers
,	O
came	O
home	O
very	O
weary	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
about	O
Nine	O
a	O
Clock	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Bridgman	I-pers
,	O
his	O
Landlord	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
about	O
Nine	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
out	O
any	O
more	O
that	O
Night	O
as	O
he	O
knew	O
of	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
no	O
black	O
Coat	O
.	O
His	O
Landlady	O
,	O
Susan	B-pers
Bridgman	I-pers
,	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
adding	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
going	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Room	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
see	O
him	O
in	O
Bed	O
between	O
Ten	O
and	O
Eleven	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
him	O
go	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Richard	B-pers
Tisdale	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
rob	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Bow	B-place
to	O
Mile	B-place
End	I-place
,	O
between	O
Nine	O
and	O
Ten	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
gone	O
beyond	O
the	O
Barn	O
,	O
he	O
overtook	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
a	O
short	O
black	O
Coat	O
,	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
inches	O
above	O
the	O
Knee	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
telling	O
him	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
afraid	O
of	O
a	O
former	O
Man	O
he	O
saw	O
,	O
but	O
adding	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
to	O
loose	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
,	O
indeed	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Watch	O
and	O
Ring	O
,	O
he	O
soon	O
after	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
Dog	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
you	O
down	O
,	O
lie	O
still	O
you	O
Son	O
of	O
a	O
Bitch	O
,	O
deliver	O
your	O
Money	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
hearken	O
if	O
any	O
Body	O
was	O
coming	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
ran	O
towards	O
Bow	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
his	O
Tread	O
near	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
stop	O
'd	O
short	O
,	O
and	O
slipp	O
'd	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
towards	O
London	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
bidding	O
him	O
stand	O
,	O
and	O
fir	O
'd	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
miss	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ran	O
to	O
the	O
Coach	O
and	O
Horses	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
he	O
heard	O
Horses	O
coming	O
on	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
them	O
how	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
serv	O
'd	O
;	O
they	O
carried	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
Bow	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
describ	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
positive	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
following	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Havers	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
,	O
be	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
Eight	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
his	O
Mare	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
rub	O
down	O
,	O
bidding	O
him	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
come	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Head	O
.	O
That	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
he	O
did	O
so	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
sent	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Red	O
Lion	O
on	O
an	O
Errand	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
Money	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Drink	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
again	O
in	O
a	O
Time	O
too	O
short	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
the	O
fact	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
stay	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Head	O
till	O
near	O
Eleven	O
a	O
Clock	O
.	O
Several	O
of	O
these	O
Circumstances	O
were	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
two	O
other	O
Evidences	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
as	O
an	O
industrious	O
Fellow	O
,	O
working	O
as	O
a	O
Labourer	O
at	O
any	O
sort	O
of	O
Work	O
that	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
objected	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Bailiff	O
's	O
Follower	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
not	O
deny	O
'd	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
But	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
this	O
indictment	O
also	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
solliciting	O
and	O
perswading	O
Edward	B-pers
Cheesebrook	I-pers
,	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
on	O
him	O
the	O
Name	O
,	O
and	O
personate	O
Elias	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
of	O
Brownley	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
without	O
his	O
Knowledge	O
and	O
Consent	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
a	O
frandulent	O
Transfer	O
,	O
of	O
500	O
l	O
Original	O
South	O
Sea	O
Stock	O
,	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Francis	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
.	O
Edmund	B-pers
Cheesebrook	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
transfer	O
South	O
Sea	O
Stock	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
How	O
could	O
he	O
do	O
that	O
,	O
having	O
none	O
in	O
,	O
nor	O
was	O
he	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Persons	O
who	O
had	O
any	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
he	O
know	O
the	O
Manner	O
of	O
it	O
:	O
That	O
King	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Clerks	O
of	O
the	O
South	O
Sea	O
Company	O
,	O
could	O
procure	O
him	O
Persons	O
Names	O
,	O
and	O
Places	O
of	O
Abode	O
,	O
that	O
had	O
Stock	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
what	O
Stock	O
they	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
as	O
for	O
the	O
Manner	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
easily	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
little	O
Danger	O
of	O
being	O
discover	O
'd	O
,	O
especially	O
they	O
being	O
in	O
that	O
Hurry	O
;	O
that	O
with	O
his	O
Perswasions	O
,	O
he	O
undertook	O
to	O
be	O
concern	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
that	O
Affair	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
some	O
Time	O
after	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
him	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
Stock	O
of	O
one	O
Kales	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
of	O
one	O
Skinner	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
1000	O
l.	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
transfer	O
that	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
not	O
,	O
upon	O
Examination	O
,	O
so	O
much	O
,	O
but	O
about	O
,	O
300	O
l.	O
that	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
brought	O
him	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Stock	O
of	O
Elias	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Bromely	O
Esq	O
;	O
ordering	O
him	O
to	O
employ	O
a	O
Broker	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
about	O
1700	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
employ	O
a	O
Broker	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Fenton	O
,	O
to	O
sell	O
500	O
l.	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
Fenton	O
did	O
dispose	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Fisher	O
,	O
or	O
his	O
Broker	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
South	B-place
Sea	I-place
House	I-place
,	O
transferred	O
the	O
Stock	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Fisher	O
,	O
signing	O
the	O
Books	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Elias	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
King	O
being	O
them	O
present	O
in	O
the	O
South	O
Sea	O
House	O
:	O
That	O
the	O
Broker	O
Fenton	O
and	O
himself	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Fleece	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
paid	O
him	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
be	O
can	O
remember	O
,	O
about	O
490	O
l.	O
in	O
Bills	O
and	O
Money	O
;	O
that	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
Broker	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
King	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
shar	O
'd	O
the	O
Bills	O
and	O
Money	O
equally	O
betwixt	O
them	O
,	O
as	O
had	O
been	O
the	O
Agreement	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
sell	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Russel	O
's	O
Stock	O
,	O
these	O
Times	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
like	O
Management	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Morrison	O
,	O
a	O
Clerk	O
to	O
the	O
South	O
Sea	O
Company	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
King	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Lock	O
and	O
Key	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
enquire	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
concerning	O
the	O
Stock	O
of	O
some	O
Persons	O
in	O
the	O
South	O
Sea	O
Company	O
's	O
Books	O
;	O
that	O
as	O
for	O
the	O
Stock	O
of	O
Hales	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
give	O
a	O
very	O
particular	O
Account	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Russel	O
's	O
Stock	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
so	O
particular	O
;	O
but	O
does	O
remember	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
July	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
just	O
parted	O
with	O
a	O
Friend	O
,	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Elias	O
Russell	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
Stock	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
just	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
Time	O
to	O
enquire	O
into	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
has	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
particular	O
Account	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
afterwards	O
did	O
deliver	O
him	O
a	O
Paper	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Lock	O
and	O
Key	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
not	O
swear	O
positively	O
it	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Russel	O
's	O
Stock	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
did	O
own	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
much	O
Pains	O
taken	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
by	O
the	O
Counsel	O
,	O
to	O
invalidate	O
Cheesbrook	O
's	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
establish	O
the	O
Credit	O
of	O
Mr.	O
King	O
:	O
And	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
many	O
Persons	O
to	O
him	O
Reputation	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
esteem	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
to	O
be	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
by	O
several	O
Circumstances	O
;	O
the	O
Court	O
sentenc	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
pay	O
a	O
Fine	O
of	O
400	O
l.	O
to	O
suffer	O
a	O
Year	O
's	O
Imprisonment	O
,	O
and	O
stand	O
once	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
at	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchre	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
and	O
carnally	O
knowing	O
Susannah	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
an	O
infant	O
under	O
ten	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
Susannah	O
Mitchel	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
enter	O
her	O
Body	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
afterwards	O
he	O
threaten	O
'd	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
told	O
any	O
Body	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
cut	O
her	O
Tongue	O
out	O
;	O
that	O
therefore	O
being	O
afraid	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
her	O
Mistress	O
,	O
till	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
out	O
by	O
her	O
Linnen	O
.	O
Her	O
Mistress	O
and	O
the	O
Midwife	O
,	O
both	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
girl	O
had	O
been	O
much	O
injured	O
and	O
abus	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
latter	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
Opinion	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
penetrated	O
.	O
Two	O
Surgeons	O
were	O
called	O
,	O
who	O
did	O
own	O
the	O
Girl	O
had	O
been	O
much	O
injured	O
,	O
but	O
were	O
of	O
Opinion	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
penetrated	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
Hester	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Wills	I-pers
Upon	O
an	O
Affidavit	O
made	O
,	O
That	O
Sally	B-pers
Salisbury	I-pers
was	O
Sick	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
brought	O
down	O
to	O
her	O
Tryal	O
,	O
without	O
the	O
Danger	O
of	O
her	O
Life	O
,	O
her	O
Tryal	O
is	O
defer	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
Sessions	O
when	O
it	O
is	O
fixed	O
to	O
be	O
by	O
a	O
Rule	O
of	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
over	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
Three	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Summerfield	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Barks	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Frost	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
Two	O
.	O
Griffith	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
convicted	O
last	O
Sessions	O
.	O
For	O
Transportation	O
,	O
Thirty	O
Five	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Allan	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Biggs	O
,	O
Frances	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Mary	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Cole	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Keatly	I-pers
,	O
Richard	O
Evans	O
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Richard	B-pers
Henley	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Burgess	I-pers
,	O
Harnah	O
Thompson	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Map	I-pers
,	O
Roger	O
Stephens	O
;	O
Martha	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
Philip	B-pers
Large	I-pers
,	O
Anthony	B-pers
Dubart	I-pers
,	O
Soloman	O
Barlow	O
,	O
Samuel	O
Eslic	O
,	O
Isabel	O
Carr	O
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Sammon	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Thornton	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Black	O
Jenny	O
,	O
Henry	O
Inon	O
,	O
Sarah	O
Swan	O
Mary	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Wallace	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Whitehall	I-pers
,	O
William	O
Anderson	O
,	O
John	O
Robinson	O
,	O
Henry	O
Owen	O
,	O
William	O
Moore	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Bowes	I-pers
,	O
Amy	O
Scriven	O
,	O
William	O
Broughton	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Merriday	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Paul	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Bissat	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
,	O
Four	O
.	O
Stephen	O
Davenport	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wicks	I-pers
,	O
Formerly	O
convicted	O
,	O
Hester	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Wills	I-pers
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
King	I-pers
Sin	I-pers
'd	O
400	O
l.	O
sentensc	O
'd	O
to	O
a	O
Year	O
's	O
Imprisonment	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
once	O
in	O
the	O
pillory	O
at	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
.	O
Thomas	O
,	O
fin	O
'd	O
twenty	O
Marks	O
and	O
three	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
,	O
fin	O
'd	O
ten	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
Just	O
publish	O
'd	O
the	O
Sixth	O
Edition	O
(	O
with	O
many	O
Additions	O
and	O
Ammendments	O
)	O
of	O
A	O
Rational	O
and	O
Useful	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Venereal	O
Disease	O
With	O
Observations	O
on	O
the	O
Nature	O
,	O
Symptoms	O
and	O
Care	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bad	O
Consequences	O
that	O
attend	O
by	O
ill	O
Management	O
;	O
with	O
proper	O
Admonitions	O
;	O
recommended	O
as	O
a	O
Friendly	O
Instruction	O
to	O
all	O
Persons	O
who	O
do	O
,	O
or	O
may	O
,	O
labour	O
under	O
this	O
Misfortune	O
.	O
Also	O
,	O
A	O
short	O
Inquiry	O
into	O
Old	O
Gleets	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Weaknesses	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Reason	O
why	O
they	O
are	O
so	O
seldom	O
cured	O
:	O
With	O
the	O
Author	O
's	O
Methods	O
of	O
Cure	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
are	O
added	O
,	O
Some	O
Hints	O
on	O
the	O
Practical	O
Scheme	O
,	O
the	O
Methods	O
and	O
Medicines	O
therein	O
expected	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
gross	O
Impositions	O
justly	O
detected	O
:	O
With	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
Specifick	O
,	O
the	O
life	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
Name	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
it	O
covers	O
ignorance	O
and	O
a	O
Cheat	O
.	O
By	O
Joseph	O
cam	O
M.D	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
G.	O
Strahan	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
W.	O
Means	O
without	O
Temple-Bar	O
,	O
G.	O
King	O
in	O
Westminster-Hall	O
,	O
T.	O
Norris	O
on	O
London	O
Bridge	O
,	O
J.	O
Baker	O
against	O
Hatton-Garden	O
in	O
Holborn	O
;	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Author	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Golden	O
Ball	O
and	O
Lamp	O
in	O
Bow	O
Church	O
Yard	O
,	O
Cheapside	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
A	O
Water	O
that	O
perfectly	O
cures	O
the	O
Itch	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
Itching	O
Humour	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
,	O
without	O
Necessity	O
of	O
Purging	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
dangerous	O
Use	O
of	O
Mercury	O
,	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
only	O
is	O
prepared	O
and	O
sold	O
,	O
by	O
A	O
.	O
Downing	O
,	O
Chymist	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
and	O
Ball	O
,	O
in	O
George	O
Court	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
John	O
's	O
Lane	O
,	O
by	O
Hicks's-Hall	O
,	O
near	O
West-Smithfield	O
.	O
Where	O
also	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
the	O
best	O
Spirits	O
of	O
Scnrvy	O
Grass	O
,	O
by	O
Wholesale	O
or	O
Retale	O
,	O
at	O
8	O
d.	O
a	O
Bottle	O
.	O
A	O
most	O
effectual	O
Remedy	O
for	O
the	O
violent	O
Pain	O
in	O
the	O
Teeth	O
,	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
Also	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Remedy	O
for	O
the	O
Teeth	O
,	O
and	O
clearing	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
.	O
A	O
Fall	O
and	O
Compleat	O
History	O
of	O
the	O
Lives	O
,	O
Robberies	O
,	O
and	O
Murders	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
most	O
notorious	O
Highwaymen	O
that	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
England	O
,	O
Scotland	O
,	O
France	O
and	O
Ireland	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Reign	O
of	O
William	O
the	O
Conqueror	O
,	O
to	O
this	O
present	O
Year	O
1723.	O
beginning	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Don	I-pers
,	O
Robin	B-pers
Hood	I-pers
and	O
Little	O
John	O
,	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Falstaff	I-pers
,	O
Capt	O
.	O
Hind	O
,	O
the	O
Golden	O
Framer	O
,	O
Nevison	O
,	O
Witney	O
,	O
and	O
above	O
a	O
Hundred	O
more	O
:	O
also	O
giving	O
a	O
more	O
full	O
Account	O
than	O
any	O
yet	O
published	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Robberies	O
committed	O
by	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Child	I-pers
,	O
