TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice	O
Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Tenth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
PETER	B-pers
DELME	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Tracey	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
JURORS	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
The	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Husband	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Fleming	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Marshal	I-pers
,	O
Laurence	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
Gerard	B-pers
Pitham	I-pers
,	O
Edmund	B-pers
Dew	I-pers
,	O
Branden	B-pers
Hatch	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Hatham	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Dent	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Chandler	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Long	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Forster	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Devenish	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Waddel	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Chad	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Chandler	I-pers
,	O
Jacob	B-pers
Broughton	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Breatcliffe	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Patty	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Burden	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Twittenham	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
violently	O
Assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Zouch	I-pers
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
Fear	O
and	O
Danger	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
him	O
of	O
31	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
William	O
Zouch	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
House	O
much	O
about	O
Noon	O
,	O
and	O
forc	O
'd	O
a	O
Discourse	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
asking	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
his	O
Neighbours	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
visit	O
him	O
?	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
some	O
Times	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
Home	O
.	O
That	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Body	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
but	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
Time	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
must	O
give	O
him	O
his	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
a	O
Stick	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
he	O
presently	O
drew	O
a	O
Tuck	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
presented	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
threatned	O
im	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
immediately	O
tell	O
him	O
where	O
his	O
Money	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
run	O
him	O
through	O
;	O
and	O
prest	O
it	O
so	O
hard	O
against	O
his	O
Breast	O
,	O
he	O
thought	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
run	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Body	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
telling	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
but	O
a	O
poor	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
31	O
s.	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
gotten	O
was	O
all	O
the	O
Money	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
had	O
been	O
given	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
Charity	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
very	O
old	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
Gold	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
then	O
thrust	O
him	O
down	O
into	O
his	O
Chair	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
cut	O
down	O
a	O
Line	O
that	O
was	O
ty	O
'd	O
up	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
ty	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
Chair	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
and	O
left	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
several	O
Times	O
to	O
have	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
unbind	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
having	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
often	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
hearing	O
him	O
make	O
any	O
Answer	O
,	O
he	O
supposed	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
left	O
Arm	O
not	O
being	O
ty	O
'd	O
down	O
very	O
tight	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
Shift	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
out	O
his	O
Knife	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
it	O
cut	O
the	O
Line	O
and	O
set	O
himself	O
at	O
Liberty	O
;	O
and	O
getting	O
out	O
,	O
acquainted	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
one	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Pearse	I-pers
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
made	O
it	O
known	O
to	O
others	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
one	O
Greenbury	O
a	O
Carpenter	O
,	O
seeing	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
riding	O
by	O
,	O
he	O
acquainted	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
lent	O
him	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
he	O
pursu	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
some	O
other	O
Help	O
,	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
publick	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
31	O
s.	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
same	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Money	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
being	O
one	O
Five	O
Shilling	O
Piece	O
,	O
4	O
Half	O
Crowns	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
in	O
Shillings	O
and	O
Six	O
Pences	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
would	O
have	O
return	O
'd	O
him	O
the	O
Money	O
again	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
set	O
at	O
Liberty	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
deny	O
his	O
having	O
taken	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
-	B-pers
Greenbury	I-pers
a	O
Carpenter	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Bushel	O
's	O
Yard	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
go	O
in	O
and	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
come	O
out	O
at	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
away	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
Hurry	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
out	O
and	O
complain	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
seeing	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
riding	O
by	O
,	O
he	O
acquainted	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
ride	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
directing	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Way	O
he	O
took	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
not	O
caring	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
himself	O
,	O
lent	O
him	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
rode	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
overtook	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
kept	O
at	O
some	O
Distance	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
fearing	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
Pistols	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
one	O
Whittington	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
his	O
Assistance	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
Dismounting	O
advanced	O
nearer	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Collar	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drew	O
out	O
a	O
Tuck	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Stick	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
several	O
Passes	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
avoided	O
,	O
defending	O
himself	O
with	O
his	O
Whip	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
it	O
cut	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
across	O
the	O
Face	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
mounted	O
his	O
Horse	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
rode	O
at	O
a	O
little	O
Distance	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
surrender	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
his	O
Tuck	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Man	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
suspected	O
to	O
have	O
committed	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
secure	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
seeing	O
no	O
likelyhood	O
of	O
getting	O
clear	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
pretended	O
he	O
would	O
deliver	O
his	O
Tuck	O
;	O
he	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
throw	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
fearing	O
least	O
if	O
he	O
adventured	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
he	O
pretending	O
to	O
deliver	O
it	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
might	O
have	O
stabb	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
defend	O
himself	O
with	O
but	O
a	O
Horse	O
Whip	O
;	O
that	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
did	O
throw	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
Whittington	O
holding	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
apprehended	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
who	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
old	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
bound	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
Chair	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
31	O
s.	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
give	O
it	O
them	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
.	O
-	O
Whittington	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
hearing	O
a	O
Woman	O
cry	O
out	O
William	O
Zouch	O
is	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
pursued	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
within	O
sight	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
had	O
got	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
attempted	O
to	O
throw	O
Greenbury	O
off	O
from	O
his	O
Horse	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
afterwards	O
apprehended	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
has	O
been	O
before	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
near	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
would	O
have	O
gone	O
into	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
return	O
the	O
Money	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
Give	O
me	O
my	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
neither	O
deny	O
his	O
having	O
taken	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
nor	O
refuse	O
to	O
return	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
sending	O
for	O
an	O
Officer	O
,	O
secured	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
his	O
Hands	O
,	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
who	O
committed	O
him	O
to	O
Goal	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
did	O
not	O
absolutely	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
pleaded	O
,	O
seeing	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
light	O
a	O
Pipe	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Pints	O
of	O
Cyder	O
,	O
and	O
asking	O
the	O
old	O
Man	O
for	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
a	O
pint	O
Pot	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
25	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
lent	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
though	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
old	O
Man	O
he	O
was	O
but	O
a	O
young	O
Thief	O
.	O
Upon	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Millmash	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Middlemath	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
18	O
Cheesecakes	O
,	O
and	O
12	O
Apple-pies	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Gardener	I-pers
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
April	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Red	B-place
Lyon	I-place
,	O
at	O
Hoxton	B-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
several	O
Times	O
he	O
had	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
there	O
on	O
the	O
over	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
imagine	O
which	O
way	O
they	O
should	O
be	O
gone	O
,	O
without	O
the	O
Privity	O
of	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Family	O
,	O
was	O
resolved	O
to	O
watch	O
narrowly	O
to	O
discover	O
which	O
way	O
they	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
sitten	O
up	O
once	O
or	O
twice	O
before	O
.	O
That	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
a	O
Servant	O
sat	O
up	O
to	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
a	O
Clock	O
on	O
Monday	O
Morning	O
his	O
Servant	O
acquainted	O
him	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
come	O
up	O
the	O
Walks	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
had	O
secured	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Bakehouse	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
taken	O
Cheesecakes	O
out	O
of	O
an	O
Iron	O
Oven	O
that	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
was	O
eating	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
set	O
out	O
a	O
Dozen	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
putting	O
into	O
his	O
Cap	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
have	O
carried	O
them	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Lad	O
that	O
not	O
long	O
before	O
had	O
been	O
his	O
Servant	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Leech	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
having	O
sat	O
up	O
to	O
watch	O
,	O
did	O
,	O
between	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
up	O
her	O
Masters	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Dogs	O
barked	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
being	O
known	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
soon	O
pacified	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
and	O
got	O
in	O
.	O
Another	O
Servant	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
setting	O
up	O
to	O
watch	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
up	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Ground	O
,	O
between	O
4	O
and	O
5	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
very	O
softly	O
,	O
without	O
his	O
Shoes	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
Pin	O
,	O
let	O
down	O
a	O
sliding	O
Shutter	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
into	O
the	O
Bakehouse	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
let	O
him	O
do	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
him	O
open	O
the	O
Oven	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
catch	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
his	O
Mouth	O
being	O
full	O
of	O
Cheesecake	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Dozen	O
taken	O
out	O
and	O
set	O
in	O
Order	O
to	O
be	O
carried	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Buttolphs	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Tustien	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barnet	I-pers
,	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
Master	O
keeps	O
a	O
Distillers	O
Shop	O
in	O
East-Smithfield	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
which	O
lay	O
upon	O
a	O
Cask	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Hat	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
Coat	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Scotcher	I-pers
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
She	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
after	O
her	O
Apprehension	O
.	O
Her	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
So	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Sparks	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Leonard	I-place
Bromley	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Gown	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Benson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Gown	O
was	O
taken	O
off	O
from	O
a	O
Line	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
Man	O
brought	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Gown	O
,	O
before	O
she	O
knew	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hynde	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
out	O
with	O
the	O
Gown	O
,	O
through	O
a	O
Hole	O
in	O
the	O
Pales	O
,	O
and	O
apprehending	O
him	O
,	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Gown	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
,	O
not	O
deny	O
this	O
having	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
pretended	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Gown	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
high	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Lovel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pauls	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
That	O
whereas	O
Henry	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Robertson	B-pers
was	O
try	O
'd	O
and	O
convicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
of	O
2	O
Sacks	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
8	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Malt	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Burnham	I-pers
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
said	O
Richard	O
Lovel	O
did	O
receive	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
The	O
Evidences	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Henry	O
Robertson	O
confest	O
that	O
he	O
sold	O
the	O
Malt	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
other	O
Proof	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Vestry	I-pers
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
April	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Body	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Court	O
order	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Recognizance	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Winderam	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
taking	O
a	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
Things	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Garford	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
April	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Garford	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Man	O
coming	O
down	O
Chick-Lane	B-place
,	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
past	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
shutting	O
her	O
Shop	O
Windows	O
,	O
her	O
Arms	O
being	O
extended	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
having	O
past	O
by	O
her	O
several	O
Times	O
,	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
under	O
her	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
a	O
violent	O
Pull	O
,	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
pursue	O
him	O
,	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
committing	O
another	O
Robbery	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
positive	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
the	O
Person	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Parish	O
,	O
for	O
taking	O
a	O
Pocket	O
,	O
Value	O
2	O
d.	O
a	O
Tortoise	O
Shell	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
8	O
Shillings	O
and	O
9	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
Latter	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Phebe	B-pers
Ridings	I-pers
the	O
same	O
Day	O
.	O
Phebe	O
Ridings	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Chick-Lane	B-place
,	O
leaning	O
on	O
her	O
Husbands	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
,	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
violently	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Husband	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
and	O
catch	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
with	O
the	O
Violence	O
of	O
the	O
Pull	O
,	O
he	O
also	O
tore	O
off	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
her	O
Apron	O
from	O
her	O
side	O
.	O
A	O
Watchman	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
hearing	O
an	O
Out-cry	O
of	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
run	O
into	O
a	O
Brewhouse	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
on	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Pocket	O
and	O
Goods	O
were	O
afterwards	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
apprehended	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ridings	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
Chick-Lane	O
,	O
a	O
tall	O
Fellow	O
came	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
a	O
Jostle	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
crying	O
out	O
her	O
Pocket	O
was	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
hold	O
by	O
the	O
Collar	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
the	O
Piece	O
of	O
his	O
Wife	O
's	O
Apron	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
torn	O
off	O
in	O
pulling	O
off	O
her	O
Pocket	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Pocket	O
and	O
Things	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
the	O
Brewhouse	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
apprehended	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gunner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Gregory	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
11	O
Guineas	O
,	O
a	O
broad	O
Piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Moidore	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Theophilus	B-pers
Perkins	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
several	O
Times	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Money	O
out	O
or	O
a	O
Scriptore	O
,	O
behind	O
his	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Liberty	O
of	O
going	O
out	O
on	O
Easter	O
Monday	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
some	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
desired	O
a	O
Smith	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Box	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
home	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
proper	O
Tools	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
open	O
'd	O
his	O
Box	O
,	O
found	O
there	O
6	O
Guineas	O
and	O
the	O
Moidore	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
a	O
particular	O
Mark	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
positively	O
swear	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
;	O
That	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
he	O
examin	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Scriptore	O
behind	O
the	O
Bar	O
;	O
and	O
asking	O
the	O
Reason	O
why	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
ow	O
'd	O
8	O
s.	O
to	O
the	O
Porter	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
never	O
let	O
him	O
alone	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
at	O
a	O
certain	O
Time	O
,	O
when	O
his	O
Master	O
and	O
Mistress	O
were	O
gone	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
now	O
he	O
might	O
go	O
behind	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
get	O
the	O
Cash	O
.	O
Atwell	O
a	O
Smith	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
being	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
Desire	O
he	O
did	O
fetch	O
Tools	O
,	O
and	O
open	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
found	O
6	O
Guineas	O
and	O
the	O
Moidore	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
was	O
his	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
also	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
another	O
Evidence	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
Contradiction	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Joire	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Michael	I-place
's	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
violently	O
assaulting	O
and	O
robbing	O
Sarah	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High-Way	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Pocket	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
a	O
half	O
Moidore	O
,	O
a	O
Duccatoon	O
,	O
a	O
broad	O
Piece	O
,	O
and	O
7	O
l.	O
17	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
having	O
her	O
Sister	O
by	O
the	O
Arm	O
,	O
the	O
Day	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
was	O
coming	O
through	O
Exchange-Alley	B-place
,	O
about	O
8	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
some	O
Body	O
came	O
by	O
her	O
side	O
,	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
violent	O
Push	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
fell	O
against	O
the	O
wall	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
his	O
Hand	O
under	O
her	O
Petticoat	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
put	O
her	O
into	O
a	O
Fright	O
,	O
and	O
such	O
Disorder	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
recover	O
her	O
self	O
in	O
two	O
Months	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Godfrey	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
formerly	O
imploy	O
'd	O
in	O
cleaning	O
out	O
Justice	O
Kerby	O
's	O
Ship	O
Yard	O
,	O
became	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
15	O
Months	O
since	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
himself	O
had	O
done	O
a	O
few	O
Disploits	O
(	O
meaning	O
Exploits	O
)	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
this	O
Evidence	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
as	O
he	O
should	O
do	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
afterwards	O
they	O
went	O
a	O
robbing	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
meeting	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
shov	O
'd	O
her	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
were	O
the	O
Things	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
acquainted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Manner	O
of	O
her	O
being	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Description	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
2	O
Persons	O
at	O
the	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
Man	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Cap	O
under	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
before	O
been	O
inform	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
rearing	O
off	O
Pockets	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
John	O
Godfrey	O
,	O
having	O
signified	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
come	O
and	O
go	O
without	O
being	O
detained	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
come	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
inquiring	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
at	O
first	O
was	O
not	O
willing	O
to	O
own	O
he	O
knew	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
secure	O
Edward	O
Joice	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
say	O
something	O
material	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
afterwards	O
by	O
Accident	O
apprehend	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
sending	O
for	O
John	O
Godfrey	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
voluntarily	O
,	O
and	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
or	O
his	O
having	O
any	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
John	O
Godfrey	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
Evidences	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
that	O
should	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
elsewhere	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
when	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
was	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Roche	I-pers
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Sawyer	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
his	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
served	O
his	O
Time	O
to	O
him	O
very	O
truly	O
,	O
had	O
always	O
been	O
an	O
honest	O
and	O
faithful	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Time	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
some	O
Persons	O
present	O
desir	O
'd	O
the	O
Court	O
to	O
inquire	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Service	O
during	O
his	O
Apprenticeship	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
Sea	O
for	O
18	O
Months	O
,	O
or	O
more	O
?	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
receiv	O
'd	O
his	O
Wages	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
accounted	O
him	O
to	O
have	O
serv	O
'd	O
his	O
Time	O
to	O
him	O
Faithfully	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
interrogated	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
so	O
behav	O
'd	O
himself	O
in	O
his	O
Service	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
procur	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
committed	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
?	O
He	O
acknowledged	O
he	O
had	O
so	O
done	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
insinuate	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
only	O
for	O
being	O
drunk	O
or	O
so	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
perceiving	O
him	O
to	O
prevaricate	O
in	O
favour	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
order	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
into	O
Custody	O
,	O
and	O
bound	O
by	O
Recognizance	O
with	O
two	O
Securities	O
to	O
appear	O
at	O
the	O
Court	O
the	O
next	O
Sessions	O
,	O
to	O
answer	O
to	O
such	O
Matters	O
as	O
should	O
be	O
alledg	O
'd	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
Two	O
or	O
Three	O
other	O
Persons	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
knew	O
no	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Father	O
appear	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
behalf	O
,	O
and	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
held	O
a	O
small	O
Farm	O
in	O
Tottenham	O
,	O
Freehold	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Time	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
about	O
a	O
Month	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
farther	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
for	O
about	O
a	O
Month	O
more	O
.	O
But	O
being	O
interrogated	O
,	O
whether	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
never	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
nor	O
at	O
London	O
in	O
all	O
that	O
Time	O
?	O
He	O
did	O
own	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sometimes	O
come	O
to	O
London	O
about	O
his	O
Business	O
,	O
but	O
came	O
Home	O
to	O
him	O
again	O
orderly	O
;	O
nor	O
could	O
he	O
take	O
upon	O
him	O
on	O
Oath	O
to	O
say	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
actually	O
at	O
Tottenham	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
when	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
this	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Sister	O
spoke	O
also	O
much	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Purpose	O
.	O
To	O
this	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
indeed	O
he	O
did	O
go	O
to	O
his	O
Father	O
,	O
and	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
skreen	O
him	O
from	O
being	O
apprehended	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
an	O
Information	O
of	O
one	O
Henry	B-pers
Salter	I-pers
.	O
Upon	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Lewis	B-pers
Hussare	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
try	O
'd	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
marrying	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hern	I-pers
in	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
his	O
former	O
Wife	O
Ann	B-pers
Hussare	I-pers
(	O
since	O
murthered	O
)	O
being	O
then	O
alive	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
first	O
Marriage	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Briel	I-pers
,	O
Minister	O
of	O
the	O
French	O
Church	O
in	O
Spittle-Fields	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
4th	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
present	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
by	O
Licence	O
,	O
marry	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Rondeau	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Church	O
,	O
3	O
of	O
his	O
Elders	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
other	O
Persons	O
being	O
present	O
,	O
her	O
Father	O
and	O
Mother	O
belonging	O
to	O
his	O
Church	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
afterwards	O
cohabit	O
together	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
thinks	O
,	O
about	O
3	O
Years	O
,	O
he	O
following	O
the	O
Trade	O
of	O
a	O
Barber	O
at	O
Hoxton	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
second	O
Marriage	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Clerk	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
taken	O
out	O
a	O
Licence	O
at	O
the	O
Commons	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hern	I-pers
came	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
to	O
Queenhith	B-place
,	O
to	O
be	O
married	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Lazenby	O
the	O
Minister	O
of	O
St.	O
Anthony	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
married	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Dog-Tavern	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
went	O
thither	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
observe	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
alter	O
in	O
his	O
Countenance	O
;	O
and	O
all	O
that	O
the	O
Company	O
could	O
say	O
,	O
seem	O
'd	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
enough	O
to	O
compose	O
the	O
Disorder	O
that	O
appear	O
'd	O
in	O
him	O
:	O
So	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
he	O
repented	O
of	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
.	O
But	O
he	O
answered	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
invited	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
spend	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
go	O
to	O
them	O
at	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
near	O
Sion	O
College	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
them	O
in	O
Bed	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Satchell	I-pers
added	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
Elizabeth	O
Hern	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Marriage	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
married	O
as	O
Thomas	O
Smith	O
had	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
several	O
other	O
Persons	O
being	O
present	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
own	O
'd	O
his	O
Marriage	O
with	O
Elizabeth	O
Hern	O
,	O
but	O
deny	O
'd	O
his	O
being	O
ever	O
married	O
to	O
Ann	O
Rondeau	O
.	O
Upon	O
some	O
Disputes	O
in	O
Court	O
concerning	O
the	O
first	O
Marriage	O
,	O
it	O
having	O
been	O
perform	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
Minister	O
or	O
the	O
French	O
Church	O
of	O
the	O
Presbyterian	O
Persuasion	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
in	O
their	O
Verdict	O
Special	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
must	O
remain	O
confin	O
'd	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
Determination	O
of	O
the	O
Judges	O
shall	O
be	O
obtain	O
'd	O
relating	O
to	O
that	O
Point	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Dowler	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Avice	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
April	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
imploy	O
'd	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
upon	O
Occasion	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
her	O
Mistress	O
was	O
gone	O
Abroad	O
,	O
carried	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
East	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
violently	O
Assaulting	O
Audley	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
him	O
of	O
a	O
Silver	O
-	O
hilted	O
Sword	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
April	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
passing	O
through	O
Smithfield	B-place
,	O
about	O
12	O
a-Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
Sort	O
of	O
Scuffle	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
outcry	O
of	O
Link	O
,	O
Link	O
,	O
that	O
thereupon	O
apprehending	O
some	O
Disorder	O
,	O
he	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
others	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
enquiring	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
for	O
a	O
Link	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
ill	O
Language	O
,	O
fell	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
Stick	O
broke	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
gave	O
him	O
20	O
Blows	O
or	O
more	O
on	O
the	O
Face	O
and	O
Head	O
,	O
bruising	O
him	O
most	O
wretchedly	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
wrested	O
the	O
Hilt	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
breaking	O
off	O
a	O
Part	O
in	O
the	O
Violence	O
of	O
doing	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
A	O
Watchman	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
coming	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
complaining	O
of	O
the	O
Injury	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
seen	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
go	O
by	O
with	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
a	O
Sword	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
the	O
Sword	O
Hilt	O
and	O
Piece	O
of	O
the	O
Blade	O
in	O
it	O
lying	O
by	O
his	O
Bed	O
Side	O
.	O
His	O
Evidence	O
was	O
also	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Constable	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
also	O
being	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
ill	O
Fame	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sheet	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Brandrith	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
her	O
Husband	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
to	O
sell	O
Linnen	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
their	O
Occupation	O
so	O
to	O
do	O
about	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
that	O
between	O
them	O
the	O
Sheet	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
rather	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
taken	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Husband	O
than	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
she	O
being	O
supposed	O
to	O
be	O
under	O
the	O
Direction	O
of	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Stevenson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
an	O
Assault	O
on	O
Joseph	B-pers
Woolley	I-pers
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
April	O
.	O
Joseph	O
Woolley	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
carrying	O
a	O
Burden	O
,	O
pitch	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
rest	O
him	O
at	O
Middle	B-place
Fleet	I-place
Bridge	I-place
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
laid	O
his	O
Hand	O
upon	O
the	O
Bag	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
Cocoa	O
Nuts	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
them	O
?	O
That	O
he	O
answered	O
him	O
,	O
what	O
was	O
that	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
demanded	O
of	O
him	O
the	O
Bill	O
of	O
Parcels	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
none	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
would	O
stop	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
two	O
Porters	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
neither	O
of	O
them	O
would	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
mark	O
'd	O
the	O
Bags	O
with	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Mark	O
,	O
the	O
Broad	O
Arrow	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
came	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
seiz	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
.	O
The	O
Person	O
that	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
taking	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
Difference	O
between	O
the	O
Porter	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
Broad	O
Arrow	O
upon	O
the	O
Bags	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Porter	O
coming	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
his	O
Deputation	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
show	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
shown	O
it	O
once	O
already	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
oblig	O
'd	O
to	O
show	O
it	O
50	O
People	O
;	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
,	O
he	O
insisting	O
upon	O
seeing	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
pretended	O
to	O
consent	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Alleys	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
supposing	O
that	O
he	O
intended	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
Drop	O
,	O
he	O
secur	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
charg	O
'd	O
a	O
Constable	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Porter	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
Assistance	O
to	O
help	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Hole	O
in	O
the	O
Bag	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
of	O
the	O
Nuts	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
set	O
the	O
Broad	O
Arrow	O
on	O
the	O
Bags	O
.	O
He	O
acknowledg	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Authority	O
so	O
to	O
do	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
set	O
on	O
him	O
a	O
Fine	O
of	O
10	O
Marks	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Polson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Woolley	I-pers
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Felony	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wilkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Simpkins	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
16	O
s.	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
had	O
been	O
broken	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
separate	O
Apartment	O
from	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
but	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
found	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
sold	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bellamy	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bull	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Tailor	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Marrying	O
Ann	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
having	O
before	O
married	O
Ann	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
still	O
alive	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Marriage	O
not	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
they	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Bunstan	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Travers	I-pers
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
who	O
kept	O
a	O
Cook	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
their	O
Departure	O
,	O
the	O
Plates	O
were	O
missing	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
Samuel	O
Bunstan	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
that	O
Smith	O
was	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
stealing	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
former	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
's	I-place
Wood-street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Piles	I-pers
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
April	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Cooper	O
having	O
laid	O
down	O
his	O
Coat	O
in	O
the	O
Entry	O
of	O
the	O
Three	B-place
Tun-Tavern	I-place
,	O
at	O
Wood	B-place
street	I-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
bring	O
out	O
the	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
another	O
Man	O
,	O
who	O
carried	O
it	O
off	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
was	O
apprehended	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Buttolphs	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Marriot	I-pers
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Body	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Le	B-pers
Bass	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
defrauding	O
Robert	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
of	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Silk	O
Clothes	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
l.	O
by	O
false	O
Pretences	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
having	O
a	O
rich	O
Silver	O
Silk	O
Suit	O
of	O
Clothes	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
was	O
recommended	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
as	O
being	O
a	O
Person	O
that	O
dealt	O
in	O
Tea	O
and	O
Snuff	O
,	O
and	O
who	O
had	O
Acquaintance	O
among	O
rich	O
Jewish	O
Families	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
was	O
a	O
proper	O
Person	O
to	O
help	O
her	O
to	O
a	O
Chapman	O
for	O
the	O
Clothes	O
.	O
That	O
thereupon	O
she	O
left	O
a	O
Breadth	O
of	O
the	O
Petticoat	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Abraham	B-pers
Lyon	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	B-place
,	O
as	O
a	O
Pattern	O
to	O
show	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
afterwards	O
,	O
unknown	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
or	O
without	O
her	O
Order	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
Abraham	B-pers
Lyons	I-pers
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Piece	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
left	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
telling	O
her	O
he	O
had	O
show	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Family	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Moses	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Jew	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Family	O
being	O
about	O
Marriage	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
approv	O
'd	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
bring	O
her	O
30	O
l.	O
in	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Hours	O
Time	O
,	O
or	O
at	O
farthest	O
by	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
;	O
and	O
to	O
induce	O
her	O
to	O
trust	O
him	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
clap	O
'd	O
his	O
Hand	O
on	O
his	O
Breast	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Word	O
was	O
his	O
Bond	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Reader	O
of	O
the	O
Synagogue	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Place	O
was	O
worth	O
an	O
Hundred	O
Pounds	O
a	O
Year	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
she	O
need	O
not	O
be	O
under	O
any	O
Apprehension	O
of	O
any	O
foul	O
Dealing	O
concerning	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
that	O
relying	O
on	O
these	O
Things	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
deliver	O
the	O
Goods	O
into	O
his	O
Hands	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
never	O
either	O
brought	O
the	O
Money	O
or	O
return	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
That	O
thereupon	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Moses	O
Hart	O
's	O
,	O
to	O
enquire	O
if	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
inform	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
pitied	O
her	O
for	O
intrusting	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
on	O
those	O
Pretensions	O
,	O
telling	O
her	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
Reader	O
of	O
the	O
Synagogue	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
turn	O
'd	O
out	O
long	O
before	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
actually	O
bought	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
for	O
30	O
l.	O
and	O
design	O
'd	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
prevented	O
,	O
in	O
that	O
a	O
certain	O
Person	O
had	O
come	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
buying	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
carry	O
Abroad	O
,	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
away	O
from	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
for	O
10	O
l.	O
and	O
was	O
gone	O
beyond	O
Sea	O
.	O
But	O
being	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
to	O
prove	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
the	O
Disappointment	O
he	O
pretended	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
having	O
actually	O
bought	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
deny	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
several	O
Evidences	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
having	O
sold	O
him	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
all	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
if	O
true	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
after	O
his	O
having	O
gotten	O
the	O
Goods	O
into	O
his	O
Possession	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
perform	O
'd	O
the	O
Conditions	O
on	O
which	O
he	O
obtain	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
sentenc	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
pay	O
a	O
Fine	O
of	O
20	O
l.	O
and	O
to	O
suffer	O
2	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
making	O
Application	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
for	O
a	O
Permission	O
to	O
charge	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
an	O
Action	O
of	O
30	O
l.	O
they	O
granted	O
it	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Perjury	O
:	O
The	O
Council	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
having	O
opened	O
and	O
stated	O
the	O
Evidence	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
stated	O
and	O
what	O
was	O
given	O
in	O
Evidence	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
was	O
not	O
sufficient	O
to	O
maintain	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
self	O
also	O
insufficient	O
)	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
conceiving	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
groundless	O
and	O
malicious	O
Indictment	O
,	O
the	O
Defendant	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Defendant	O
's	O
Council	O
pray	O
'd	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
opposed	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Council	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
granted	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
appearing	O
some	O
Differences	O
to	O
have	O
arisen	O
between	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
the	O
Defendant	O
's	O
Son	O
in	O
Law	O
)	O
and	O
the	O
Defendant	O
;	O
the	O
Court	O
proposed	O
that	O
all	O
Matters	O
and	O
Differences	O
between	O
them	O
might	O
be	O
ended	O
by	O
a	O
Reference	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchres	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Pugh	I-pers
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
April	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
drink	O
at	O
the	O
Shed	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
drank	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Landlord	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
drink	O
to	O
her	O
any	O
more	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
staid	O
there	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
afterwards	O
along	O
Chick	B-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
replied	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
drank	O
to	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Shed	O
,	O
and	O
thank	O
'd	O
him	O
for	O
her	O
Drink	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
very	O
dark	O
,	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
a	O
little	O
Way	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
to	O
set	O
her	O
on	O
her	O
way	O
Home	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
Home	O
,	O
she	O
talking	O
to	O
him	O
so	O
fair	O
and	O
prettily	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
forbear	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
near	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
a	O
Watchman	O
bid	O
him	O
take	O
Care	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
laid	O
his	O
Hand	O
upon	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sure	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
neither	O
felt	O
nor	O
saw	O
any	O
Thing	O
there	O
but	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
staid	O
there	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
very	O
willing	O
he	O
should	O
stay	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
getting	O
up	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
,	O
the	O
Candle	O
fell	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
Way	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
his	O
Watch	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
procceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
followeth	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
Five	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Burden	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Winderham	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	O
East	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Gunner	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Joyce	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
,	O
Nine	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Mildmash	I-pers
alias	O
Mildmath	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Sparkes	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
,	O
Ann	O
Dowler	O
,	O
Joseph	O
Wilkins	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bellam	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	O
Bunstan	O
,	O
Abraham	O
Smith	O
.	O
Joseph	O
Saunders	O
,	O
alias	O
Le	O
Bass	O
,	O
fin	O
'd	O
20	O
l.	O
and	O
to	O
suffer	O
two	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
Henry	O
Stevenson	O
,	O
fin	O
'd	O
10	O
Marks	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
Just	O
publish	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Seventh	O
Edition	O
(	O
with	O
many	O
Additions	O
and	O
Amendments	O
)	O
of	O
A	O
Rational	O
and	O
Useful	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Venereal	O
Disease	O
.	O
With	O
Observations	O
on	O
the	O
Nature	O
,	O
Symptoms	O
,	O
and	O
Cure	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
ill	O
Consequences	O
that	O
attend	O
it	O
by	O
ill	O
Management	O
;	O
with	O
proper	O
Admonitions	O
;	O
recommended	O
as	O
a	O
Friendly	O
Instruction	O
to	O
all	O
Persons	O
who	O
do	O
,	O
or	O
may	O
,	O
labour	O
under	O
this	O
Misfortune	O
.	O
Also	O
,	O
A	O
short	O
Inquiry	O
into	O
Old	O
Gleets	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Weaknesses	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Reason	O
why	O
they	O
are	O
so	O
seldom	O
cured	O
:	O
With	O
the	O
Author	O
's	O
Method	O
of	O
Cure	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
are	O
added	O
.	O
Some	O
Hints	O
on	O
the	O
Practical	O
Scheme	O
.	O
The	O
Methods	O
and	O
Medicines	O
therein	O
exposed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
gross	O
Impositions	O
justly	O
detected	O
:	O
With	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
Specificks	O
,	O
the	O
Use	O
and	O
Abuse	O
of	O
the	O
Name	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
it	O
covers	O
Ignorance	O
and	O
a	O
Cheat	O
.	O
By	O
Joseph	B-pers
Cam	I-pers
,	O
M.D	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
G.	O
Strahan	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
W.	O
Mears	O
,	O
without	O
Temple-Bar	O
,	O
C.	O
King	O
,	O
in	O
Westminster-Hall	O
,	O
T.	O
Norris	O
on	O
London-Bridge	O
,	O
J.	O
Baker	O
against	O
Hatton-Garden	O
in	O
Holborn	O
;	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Author	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Golden	O
Ball	O
and	O
Lamp	O
in	O
Bow-Church-Yard	O
,	O
Cheapside	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
An	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Lives	O
,	O
Intreagues	O
,	O
and	O
Comical	O
Adventures	O
of	O
Rob	O
Roy	O
,	O
alias	O
Robert	B-pers
Mac	I-pers
Gregor	I-pers
,	O
Capt	O
.	O
Stanley	O
.	O
Sally	B-pers
Salisbury	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Sarah	B-pers
Pridden	I-pers
,	O
and	O
near	O
a	O
hunred	O
more	O
,	O
who	O
have	O
either	O
dy	O
'd	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
or	O
been	O
executed	O
for	O
several	O
Villanies	O
and	O
Murders	O
committed	O
by	O
them	O
:	O
Wherein	O
is	O
contained	O
a	O
more	O
full	O
and	O
true	O
Account	O
,	O
than	O
has	O
been	O
publish	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Ordinary	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
other	O
.	O
The	O
Whole	O
being	O
not	O
only	O
very	O
Diverting	O
to	O
read	O
,	O
but	O
very	O
Useful	O
to	O
preserve	O
others	O
from	O
being	O
impos	O
'd	O
upon	O
by	O
Sharpers	O
,	O
and	O
such	O
as	O
desire	O
to	O
avoid	O
falling	O
into	O
ill	O
Company	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Where	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
also	O
,	O
A	O
compleat	O
List	O
of	O
above	O
6000	O
of	O
the	O
Insolvent	O
Debtors	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
cleared	O
at	O
Guilford	O
,	O
Kingston	O
and	O
Croydon	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Dissolution	O
of	O
the	O
Mint	O
:	O
And	O
also	O
of	O
all	O
those	O
who	O
are	O
yet	O
to	O
be	O
discharg	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Quarter	O
Sessions	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Ryegate	O
,	O
April	O
the	O
14th	O
,	O
1724	O
,	O
containing	O
the	O
several	O
Places	O
of	O
their	O
Abode	O
,	O
with	O
their	O
various	O
Stations	O
and	O
Occupations	O
,	O
Alphabetically	O
digested	O
,	O
and	O
distinguish	O
'd	O
under	O
their	O
proper	O
Heads	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
more	O
easy	O
finding	O
out	O
any	O
particular	O
Person	O
.	O
Publish	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
general	O
Information	O
to	O
all	O
Mankind	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Both	O
printed	O
for	O
M.	O
Hotham	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Black-Boy	O
on	O
L	O
ondon-Bridge	O
.	O
A	O
Water	O
that	O
perfectly	O
cures	O
the	O
Itch	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
Itching	O
Humour	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
,	O
without	O
Necessity	O
of	O
Purging	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
dangerous	O
Use	O
of	O
Mercury	O
,	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
only	O
is	O
prepared	O
and	O
sold	O
,	O
by	O
A	O
.	O
Downing	O
,	O
Chymist	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
and	O
Ball	O
,	O
in	O
George	O
Court	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
John	O
's	O
Lane	O
,	O
by	O
Hicks's-Hall	O
,	O
near	O
West-Smithfield	O
.	O
Where	O
also	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
the	O
best	O
Spirits	O
of	O
Scurvy-Grass	O
,	O
by	O
Wholesale	O
or	O
Retale	O
,	O
at	O
8	O
d.	O
a	O
Bottle	O
.	O
A	O
most	O
effectual	O
Remedy	O
for	O
the	O
violent	O
Pain	O
in	O
the	O
Teeth	O
,	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
Also	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Remedy	O
for	O
the	O
Teeth	O
,	O
and	O
clearing	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
.	O
Youth	O
's	O
Introduction	O
to	O
Trade	O
and	O
Business	O
:	O
Containing	O
,	O
1	O
.	O
Tables	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
usual	O
Clerk-like	O
Contractions	O
of	O
Words	O
:	O
A	O
Collection	O
of	O
English	O
Words	O
,	O
alike	O
in	O
Sound	O
,	O
but	O
different	O
in	O
Signification	O
;	O
with	O
proper	O
Directions	O
how	O
to	O
address	O
to	O
Persons	O
of	O
elevated	O
Rank	O
,	O
and	O
those	O
in	O
Office	O
.	O
II	O
.	O
Acquittances	O
and	O
Promissory	O
Notes	O
diversify	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
adapted	O
to	O
such	O
Circumstances	O
as	O
occur	O
in	O
real	O
Business	O
.	O
III	O
.	O
Variety	O
of	O
Bills	O
of	O
Parcels	O
,	O
and	O
Bills	O
on	O
Book	O
Debts	O
,	O
to	O
enter	O
the	O
Learner	O
in	O
the	O
Manner	O
and	O
Methods	O
of	O
Commerce	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
ready	O
at	O
Computation	O
.	O
IV	O
.	O
Bills	O
of	O
Exchange	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
necessary	O
for	O
the	O
right	O
Understanding	O
and	O
Management	O
of	O
Remittances	O
;	O
several	O
Orders	O
for	O
Goods	O
,	O
Letters	O
of	O
Credit	O
,	O
Invoyces	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Merchant-like	O
Examples	O
.	O
V.	O
Authentick	O
Forms	O
of	O
such	O
Law-Precedents	O
as	O
are	O
most	O
frequently	O
to	O
be	O
met	O
with	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Course	O
of	O
Traffick	O
.	O
VI	O
.	O
A	O
Collection	O
of	O
Questions	O
to	O
exemplify	O
the	O
common	O
Rules	O
of	O
Arithmetick	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
reduce	O
them	O
to	O
Practice	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Use	O
of	O
Schools	O
.	O
Done	O
upon	O
the	O
Plan	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
Col.	O
Ayre	B-pers
's	O
Essay	O
.	O
By	O
M.	O
Clare	O
,	O
School-Masters	O
in	O
Soho-Square	O
,	O
London	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
Edward	O
Symon	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Pope	O
's	O
Head	O
Alley	O
,	O
is	O
Cornhill	O
.	O
BOOKS	O
Printed	O
for	O
EDWARD	O
SYMON	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Popes-Head-Alley	O
,	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
.	O
THE	O
History	O
of	O
the	O
Revolutions	O
that	O
happened	O
in	O
the	O
Government	O
of	O
the	O
Roman	B-pers
Republick	I-pers
.	O
Written	O
in	O
French	O
by	O
the	O
Abbot	O
de	O
Vertot	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Royal	O
Academy	O
of	O
Inscriptions	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
English	O
'd	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Ozell	O
from	O
the	O
Original	O
,	O
newly	O
reprinted	O
at	O
Paris	O
,	O
with	O
Amendments	O
and	O
Additions	O
by	O
the	O
Author	O
himself	O
,	O
in	O
almost	O
every	O
Page	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
prefix	O
'd	O
,	O
a	O
Translation	O
of	O
a	O
Memorial	O
sent	O
from	O
London	O
by	O
the	O
late	O
Earl	B-pers
Stanhope	I-pers
,	O
to	O
the	O
Abbot	O
de	O
Vertot	O
at	O
Paris	O
;	O
containing	O
divers	O
Questions	O
relating	O
to	O
the	O
Constitution	O
of	O
the	O
Roman	B-pers
Senate	I-pers
.	O
With	O
the	O
Abbot	O
's	O
Answer	O
.	O
The	O
Third	O
Edition	O
.	O
In	O
2	O
Vol	O
.	O
An	O
universal	O
Etymological	O
English	O
Dictionary	O
:	O
Comprehending	O
the	O
Derivations	O
of	O
the	O
Generality	O
of	O
Words	O
in	O
the	O
English	O
Tongue	O
,	O
either	O
Ancient	O
or	O
Modern	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Ancient	O
British	O
,	O
Saxon	O
,	O
Danish	O
,	O
Norman	O
,	O
and	O
Modern	O
French	O
,	O
Teutonic	O
,	O
Dutch	O
,	O
Spanish	O
,	O
Italian	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
from	O
the	O
Latin	O
,	O
Greek	O
,	O
and	O
Hebrew	O
Languages	O
,	O
each	O
in	O
their	O
proper	O
Characters	O
.	O
And	O
also	O
a	O
brief	O
and	O
clear	O
Explication	O
of	O
all	O
difficult	O
Words	O
derived	O
from	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Languages	O
;	O
and	O
Terms	O
of	O
Art	O
,	O
relating	O
to	O
Anatomy	O
,	O
Botany	O
,	O
Physick	O
,	O
Pharmacy	O
,	O
Surgery	O
,	O
Chymistry	O
,	O
Philosophy	O
,	O
Divinity	O
,	O
Mathematicks	O
,	O
Grammer	O
,	O
Logick	O
,	O
Rhetorick	O
,	O
Musick	O
,	O
Heraldry	O
,	O
Maritime	O
Affairs	O
,	O
Military	O
Discipline	O
,	O
Horsemanship	O
,	O
Hunting	O
,	O
Hawking	O
,	O
Fowling	O
,	O
Fishing	O
,	O
Gardening	O
,	O
Husbandry	O
,	O
Handicrafts	O
,	O
Confectionary	O
,	O
Carving	O
,	O
Cookery	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Together	O
with	O
a	O
large	O
Collection	O
and	O
Explication	O
of	O
Words	O
and	O
Phrases	O
us	O
'd	O
in	O
our	O
Ancient	O
Statutes	O
,	O
Charters	O
,	O
Writs	O
,	O
old	O
Records	O
,	O
and	O
Processes	O
at	O
Law	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Etymology	O
and	O
Interpretation	O
of	O
the	O
Proper	O
Names	O
of	O
Men	O
,	O
Women	O
,	O
and	O
remarkable	O
Places	O
in	O
Great	O
Britain	O
:	O
Also	O
the	O
Dialects	O
of	O
our	O
different	O
Countries	O
.	O
Containing	O
many	O
Thousand	O
Words	O
more	O
than	O
either	O
Harris	O
,	O
Philips	O
,	O
Kersey	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
English	O
Dictionary	O
before	O
Extant	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
a	O
Collection	O
of	O
our	O
most	O
common	O
Proverbs	O
,	O
with	O
their	O
Explication	O
and	O
illustration	O
.	O
The	O
whole	O
Work	O
compiled	O
and	O
Methodcially	O
digested	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
for	O
the	O
Entertainment	O
of	O
the	O
Curious	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Information	O
of	O
the	O
Ignorant	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
young	O
Students	O
,	O
Artificers	O
,	O
Tradesmen	O
and	O
Foreigners	O
,	O
who	O
are	O
desirous	O
thorowly	O
to	O
understand	O
what	O
they	O
Speak	O
,	O
Read	O
or	O
Write	O
.	O
The	O
second	O
Edition	O
,	O
with	O
large	O
Additions	O
.	O
By	O
N.	O
Bailey	O
,	O
Philologos	O
.	O
M.	O
Misson	O
's	O
Memoirs	O
and	O
Observations	O
in	O
his	O
Travels	O
over	O
England	O
:	O
With	O
some	O
Account	O
of	O
Scotland	O
and	O
Ireland	O
.	O
Dispos	O
'd	O
in	O
Alphabetical	O
Order	O
.	O
Written	O
originally	O
in	O
French	O
,	O
and	O
translated	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Ozell	O
.	O
The	O
Miscellaneous	O
Works	O
of	O
that	O
eminent	O
Statesman	O
Francis	B-pers
Osborn	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
In	O
two	O
Vol	O
.	O
The	O
Eleventh	O
Edition	O
.	O
Lately	O
Publish	O
'd	O
,	O
A	O
Gray	B-pers
Cap	I-pers
for	O
a	O
Green	O
Head	O
.	O
Written	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Puckle	O
.	O
A	O
compleat	O
History	O
of	O
the	O
Lives	O
and	O
Robberies	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
Notorious	O
Highway-men	O
,	O
Foot-pads	O
,	O
Shop-lists	O
,	O
and	O
Cheats	O
,	O
of	O
both	O
Sexes	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
about	O
London	O
,	O
Westminster	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
Parts	O
of	O
Great	O
Britain	O
,	O
for	O
above	O
an	O
hundred	O
Years	O
past	O
,	O
continued	O
to	O
the	O
present	O
Time	O
.	O
By	O
Capt	O
.	O
Alex	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
In	O
two	O
Vol	O
.	O
Miscellaneous	O
Essays	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
I	O
.	O
Of	O
Company	O
and	O
Conversation	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
Of	O
Solitariness	O
and	O
Retirement	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
Of	O
Nobility	O
.	O
4	O
.	O
Of	O
Contentment	O
.	O
5	O
.	O
Of	O
Women	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
Of	O
the	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
God	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
Atheism	O
.	O
7	O
.	O
Of	O
Religion	O
.	O
8	O
.	O
Of	O
Kings	O
,	O
Princes	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Education	O
of	O
a	O
Prince	O
.	O
9	O
.	O
Of	O
Greatness	O
of	O
Mind	O
.	O
10	O
.	O
Of	O
the	O
Education	O
of	O
Children	O
.	O
11	O
.	O
Of	O
Law	O
.	O
12	O
.	O
Of	O
Man	O
.	O
13	O
.	O
Of	O
Old	O
Age	O
.	O
With	O
the	O
Life	O
and	O
Conversion	O
of	O
St.	O
Mary	O
Magdalen	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Reflections	O
upon	O
the	O
Conversion	O
of	O
the	O
good	O
Thief	O
;	O
also	O
,	O
the	O
Life	O
and	O
Conversion	O
of	O
St.	O
Paul	O
.	O
By	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Bulstrode	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Envoy	O
at	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
Brussels	O
,	O
from	O
King	O
Charles	B-pers
II	I-pers
.	O
and	O
King	O
James	B-pers
II	I-pers
.	O
Published	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Preface	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
Son	O
Whitlocke	O
Bulstrode	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
The	O
Second	O
Edition	O
.	O
An	O
Essay	O
on	O
Perspective	O
.	O
Written	O
in	O
French	O
by	O
William	B-pers
James	I-pers
's	O
Gravesande	O
,	O
Doctor	O
of	O
Laws	O
and	O
Philosophy	O
;	O
Professor	O
of	O
Mathematicks	O
and	O
Astronomy	O
at	O
Leyden	O
,	O
and	O
Fellow	O
of	O
the	O
Royal	O
Society	O
at	O
London	O
.	O
And	O
now	O
translated	O
into	O
English	O
.	O
Printed	O
by	O
J.	O
Humsreys	O
,	O
in	O
Bartholomew-lane	O
,	O
behind	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
;	O
for	O
E.	O
Symax	O
,	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Pope	O
's	O
Head	O
Alley	O
,	O
Cornhill	O
:	O
And	O
Sold	O
by	O
J.	O
Roberts	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Oxford-Arms	O
,	O
Warwick-Lane	O
,	O
1724	O
.	O
Where	O
Advertisements	O
are	O
taken	O
in	O
.	O
Price	O
Three	O
Pence	O
.	O
