TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
'S	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
During	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
the	O
Rt	O
.	O
Honble	O
Sir	O
George	O
Mertins	O
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
11th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
1725	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
George	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Little	O
Britain	O
.	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Jail-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTRY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
On	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
,	O
Monday	O
,	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
and	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
4th	O
,	O
5th	O
,	O
7th	O
,	O
8th	O
,	O
and	O
9th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Eleventh	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
GEORGE	B-pers
MERTTINS	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
King	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Dormer	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
Sergeant	O
at	O
Law	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
Country	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
JURORS	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
The	O
London	O
Jury	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Howsell	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Henchman	I-pers
,	O
Philip	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Markham	I-pers
,	O
Stephen	B-pers
Chidwick	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wyton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Stringer	I-pers
,	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Catlin	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Percival	I-pers
,	O
Elisha	B-pers
Impey	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Carpenter	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Whitemarsh	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hossack	I-pers
,	O
Walter	B-pers
Bury	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
follows	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Rider	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Regar	B-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
fifty	O
six	O
Pound	O
of	O
Butter	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Rich	B-pers
.	I-pers
Spearing	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
sixty	O
Firkins	O
of	O
Butter	O
were	O
landed	O
near	O
the	O
Custom-House	B-place
Key	I-place
,	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
between	O
Three	O
and	O
Four	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
taken	O
from	O
thence	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
stopt	O
with	O
it	O
under	O
the	O
Custom-House	O
Gate	O
by	O
Philip	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
Tide-waiter	O
.	O
)	O
Harison	O
had	O
but	O
just	O
eased	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
of	O
his	O
Burden	O
,	O
when	O
Peacock	O
(	O
a	O
Watchman	O
on	O
the	O
Keys	O
)	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
claim	O
'd	O
a	O
Share	O
of	O
the	O
Seizure	O
;	O
for	O
both	O
he	O
and	O
Harrison	O
at	O
first	O
imagined	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Smugler	O
;	O
but	O
finding	O
their	O
Mistake	O
,	O
they	O
carry	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
Newgate	O
by	O
Sir	O
Francis	B-pers
Forbes	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Butter	O
upon	O
the	O
Keys	O
,	O
about	O
Four	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
and	O
added	O
,	O
(	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
Innocence	O
more	O
visible	O
)	O
that	O
a	O
Carman	O
's	O
Boy	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Amy	B-pers
Burrows	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Toothaker	I-pers
,	O
12	O
Yards	O
of	O
Scarlet	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
value	O
6s	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
Mary	O
Toothaker	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
came	O
into	O
her	O
Shop	O
,	O
next	O
the	O
Cross-Keys	B-place
Tavern	I-place
in	O
Holborn	B-place
,	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Cross-Knot	O
;	O
at	O
which	O
time	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
having	O
no	O
body	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
her	O
Shop	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
pursue	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
the	O
others	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
should	O
rob	O
her	O
of	O
something	O
more	O
valuable	O
:	O
But	O
two	O
Weeks	O
after	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
causing	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
apprehended	O
,	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
for	O
2s	O
.	O
at	O
a	O
Chandler	O
's	O
Shop	O
in	O
Plumb-Tree	O
Court	O
in	O
Holborn	O
;	O
at	O
which	O
Place	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
William	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Colechurch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Pead	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Vergow	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Robert	O
Pead	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
(	O
an	O
Apothecary	O
)	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Halfpennyworth	O
of	O
Spanish	O
Liquorish	O
.	O
Vergow	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Back-Shop	O
,	O
came	O
out	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
use	O
to	O
sell	O
such	O
small	O
Quantities	O
;	O
with	O
which	O
Answer	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
Vergow	O
immediately	O
missing	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
(	O
both	O
which	O
before	O
hung	O
on	O
the	O
Pegs	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
)	O
he	O
pursued	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
His	O
Master	O
's	O
Hat	O
,	O
with	O
four	O
more	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
Basket	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
on	O
his	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
own	O
Hat	O
under	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
great	O
Coat	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
to	O
excuse	O
himself	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
the	O
Hats	O
but	O
just	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
John	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Gardener	O
at	O
the	O
Old	O
Rose	O
in	O
Marybone	O
,	O
had	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
20	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
often	O
employ	O
'd	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
Business	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
Dishonesty	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Defence	O
being	O
frivolous	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4s	O
.	O
10d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hughs	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Sepulchre	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
six	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
value	O
6s	O
.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Medley	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Chair-woman	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
of	O
carrying	O
away	O
the	O
Plates	O
;	O
but	O
offering	O
them	O
to	O
Sale	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
stopt	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
Examination	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Sheet	O
,	O
value	O
7s	O
.	O
and	O
several	O
Diaper	O
Clouts	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Walter	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
Barbara	B-pers
George	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
a	O
Nurse	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Walter	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
Druggist	O
,	O
in	O
Cheapside	B-place
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
she	O
often	O
missed	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
Clouts	O
in	O
washing	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
never	O
think	O
what	O
became	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
till	O
one	O
day	O
she	O
happened	O
to	O
find	O
the	O
Maid	O
's	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
made	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Clouts	O
that	O
before	O
had	O
been	O
missing	O
.	O
And	O
upon	O
further	O
Search	O
,	O
found	O
a	O
Gown	O
of	O
her	O
's	O
that	O
was	O
lined	O
with	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Sheet	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fryer	I-pers
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
threw	O
the	O
remaining	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Sheet	O
down	O
the	O
Vault	O
,	O
to	O
prevent	O
a	O
Discovery	O
,	O
having	O
dream	O
'd	O
that	O
her	O
Mistress	O
had	O
found	O
out	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
.	O
But	O
this	O
she	O
deny	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
that	O
Gown	O
was	O
lined	O
with	O
two	O
of	O
her	O
own	O
Aprons	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Petticoat	O
before	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Service	O
.	O
Her	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Templeman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
near	O
Aldersgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Robert	O
Ray	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Ray	I-pers
.	O
And	O
also	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
4	O
more	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
.	O
Robert	O
Ray	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Church	I-place
on	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
left	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Seat	O
;	O
and	O
returning	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
Mrs.	O
Smith	O
holding	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
her	O
say	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Pickpocket	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
the	O
Vestry	O
and	O
search	O
'd	O
.	O
Four	O
Handkerchiefs	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
lying	O
at	O
the	O
Vestry-Door	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
at	O
last	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Smith	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Hand	O
in	O
her	O
Cousin	O
D.	O
Humphries	O
's	O
Pocket	O
,	O
she	O
clapt	O
her	O
Hand	O
upon	O
his	O
,	O
held	O
him	O
fast	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
a	O
Pickpocket	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
Beadle	O
came	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Vestry	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
positive	O
Proof	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
dropt	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Handkerchief	O
at	O
the	O
Vestry-Door	O
;	O
and	O
no	O
body	O
owning	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Handkerchiefs	O
that	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Crisp	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Blackfryers	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Matth.ew	O
Bond	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
16	O
s.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Matthew	O
Bond	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
Time	O
.	O
Matthew	O
Bond	O
being	O
dry	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
about	O
Two	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
all	O
the	O
Doors	O
fast	O
;	O
he	O
returned	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
rising	O
again	O
about	O
7	O
,	O
found	O
that	O
his	O
Shop	O
Door	O
and	O
his	O
Till	O
were	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
taken	O
out	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Collier	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
done	O
by	O
somebody	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
Collier	O
answered	O
,	O
I	O
wish	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
Peter	O
,	O
for	O
be	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Vault	O
about	O
Six	O
this	O
Morning	O
They	O
examined	O
Peter	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
:	O
He	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
strongly	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
make	O
the	O
Matter	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
pay	O
them	O
whatever	O
they	O
had	O
lost	O
,	O
by	O
so	O
much	O
a	O
Week	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Collier	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Looking	O
Glass	O
Polisher	O
,	O
lodged	O
in	O
Mr	O
.	O
Bond	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
work	O
'd	O
Journey-work	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
Night	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
quarrel	O
'd	O
with	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
Leave	O
to	O
lie	O
for	O
one	O
Night	O
in	O
Mr.Bond	O
's	O
Garret	O
,	O
with	O
another	O
Servant	O
of	O
Mr.Collier	O
's	O
.	O
About	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Bedfellow	O
got	O
up	O
to	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
6	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
griped	O
,	O
and	O
must	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Vault	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
staid	O
near	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
told	O
his	O
Master	O
Collier	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
Mr	O
.	O
Bond	O
's	O
Shop	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
shut	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
fixing	O
the	O
Fact	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
bringing	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Noon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Burgess	I-pers
two	O
Guineas	O
and	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
Tho	O
.	O
Burgess	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
S.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Church	I-place
in	I-place
Fleetstreet	I-place
,	O
being	O
indifferently	O
drunk	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
ran	O
full	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
held	O
him	O
fast	O
,	O
and	O
pickt	O
his	O
Pocket	O
in	O
half	O
a	O
Minute	O
.	O
He	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Watch	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Men	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
beat	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
him	O
down	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Mob	O
gathering	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Watch	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
Men	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Women	O
that	O
assaulted	O
him	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
secur	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Watch	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
proved	O
upon	O
her	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Indictment	O
being	O
laid	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
open	O
Assault	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Edgworth	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Montague	I-pers
18	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
George	O
Montague	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
Yard	O
of	O
Sattin	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Brasier	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Montague	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
October	O
she	O
put	O
80	O
Guineas	O
into	O
a	O
Cup	O
,	O
and	O
lock	O
'd	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
Father	O
's	O
Cupboard	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
Bed-Chamber	O
.	O
That	O
her	O
Father	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
just	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Dunstable	O
Fair	O
,	O
sent	O
her	O
up	O
to	O
fetch	O
him	O
some	O
Money	O
;	O
at	O
which	O
time	O
she	O
miss	O
'd	O
13	O
Guineas	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
her	O
Father	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
Anger	O
,	O
nor	O
her	O
Sister	O
till	O
her	O
Father	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
When	O
her	O
father	O
return	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
some	O
Money	O
to	O
lay	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
miss	O
'd	O
5	O
Gunieas	O
more	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
told	O
her	O
Sister	O
.	O
They	O
then	O
searched	O
the	O
Cupboard	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
a	O
Board	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
loosen	O
'd	O
and	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Their	O
Father	O
died	O
.	O
They	O
examined	O
all	O
the	O
Servants	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
body	O
was	O
more	O
suspected	O
than	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
a	O
Higler	O
,	O
was	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Days	O
in	O
a	O
Week	O
at	O
Country	O
Fairs	O
and	O
Markets	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
left	O
the	O
Care	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Servants	O
never	O
used	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
her	O
Father	O
's	O
Room	O
;	O
nor	O
did	O
they	O
know	O
that	O
any	O
Money	O
was	O
kept	O
there	O
.	O
Mary	O
Montague	O
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
,	O
and	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
in	O
searching	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Trunk	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
half	O
Yard	O
of	O
Sattin	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Brasier	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
having	O
bought	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Sattin	O
for	O
a	O
Suit	O
,	O
she	O
left	O
it	O
at	O
her	O
Father	O
Montagne	O
's	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Charge	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
fetching	O
it	O
away	O
again	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
home	O
to	O
Bedford	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
sending	O
for	O
her	O
Mantua-maker	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
half	O
a	O
Yard	O
of	O
Shorter	O
than	O
when	O
she	O
bought	O
it	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
half	O
Yard	O
that	O
was	O
afterwards	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Trunk	O
was	O
exactly	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
kind	O
,	O
Stripe	O
and	O
Colour	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
Rooms	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
were	O
kept	O
lockt	O
;	O
that	O
people	O
were	O
frequently	O
coming	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Servants	O
often	O
going	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
might	O
know	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
the	O
where	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
kept	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
busy	O
a	O
Washing	O
when	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
observe	O
every	O
body	O
that	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
out	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Sattin	O
was	O
given	O
her	O
two	O
Years	O
ago	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
Masters	O
Daughters	O
had	O
several	O
times	O
bought	O
new	O
Cloths	O
without	O
his	O
Knowledge	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
often	O
complain	O
'd	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
more	O
Charges	O
now	O
than	O
when	O
his	O
Wife	O
was	O
alive	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Blackbeard	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Evans	B-pers
of	O
Thistleworth	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
She	O
Ass	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
Ram	O
5s	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
tame	O
Deer	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Mead	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
in	O
breaking	O
into	O
an	O
enclosed	O
Ground	O
of	O
John	O
Mead	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
killing	O
two	O
Fallow	O
Deer	O
,	O
value	O
20s	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Mead	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deer	O
were	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Ground	O
at	O
the	O
Times	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
soon	O
after	O
inform	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Persons	O
that	O
stole	O
them	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
of	O
Brentford	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
in	O
August	O
last	O
he	O
and	O
Tho	B-pers
James	I-pers
laid	O
a	O
Toil	O
(	O
or	O
Snare	O
)	O
to	O
catch	O
Deer	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Mead	O
's	O
Park	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
that	O
was	O
caught	O
in	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
She	O
Ass	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
a	O
Ram	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
third	O
a	O
tame	O
Deer	O
.	O
They	O
set	O
the	O
Ass	O
and	O
Ram	O
at	O
liberty	O
,	O
but	O
took	O
the	O
Deer	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
23s	O
.	O
to	O
Richard	B-pers
Beck	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Porter	O
in	O
Aldersgate	O
street	O
,	O
who	O
frequently	O
bought	O
Venison	O
that	O
was	O
stolen	O
.	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
this	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
Tho	O
.	O
James	O
,	O
met	O
at	O
the	O
King's-Head	O
at	O
Eling	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
went	O
together	O
to	O
Mr.Mead	O
's	O
Park	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
away	O
a	O
white	O
Doe	O
and	O
a	O
Fawn	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
brought	O
to	O
Smalbury-Green	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
this	O
Evidence	O
left	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Misselbrook	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Butcher	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
in	O
last	O
August	O
,	O
falling	O
into	O
Discourse	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
Deer-stealing	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
one	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Mead	O
's	O
tame	O
Deer	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
caught	O
in	O
a	O
Toil	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Goodneighbour	O
at	O
the	O
Two	O
Cocks	O
in	O
Thistleworth	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Night	O
Mr.Mead	O
's	O
tame	O
Deer	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
with	O
a	O
Toil	O
in	O
a	O
Basket	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
acknowledg	O
'd	O
the	O
killing	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
wild	O
Deer	O
in	O
October	O
,	O
but	O
deny	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
taking	O
the	O
same	O
Deer	O
in	O
August	O
,	O
any	O
farther	O
than	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
Persons	O
that	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
because	O
they	O
had	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
refused	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
Indictment	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
Fined	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
3d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
black	O
Gelding	O
Value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ralph	B-pers
Farr	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
Oct.	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
Farr	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Constance	B-pers
Hales	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Nelson	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Dixon	B-pers
,	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
quilted	O
Petticoat	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Dragget	O
Coat	O
and	O
Wastecoat	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Mosely	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
James	O
Mosely	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
lives	O
in	O
Well-close-Square	B-place
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
his	O
Lodgers	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
about	O
Four	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
another	O
of	O
his	O
Lodgers	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
Thieves	O
.	O
He	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
ran	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
found	O
his	O
Wastecoat	O
upon	O
the	O
Wall	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
going	O
into	O
his	O
Closet	O
,	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
other	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
suppos	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
by	O
some	O
body	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
Soon	O
after	O
Mrs.	O
Shepherd	O
,	O
(	O
another	O
of	O
his	O
Lodgers	O
)	O
inform	O
'd	O
him	O
that	O
his	O
Goods	O
were	O
pawn	O
'd	O
at	O
Mrs	O
Goodfellow	O
's	O
in	O
King-Street	O
,	O
Wapping	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
apprehend	O
James	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
and	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
know	O
more	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
.	O
He	O
thereupon	O
apprehended	O
Goodwin	O
,	O
(	O
who	O
pass	O
'd	O
for	O
Hales	O
's	O
Husband	O
)	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
committed	O
to	O
New-Prison	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
set	O
out	O
upon	O
Bail	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Goodfellow	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Hales	O
,	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
Nelson	O
,	O
brought	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
for	O
12	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Hales	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Goodwin	O
was	O
her	O
Country	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
to	O
visit	O
her	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Mosely	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
(	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
common	O
for	O
her	O
to	O
tell	O
any	O
Man	O
that	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
other	O
Lodgers	O
)	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
Lodging	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
lie	O
with	O
her	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
all	O
Night	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
refus	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
Landlady	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Husband	O
at	O
Sea	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
defile	O
his	O
Bed	O
for	O
the	O
World	O
.	O
Goodwin	O
soon	O
after	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Mrs.	O
Shepherd	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Take	O
your	O
Landlady	O
Mosely	O
aside	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Dram	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
I	O
'll	O
carry	O
off	O
her	O
Box	O
with	O
the	O
Rings	O
in	O
it	O
:	O
But	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
consent	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
However	O
Shepherd	O
brought	O
out	O
a	O
Bundle	O
of	O
Cloaths	O
:	O
She	O
desired	O
Shepherd	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
from	O
;	O
but	O
instead	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
Shepherd	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
Sister	O
,	O
who	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
out	O
to	O
Goodwin	O
,	O
from	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Nelson	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
pawn	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Goodfellow	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
received	O
the	O
Money	O
herself	O
.	O
Nelson	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
accidentally	O
met	O
Hales	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
of	O
Cloaths	O
:	O
Hales	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
Goodfellow	O
's	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
Hales	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
herself	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
Hales	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
reaching	O
Nelson	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hicks	I-pers
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Archer	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Tho	O
.	O
Parks	O
,	O
36	O
Iron	O
Hinges	O
,	O
value	O
35	O
s.	O
and	O
five	O
Locks	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Parks	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
Tho	O
.	O
Parks	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
keeps	O
a	O
Smith	O
's	O
Shop	O
in	O
Leather-Lane	B-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Hicks	O
was	O
his	O
Journeyman	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
intimate	O
with	O
Archer	O
the	O
other	O
Journeyman	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
Daniel	B-pers
Carpenter	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Carpenter	O
.	O
That	O
missing	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
he	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
Enquiry	O
,	O
found	O
that	O
Hicks	O
,	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
Archer	O
,	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Carpenter	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Panta	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
against	O
Archer	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
;	O
but	O
Hicks	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4s	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Randal	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Woodroff	I-pers
a	O
Handkerchief	O
value	O
10d	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Playhouse	B-place
in	O
Drury-Lane	B-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ran	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Mr.Shrimpton	O
saw	O
him	O
commit	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
searched	O
,	O
4	O
other	O
Handkerchiefs	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Mary	B-pers
Tipping	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
three	O
Smocks	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Penny	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
John	O
Penny	O
,	O
Constable	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
between	O
One	O
and	O
Two	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
and	O
a	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
had	O
beat	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
another	O
Woman	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
she	O
catch	O
'd	O
up	O
those	O
Things	O
to	O
secure	O
them	O
at	O
a	O
Friend	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
He	O
bid	O
her	O
send	O
for	O
somebody	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Women	O
came	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
believed	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
her	O
own	O
.	O
However	O
,	O
he	O
carry	O
'd	O
her	O
and	O
her	O
two	O
Friends	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
who	O
finding	O
nothing	O
proved	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
discharged	O
her	O
.	O
They	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
drink	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
sent	O
for	O
three	O
Quarts	O
of	O
Twopenny	O
to	O
treat	O
him	O
and	O
her	O
two	O
Friends	O
.	O
While	O
they	O
were	O
drinking	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
his	O
Return	O
found	O
her	O
at	O
Dinner	O
with	O
his	O
Wife	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Penny	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
after	O
her	O
Husband	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
who	O
having	O
some	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
fell	O
into	O
Discourse	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
tumbled	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Chair	O
;	O
she	O
rais	O
'd	O
her	O
again	O
,	O
carried	O
her	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
laid	O
her	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
considerately	O
set	O
a	O
Chamber-Pot	O
by	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
she	O
might	O
have	O
Occasion	O
to	O
make	O
Water	O
.	O
This	O
done	O
,	O
she	O
left	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
,	O
thinking	O
she	O
heard	O
her	O
rising	O
,	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
see	O
how	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
kneeling	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Chamber-Pot	O
betwixt	O
her	O
Legs	O
.	O
She	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
little	O
recover	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
Persuasion	O
came	O
down	O
to	O
Dinner	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
Dinner	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
Next	O
day	O
this	O
Evidence	O
miss	O
'd	O
her	O
Linnen	O
,	O
and	O
suspecting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
enquired	O
after	O
her	O
of	O
the	O
Neighbour	O
that	O
accidentally	O
met	O
with	O
her	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
;	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
she	O
found	O
her	O
,	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
her	O
before	O
Justice	O
Kirby	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
at	O
Pawn	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Daughter	O
came	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
beg	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
pawn	O
those	O
three	O
Smocks	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
bring	O
her	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
She	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
accordingly	O
,	O
and	O
intended	O
to	O
bring	O
her	O
the	O
Money	O
next	O
day	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
very	O
busy	O
,	O
was	O
prevented	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
very	O
unlikely	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Daughter	O
should	O
,	O
on	O
such	O
a	O
short	O
Acquaintance	O
,	O
put	O
so	O
much	O
Confidence	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
especially	O
when	O
she	O
saw	O
her	O
in	O
such	O
ill	O
Circumstances	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Betty	I-pers
,	O
Katharine	B-pers
Betty	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Cook	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Macoon	B-pers
,	O
and	O
Katharine	B-pers
Keys	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Rawlings	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
set	O
with	O
Diamonds	O
,	O
Value	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
Value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Watch	O
Value	O
30	O
s.	O
five	O
Silver	O
handled	O
Forks	O
Value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
Value	O
30s	O
.	O
six	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
Value	O
38	O
s.	O
three	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
Value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Gold	O
Studs	O
Value	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Handled	O
Knife	O
Value	O
3	O
s.	O
three	O
Tortoiseshell-Snuff-Boxes	O
Value	O
18	O
s.	O
twelve	O
Ells	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
2	O
Neckcloths	O
,	O
32	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Silver	O
,	O
Value	O
6	O
l.	O
6	O
Perukes	O
Value	O
6	O
l.	O
and	O
6	O
l.	O
6	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Robert	O
Rawlings	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Rawlings	I-pers
,	O
and	O
five	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
Value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Watch	O
Value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Ear-Rings	O
,	O
six	O
Cane-Heads	O
,	O
one	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
two	O
Gowns	O
,	O
a	O
Drugget	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
.	O
Robert	O
Rawlings	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
Oct.	O
last	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
no	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
next	O
Morning	O
that	O
his	O
House	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Entrance	O
was	O
made	O
at	O
the	O
Cellar	O
Window	O
under	O
the	O
Shop	O
Bulk	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
they	O
came	O
up	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
forced	O
off	O
a	O
Staple	O
,	O
into	O
which	O
the	O
Bolt	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
shut	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
.	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Month	O
,	O
Jack	B-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
(	O
who	O
has	O
since	O
been	O
executed	O
)	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
those	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
Katharine	O
Keys	O
being	O
in	O
his	O
Company	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
they	O
suspected	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Accomplice	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
escaping	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
Intelligence	O
where	O
she	O
lodged	O
,	O
went	O
thither	O
with	O
some	O
others	O
in	O
quest	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
told	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
her	O
Husband	O
in	O
Ludgate	O
.	O
They	O
followed	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
they	O
were	O
come	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
Lodging	O
.	O
A	O
Man	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
key	O
to	O
have	O
gone	O
to	O
her	O
Lodging	O
before	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
readily	O
offered	O
to	O
give	O
it	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
would	O
not	O
suffer	O
it	O
,	O
thinking	O
that	O
his	O
Design	O
was	O
to	O
remove	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
before	O
any	O
other	O
came	O
there	O
.	O
K.	O
Keys	O
then	O
desired	O
them	O
not	O
to	O
expose	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
quietly	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
found	O
9	O
Ells	O
of	O
Gulix	O
Holland	O
,	O
which	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
12	O
Ells	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
had	O
lost	O
.	O
By	O
examining	O
her	O
,	O
they	O
understood	O
that	O
Kate	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
alias	O
Macoon	B-pers
was	O
another	O
Acquaintance	O
of	O
Jack	O
Sheppard	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
and	O
Ned	O
Betty	O
(	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
frequently	O
lay	O
together	O
lay	O
together	O
at	O
his	O
Lodging	O
in	O
Litchfield-Street	O
.	O
Thither	O
they	O
went	O
with	O
a	O
Search	O
Warrant	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shoes	O
,	O
but	O
neither	O
Kate	O
Cook	O
nor	O
her	O
Bedfellow	O
.	O
From	O
thence	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
another	O
Lodging	O
that	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
Cook	O
in	O
Cranborn-Alley	O
,	O
Leicester-Fields	O
,	O
where	O
Kate	O
Keys	O
and	O
she	O
sometimes	O
lived	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
which	O
Kate	O
Keys	O
had	O
the	O
Key	O
.	O
Here	O
was	O
likewise	O
no	O
body	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Sword	O
,	O
the	O
remaining	O
3	O
Ells	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Basket	O
with	O
Thieving	O
Tools	O
,	O
and	O
Jack	O
Sheppard	O
's	O
Feetlocks	O
and	O
Handcuffs	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gowder	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Dolphin	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
Long	O
Alley	O
,	O
Moorfields	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
Nov.	O
about	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
of	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
Drink	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
very	O
earnest	O
in	O
whispering	O
,	O
and	O
often	O
mention	O
'd	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Jack	O
Sheppard	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
him	O
suspect	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
stolen	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
had	O
drank	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Pints	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
seek	O
for	O
a	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
this	O
Evidence	O
and	O
his	O
Man	O
searched	O
the	O
Bundle	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
they	O
found	O
several	O
Wigs	O
,	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
Gown	O
,	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
tumbled	O
together	O
.	O
This	O
increasing	O
his	O
suspicion	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
his	O
Return	O
was	O
inform	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Ned	O
Betty	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
again	O
for	O
the	O
Bundle	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
just	O
gone	O
to	O
the	O
Black	O
Dog	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Place	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
Constable	O
and	O
other	O
Assistance	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
apprehended	O
all	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
They	O
found	O
a	O
Silver	O
Handled	O
Knife	O
and	O
Fork	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
in	O
Kate	O
Cook	O
's	O
Stockings	O
.	O
She	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
from	O
Jack	O
Sheppard	O
,	O
and	O
added	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
vulgar	O
double	O
Entendre	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
Jack	O
Sheppard	O
's	O
Washerwoman	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
many	O
a	O
time	O
wash	O
'd	O
his	O
three	O
Pieces	O
betwixt	O
her	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
.	O
She	O
farther	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
Ned	O
Betty	O
was	O
entirely	O
innocent	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
had	O
only	O
hired	O
him	O
as	O
a	O
Porter	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
Bundle	O
.	O
These	O
Depositions	O
being	O
corroborated	O
by	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
then	O
made	O
their	O
Defence	O
.	O
Edward	O
Betty	O
protested	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
wholly	O
ignorant	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
hired	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
Bundle	O
for	O
a	O
Shilling	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Shoos	O
that	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
his	O
Lodging	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
sent	O
him	O
by	O
Kath	O
Cook	O
.	O
Kath	O
Keys	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Seamstress	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Linnen	O
that	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Room	O
was	O
brought	O
her	O
by	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
3	O
Shirts	O
.	O
Kath	O
Cook	O
in	O
Defence	O
of	O
herself	O
and	O
Ned	O
Betty	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Shoos	O
were	O
left	O
her	O
in	O
Pawn	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Owner	O
never	O
came	O
to	O
redeem	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
wash	O
'd	O
Linnen	O
for	O
Ned	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
coming	O
to	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
Shoos	O
,	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
lend	O
them	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
Goods	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
with	O
in	O
Long-Alley	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
cohabited	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
as	O
was	O
reported	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
her	O
own	O
part	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
Bundle	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
her	O
one	O
Morning	O
by	O
a	O
Coachman	O
,	O
whom	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
.	O
She	O
asked	O
him	O
who	O
they	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
bid	O
her	O
take	O
Care	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
that	O
own	O
'd	O
them	O
would	O
be	O
with	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
.	O
This	O
Gentleman	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
Jack	O
Sheppard	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
Wife	O
's	O
Cloaths	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
Sheppard	O
for	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
least	O
imagine	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
stolen	O
,	O
till	O
afterwards	O
she	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
.	O
She	O
own	O
'd	O
indeed	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
known	O
Sheppard	O
two	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
became	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
by	O
living	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
Apprentice	O
;	O
and	O
yet	O
she	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
ignorant	O
of	O
his	O
ever	O
being	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
tho	O
his	O
twice	O
escaping	O
from	O
thence	O
had	O
been	O
the	O
common	O
Discourse	O
of	O
the	O
whole	O
Nation	O
.	O
She	O
then	O
called	O
two	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
Sheppard	O
that	O
Night	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Polson	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Nag's-Head	O
in	O
Newport-Market	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
Ned	O
Betty	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Laycock	O
(	O
a	O
very	O
sufficient	O
Man	O
)	O
came	O
to	O
drink	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
to	O
they	O
were	O
follow	O
'd	O
by	O
Kate	O
Cook	O
.	O
Laycock	O
went	O
away	O
about	O
One	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
Ned	O
and	O
Kate	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Farmer's-Court	O
in	O
Dyers	O
Street	O
,	O
near	O
S.	O
Giles	O
's	O
Church	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
Two	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
Ned	O
Betty	O
and	O
Kate	O
Cook	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
there	O
(	O
but	O
not	O
together	O
)	O
till	O
7	O
the	O
same	O
Morning	O
.	O
Each	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Burglary	O
not	O
being	O
positively	O
proved	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Court	O
ordered	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
bring	O
a	O
second	O
Indictment	O
against	O
Cook	O
and	O
Keys	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Goods	O
Pursuant	O
to	O
which	O
,	O
Katharine	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
in	O
receiving	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Rawlings	I-pers
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stoln	O
.	O
The	O
Depositions	O
in	O
the	O
former	O
Trial	O
were	O
repeated	O
in	O
this	O
,	O
with	O
additional	O
Proofs	O
of	O
her	O
Intimacy	O
with	O
Sheppard	O
,	O
by	O
her	O
frequently	O
coming	O
to	O
him	O
when	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
acknowledging	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
often	O
lain	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
confessing	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
in	O
Long-Alley	O
came	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
Fined	O
and	O
Imprison	O
'd	O
.	O
Katharine	B-pers
Keys	I-pers
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
9	O
Ells	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Rawlings	I-pers
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stoln	O
.	O
Tho	O
.	O
Lewin	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
with	O
his	O
Master	O
from	O
the	O
Round-house	O
with	O
another	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
told	O
by	O
a	O
Boy	O
that	O
Sheppard	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
neighbouring	O
Brandy	O
Shop	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
Parker-Lane	O
:	O
He	O
went	O
directly	O
thither	O
,	O
and	O
rushing	O
in	O
between	O
two	O
Watchman	O
,	O
seized	O
upon	O
Sheppard	O
,	O
just	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
saying	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
go	O
Landlady	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
can	O
stay	O
no	O
longer	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
there	O
,	O
immediately	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
this	O
Evidence	O
's	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Hold	O
,	O
hold	O
,	O
where	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
to	O
carry	O
him	O
?	O
The	O
Linnen	O
,	O
as	O
before	O
deposed	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
her	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
at	O
first	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
Kate	O
Cook	O
;	O
but	O
afterwards	O
that	O
Sheppard	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
some	O
Shirts	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
stolen	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Stratton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Peter	I-place
Cheap	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
19	O
Yards	O
of	O
Tape	O
,	O
one	O
Thousand	O
of	O
Pins	O
,	O
10	O
Yards	O
of	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
Hand	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Leather	O
Belt	O
,	O
Value	O
18	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Hartshorn	O
Handled	O
Hanger	O
,	O
Value	O
16	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
Oct	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
be	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Scurrier	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Dunston	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
Value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Bine	I-pers
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
Nov	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
Bine	O
(	O
who	O
keeps	O
the	O
Bull	O
in	O
Rochester	O
)	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Bine	O
's	O
Recognizances	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hawks	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Magnus	I-place
Martyr	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	O
Hammerton	O
,	O
a	O
Gown	O
value	O
12d	O
.	O
a	O
Ring	O
value	O
12s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
;	O
a	O
Smock	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Eliz	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
,	O
and	O
6	O
Guineas	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hammerton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
Nov	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
(	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	B-place
Alehouse	I-place
on	O
Fishstreet-Hill	B-place
)	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bull	O
Head	O
in	O
Leadonhall-Street	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Okely	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.Botolph	B-place
's	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Cock	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
President	B-pers
and	O
Governor	B-pers
of	I-pers
the	I-pers
Poor	I-pers
of	I-pers
the	I-pers
London	I-pers
Work-house	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
Whipt	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Elan	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
of	O
S.Antholin	B-place
's	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Josiah	B-pers
Lambert	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Wig	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Trustan	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
to	O
have	O
their	O
Wigs	O
powdered	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
none	O
but	O
a	O
Boy	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
stole	O
the	O
Wig	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
quickly	O
miss	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
pursued	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
Elan	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
;	O
and	O
acquitted	O
Philips	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Mace	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Hancock	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
Dec.	O
last	O
.	O
John	O
Hancock	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
having	O
been	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
Coach	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
the	O
Coachman	O
to	O
drive	O
to	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
at	O
Mr	O
.	O
Pain	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
Brasier	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Golden	O
Lyon	O
in	O
Grace-Church-Street	O
.	O
The	O
Coach	O
stopt	O
by	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
what	O
means	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
disordered	O
with	O
drinking	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
the	O
Coachman	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
in	O
Fleet-Street	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
.	O
Why	O
do	O
you	O
get	O
out	O
here	O
,	O
Sir	O
?	O
says	O
the	O
Coachman	O
.	O
Because	O
I	O
am	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
says	O
Mr.	O
Hancock	O
.	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
in	O
Fleet-Street	O
.	O
-	O
Pray	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
trouble	O
yourself	O
about	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
take	O
your	O
Money	O
and	O
begone	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
;	O
and	O
taking	O
out	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
offered	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Coachman	O
for	O
his	O
Fare	O
.	O
As	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
this	O
Discourse	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Watch	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
;	O
Come	O
,	O
my	O
Dear	O
,	O
says	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
let	O
you	O
and	O
I	O
go	O
home	O
to	O
Bed	O
together	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
then	O
put	O
them	O
both	O
into	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Evidence	O
drove	O
on	O
to	O
Ludgate-Hill	B-place
,	O
where	O
the	O
Women	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
ran	O
down	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
(	O
the	O
Evidence	O
)	O
jumping	O
off	O
the	O
Coach-Box	O
,	O
stopt	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Watch	O
coming	O
to	O
his	O
Assistance	O
,	O
secured	O
her	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Jomes	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
three	O
times	O
offered	O
him	O
a	O
Shilling	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
refused	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
her	O
before	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
searched	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
not	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
from	O
Wood-Street	O
Compter	O
,	O
where	O
her	O
Husband	O
was	O
confined	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Man	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
talking	O
together	O
at	O
a	O
Coach-Door	O
,	O
they	O
asked	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
drink	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
refused	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
on	O
towards	O
Fleet	O
-	O
Ditch	O
,	O
where	O
a	O
Man	O
clapt	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
surprized	O
;	O
and	O
turning	O
back	O
,	O
he	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Watch	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
was	O
then	O
as	O
innocent	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
her	O
Birth	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Penelope	B-pers
Adair	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Bertless	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Countess	B-pers
Spinello	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Sylvia	B-pers
Anna	I-pers
Landina	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Aldermary	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
12	O
Gross	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Silk	O
Lacing	O
,	O
value	O
8l	O
.	O
324	O
Yards	O
of	O
Ribbon	O
value	O
54s	O
.	O
70	O
Yards	O
of	O
Silk	O
Breed	O
value	O
4l	O
.	O
4	O
Gross	O
of	O
Silk	O
Binding	O
value	O
4l	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Birch	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
Nov.	O
last	O
.	O
Aaron	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
keeps	O
a	O
Warehouse	O
at	O
the	O
Blue	B-place
Leg	I-place
in	O
Bow-Lane	B-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
Quality	O
of	O
Factor	O
for	O
James	O
Birch	O
of	O
Coventry	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
being	O
recommended	O
to	O
him	O
by	O
Capt	O
.	O
Murray	O
,	O
who	O
brought	O
her	O
over	O
from	O
Ireland	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
Daughter	O
of	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Adair	I-pers
,	O
Bart	O
.	O
and	O
Widow	O
of	O
Count	O
Spinello	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
whatever	O
Charges	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
on	O
her	O
Account	O
,	O
should	O
be	O
repaid	O
him	O
with	O
Advantage	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
as	O
tender	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
his	O
Daughter	O
;	O
sent	O
her	O
Money	O
,	O
bought	O
fine	O
Cloaths	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
made	O
her	O
welcome	O
to	O
a	O
plentiful	O
Table	O
,	O
kept	O
her	O
in	O
her	O
Sickness	O
,	O
paid	O
her	O
Doctor	O
,	O
and	O
defray	O
'd	O
the	O
Charges	O
of	O
her	O
Lying-in	O
,	O
the	O
Nursing	O
and	O
Burial	O
of	O
her	O
Child	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
as	O
kind	O
to	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
his	O
own	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
for	O
some	O
Reasons	O
(	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
fit	O
to	O
mention	O
in	O
Court	O
)	O
took	O
her	O
another	O
Lodging	O
at	O
Hoxton	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
third	O
Lodging	O
in	O
Wardrobe-Court	O
in	O
Carter-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
fourth	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Falkenham	O
's	O
in	O
Thames-Street	O
.	O
So	O
that	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
she	O
had	O
cost	O
him	O
near	O
a	O
hundred	O
Pounds	O
.	O
Yet	O
,	O
after	O
all	O
this	O
,	O
she	O
ungratefully	O
,	O
and	O
like	O
a	O
wicked	O
jade	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
,	O
had	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
ruin	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
lost	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Warehouse	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Amount	O
of	O
about	O
300	O
l.	O
But	O
little	O
!	O
Ah	O
very	O
little	O
did	O
he	O
think	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Adair	O
,	O
that	O
Sylvia	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Countess	O
Spinello	O
was	O
the	O
Thief	O
!	O
He	O
sometimes	O
found	O
Letters	O
directed	O
to	O
her	O
from	O
Dublin	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
great	O
Things	O
were	O
promised	O
her	O
by	O
her	O
Relations	O
in	O
Ireland	O
.	O
These	O
he	O
then	O
thought	O
she	O
had	O
carelesly	O
mislaid	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
so	O
established	O
his	O
good	O
Opinion	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
lent	O
her	O
91	O
l.	O
She	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
gave	O
him	O
in	O
part	O
of	O
Payment	O
a	O
Note	O
of	O
Hand	O
for	O
42	O
l.	O
from	O
her	O
supposed	O
Brother	O
Robert	B-pers
William	I-pers
Adair	I-pers
,	O
which	O
was	O
endorsed	O
with	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Shelden	I-pers
,	O
Sheriff	O
of	O
Worcoster	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
he	O
wrote	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Sheldon	O
,	O
who	O
returned	O
him	O
no	O
Answer	O
;	O
but	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
Week	O
he	O
received	O
a	O
Letter	O
dated	O
from	O
Salop	O
,	O
and	O
signed	O
as	O
the	O
Note	O
,	O
R.W.Adair	O
.	O
In	O
this	O
he	O
had	O
Thanks	O
return	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
Promises	O
of	O
Recompence	O
made	O
for	O
the	O
Care	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Penelope	O
.	O
It	O
concluded	O
with	O
Advice	O
to	O
meet	O
Mr.	O
Sheldon	O
,	O
(	O
who	O
would	O
be	O
in	O
London	O
in	O
the	O
following	O
Week	O
)	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
's	O
a	O
Woollen-Draper	O
in	O
Covent-Garden	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
his	O
Sylvia	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
thither	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
received	O
her	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
Shew	O
of	O
Respect	O
,	O
and	O
spoke	O
much	O
in	O
the	O
Favour	O
of	O
her	O
Brother	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
sorry	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
a	O
day	O
sooner	O
,	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Sheldon	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
then	O
gone	O
back	O
for	O
Worcester	O
.	O
Being	O
thus	O
disappointed	O
,	O
he	O
returned	O
home	O
with	O
his	O
Lady	O
.	O
But	O
yet	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
far	O
from	O
entertaining	O
even	O
the	O
least	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
her	O
Dishonesty	O
,	O
till	O
one	O
Day	O
,	O
to	O
his	O
great	O
Astonishment	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
informed	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Goods	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Camm	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
he	O
apprehended	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
beside	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
offered	O
to	O
Camm	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
several	O
Parcels	O
to	O
Tho	B-pers
Baylis	I-pers
a	O
Dealer	O
in	O
Irish	O
Linnen	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Two-Neck	O
'd	O
Swan	O
in	O
Lad-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
but	O
15	O
d.	O
a	O
piece	O
for	O
the	O
best	O
Sort	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
worth	O
a	O
Crown	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Camm	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Silk	O
Lacing	O
to	O
Sale	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
for	O
an	O
old	O
Debt	O
that	O
was	O
owing	O
her	O
at	O
Coventry	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
recommended	O
to	O
him	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
King	O
,	O
a	O
Porteress	O
at	O
an	O
Inn	O
in	O
White	O
-	O
Chappel	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
buy	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
be	O
satisfy	O
'd	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
Property	O
.	O
She	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
leave	O
them	O
with	O
him	O
till	O
10	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
should	O
either	O
buy	O
them	O
or	O
return	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
left	O
them	O
accordingly	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
but	O
presently	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
she	O
had	O
bethought	O
herself	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
take	O
them	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
buy	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
willing	O
to	O
look	O
them	O
over	O
first	O
;	O
and	O
since	O
't	O
was	O
your	O
Proposal	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
keep	O
them	O
till	O
to-morrow	O
Morning	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
part	O
with	O
them	O
before	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
away	O
in	O
a	O
Huff	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
sent	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
King	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
but	O
her	O
Husband	O
told	O
the	O
Messenger	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
believed	O
the	O
Lady	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Sisters	O
,	O
neither	O
true	O
nor	O
trusty	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Evening	O
Madam	O
Adair	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
with	O
Gilbert	O
an	O
Attorney	O
,	O
at	O
Numb.5	O
.	O
in	O
Garden-Court	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
King	O
was	O
again	O
sent	O
for	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
admired	O
the	O
Gentlewoman	O
should	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
her	O
Name	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Camm	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
never	O
sent	O
her	O
,	O
nor	O
ever	O
saw	O
her	O
but	O
once	O
,	O
accidentally	O
at	O
a	O
Friend	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
This	O
gave	O
this	O
Deponent	O
a	O
greater	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
Miss	O
Penny	O
than	O
he	O
had	O
before	O
;	O
and	O
therefore	O
he	O
positively	O
refused	O
to	O
part	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
farther	O
Enquiry	O
.	O
The	O
Countess	O
and	O
her	O
Attorney	O
,	O
went	O
away	O
very	O
angry	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Menaces	O
behind	O
them	O
.	O
Next	O
day	O
,	O
this	O
Deponent	O
's	O
Servant	O
found	O
out	O
Mr.	O
Pritchard	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Winnock	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
having	O
heard	O
that	O
Pritchard	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
Baylis	O
in	O
Lad-Lane	O
offering	O
to	O
sell	O
him	O
such	O
Goods	O
,	O
he	O
informed	O
Pritchard	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
own	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
all	O
of	O
Pritchard	O
,	O
except	O
some	O
odd	O
Parcels	O
which	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
bid	O
her	O
produce	O
her	O
Bills	O
of	O
Parcels	O
and	O
Receipts	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
none	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
commonly	O
bought	O
for	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
conditionally	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
or	O
return	O
the	O
Goods	O
if	O
not	O
sold	O
;	O
and	O
for	O
that	O
Reason	O
,	O
she	O
always	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Note	O
of	O
Hand	O
under	O
his	O
Bills	O
,	O
and	O
whenever	O
she	O
paid	O
him	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
her	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
indors	O
'd	O
it	O
off	O
.	O
These	O
Bills	O
she	O
called	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
expose	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
produce	O
what	O
Bills	O
he	O
had	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
took	O
some	O
Papers	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
but	O
of	O
little	O
Signification	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Point	O
in	O
hand	O
,	O
being	O
only	O
Accounts	O
of	O
the	O
Expences	O
she	O
had	O
put	O
him	O
to	O
for	O
Childbed-Linnen	O
,	O
a	O
Midwife	O
,	O
Nurses	O
,	O
Chickens	O
,	O
Caudles	O
,	O
Possets	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Necessaries	O
.	O
She	O
farther	O
said	O
then	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
from	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
often	O
ordered	O
a	O
Porter	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
Goods	O
in	O
her	O
Name	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
always	O
sent	O
,	O
-	O
if	O
his	O
Wife	O
did	O
not	O
happen	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
would	O
afterwards	O
have	O
persuaded	O
her	O
to	O
have	O
confess	O
'd	O
a	O
Bond	O
and	O
Judgement	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
which	O
she	O
urged	O
as	O
an	O
Argument	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
bought	O
them	O
fairly	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
often	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
sorry	O
he	O
had	O
troubled	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
had	O
never	O
wrong	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
only	O
did	O
it	O
to	O
secure	O
his	O
Credit	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Birch	O
;	O
for	O
if	O
that	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
ruin	O
'd	O
.	O
She	O
then	O
called	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
these	O
Assertions	O
.	O
Thompson	O
the	O
Porter	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
often	O
went	O
for	O
Mrs.	O
Adair	O
to	O
Prichard	O
for	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
Orders	O
not	O
to	O
let	O
Prichard	O
's	O
Wife	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
knew	O
who	O
he	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
.	O
That	O
Prichard	O
himself	O
did	O
several	O
times	O
deliver	O
Parcels	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
And	O
one	O
time	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
rainy	O
,	O
Pritchard	O
bid	O
him	O
take	O
Care	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
let	O
the	O
Parcel	O
be	O
wet	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
Silk	O
Lacing	O
.	O
Another	O
time	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
brought	O
a	O
Parcel	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Adair	O
,	O
she	O
opened	O
it	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
saw	O
it	O
was	O
Silk	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
Parcel	O
as	O
was	O
then	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Camm	O
had	O
before	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
was	O
offered	O
to	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
An	O
Attorney	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
in	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
Prichard	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
draw	O
a	O
Warrant	O
of	O
Attorney	O
,	O
to	O
confess	O
a	O
Bond	O
and	O
Judgment	O
from	O
the	O
said	O
Mrs.	O
Adair	O
to	O
him	O
(	O
Prichard	O
)	O
for	O
Money	O
and	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Prichard	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
Cloaths	O
which	O
he	O
bought	O
for	O
her	O
in	O
Henrietta-Street	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
living	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Falkenham	O
's	O
in	O
Thomas-Street	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodged	O
16	O
Weeks	O
,	O
commencing	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
Prichard	O
often	O
came	O
to	O
visit	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
times	O
gave	O
her	O
Lace	O
and	O
Ribbon	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
That	O
one	O
time	O
in	O
particular	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
at	O
Nine	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
six	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Silk	O
Lacing	O
and	O
Breed	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
Vaux-Hall	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Another	O
time	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
brought	O
Coffee	O
,	O
staid	O
and	O
drank	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
must	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
gave	O
him	O
2d	O
.	O
and	O
he	O
laugh	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Parcel	O
seal	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Paper-Bag	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
open	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
saw	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
Yellow	O
Lacing	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Falkenham	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
Prichard	O
often	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
Word	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Ray	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Nurse	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
times	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Falkenham	O
's	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
give	O
her	O
Silk	O
;	O
and	O
often	O
heard	O
him	O
bid	O
her	O
make	O
free	O
with	O
him	O
when-ever	O
she	O
wanted	O
Money	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
her	O
dear	O
Bosom-Friend	O
:	O
That	O
she	O
attended	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
when	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
and	O
Prichard	O
constantly	O
visited	O
her	O
every	O
Day	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
she	O
had	O
ever	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
only	O
he	O
beg	O
'd	O
of	O
her	O
to	O
own	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
,	O
because	O
otherwise	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
ruin	O
'd	O
,	O
for	O
his	O
Goods	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
make	O
up	O
his	O
Accompts	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Birch	O
;	O
And	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
serve	O
him	O
so	O
far	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
afterwards	O
make	O
her	O
whatever	O
Amends	O
she	O
would	O
require	O
.	O
The	O
Turnkey	O
of	O
Woodstreet	O
Compter	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
there	O
,	O
Prichard	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
He	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
against	O
her	O
for	O
the	O
World	O
:	O
That	O
Prichard	O
agreed	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Lodging	O
for	O
the	O
first	O
5	O
Nights	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
rate	O
of	O
Half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
Fee	O
,	O
2s	O
.	O
for	O
the	O
first	O
Night	O
;	O
and	O
1	O
s.	O
each	O
for	O
the	O
4	O
next	O
.	O
Moses	B-pers
Levi	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Prichard	O
told	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Mitre	O
Tavern	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
never	O
have	O
sworn	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
had	O
he	O
not	O
been	O
oblig	O
'd	O
to	O
it	O
:	O
That	O
Prichard	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
to	O
her	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
O	O
my	O
Dear	O
,	O
how	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
?	O
I	O
neither	O
can	O
nor	O
would	O
swear	O
against	O
you	O
for	O
the	O
World	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Dugdale	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
at	O
the	O
Tavern	O
with	O
Prichard	O
,	O
after	O
Mrs.	O
Adair	O
was	O
in	O
Custody	O
,	O
Prichard	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
He	O
could	O
never	O
swear	O
against	O
her	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
ye	O
mean	O
,	O
(	O
says	O
this	O
Witness	O
)	O
have	O
you	O
not	O
swore	O
against	O
her	O
already	O
?	O
Is	O
she	O
not	O
committed	O
upon	O
your	O
Oath	O
?	O
No	O
,	O
(	O
says	O
Prichard	O
)	O
I	O
neither	O
have	O
,	O
nor	O
will	O
,	O
nor	O
can	O
swear	O
against	O
her	O
;	O
-	O
it	O
was	O
an	O
Imposition	O
of	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
Clerk	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
see	O
if	O
the	O
Bill	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
brought	O
in	O
Ignoramus	O
.	O
Prichard	O
then	O
called	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
invalidate	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
her	O
Porter	O
Thompson	O
,	O
who	O
plies	O
in	O
S.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-yard	O
.	O
Smith	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
but	O
last	O
Night	O
he	O
heard	O
Thompson	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
thought	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
as	O
great	O
a	O
Thief	O
,	O
a	O
Bite	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Cheat	O
,	O
as	O
any	O
England	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
she	O
'd	O
never	O
have	O
the	O
Punishment	O
she	O
deserved	O
.	O
Several	O
others	O
gave	O
Thompson	O
but	O
a	O
scurvy	O
Character	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Whole	O
,	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Clutterbuck	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Michael	I-place
Crooked-Lane	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
40lb	O
.	O
of	O
Tallow	O
,	O
value	O
30s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Hutchinson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Joyner	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Cecily	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wagstaff	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Fellows	I-pers
,	O
2	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Sewing	O
Silk	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Wagstaff	O
and	O
Fellows	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
clearly	O
proved	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Landis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Undershaft	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
13	O
Canes	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ralph	B-pers
Martland	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
Oct.	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
as	O
Jos	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Cornhill	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
met	O
him	O
and	O
cheapen	O
'd	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Cross-Keys	B-place
Tavern	I-place
Door	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Bundle	O
from	O
the	O
Boy	O
,	O
under	O
Pretence	O
of	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Candle	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
to	O
choose	O
one	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
wait	O
in	O
the	O
Entry	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Aunt	O
(	O
who	O
he	O
said	O
kept	O
the	O
Bar	O
)	O
might	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
(	O
the	O
Boy	O
)	O
;	O
for	O
(	O
continues	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
Kinsman	O
that	O
sells	O
Canes	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Aunt	O
would	O
be	O
angry	O
if	O
she	O
knew	O
that	O
I	O
bought	O
one	O
of	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
.	O
The	O
Boy	O
waited	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
wondering	O
why	O
his	O
Chapman	O
was	O
so	O
long	O
in	O
choosing	O
2	O
Cane	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Bar-Keeper	O
,	O
and	O
enquir	O
'd	O
for	O
her	O
Nephew	O
.	O
The	O
Gentlewoman	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
Nephew	O
:	O
But	O
when	O
he	O
mention	O
'd	O
the	O
Canes	O
,	O
the	O
Drawers	O
inform	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Tavern	O
was	O
a	O
Thorowfare	O
,	O
and	O
remember	O
'd	O
that	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
ago	O
they	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
go	O
through	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
of	O
Canes	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
afterwards	O
selling	O
the	O
Canes	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Powel	O
in	O
the	O
Borough	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
discover	O
'd	O
and	O
apprehended	O
,	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
no	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
Cheat	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
directed	O
the	O
Jury	O
to	O
acquit	O
him	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
order	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
prefer	O
another	O
Bill	O
against	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
unlawfully	O
and	O
fraudulently	O
taking	O
away	O
the	O
said	O
Canes	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
done	O
accordingly	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
Fined	O
and	O
Imprisoned	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hilliard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Tho	O
.	O
Nash	O
three	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
two	O
Silk	O
Aprons	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
Mob	O
and	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Howell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
Sep.	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Nash	O
,	O
a	O
Victualler	O
in	O
Peter-street	B-place
.	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
following	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
offer	O
'd	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
Reward	O
for	O
apprehending	O
her	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
a	O
Men	O
that	O
lay	O
with	O
her	O
the	O
preceding	O
Night	O
came	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
her	O
Lodging	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
took	O
her	O
a-bed	O
.	O
Her	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Susan	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Sallis	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
Aug	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
too	O
weak	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Allington	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Aldrington	B-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hoop-Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Farmer	I-pers
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
worked	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
stopt	O
in	O
offering	O
it	O
to	O
Sale	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
Sarah	B-pers
Clarkson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
Prig	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Mug	O
value	O
36s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Tho	O
.	O
Prig	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
Nov	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
of	O
Norton-Folgate	B-place
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
T.	O
Smith	O
,	O
three	O
Coats	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
Smith	O
lett	O
a	O
Garret	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
her	O
Mother	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
several	O
Things	O
in	O
the	O
second	O
Indictment	O
were	O
lost	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
her	O
Mother	O
being	O
charged	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
forsook	O
their	O
Lodging	O
at	O
Smith	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
another	O
:	O
Upon	O
which	O
Smith	O
procured	O
Prig	O
the	O
Constable	O
to	O
apprehend	O
them	O
.	O
Prig	O
brought	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
stole	O
from	O
thence	O
a	O
Silver	O
Mug	O
,	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
hid	O
it	O
under	O
the	O
Coats	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
mist	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
suspected	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
accused	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
confess	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
each	O
Indictment	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Whipt	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Alexander	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Rob	B-pers
Gaston	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Gown	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
15	O
s.	O
six	O
Smocks	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
12	O
Suits	O
of	O
Head-Cloaths	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Blakeway	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Box	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
in	O
her	O
Room	O
unlock	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
upon	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
another	O
Robbery	O
;	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
hearing	O
,	O
went	O
thither	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
awkwardly	O
rigg	O
'd	O
in	O
her	O
Cloaths	O
.	O
Roberts	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Alexander	O
put	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
fill	O
'd	O
her	O
Apron	O
with	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
:	O
But	O
Alexander	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
met	O
Roberts	O
in	O
Short's-Gardens	O
with	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
in	O
her	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
together	O
to	O
a	O
Gin-Shop	O
in	O
Vinegar-Yard	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
drest	O
Roberts	O
in	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
rest	O
in	O
Pawn	O
for	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
Roberts	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
And	O
acquitted	O
Alexander	O
.	O
Margaret	O
Roberts	O
and	O
Sarah	O
Alexander	O
,	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
on	O
the	O
23rd	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
a	O
Gown	O
val	O
.	O
5s	O
.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoos	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Eliz	B-pers
Ellison	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Head-Cloaths	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
.	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Ellison	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
lives	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Jones	O
's	O
in	O
Holesford-Alley	B-place
in	O
Drury-Lane	B-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
as	O
she	O
lay	O
a-bed	O
in	O
a	O
Moon-light	O
Night	O
,	O
between	O
2	O
and	O
3	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
Peg	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
came	O
into	O
her	O
Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
off	O
the	O
Bed	O
;	O
which	O
awakening	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
started	O
up	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
Who	O
's	O
there	O
?	O
Peg	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
Tis	O
I.	O
I	O
!	O
Who	O
are	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
?	O
-	O
Why	O
,	O
my	O
Mistress	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
the	O
Candle	O
was	O
safe	O
.	O
-	O
Your	O
Mistress	O
!	O
Who	O
is	O
your	O
Mistress	O
?	O
-	O
Go	O
look	O
,	O
says	O
Peg	O
;	O
and	O
snatching	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Head-Cloaths	O
off	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
ran	O
down	O
Stairs	O
.	O
She	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
then	O
jumpt	O
out	O
of	O
Bed	O
quite	O
naked	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
ran	O
down	O
after	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Watch	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
got	O
off	O
for	O
the	O
present	O
,	O
but	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
Round-house	O
,	O
where	O
Roberts	O
confesed	O
,	O
that	O
Alexander	O
put	O
her	O
down	O
the	O
Cellar-Window	O
.	O
But	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
Defence	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
Ellison	O
was	O
a	O
common	O
whore	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Gown	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
follow	O
the	O
same	O
Trade	O
,	O
in	O
Coleston's-court	O
(	O
and	O
not	O
Holesford	O
's	O
Alley	O
)	O
in	O
Drury	O
Lane	O
:	O
But	O
she	O
refusing	O
to	O
comply	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
prosecuted	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Aldgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Hannah	B-pers
Rickaby	I-pers
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Pocket	O
value	O
9	O
d.	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
26	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
Oct	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
Hannah	O
Rickaby	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
by	O
Alderman	O
Parsons	O
's	O
Brewhouse	O
in	O
Wapping	B-place
,	O
a	O
Man	O
shoved	O
her	O
from	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
snatch	O
'd	O
off	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
up	O
Barr-Street	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
pursued	O
him	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
she	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
to	O
her	O
by	O
William	B-pers
Cuthbert	I-pers
.	O
She	O
believ	O
'd	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
Man	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Pocket	O
was	O
not	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Eliz	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
walking	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
Arm	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
:	O
That	O
as	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taking	O
the	O
Wall	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
turn	O
'd	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Lamp	O
then	O
shining	O
full	O
in	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
she	O
was	O
positive	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
very	O
Man	O
that	O
snatch	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Pocket	O
.	O
William	O
Cuthbert	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
hearing	O
a	O
Woman	O
cry	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
perceiving	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
running	O
apace	O
,	O
he	O
stood	O
to	O
receive	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
up	O
his	O
Heels	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
beg	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
let	O
go	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
pursued	O
by	O
Bailiffs	O
.	O
But	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
go	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Woman	O
first	O
.	O
The	O
Watch	O
quickly	O
came	O
to	O
their	O
Assistance	O
,	O
and	O
secur	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Execution-Dock	O
,	O
a	O
Man	O
clapt	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
under	O
fear	O
of	O
an	O
Arrest	O
,	O
thought	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Bailiff	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
took	O
to	O
his	O
Heels	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
only	O
Reason	O
of	O
his	O
running	O
up	O
Burr	O
Street	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Strong	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Whitechappel	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Shirt	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
Smock	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
Napkins	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Susan	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
Nov	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
others	O
were	O
seen	O
in	O
the	O
Ground	O
where	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
hung	O
to	O
dry	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
being	O
taken	O
off	O
the	O
Lines	O
and	O
carried	O
away	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
but	O
nothing	O
being	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Nixon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Whitechappel	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
12	O
yards	O
of	O
Stuffs	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
Nov	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
whom	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
Sister	O
,	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
looking	O
on	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
afraid	O
to	O
pursue	O
her	O
,	O
left	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
should	O
rob	O
him	O
of	O
a	O
greater	O
Value	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
while	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
was	O
a	O
Stranger	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
by	O
Chance	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Iron	O
Key	O
of	O
a	O
Turn-cock	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Dame	O
Eliz	B-pers
Feast	I-pers
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Dolden	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
who	O
had	O
formerly	O
work	O
'd	O
at	O
that	O
Brewhouse	O
)	O
was	O
seen	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
with	O
the	O
Key	O
under	O
his	O
great	O
Coat	O
.	O
In	O
his	O
Defence	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
left	O
carelesly	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
only	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
its	O
place	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
Midford	I-pers
Esq	O
,	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
Nov	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Rutter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Master	O
's	O
House	O
a	O
Silver	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
two	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Not	O
guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Chelsea	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
Wastecoat	O
,	O
Breeches	O
,	O
Shirt	O
,	O
and	O
Hat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Man	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23rd	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
over	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
into	O
his	O
Room	O
,	O
took	O
away	O
his	O
Cloths	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
stopt	O
selling	O
them	O
in	O
Monmouth-Street	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gritton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
Margaret	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
,	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
a	O
Fan	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
Guineas	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
Nov	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Mow	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
-	O
Hawes	O
Esq	O
;	O
in	O
Channel-Row	O
,	O
Westminster	O
;	O
that	O
having	O
a	O
Holiday	O
given	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
a	O
Stranger	O
in	O
London	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
desire	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
City	O
to	O
find	O
out	O
a	O
Person	O
that	O
ow	O
'd	O
her	O
some	O
Money	O
:	O
They	O
went	O
,	O
she	O
received	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
he	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
staid	O
till	O
about	O
Eight	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Katharine-Street	O
in	O
Covent-Garden	O
.	O
Marg	O
.	O
Dixon	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
soon	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
parted	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Mow	O
,	O
she	O
enquired	O
the	O
Way	O
of	O
two	O
Men	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
lived	O
not	O
far	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
her	O
:	O
He	O
carry	O
'd	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
her	O
into	O
a	O
Tavern	O
in	O
a	O
strange	O
Place	O
;	O
she	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
beg	O
'd	O
of	O
him	O
to	O
to	O
put	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
right	O
Way	O
;	O
he	O
promised	O
her	O
he	O
would	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
which	O
drove	O
to	O
an	O
Inn	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Way	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
her	O
Rings	O
off	O
her	O
Finger	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
her	O
Handkerchief	O
and	O
Fan	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
frighted	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
to	O
do	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Inn	O
,	O
she	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
back	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
from	O
her	O
:	O
He	O
swore	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
except	O
she	O
would	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
Wine	O
and	O
the	O
Coach	O
.	O
She	O
consented	O
,	O
rather	O
than	O
lose	O
her	O
Things	O
;	O
and	O
knowing	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
three	O
Guineas	O
before	O
she	O
met	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
put	O
her	O
Hand	O
into	O
her	O
Bosom	O
to	O
take	O
one	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
gone	O
.	O
She	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
that	O
the	O
Rogue	O
had	O
got	O
her	O
Money	O
too	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
get	O
off	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
prevented	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
fell	O
into	O
a	O
Swoon	O
.	O
The	O
Tapster	O
and	O
the	O
Maid	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bear-Inn	O
in	O
Piccadilly	O
,	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
latter	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Evidence	O
;	O
adding	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
Rogue	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
her	O
of	O
all	O
,	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
Damn	O
the	O
Bitch	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
have	O
no	O
more	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Maid	O
catch	O
'd	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Hair	O
and	O
stopt	O
him	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
corroborated	O
by	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
who	O
farther	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
conducted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
Round-House	O
;	O
and	O
thence	O
next	O
Morning	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
deliver	O
'd	O
the	O
Rings	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
Constable	O
)	O
and	O
the	O
Constable	O
produced	O
them	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
-	O
Hawes	O
Esq	O
;	O
gave	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
of	O
his	O
Maid	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
by	O
assuring	O
the	O
Court	O
that	O
he	O
believed	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
good	O
natur	O
'd	O
,	O
innocent	O
,	O
modest	O
,	O
honest	O
,	O
Country	O
Girl	O
,	O
and	O
entirely	O
unacquainted	O
with	O
the	O
Town	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
talking	O
with	O
his	O
Friend	O
in	O
Russel-street	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
by	O
very	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
shew	O
her	O
the	O
Way	O
to	O
Channel-Row	O
;	O
he	O
having	O
Business	O
that	O
Way	O
,	O
was	O
glad	O
of	O
her	O
Company	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
across	O
the	O
Park	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
having	O
Occasion	O
to	O
make	O
Water	O
,	O
went	O
aside	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
while	O
a	O
Man	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
round	O
the	O
Waste	O
:	O
She	O
was	O
frighted	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
stepping	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
meant	O
by	O
it	O
?	O
Sir	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
I	O
ask	O
your	O
Pardon	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
Lady	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
you	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
retired	O
.	O
Soon	O
after	O
,	O
she	O
dropt	O
her	O
Handkerchief	O
and	O
Fan	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
pray	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
'em	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
They	O
then	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Sun	O
Tavern	O
in	O
King-Street	O
,	O
Westminster	O
;	O
where	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
she	O
would	O
treat	O
him	O
for	O
his	O
Trouble	O
in	O
coming	O
so	O
far	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
They	O
drank	O
two	O
Pints	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
so	O
drunk	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
fell	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Chair	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Rings	O
dropt	O
off	O
her	O
Finger	O
:	O
He	O
took	O
both	O
her	O
and	O
them	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
them	O
till	O
they	O
parted	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
late	O
for	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
beg	O
'd	O
of	O
him	O
to	O
provide	O
a	O
Lodging	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
They	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Brandy-Shop	O
by	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
they	O
took	O
Coach	O
to	O
the	O
Bear-Inn	O
in	O
Piccadilly	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
spoke	O
for	O
a	O
Bed	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
being	O
willing	O
to	O
drink	O
first	O
,	O
they	O
sat	O
down	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
the	O
began	O
to	O
cry	O
about	O
her	O
Rings	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
refuse	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
Wine	O
and	O
the	O
Coach	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
falling	O
into	O
Fits	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
was	O
called	O
,	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Round-House	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Ship	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
stood	O
talking	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
when	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
shew	O
her	O
the	O
Way	O
home	O
.	O
Robert	O
Mow	O
then	O
deposed	O
again	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
sober	O
when	O
he	O
left	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Tapster	O
,	O
Maid	O
,	O
and	O
Constable	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bear-Inn	O
,	O
farther	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
in	O
Fitts	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
drunk	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
that	O
House	O
.	O
but	O
yet	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Gentlemen	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Reputation	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
Servant	O
to	O
some	O
of	O
their	O
Acquaintance	O
:	O
One	O
more	O
in	O
particular	O
said	O
,	O
having	O
once	O
by	O
Mistake	O
given	O
him	O
a	O
Guinea	O
in	O
changing	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
he	O
very	O
honestly	O
brought	O
it	O
him	O
again	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
Tho	B-pers
Hemmer	I-pers
,	O
Tho	B-pers
Rowden	I-pers
and	O
Rich	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
take	O
from	O
thence	O
16	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
Value	O
36	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Stephen	O
Watts	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
Nov	O
.	O
about	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
Stephen	O
Watts	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
keeps	O
a	O
Sale-Shop	O
at	O
the	O
Cross-Keys	B-place
in	O
Monmouth-street	B-place
,	O
and	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
he	O
made	O
fast	O
his	O
Door	O
and	O
Windows	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
;	O
but	O
about	O
3	O
he	O
was	O
called	O
up	O
again	O
by	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
the	O
Shop	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
.	O
Tho	B-pers
Flemm	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Tho	O
.	O
Rowdon	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
met	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
about	O
7	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
agreed	O
to	O
try	O
their	O
Fortune	O
in	O
Monmonth-street	O
.	O
About	O
Midnight	O
they	O
all	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
passing	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
Mason	O
struck	O
the	O
Bar	O
of	O
the	O
Windows	O
with	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
no	O
great	O
Difficulty	O
for	O
them	O
to	O
get	O
in	O
there	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
forced	O
off	O
the	O
Staple	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
ript	O
off	O
the	O
Hinges	O
of	O
the	O
Outer-Shutters	O
,	O
and	O
wrenched	O
off	O
the	O
Runner	O
of	O
those	O
within	O
,	O
and	O
pushing	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
back	O
,	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
all	O
returned	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
spent	O
the	O
remaining	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
Next	O
day	O
they	O
put	O
the	O
Breeches	O
into	O
a	O
Sack	O
,	O
went	O
all	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
by	O
turns	O
,	O
till	O
they	O
had	O
dispos	O
'd	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Two	O
Pair	O
this	O
Evidence	O
pawn	O
'd	O
to	O
Norwood	O
in	O
Hart-street	O
,	O
Covent-Garden	O
for	O
4s	O
.	O
Five	O
Pair	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sold	O
to	O
Jos	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
4	O
Pair	O
to	O
Sarah	B-pers
Shad	I-pers
,	O
both	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	O
.	O
Collins	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
Breeches	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Taylor	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
them	O
himself	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
.	O
He	O
observed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
go	O
a-cross	O
the	O
Way	O
to	O
two	O
of	O
his	O
Companions	O
,	O
who	O
waited	O
for	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
in	O
a	O
Sack	O
.	O
This	O
made	O
him	O
suspect	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
stol'n	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
he	O
stept	O
out	O
after	O
these	O
3	O
Men	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
being	O
aware	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
made	O
off	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
had	O
the	O
Breeches	O
cry	O
'd	O
;	O
by	O
which	O
he	O
found	O
that	O
they	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Watts	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Shorey	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
having	O
heard	O
of	O
Watts	O
's	O
being	O
robbed	O
;	O
and	O
going	O
along	O
Hart-street	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
Flemmer	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
knew	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Rogue	O
,	O
go	O
into	O
Norwood	O
's	O
with	O
2	O
Pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Mason	O
waited	O
with	O
a	O
Sack	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
.	O
All	O
which	O
gave	O
him	O
ground	O
to	O
think	O
that	O
these	O
were	O
the	O
Men	O
that	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Watts	O
;	O
and	O
therefore	O
he	O
stood	O
still	O
to	O
take	O
Notice	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
suspecting	O
,	O
said	O
to	O
Mason	O
-	O
D	O
-	O
that	O
Chuckle-beaded	O
Son	O
of	O
a	O
Bitch	O
.	O
What	O
does	O
he	O
stand	O
watching	O
us	O
for	O
?	O
-	O
Go	O
over	O
and	O
take	O
him	O
a	O
Knock	O
.	O
As	O
Mason	O
was	O
coming	O
towards	O
him	O
,	O
Flemmer	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
without	O
the	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
together	O
.	O
This	O
Evidence	O
then	O
went	O
and	O
gave	O
Norwood	O
a	O
Hint	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
stop	O
them	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
again	O
And	O
Flemmer	O
happening	O
to	O
come	O
the	O
same	O
Evening	O
,	O
Norwood	O
apprehended	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
impeached	O
the	O
others	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
himself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
others	O
indeed	O
were	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
the	O
Evening	O
before	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
him	O
gone	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
refused	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
them	O
below	O
with	O
his	O
Wife	O
.	O
About	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
they	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
made	O
no	O
Answer	O
.	O
They	O
came	O
a	O
23d	O
time	O
at	O
Break	O
of	O
Day	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Sack	O
,	O
and	O
Breeches	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
vend	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
but	O
was	O
no	O
way	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
60	O
lb	O
.	O
Weight	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
Value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
and	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
Nov	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Frances	B-pers
Watlin	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Roper	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
F.	O
Watling	O
for	O
stealing	O
privately	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
36	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Yarn	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
Oct	O
.	O
last	O
;	O
and	O
S.	O
Roper	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Eagle	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Yards	O
of	O
Lace	O
,	O
1	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Half	O
Guinea	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
Gordon	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
Sanders	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
Sep.	O
last	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S	B-place
Bride	I-place
's	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
Value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Hen	B-pers
.	I-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
Nov	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
at	O
Night	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
left	O
his	O
Watch	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
at	O
the	O
Bricklayers	B-place
Arms	I-place
by	O
Fleet-ditch	B-place
.	O
He	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
;	O
but	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
Week	O
after	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
Tapster	O
at	O
that	O
House	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10.	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Bride	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Barton	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
2	O
other	O
Watches	O
,	O
Value	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
Sept	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
Tho	O
.	O
Martin	O
Watchmaker	O
in	O
Fleet-street	B-place
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
about	O
8	O
at	O
Night	O
he	O
left	O
his	O
Boy	O
at	O
Work	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
;	O
but	O
returning	O
soon	O
after	O
,	O
found	O
his	O
Sash	O
broke	O
,	O
3	O
Watches	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Gimblet	O
sticking	O
in	O
the	O
Door-Post	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
it	O
appeared	O
the	O
Knocker	O
had	O
been	O
ty	O
'd	O
to	O
prevent	O
a	O
Pursuit	O
.	O
The	O
Boy	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
,	O
Jack	B-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
Shop	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
bad	O
him	O
stick	O
up	O
his	O
Tools	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
use	O
his	O
Master	O
to	O
such	O
ill	O
Habits	O
of	O
working	O
so	O
late	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
came	O
by	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
repeated	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
past	O
to	O
and	O
fro	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
The	O
last	O
time	O
they	O
came	O
together	O
,	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
the	O
Drawer	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
something	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
thinking	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
put	O
his	O
Tools	O
up	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
,	O
Well	O
done	O
,	O
my	O
Lad	O
,	O
now	O
I	O
like	O
you	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
they	O
seemed	O
to	O
part	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
after	O
,	O
Sheppard	O
dash	O
'd	O
his	O
Hand	O
thro	O
the	O
Glass	O
,	O
and	O
snatched	O
away	O
3	O
Watches	O
.	O
He	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
went	O
to	O
run	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
fasted	O
on	O
the	O
Outside	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10.d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	O
Page	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
whereas	O
John	O
Sheppard	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Savoy	O
,	O
was	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
Aug.	O
last	O
indicted	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Kneebone	I-pers
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
108	O
Yards	O
of	O
Woollen	O
Cloth	O
,	O
2	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
then	O
and	O
there	O
convicted	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
Sheppard	O
afterwards	O
flying	O
from	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
Page	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
Sheppard	O
to	O
be	O
convicted	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
did	O
notwithstanding	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
Sept	O
.	O
last	O
,	O
receive	O
,	O
comfort	O
,	O
and	O
harbour	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
Sheppard	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
after	O
Sheppard	O
's	O
first	O
Escape	O
from	O
Newgate	O
,	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
Keepers	O
,	O
Mr	O
.	O
Rouse	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Langly	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Alston	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Ireton	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
3	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
many	O
on	O
Horseback	O
,	O
rode	O
to	O
Finchly	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
having	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
seen	O
thereabouts	O
,	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Clare-Market	O
Butcher	O
