TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice	O
Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
,	O
On	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
17th	O
,	O
18th	O
,	O
and	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Tenth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
PETER	B-pers
DELME	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Fortescue	O
Aland	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justice	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
JURORS	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
The	O
London	O
Jury	O
John	B-pers
Short	I-pers
,	O
Joshua	B-pers
Walfrey	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
Johns	B-pers
Rutty	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Cowell	I-pers
,	O
Benoni	B-pers
Pistor	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
March	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Bourn	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Pennyman	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Goddard	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Prater	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wootton	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
George	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Worsey	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Brounker	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Gouge	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bushel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Linnen	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Briton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
other	O
Persons	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Confession	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fryer	I-pers
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Tailor	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
15	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
having	O
been	O
at	O
Clare	O
Market	O
with	O
a	O
Friend	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
met	O
him	O
about	O
Fleet	B-place
Ditch	I-place
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
refused	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
she	O
stand	O
for	O
her	O
Brother	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
sit	O
down	O
by	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
Bench	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
several	O
Times	O
perceived	O
Ann	O
Tailor	O
's	O
Hand	O
about	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
he	O
missed	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sure	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
as	O
he	O
safe	O
upon	O
the	O
Bench	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
pleaded	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Company	O
of	O
two	O
other	O
Women	O
,	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
his	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
appearing	O
to	O
the	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
they	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Maslam	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
several	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Coach-house	O
of	O
the	O
Honourable	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
Earl	I-pers
of	I-pers
Macclesfield	I-pers
,	O
Lord	O
High	O
Chancellor	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
hired	O
as	O
an	O
extraordinary	O
Servant	O
,	O
to	O
assist	O
in	O
his	O
Lordship	O
's	O
Stables	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Absence	O
of	O
another	O
Servant	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
sick	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
discharg	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Curtains	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
were	O
missing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Coach-house	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Lodgings	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Defence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Strand	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Morrice	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Prestock	I-pers
,	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Shops	O
,	O
under	O
Pretence	O
to	O
buy	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
suspected	O
to	O
have	O
stolen	O
Stockings	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Prescott	O
's	O
,	O
being	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
each	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
,	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
drawn	O
into	O
the	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
by	O
another	O
Woman	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
on	O
each	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Coats	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Tailor	I-pers
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Throwster	O
's	O
Star	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Length	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Month	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
for	O
Manslaughter	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
.	O
Three	O
Evidences	O
who	O
were	O
present	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
one	O
a	O
Journey-man	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
a	O
hired	O
Servant	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Newcomen	O
,	O
Throwster	O
,	O
that	O
Anthony	B-pers
Wharton	I-pers
who	O
turn	O
'd	O
the	O
Mill	O
,	O
called	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
come	O
to	O
his	O
Work	O
,	O
and	O
tie	O
up	O
the	O
Threads	O
which	O
were	O
broke	O
at	O
the	O
Mill	O
;	O
that	O
telling	O
him	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
Threads	O
down	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Deceased	O
swore	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
come	O
for	O
three	O
Threads	O
;	O
that	O
thereupon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
spoke	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
to	O
do	O
his	O
Work	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
treat	O
a	O
Man	O
who	O
was	O
his	O
Betters	O
,	O
with	O
saucy	O
Language	O
;	O
that	O
upon	O
this	O
the	O
Deceased	O
gave	O
him	O
very	O
saucy	O
and	O
reviling	O
Language	O
,	O
and	O
persisting	O
in	O
his	O
saucy	O
Carriage	O
,	O
he	O
followed	O
him	O
to	O
catch	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Boy	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
running	O
round	O
the	O
Mill	O
,	O
and	O
still	O
reviling	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
catch	O
him	O
,	O
did	O
at	O
last	O
catch	O
up	O
the	O
Throwster	O
's	O
star	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
towards	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
being	O
stooping	O
,	O
and	O
raising	O
up	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
received	O
the	O
Blow	O
on	O
his	O
Head	O
.	O
The	O
Surgeon	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Scull	O
was	O
broken	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
believe	O
it	O
might	O
occasion	O
his	O
Death	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
more	O
hopeful	O
Way	O
of	O
Recovery	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
Nurse	O
gave	O
him	O
Ale	O
and	O
Brandy	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
he	O
fell	O
into	O
a	O
Fever	O
and	O
Delirium	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
divers	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
an	O
extraordinary	O
Character	O
,	O
for	O
Piety	O
and	O
peaceable	O
Carriage	O
,	O
as	O
never	O
inclinable	O
to	O
Passion	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Margaret	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Gunnis	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Negro	O
Black	O
Boy	O
,	O
and	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
come	O
for	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Times	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
to	O
buy	O
Liquors	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
House	O
being	O
broken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Things	O
stolen	O
,	O
she	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
Search	O
made	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
3	O
Rings	O
and	O
32	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Ring	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
bid	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
on	O
Tower-Hill	O
.	O
The	O
Boy	O
had	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
which	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
for	O
about	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
without	O
the	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
her	O
Master	O
or	O
the	O
Family	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
coming	O
to	O
a	O
Kinswoman	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
being	O
seen	O
by	O
some	O
People	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
they	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
stopt	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
secur	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
owned	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Gardiner	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Dorcus	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Linnen	O
,	O
of	O
divers	O
Persons	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
25	O
l.	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
January	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
having	O
made	O
a	O
Complaint	O
to	O
a	O
Friend	O
,	O
of	O
her	O
having	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
he	O
upon	O
Enquiry	O
,	O
heard	O
that	O
Stephen	O
Gardiner	O
,	O
who	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
Repute	O
of	O
an	O
ill	O
idle	O
Fellow	O
,	O
he	O
thereupon	O
enquired	O
for	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
thither	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
about	O
6	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
Bed	O
with	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
then	O
on	O
his	O
Back	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
worth	O
about	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
not	O
thinking	O
did	O
belong	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
taxing	O
him	O
with	O
robbing	O
Mrs.	O
Roberts	O
,	O
searching	O
between	O
the	O
bed	O
and	O
Mat	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Sack	O
in	O
which	O
were	O
the	O
Goods	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
stolen	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
except	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Shifts	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
to	O
John	O
Martin	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
Dram	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
stay	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
lockt	O
up	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
broke	O
up	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
not	O
be	O
apprehended	O
.	O
That	O
having	O
apprehended	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
John	O
Martin	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
keeps	O
a	O
little	O
Brandy	O
Shed	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
found	O
the	O
Linnen	O
put	O
wet	O
into	O
the	O
Bottom	O
of	O
a	O
Basket	O
,	O
and	O
Small	O
coal	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
John	O
Martin	O
did	O
own	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
the	O
Linnen	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
stay	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
while	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
broken	O
up	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
likewise	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Shirt	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
on	O
his	O
Back	O
,	O
he	O
pulled	O
off	O
at	O
the	O
Justices	O
,	O
and	O
deliver	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
His	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
also	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
left	O
secure	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
the	O
Shutter	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
Glass	O
of	O
the	O
Casement	O
had	O
been	O
broken	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
having	O
been	O
lock	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Lodging	O
about	O
4	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Linnen	O
,	O
in	O
an	O
Alley	O
.	O
John	O
Martin	O
pleaded	O
,	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
receive	O
the	O
Shirt	O
and	O
two	O
shifts	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
upon	O
a	O
Box	O
,	O
where	O
Gardiner	O
left	O
them	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
demanded	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
Gardiner	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
And	O
John	O
Martin	O
guilty	O
of	O
Receiving	O
,	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bonner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Archdeacon	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
feloniously	O
steal	O
a	O
Money	O
Drawer	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
also	O
Money	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Trotter	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
Penny	O
worth	O
of	O
Liquorish	O
,	O
immediately	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
the	O
Box	O
was	O
miss	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
wherein	O
he	O
had	O
acknowledg	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Confederate	O
with	O
John	O
Archdeacon	O
,	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
of	O
taking	O
the	O
Box	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
Archdeacon	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
shared	O
between	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
Second	O
Time	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	O
Trotter	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
steal	O
his	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
hearing	O
his	O
Shutters	O
boring	O
,	O
watch	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Archdeacon	O
(	O
who	O
had	O
formerly	O
been	O
his	O
Servant	O
)	O
contriving	O
how	O
to	O
get	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
design	O
'd	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
come	O
in	O
,	O
ordering	O
his	O
Servants	O
to	O
be	O
ready	O
to	O
assist	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
Archdeacon	O
did	O
come	O
in	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
Servant	O
striking	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Poker	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Person	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
in	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
to	O
be	O
Bonner	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
not	O
swear	O
it	O
,	O
This	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
his	O
two	O
Servants	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
from	O
12	O
a-Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
till	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
before	O
they	O
could	O
bore	O
the	O
Shutter	O
to	O
get	O
in	O
,	O
by	O
Reason	O
of	O
People	O
coming	O
by	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
heard	O
them	O
swear	O
violently	O
,	O
and	O
talk	O
all	O
the	O
Time	O
,	O
lying	O
Perdue	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
without	O
Light	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
wherein	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
second	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Barlow	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
one	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Exton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Drawer	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
lost	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
young	O
,	O
supposed	O
to	O
be	O
twelve	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
.	O
The	O
Child	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
given	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
would	O
have	O
taken	O
Money	O
not	O
to	O
prosecute	O
.	O
Upon	O
Consideration	O
of	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hyde	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Hannah	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
of	O
her	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
Part	O
of	O
a	O
Gold	O
Chain	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
this	O
present	O
January	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
an	O
Alley	O
where	O
was	O
an	O
Arch	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
doing	O
something	O
to	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
ten	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
her	O
her	O
Sister	O
of	O
about	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
.	O
And	O
his	O
Back	O
being	O
towards	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
to	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
but	O
heard	O
her	O
cry	O
in	O
a	O
strangling	O
Tone	O
,	O
O	O
my	O
Chain	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
calling	O
out	O
,	O
another	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
taken	O
him	O
,	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
follow	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
caus	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
apprehended	O
.	O
That	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
his	O
Hands	O
were	O
upon	O
the	O
Neck	O
of	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Child	O
had	O
the	O
Locket	O
,	O
and	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Chain	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
upon	O
Mrs.	O
Lucas	O
charging	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
saying	O
he	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
not	O
being	O
an	O
Officer	O
,	O
he	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
That	O
seeing	O
his	O
Wife	O
have	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
what	O
be	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
shut	O
his	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
to	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
take	O
any	O
Thing	O
out	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
removing	O
some	O
Yards	O
from	O
the	O
Place	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Pieces	O
of	O
the	O
Chain	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
he	O
stood	O
just	O
before	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Chain	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
drop	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
off	O
from	O
the	O
Ground	O
in	O
that	O
Place	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
some	O
Persons	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Job	B-pers
Orchard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Carrol	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Dwelling	O
house	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
keeping	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
a	O
Word	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
replied	O
he	O
might	O
speak	O
an	O
hundred	O
if	O
he	O
pleased	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
he	O
said	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
him	O
,	O
all	O
the	O
Matter	O
was	O
he	O
should	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
a	O
naked	O
Bayonet	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Bosom	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
surprise	O
got	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Handkerchief	O
was	O
ty	O
'd	O
about	O
his	O
Neck	O
with	O
a	O
loose	O
Knot	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
then	O
torn	O
all	O
to	O
Pieces	O
.	O
Three	O
Evidences	O
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Meredith	I-pers
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Day	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Simon	B-pers
Crowchin	I-pers
,	O
confirm	O
'd	O
what	O
Carrol	O
had	O
depos	O
'd	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
pull	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
off	O
from	O
Carrol	O
's	O
Neck	O
;	O
nor	O
did	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
take	O
Notice	O
of	O
any	O
Word	O
of	O
an	O
Arrest	O
being	O
given	O
,	O
nor	O
of	O
Fleming	O
Evans	O
the	O
Officer	O
's	O
being	O
there	O
,	O
nor	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
his	O
Assistant	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
about	O
12	O
Months	O
ago	O
in	O
the	O
Mint	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
barbarously	O
used	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
under	O
30	O
Pumps	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
got	O
a	O
Bench	O
Warrant	O
,	O
and	O
Information	O
that	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Persons	O
were	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Carrol	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
meeting	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Evans	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
arrest	O
Carrol	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
arrested	O
,	O
the	O
Cry	O
was	O
given	O
,	O
Bailiffs	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
at	O
the	O
New	O
Mint	O
in	O
Gravel-Lane	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
violently	O
by	O
a	O
Mob	O
,	O
barbarously	O
us	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
almost	O
Kill	O
'd	O
.	O
To	O
prove	O
this	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
Fleming	O
Evans	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
Orders	O
to	O
arrest	O
John	O
Carrol	O
,	O
for	O
five	O
Guineas	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Suit	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Natt	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Kennorly	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
Evans	O
the	O
Officer	O
Orders	O
to	O
arrest	O
John	O
Carrol	O
for	O
that	O
Sum	O
,	O
due	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Natt	O
for	O
Ale	O
and	O
Beer	O
.	O
Evans	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Joseph	O
Wright	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
assist	O
him	O
,	O
in	O
arresting	O
Carrol	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
all	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
told	O
him	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
Process	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
Cry	O
of	O
Bailiffs	O
given	O
,	O
a	O
great	O
Mob	O
presently	O
gathered	O
,	O
Carrol	O
was	O
rescu	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Warrant	O
against	O
him	O
and	O
others	O
for	O
a	O
Rescue	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
and	O
Joseph	O
Wright	O
were	O
obliged	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
their	O
Way	O
off	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
he	O
behaved	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
murdered	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
barbarously	O
used	O
.	O
Joseph	O
Wright	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
going	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Carrol	O
's	O
to	O
arrest	O
him	O
,	O
went	O
all	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
that	O
Evans	O
told	O
Carrol	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Writ	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lay	O
Hands	O
on	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Cry	O
of	O
Bailiffs	O
given	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
Mob	O
getting	O
together	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
oblig	O
'd	O
to	O
run	O
for	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
afterwards	O
barbarously	O
used	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
being	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
House	O
,	O
she	O
heard	O
an	O
Out-cry	O
of	O
Bailiffs	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
out	O
she	O
saw	O
a	O
great	O
Crowd	O
of	O
People	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
among	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
Wretched	O
filthy	O
Pickle	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
as	O
was	O
said	O
,	O
duck	O
'd	O
in	O
a	O
Place	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
Sort	O
of	O
Houses	O
of	O
Office	O
had	O
been	O
empty	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Dram	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Mob	O
threatned	O
to	O
pull	O
her	O
House	O
down	O
,	O
for	O
relieving	O
him	O
.	O
Barbara	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
also	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
us	O
'd	O
as	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
likewise	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
Dram	O
of	O
Geneva	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
fetch	O
'd	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
from	O
Carrol	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
which	O
as	O
it	O
seem	O
'd	O
had	O
been	O
left	O
there	O
,	O
before	O
they	O
put	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
stinking	O
Ditch	O
.	O
It	O
appearing	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Foundation	O
for	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
any	O
Assault	O
and	O
Robbery	O
committed	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
Carrol	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
aiding	O
and	O
assisting	O
to	O
Fleming	O
Evans	O
the	O
Officer	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
serving	O
a	O
legal	O
Process	O
on	O
Carrol	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
And	O
it	O
also	O
appearing	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
soul	O
and	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Treatment	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
unlawful	O
,	O
and	O
barbarous	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
set	O
up	O
a	O
New	O
Mint	O
in	O
Defiance	O
of	O
the	O
Law	O
,	O
they	O
ordered	O
John	O
Carrol	O
,	O
Samuel	O
Meredith	O
,	O
Charles	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
Simon	O
Crowchin	O
,	O
three	O
of	O
his	O
Evidences	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
into	O
Custody	O
,	O
and	O
bound	O
Fleming	O
Evans	O
the	O
Officer	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Job	O
Orchard	O
in	O
a	O
Recognizance	O
to	O
prosecute	O
them	O
for	O
such	O
Abuse	O
of	O
the	O
Officer	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Assistants	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
,	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
keeping	O
a	O
Tavern	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Cook	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Money	O
being	O
wrapt	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Cloth	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
in	O
a	O
Drawer	O
in	O
the	O
Bar	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
miss	O
'd	O
,	O
great	O
Inquiry	O
was	O
made	O
after	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
own	O
her	O
knowing	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
Month	O
or	O
six	O
Weeks	O
,	O
till	O
having	O
more	O
Reason	O
than	O
before	O
to	O
suspect	O
her	O
,	O
upon	O
making	O
Enquiry	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
among	O
some	O
of	O
her	O
Acquaintance	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
was	O
inform	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
lodg	O
'd	O
Money	O
in	O
the	O
Hands	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
Acquaintance	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
readily	O
delivered	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
That	O
upon	O
this	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
charg	O
'd	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
did	O
own	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
kept	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
for	O
a	O
Month	O
,	O
given	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Hands	O
of	O
her	O
Friend	O
,	O
put	O
some	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
out	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
Cloth	O
one	O
Morning	O
,	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Bar-Room	O
to	O
wash	O
the	O
Hearth	O
.	O
She	O
having	O
nothing	O
more	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
committed	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
the	O
Favour	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Eslick	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
Porringer	O
,	O
and	O
Spoon	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
her	O
Master	O
and	O
Mistress	O
were	O
abroad	O
,	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
afterwards	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
recovered	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
but	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Curtis	I-pers
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
while	O
her	O
Master	O
and	O
Mistress	O
were	O
out	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Money	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Stockings	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
4	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Bagnel	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
her	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
Shoes	O
off	O
from	O
the	O
Shelf	O
,	O
she	O
rose	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
immediately	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
hearing	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
cry	O
out	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
running	O
,	O
he	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
Shoes	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
at	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
stopt	O
;	O
which	O
Shoes	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coat	O
and	O
Breeches	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Rule	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Forket	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Mortar	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Hugh	B-pers
Dart	I-pers
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
observ	O
'd	O
by	O
some	O
Persons	O
passing	O
along	O
to	O
peep	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
and	O
take	O
something	O
off	O
from	O
the	O
Shelf	O
,	O
no	O
Person	O
but	O
a	O
Child	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
they	O
suspecting	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
him	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
with	O
the	O
Mortar	O
,	O
stopt	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Kent	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
150	O
Bricks	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wallis	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Body	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Allhallow	B-place
's	I-place
Lombardstreet	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
,	O
the	O
23th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Brandy	O
;	O
and	O
some	O
Gentlemen	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Pot	O
,	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
leaving	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
carried	O
away	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Vincent	I-pers
;	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Loyd	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
March	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
January	O
.	O
It	O
did	O
appear	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
take	O
the	O
Tankard	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
own	O
,	O
where	O
,	O
upon	O
Search	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
.	O
She	O
pleaded	O
,	O
She	O
only	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
carry	O
Home	O
a	O
Quart	O
of	O
Drink	O
that	O
she	O
then	O
fetch	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
,	O
leaving	O
Friends	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
design	O
to	O
keep	O
it	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
also	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Prosecutor	O
were	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
fetched	O
3	O
Pints	O
of	O
Drink	O
there	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
She	O
having	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
given	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
felonious	O
Intent	O
not	O
being	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Magnus	I-place
the	I-place
Martyr	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hyde	I-pers
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
Second	O
Time	O
for	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Persons	O
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
Ticket-Porter	O
s	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
employ	O
'd	O
to	O
land	O
Tobacco	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Lighter	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
seen	O
several	O
Times	O
to	O
carry	O
away	O
Tobacco	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Lighter	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
went	O
on	O
Shore	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Knees	O
of	O
their	O
Breeches	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipp	O
'd	O
.	O
Morrice	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrew	I-place
Undershaft	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
hired	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
us	O
'd	O
at	O
Times	O
to	O
take	O
Money	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
convert	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
Life	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Faulkner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
taking	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Callaway	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
under	O
Pretence	O
of	O
buying	O
a	O
Turn-over	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Bensted	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Urwin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
Tape	O
,	O
and	O
Thread	O
,	O
value	O
45	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Lewis	B-pers
Sladen	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
a	O
Fire	O
happening	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
more	O
lost	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Judith	B-pers
Weaver	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Chamber-Pot	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
coming	O
up	O
to	O
a	O
full	O
Proof	O
that	O
she	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
of	B-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
taking	O
Money	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Beaumont	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
January	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
about	O
11	O
a-Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
entertain	O
'd	O
some	O
Discourse	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
immediately	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Money	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
back	O
,	O
apprehended	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
charg	O
'd	O
a	O
Watchman	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
some	O
Time	O
,	O
they	O
designing	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Bosom	O
.	O
The	O
Watchman	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
put	O
her	O
Hand	O
in	O
her	O
Bosom	O
,	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
just	O
the	O
same	O
Sum	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
pleaded	O
,	O
It	O
was	O
her	O
own	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
obtain	O
that	O
Credit	O
with	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
they	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Horn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Chaplain	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Coachman	O
having	O
gone	O
out	O
about	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
lock	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
the	O
Coach-house	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
Servant	O
seeing	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
was	O
going	O
in	O
about	O
7	O
a-Clock	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
for	O
the	O
Coach-man	O
,	O
a	O
Man	O
came	O
out	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
Coachman	O
was	O
above	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
That	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
apprehended	O
him	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
bundled	O
up	O
ready	O
to	O
carry	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cedar	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
John	I-place
at	I-place
Hackney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Norman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Hillwell	I-pers
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
January	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Ratcliff	B-place
Highway	I-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
met	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
something	O
;	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
wanted	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
something	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
Breeches	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
him	O
full-but	O
,	O
and	O
stopp	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
felt	O
her	O
Hand	O
about	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
That	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
parted	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Money	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
talking	O
with	O
two	O
Men	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
a	O
Watchman	O
coming	O
by	O
,	O
he	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
Money	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Avery	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Precinct	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Katherine	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hinton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
January	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Lodging	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
They	O
were	O
given	O
her	O
by	O
her	O
Mistress	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
since	O
dead	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Spoon	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
what	O
she	O
always	O
used	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
Cook	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
carried	O
it	O
away	O
by	O
Forgetfulness	O
.	O
She	O
having	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
given	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jees	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
John	I-place
at	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Godsal	I-pers
,	O
the	O
12th	B-place
of	I-place
this	I-place
instant	I-place
January	I-place
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
near	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
She	O
found	O
the	O
Spoon	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
.	O
She	O
having	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
given	O
her	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Ebenezer	B-pers
Bently	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
Mrs.	O
Bentley	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
a	O
Parlour	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
off	O
from	O
a	O
Shelf	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Bentley	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
pretended	O
to	O
want	O
to	O
buy	O
Linnen	O
Cloth	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
deal	O
in	O
;	O
and	O
taxing	O
her	O
with	O
having	O
taken	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Bundle	O
dropp	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Petticoat	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
It	O
was	O
only	O
a	O
Mistake	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
such	O
a	O
Bundle	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
laid	O
down	O
on	O
a	O
Table	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
that	O
Bundle	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
thinking	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
her	O
own	O
.	O
But	O
this	O
not	O
being	O
credited	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Stratford	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Strafford	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
marrying	O
Frances	B-pers
Watkinson	I-pers
,	O
his	O
former	O
Wife	O
,	O
Agnes	B-pers
Laws	I-pers
,	O
being	O
alive	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
wanting	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
second	O
Marriage	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sevan	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Hayes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Mander	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Day-time	O
,	O
no	O
Person	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
being	O
abroad	O
at	O
their	O
Work	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
Daughter	O
gone	O
out	O
to	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
a	O
Hole	O
was	O
broken	O
in	O
the	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
stolen	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
apprehended	O
at	O
the	O
Turnpike	O
,	O
with	O
three	O
Shirts	O
,	O
all	O
upon	O
his	O
Back	O
one	O
over	O
another	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
an	O
old	O
ragged	O
Shirt	O
was	O
Left	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Room	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
He	O
found	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
Road	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
giving	O
Credit	O
to	O
his	O
Plea	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
taking	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Christian	B-pers
Hannibal	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
had	O
been	O
accidentally	O
at	O
Charing-Cross	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
Home	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
Whitechapel	B-place
,	O
and	O
then	O
,	O
Money	O
being	O
sent	O
out	O
to	O
fetch	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Candle	O
falling	O
down	O
and	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
while	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
the	O
lighted	O
again	O
,	O
she	O
sitting	O
next	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
she	O
going	O
away	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
abruptly	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Return	O
of	O
the	O
Candle	O
,	O
though	O
before	O
she	O
had	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
stay	O
there	O
all	O
Night	O
.	O
But	O
their	O
not	O
being	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Guinea	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pocket	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
10th	B-place
of	I-place
December	I-place
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
As	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Red	B-place
Lion	I-place
Street	I-place
,	O
with	O
Mary	B-pers
Mackleen	I-pers
Arm	O
in	O
Arm	O
,	O
she	O
felt	O
a	O
Hand	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
turning	O
her	O
Head	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
That	O
then	O
he	O
stoop	O
'd	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
giving	O
her	O
Pocket	O
a	O
violent	O
Full	O
,	O
pull	O
'd	O
it	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
presently	O
stopp	O
'd	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stoop	O
down	O
between	O
the	O
two	O
Women	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
a	O
great	O
Pull	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
stopp	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
Fact	O
being	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Christina	B-pers
Rhodes	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Rose	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Brass	O
Coach-Tops	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Justice	I-pers
Dormer	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
offering	O
to	O
Sale	O
10	O
or	O
11	O
Brass	O
Coach-Tops	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
sworn	O
to	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Coachman	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
She	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
Woman	O
.	O
There	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
that	O
she	O
stole	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lazenby	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Shoes	O
and	O
a	O
Slipper	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Croucher	I-pers
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Shoes	O
were	O
stolen	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop-Window	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
an	O
Outcry	O
made	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
running	O
away	O
,	O
having	O
a	O
Slipper	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Shoes	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
dropp	O
'd	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
certain	O
Wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Tailor	I-pers
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Eason	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Bromly	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Sacks	O
,	O
and	O
Malt	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Burnham	I-pers
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
having	O
set	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
on	O
Shore	O
from	O
the	O
Barge	O
,	O
which	O
lay	O
in	O
Bow	O
Creek	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
afterwards	O
to	O
drink	O
together	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
Henry	O
Robinson	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
gone	O
about	O
two	O
Hours	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
2	O
Sacks	O
of	O
Malt	O
were	O
missing	O
from	O
due	O
the	O
Barge	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
same	O
Morning	O
Robinson	O
was	O
seen	O
ridding	O
upon	O
a	O
Horse	O
on	O
two	O
Sacks	O
full	O
of	O
some	O
Grain	O
,	O
and	O
Eason	O
leading	O
the	O
Horse	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
Malt	O
said	O
to	O
one	O
Lovel	O
that	O
Morning	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Robinson	O
being	O
satisfactory	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
But	O
Robert	O
Eason	O
they	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lawton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
Russia	O
Cloth	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barkam	I-pers
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Cloth	O
off	O
from	O
a	O
Shelf	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
seen	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Family	O
that	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchin	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
out	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Stopp	O
'd	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
running	O
along	O
Red-Lion-street	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Cloth	O
drop	O
'd	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
s	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Ledget	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
a	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Frances	B-pers
Richmond	I-pers
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Ratcliff	O
Highway	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
standing	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
look	O
'd	O
her	O
full	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
along	O
:	O
He	O
came	O
before	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
her	O
full	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
again	O
,	O
went	O
on	O
before	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
Betts	B-place
's	I-place
Street	I-place
,	O
she	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
as	O
it	O
were	O
a	O
great	O
Weight	O
at	O
her	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Whereupon	O
she	O
turn	O
'd	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
squawl	O
'd	O
out	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
catch	O
'd	O
at	O
her	O
Throat	O
,	O
and	O
Tore	O
off	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
violent	O
Push	O
,	O
that	O
would	O
have	O
thrown	O
her	O
down	O
,	O
had	O
she	O
not	O
fell	O
against	O
a	O
Stall	O
,	O
the	O
Violence	O
of	O
which	O
bruis	O
'd	O
her	O
very	O
much	O
.	O
Other	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
upon	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Out-cry	O
,	O
they	O
pursued	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
apprehended	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Pocket	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Campion	I-pers
,	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Pomfroy	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jarvis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
three	O
Geese	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
stopt	O
by	O
the	O
Watch	O
with	O
the	O
Geese	O
at	O
Islington	O
,	O
they	O
not	O
giving	O
a	O
satisfactory	O
Account	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
only	O
saying	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Pond	O
.	O
They	O
pleaded	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Road	O
.	O
But	O
this	O
not	O
Satisfying	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
they	O
brought	O
them	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
de	I-place
Bow	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
9	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
lodg	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
whereas	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
laid	O
by	O
9	O
Guineas	O
,	O
wrapt	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Paper	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
of	O
them	O
9	O
Counters	O
found	O
,	O
the	O
Guineas	O
being	O
gone	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Guineas	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Skerlet	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Copper	O
Pot	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Mosely	I-pers
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
January	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Lodger	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Darvel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Botham	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
January	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Grey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
the	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Scrafton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Body	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Brace	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
body	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Welsh	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Morrice	I-pers
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Body	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
Katherine	B-pers
Dennis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Coxon	I-pers
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
January	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Sparks	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
6	O
Plates	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Hinder	I-pers
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Body	O
appearing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
an	O
Iron	O
Bar	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Phillip	B-pers
Dollard	I-pers
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Shrimpton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bone	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Stew	O
Pan	O
,	O
Value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ham	I-pers
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Bridget	B-pers
Mortimer	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Table	O
Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Isabella	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
her	O
hired	O
Servant	O
,	O
that	O
having	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
about	O
three	O
Weeks	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
away	O
abruptly	O
,	O
one	O
Sunday	O
,	O
before	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
up	O
Dinner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
missing	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Proof	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Katherine	B-pers
Oosey	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Napkins	O
,	O
a	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Glass	O
Bottles	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Crawford	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
January	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Chairwoman	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Lodging	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
One	O
Napkin	O
was	O
given	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Maid	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
she	O
took	O
home	O
with	O
broken	O
Victuals	O
,	O
the	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Candle	O
to	O
light	O
her	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
intended	O
to	O
return	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
taking	O
them	O
with	O
a	O
feloniously	O
Intent	O
,	O
not	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gan	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
taking	O
a	O
Snuff	O
Box	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
standing	O
at	O
a	O
Door	O
,	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
consented	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
People	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
brought	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Brandy	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
Snuff	O
Box	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Body-near	O
him	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
missed	O
his	O
Snuff	O
Box	O
.	O
The	O
Man	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
mistaken	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Person	O
he	O
drank	O
with	O
,	O
was	O
one	O
Lucy	B-pers
Carnock	I-pers
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
her	O
Company	O
,	O
at	O
another	O
Place	O
,	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
till	O
near	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
near	O
two	O
Hour	O
later	O
than	O
when	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
Snuff	O
Box	O
.	O
Upon	O
a	O
full	O
bearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Welsh	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Riding	O
Hood	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Justin	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
some	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
a	O
Woman	O
came	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
her	O
to	O
a	O
Pawn-Brokers	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Wallis	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
found	O
her	O
Goods	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Wallis	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
pawn	O
'd	O
by	O
another	O
Person	O
in	O
his	O
Name	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Wallis	O
was	O
an	O
ill	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
an	O
ill	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elisabeth	B-pers
Tucker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
a	O
Gown	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Rimes	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
House	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
these	O
Men	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
Room	O
below	O
,	O
they	O
carried	O
them	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Men	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
carried	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Gown	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
apprehended	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
Gown	O
was	O
her	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4s	O
.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Yarwood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Salt	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
handled	O
Knife	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
as	O
an	O
Assistant	O
to	O
the	O
Dustman	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
as	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
his	O
own	O
Confession	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Dust	O
Basket	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Christchurch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
10	O
Pound	O
of	O
Bacon	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Greenwood	I-pers
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
with	O
another	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
half	O
a	O
Firkin	O
of	O
Butter	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
went	O
away	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
after	O
her	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
missing	O
the	O
Bacon	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
Directions	O
where	O
to	O
send	O
the	O
Butter	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Bacon	O
under	O
or	O
near	O
the	O
Seat	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sat	O
,	O
and	O
something	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
slip	O
down	O
from	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
charged	O
with	O
stealing	O
it	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
thought	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
had	O
paid	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Several	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Langsdell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Drugget	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Stable	O
of	O
Owen	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
January	O
.	O
His	O
Confession	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fryer	I-pers
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Stephen	I-place
Colemanstreet	I-place
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
and	O
Breeches	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wishaw	I-pers
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
where	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
left	O
his	O
Clothes	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
carried	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
absconded	O
from	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
.	O
His	O
Confession	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	O
Fryer	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
on	O
each	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Barret	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
Queenhith	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Stable	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Whiting	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Wyers	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sauce	O
Pan	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
,	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mildred	I-place
's	I-place
Poultry	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
taking	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
January	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Nicholson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wiseham	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
near	O
Fleet	B-place
Bridge	I-place
,	O
he	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Hand	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
it	O
there	O
a	O
small	O
Time	O
,	O
asking	O
him	O
what	O
his	O
Hand	O
did	O
there	O
.	O
That	O
indeed	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
of	O
taking	O
out	O
his	O
Money	O
.	O
That	O
having	O
got	O
his	O
Hand	O
at	O
Liberty	O
,	O
he	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
hurt	O
him	O
very	O
much	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
got	O
him	O
secur	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Accomplices	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
Knock	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
sour	O
him	O
.	O
However	O
he	O
got	O
him	O
apprenhended	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
secur	O
'd	O
in	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
oblig	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
off	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Crowd	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Comrades	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
suppos	O
'd	O
,	O
being	O
bent	O
upon	O
doing	O
him	O
a	O
Mischief	O
.	O
That	O
a	O
young	O
Man	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
being	O
taken	O
by	O
them	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
was	O
wretchedly	O
beaten	O
and	O
abus	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
some	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
but	O
having	O
the	O
Misfortune	O
to	O
have	O
no	O
Person	O
there	O
but	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
with	O
whom	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
therefore	O
call	O
'd	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Officers	O
in	O
waiting	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
know	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
noted	O
Pickpocket	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Villain	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
advis	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
consent	O
to	O
go	O
abroad	O
,	O
to	O
prevent	O
the	O
Consequence	O
his	O
ill	O
Practices	O
might	O
bring	O
him	O
:	O
But	O
he	O
obstinately	O
refusing	O
,	O
they	O
impos	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
a	O
Fine	O
of	O
20	O
l.	O
Isaak	B-pers
Yewel	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
Forging	O
,	O
Counterfeiting	O
,	O
and	O
Attempting	O
to	O
utter	O
a	O
Bill	O
of	O
Exchange	O
,	O
drawn	O
by	O
Commadore	O
Philip	B-pers
Cavendish	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
Mess	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Woodword	I-pers
,	O
for	O
130	O
l.	O
payable	O
to	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
a	O
Porter	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
Marine	O
Coffee-house	O
in	O
Birchin	O
Lane	O
,	O
who	O
sent	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Bill	O
to	O
receive	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Messieurs	O
Woodward	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
asking	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
his	O
Name	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Bill	O
,	O
which	O
Name	O
was	O
Thomas	O
Smith	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
him	O
think	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Name	O
was	O
so	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
suspecting	O
the	O
Bill	O
,	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
pay	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Woodward	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Coffee-house	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Woodward	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
having	O
some	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
Note	O
,	O
though	O
Mr.	O
Cavendish	O
's	O
Hand	O
was	O
very	O
nearly	O
imitated	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
Porter	O
to	O
the	O
Marine	O
Coffee-house	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
asking	O
him	O
if	O
his	O
Name	O
was	O
Thomas	O
Smith	O
,	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
Yewel	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
just	O
come	O
from	O
Portsmouth	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
receiv	O
'd	O
that	O
Note	O
of	O
one	O
Thomas	O
Smith	O
,	O
a	O
Clerk	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Yard	O
at	O
Portsmouth	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
leave	O
the	O
Bill	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
sent	O
to	O
enquire	O
of	O
the	O
Reality	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
an	O
Account	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
done	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Cavendish	O
,	O
who	O
acquainted	O
him	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
counterfeit	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
drawn	O
no	O
such	O
Bill	O
on	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Cavendish	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
had	O
drawn	O
no	O
such	O
Bill	O
,	O
nor	O
knew	O
no	O
such	O
Person	O
as	O
Thomas	O
Smith	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
sent	O
to	O
enquire	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
hear	O
of	O
any	O
such	O
Person	O
.	O
That	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Bill	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
his	O
Hand-Writing	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
formerly	O
been	O
his	O
Clerk	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
written	O
Abundance	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
his	O
Hand	O
so	O
perfectly	O
well	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
take	O
,	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
swear	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
the	O
Bill	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
own	O
Writing	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
two	O
Hands	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
insisting	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
Thomas	O
Smith	O
aforesaid	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
could	O
prove	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Ostend	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Court	O
sentenc	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
stand	O
once	O
on	O
the	O
Pillory	O
at	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
to	O
pay	O
a	O
Fine	O
of	O
Twenty	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
suffer	O
Six	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bunworth	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
taking	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
Penny-Post	O
Letters	O
,	O
He	O
being	O
a	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
Penny-Post	O
Office	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Edward	B-pers
Frazier	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
assault	O
Mr.	O
William	B-pers
Wasey	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
a	O
Tweezer	O
Case	O
,	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
about	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
passing	O
along	O
Lincolns-Inn	B-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
he	O
was	O
attached	O
by	O
3	O
Men	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
clapt	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
pretty	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
bid	O
him	O
deliver	O
immediately	O
,	O
threatning	O
if	O
he	O
spoke	O
one	O
Word	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
shoot	O
him	O
through	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
turn	O
'd	O
him	O
aside	O
,	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Wasey	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
acquainted	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
describing	O
the	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
the	O
Persons	O
,	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
capable	O
of	O
knowing	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
replyed	O
,	O
he	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
robbing	O
him	O
under	O
a	O
Lamp	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
better	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
observe	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Wasey	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
give	O
him	O
some	O
Account	O
in	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Days	O
Time	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
heard	O
that	O
the	O
3	O
Persons	O
he	O
described	O
,	O
had	O
furnished	O
themselves	O
with	O
Pistols	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
supposed	O
,	O
for	O
some	O
such	O
Uses	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
Peter	B-pers
Leeve	I-pers
,	O
who	O
came	O
readily	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
promis	O
'd	O
him	O
upon	O
his	O
Word	O
and	O
Honour	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
come	O
and	O
go	O
free	O
;	O
which	O
be	O
always	O
punctually	O
observes	O
with	O
these	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
or	O
otherwise	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
serviceable	O
to	O
the	O
Publick	O
.	O
That	O
Peter	O
Leeve	O
being	O
come	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
now	O
his	O
Time	O
to	O
Chuse	O
whether	O
to	O
secure	O
himself	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
by	O
his	O
Accomplices	O
.	O
That	O
thereupon	O
he	O
promising	O
to	O
send	O
him	O
Word	O
when	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
one	O
or	O
both	O
of	O
his	O
Accomplices	O
,	O
he	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
away	O
;	O
he	O
sent	O
him	O
Word	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Company	O
of	O
Peter	O
Leeve	O
;	O
and	O
offering	O
a	O
Reward	O
of	O
five	O
Guineas	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
Mr.	O
Wasey	O
's	O
Watch	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
him	O
by	O
a	O
Porter	O
.	O
Peter	O
Leeve	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
Edward	O
Frazier	O
,	O
committed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
Allen	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
his	O
Watch	O
and	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Tweezer-Case	O
,	O
were	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Wife	O
's	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
or	O
his	O
knowing	O
Peter	O
Leeve	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
now	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgement	O
as	O
followeth	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
Five	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Stephan	B-pers
Gardiner	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bonner	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hyde	I-pers
,	O
John	O
Allen	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
.	O
Thirty	O
Seven	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Maslam	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
John	O
Bunworth	O
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Faulkner	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Horn	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Cedar	I-pers
,	O
Alice	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sevan	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
,	O
Martha	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Eslick	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Larenby	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
alias	O
Harrison	O
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lewton	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Ladget	I-pers
,	O
William	O
Welsh	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Tucker	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Langsdell	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Skarlet	I-pers
,	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bushell	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Edward	O
Barret	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Wyers	I-pers
,	O
George	O
Fisher	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Tarwood	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
Three	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Coats	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Spicer	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mare	I-pers
.	O
The	O
two	O
last	O
convicted	O
at	O
a	O
former	O
Sessions	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
,	O
Six	O
;	O
Robert	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Campion	I-pers
,	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Pomfrey	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jarvis	I-pers
,	O
Morrice	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Yowel	I-pers
,	O
to	O
stand	O
once	O
on	O
the	O
Pillory	O
at	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
to	O
pay	O
a	O
Fine	O
of	O
Twenty	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
be	O
imprisoned	O
for	O
Six	O
Months	O
.	O
Bartholomew	O
Nicholson	O
,	O
fined	O
Twenty	O
Pounds	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
Just	O
publish	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Seventh	O
Editions	O
(	O
with	O
many	O
Additions	O
and	O
Amendments	O
)	O
of	O
A	O
Rational	O
and	O
Useful	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Venereal	O
Disease	O
,	O
With	O
Observations	O
on	O
the	O
Nature	O
,	O
Symptoms	O
,	O
and	O
Cure	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
ill	O
Consequences	O
that	O
attend	O
it	O
by	O
ill	O
Management	O
;	O
with	O
proper	O
Additions	O
;	O
recommended	O
as	O
a	O
Friendly	O
Instruction	O
to	O
all	O
Persons	O
who	O
do	O
,	O
or	O
may	O
,	O
labour	O
under	O
this	O
Misfortune	O
.	O
Also	O
,	O
a	O
short	O
Inquiry	O
into	O
Old	O
Gleets	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Weaknesses	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Reason	O
why	O
they	O
are	O
so	O
seldom	O
cured	O
:	O
With	O
the	O
Author	O
's	O
Method	O
of	O
Cure	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
are	O
added	O
,	O
Some	O
Hints	O
on	O
the	O
Practical	O
Scheme	O
.	O
The	O
Methods	O
and	O
Medicines	O
therein	O
exposed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
gross	O
Impositions	O
justly	O
detected	O
:	O
With	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
,	O
the	O
Use	O
and	O
Abuse	O
of	O
the	O
Name	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
it	O
cowers	O
Ignorance	O
and	O
a	O
Cheat	O
.	O
By	O
Joseph	B-pers
Cane	I-pers
,	O
M.D	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
G.	O
Strahan	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
W.	O
Means	O
,	O
without	O
Temple-Bar	O
,	O
C.	O
King	O
,	O
in	O
Westminster-Hall	O
,	O
T.	O
Norris	O
on	O
London-Bridge	O
,	O
J.	O
Bakes	O
against	O
Hugton-Garden	O
in	O
Holborn	O
;	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Author	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Golden	O
Ball	O
and	O
Lamp	O
in	O
Bow-Church	O
Yard	O
,	O
Cheapside	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
A	O
Water	O
that	O
perfectly	O
cures	O
the	O
Itch	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
Itching	O
Humour	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
,	O
Without	O
Necessity	O
of	O
Purging	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
dangerous	O
Use	O
of	O
Mercury	O
,	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
only	O
is	O
prepared	O
and	O
sold	O
,	O
by	O
A	O
.	O
Downing	O
,	O
Chymist	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
and	O
Ball	O
,	O
in	O
George	O
Court	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
John	O
's	O
Lane	O
,	O
by	O
Hicks'sHall	O
,	O
near	O
West-Smithfield	O
.	O
Where	O
also	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
the	O
best	O
Spirits	O
of	O
Scurvy-Grass	O
,	O
by	O
Wholesale	O
or	O
Retale	O
,	O
at	O
8	O
d.	O
a	O
Bottle	O
.	O
A	O
most	O
effectual	O
Remedy	O
for	O
the	O
violent	O
Pain	O
in	O
the	O
Teeth	O
,	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
Also	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Remedy	O
for	O
the	O
Teeth	O
,	O
and	O
clearing	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
.	O
A	O
Full	O
and	O
Comlpeat	O
History	O
of	O
the	O
Lives	O
,	O
Robberies	O
,	O
and	O
Murders	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
most	O
notorious	O
Highwaymen	O
that	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
England	O
,	O
Scotland	O
,	O
France	O
and	O
Ireland	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Reign	O
of	O
William	O
the	O
Conqueror	O
,	O
to	O
this	O
present	O
Year	O
1723.	O
begining	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dun	I-pers
,	O
Robin	B-pers
Hood	I-pers
and	O
Little	O
John	O
,	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Falstaff	I-pers
,	O
Capt	O
.	O
Hind	O
,	O
the	O
Golden	O
Farmer	O
,	O
Nevison	O
,	O
Whitney	O
,	O
and	O
above	O
an	O
Hundred	O
more	O
;	O
Also	O
giving	O
a	O
more	O
full	O
Account	O
than	O
any	O
yet	O
published	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Robberies	O
committed	O
by	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Child	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
George	B-pers
Sympson	I-pers
,	O
who	O
were	O
all	O
Three	O
executed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
the	O
Bristol	O
Mail	O
;	O
concluding	O
with	O
the	O
Life	O
and	O
Robberies	O
of	O
the	O
famous	O
Cartouche	O
in	O
France	O
:	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Robberies	O
and	O
remarkable	O
Actions	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Malhoni	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Carrick	I-pers
,	O
lately	O
executed	O
for	O
robbing	O
William	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
in	O
his	O
Chair	O
.	O
The	O
whole	O
being	O
faithfully	O
collected	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
best	O
Histories	O
,	O
Records	O
,	O
Trials	O
,	O
Ordinaries	O
Accounts	O
,	O
and	O
Manuscripts	O
,	O
and	O
written	O
regularly	O
as	O
the	O
Facts	O
were	O
committed	O
.	O
By	O
J.W	O
.	O
The	O
Second	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
bound	O
in	O
Sheep	O
,	O
and	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Calf	O
.	O
Where	O
may	O
he	O
had	O
also	O
,	O
The	O
Life	O
and	O
most	O
Surprizing	O
Adventures	O
of	O
Robinson	B-pers
Crusoe	I-pers
,	O
of	O
York	O
,	O
Mariner	O
.	O
The	O
whole	O
Three	O
Volumes	O
done	O
into	O
One	O
,	O
with	O
Cuts	O
,	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Both	O
printed	O
for	O
M.	O
Hotham	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Black	O
Boy	O
on	O
London-Bridge	O
.	O
Youth	O
's	O
Introduction	O
to	O
Trade	O
and	O
Business	O
:	O
Containing	B-pers
,	O
I	B-pers
.	I-pers
Tables	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
usual	O
Clerk-like	O
Contractions	O
of	O
Words	O
:	O
A	O
Collection	O
of	O
English	O
Words	O
,	O
alike	O
in	O
Sound	O
,	O
but	O
different	O
in	O
Signification	O
;	O
with	O
proper	O
Directions	O
how	O
to	O
address	O
to	O
Persons	O
of	O
elevated	O
Rank	O
,	O
and	O
those	O
in	O
Office	O
.	O
II	O
.	O
Acquittances	O
and	O
Promissory	O
Notes	O
diversify	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
adapted	O
to	O
such	O
Circumstances	O
as	O
occur	O
in	O
real	O
Business	O
.	O
III	O
.	O
Variety	O
of	O
Bills	O
of	O
Parcels	O
,	O
and	O
Bills	O
on	O
Book	O
Debts	O
,	O
to	O
enter	O
the	O
Learner	O
in	O
the	O
Manner	O
and	O
Methods	O
of	O
Commerce	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
ready	O
at	O
Computation	O
.	O
IV	O
.	O
Bills	O
of	O
Exchange	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
necessary	O
for	O
the	O
right	O
Understanding	O
and	O
Management	O
of	O
Remittances	O
;	O
Several	O
Orders	O
for	O
Goods	O
,	O
Letters	O
of	O
Credit	O
,	O
Invoyces	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Merchant-like	O
Examples	O
.	O
V.	O
Authentick	O
Forms	O
of	O
such	O
Law-Precedents	O
as	O
are	O
most	O
frequently	O
to	O
be	O
met	O
with	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Course	O
of	O
Traffick	O
.	O
VI	O
.	O
A	O
Collection	O
of	O
Questions	O
to	O
exemplify	O
the	O
common	O
Rules	O
of	O
Arthmetick	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
reduce	O
them	O
to	O
Practice	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Use	O
of	O
Schools	O
.	O
Done	O
upon	O
the	O
Plan	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
Col.	O
Ayre	B-pers
's	O
Essay	O
.	O
By	O
M.	O
Clare	O
,	O
School	O
Matter	O
in	O
Soho-Square	O
,	O
London	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
Edward	B-pers
Symon	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Pope	O
's	O
Head	O
Alley	O
,	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
.	O
