TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice	O
Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
9th	O
,	O
and	O
10th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Tenth	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
PETER	B-pers
DELME	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Dormer	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Sergeant	O
at	O
Law	O
;	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
JURORS	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
The	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Lukenor	B-pers
Kervel	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Lathwell	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Pickering	I-pers
,	O
Simon	B-pers
Tunk	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wyatt	I-pers
,	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Piggot	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Frankling	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Jefferies	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Maund	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Yeoman	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hull	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Gunny	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Tompkins	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Champion	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
,	O
Arthur	B-pers
Beech	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Combs	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Albert	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Andrew	B-pers
Alexander	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Fryday-street	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
an	O
Amethist	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Belch	I-pers
,	O
Senior	O
and	O
Junior	O
,	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
Shop	O
with	O
a	O
foreign	O
Gentleman	O
to	O
buy	O
an	O
Amethist	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
that	O
was	O
present	O
laid	O
it	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
never	O
by	O
them	O
seen	O
after	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
at	O
it	O
for	O
some	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
never	O
saw	O
it	O
after	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Amethist	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
Hands	O
of	O
the	O
foreign	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
became	O
of	O
it	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
foreign	O
Gentleman	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Holland	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Robins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Buttolph	I-place
's	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Drudging-box	O
and	O
Pepper-box	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
The	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Maccaskery	I-pers
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
to	O
sell	O
a	O
Pot	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
her	O
Pocket	O
or	O
Hole	O
of	O
a	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Other	O
Evidences	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
after	O
the	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
why	O
the	O
did	O
the	O
Fact	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
the	O
Things	O
with	O
any	O
ill	O
Design	O
,	O
but	O
having	O
bought	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
she	O
reckoned	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
over	O
reckoned	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Weight	O
of	O
the	O
Pot	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Things	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
self	O
amends	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
her	O
having	O
taken	O
them	O
with	O
Intent	O
to	O
have	O
stolen	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
having	O
them	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
to	O
look	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
and	O
charg	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
stealing	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cully	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Sland	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolph	I-place
's	I-place
Bishopgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
as	O
a	O
Chair-Woman	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Spoon	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
at	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
offered	O
it	O
to	O
sale	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
stopped	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
She	O
found	O
the	O
Spoon	O
in	O
a	O
Sink	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
cleaning	O
of	O
it	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Spoon	O
being	O
black	O
,	O
she	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Goldsmith	O
's	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
Silver	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Webster	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
4	O
Books	O
,	O
called	O
Marshal	O
's	O
Epigrams	O
,	O
in	O
Quires	O
,	O
three	O
Quire	O
of	O
Paper	O
,	O
and	O
76	O
Pound	O
of	O
Printed	O
Paper	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Redmayne	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Redmayne	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Books	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
confessed	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
Books	O
before	O
Sir	O
George	B-pers
Merttins	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Longwood	I-pers
the	O
25th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
Cow-Lane	B-place
,	O
about	O
Eleven	O
a-Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
stopp	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
Water	O
.	O
and	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
were	O
snatch	O
'd	O
off	O
from	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
running	O
,	O
he	O
pursu	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
throw	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Sheep	O
pens	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
overtook	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
apprehended	O
him	O
.	O
Nehemiah	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Sheep-pens	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
thrown	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Ramsey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Mackdonald	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
6	O
Guineas	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
be	O
going	O
along	O
Fleet	B-place
Street	I-place
about	O
Eleven	O
a-Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
who	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
their	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
refusing	O
to	O
do	O
that	O
,	O
they	O
carried	O
him	O
down	O
into	O
an	O
Alley	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
talking	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
Mackdonald	O
was	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
Ramsey	O
either	O
behind	O
or	O
on	O
one	O
Side	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
perceived	O
the	O
Hand	O
of	O
Ramsey	O
near	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
thereupon	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Money	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
Money	O
but	O
just	O
before	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
charg	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
them	O
secur	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Constable	O
did	O
not	O
search	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Watchman	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Ramsey	O
denied	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
any	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
gave	O
her	O
to	O
lie	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
Hannah	O
Ramsey	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
But	O
found	O
Sarah	O
Mackdonald	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
privately	O
taking	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Man	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Hillenden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
and	O
Robbing	O
Mary	B-pers
Forster	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Ambrose	B-pers
Forster	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Ambrose	O
Forster	O
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
Mary	O
Forster	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
one	O
Edward	B-pers
Roffe	I-pers
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
a	O
poor	O
Man	O
drinking	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
quarrelled	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
beat	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
,	O
that	O
afterwards	O
they	O
wanted	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
Guinea	O
chang	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
Chamber	O
to	O
get	O
Change	O
for	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
told	O
out	O
a	O
Guinea	O
worth	O
of	O
Silver	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
put	O
the	O
rest	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Purse	O
,	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Box	O
again	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
unexpectedly	O
came	O
behind	O
her	O
,	O
threw	O
her	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
her	O
rudely	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
She	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
40	O
s.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
pleaded	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
put	O
upon	O
it	O
by	O
Edward	O
Rosse	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Horn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Pancras	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Edward	B-pers
Abberathot	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
hat	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
walking	O
betwixt	O
Kentish	B-place
Town	I-place
and	O
Hampstead	B-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
walking	O
in	O
another	O
Path	O
,	O
but	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Way	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
passing	O
by	O
,	O
he	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Collar	O
,	O
and	O
tore	O
off	O
his	O
Stock	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
a	O
Struggle	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
threw	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
him	O
under	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
if	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
he	O
would	O
murther	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
his	O
Watch	O
and	O
Money	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
followed	O
him	O
towards	O
Kentish	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
crying	O
out	O
to	O
stop	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
next	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wyman	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
hearing	O
a	O
Person	O
call	O
out	O
to	O
stop	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
laid	O
bold	O
of	O
him	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
running	O
along	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Chester	B-pers
Colson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
printed	O
Linnen	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
broken	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
His	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
where	O
in	O
he	O
confes	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
proposed	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
break	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
consent	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
did	O
break	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
handed	O
out	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
till	O
they	O
called	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
However	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
this	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
pleaded	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Persons	O
before	O
mentioned	O
,	O
who	O
are	O
since	O
absconded	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
But	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Skeaff	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
12	O
Napkins	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Langhorn	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
latter	O
for	O
receiving	O
them	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
Margaret	B-pers
Skeaff	I-pers
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Elizabeth	O
Powel	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Montross	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Hastings	I-pers
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
her	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Felony	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
But	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
Leonard	B-pers
Buck	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
taking	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Crofts	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Tate	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
July	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Cowel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Mug	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Brock	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Keysar	I-pers
the	O
30th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Mug	O
and	O
Spoon	O
had	O
been	O
pawn	O
'd	O
to	O
Elizabeth	O
Keysar	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
stolen	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
at	O
another	O
Pawn	O
Brokers	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
sent	O
it	O
to	O
pawn	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
It	O
was	O
given	O
her	O
to	O
pawn	O
by	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
Her	O
Plea	O
being	O
allowed	O
to	O
be	O
probable	O
,	O
even	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Eyles	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Susannah	B-pers
Craven	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Browning	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
an	O
Acquaintance	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
,	O
being	O
admitted	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
destitute	O
of	O
a	O
Lodging	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
,	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Pugh	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
and	O
4	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Britton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
hired	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
Trunk	O
of	O
Goods	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
from	O
Frying-Pan	O
Alley	O
into	O
Whitechapel	O
,	O
and	O
over	O
against	O
Whitechapel	B-place
Church	I-place
she	O
gave	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
the	O
Drop	O
,	O
turning	O
up	O
Black-Lion	O
Yard	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Pancrass	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Salmon	I-pers
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Chair-Woman	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
missing	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Tompkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Stockings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bee	I-pers
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Bacon	B-pers
Wynn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Iron	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Miles	I-pers
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Breeden	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Gun	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
Plate	O
,	O
and	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
value	O
60	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Susannah	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Wissin	I-pers
depo	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
going	O
to	O
Graves-End	O
in	O
the	O
Boat	O
with	O
Elizabeth	O
Breeden	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
a	O
Watch	O
strike	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
an	O
ordinary	O
Person	O
,	O
he	O
suspected	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
searching	O
her	O
found	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
her	O
Father	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Watch-Maker	O
;	O
but	O
afterwards	O
being	O
strictly	O
examined	O
,	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
stolen	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
Mistress	O
Susannah	O
Collins	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Mary	O
Gun	O
was	O
confederate	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Dormer	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
She	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Chatham	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Confession	O
of	O
Elizabeth	O
Breeden	O
,	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
she	O
plainly	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
Breeden	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Mary	O
Gun	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
Elizabeth	O
Breeden	O
alledg	O
'd	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
not	O
being	O
Evidence	O
in	O
Law	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Susan	B-pers
Staples	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Mosely	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Pindar	I-pers
,	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Fore-street	B-place
,	O
about	O
10	O
or	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
,	O
who	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
make	O
them	O
drink	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
refusing	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
offered	O
to	O
treat	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
did	O
call	O
at	O
a	O
Brandy	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
treated	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Quartern	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
by	O
Way	O
of	O
Retaliation	O
,	O
he	O
offered	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Castle-Tavern	B-place
,	O
and	O
having	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
he	O
laid	O
down	O
a	O
Shilling	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
then	O
pulling	O
out	O
two	O
half	O
Crowns	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
snatch	O
'd	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
thrust	O
them	O
down	O
her	O
Bosom	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
a	O
full	O
Hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Billingsly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Lancelot	B-pers
Baw	I-pers
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
their	O
House	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
New	O
River	O
Water	O
,	O
whereas	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
examine	O
the	O
Pipes	O
,	O
pretending	O
they	O
were	O
out	O
of	O
Order	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
permitted	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
2	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
in	O
a	O
Cooler	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
immediately	O
missed	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Person	O
else	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Vickery	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
this	O
present	O
July	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
employ	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
as	O
a	O
Chair	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
put	O
the	O
Ring	O
into	O
a	O
Mortar	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
having	O
scoured	O
the	O
Brass	O
,	O
the	O
Ring	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
taxing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
Ring	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Lamb	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
divers	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Barton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Persons	O
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
about	O
one	O
a-Clock	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Goods	O
were	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
4	O
a-Clock	O
his	O
Landlady	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
Notice	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
upon	O
suspecting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
at	O
last	O
did	O
own	O
he	O
had	O
let	O
in	O
2	O
Persons	O
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Grace	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
,	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
about	O
2	O
a-Clock	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
opened	O
the	O
Rooms	O
where	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
His	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
wherein	O
he	O
confest	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
what	O
was	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
Anthony	B-pers
Bragget	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
lost	O
12	O
Yards	O
of	O
Drugget	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
push	O
off	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
help	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
Drugget	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Barton	O
should	O
have	O
his	O
Goods	O
again	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
Apprentice	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Landlord	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
pretended	O
he	O
was	O
terrified	O
into	O
his	O
Confession	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Loch	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Lach	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Lake	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Mary	B-pers
Worley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
Second	O
Time	O
,	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Thomas	O
Miller	O
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
her	O
Hand	O
into	O
the	O
Drawer	O
,	O
took	O
out	O
Six	O
Pence	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
saw	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
Indictment	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Second	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Stanford	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
together	O
with	O
George	B-pers
Bickham	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
William	B-pers
Gould	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Mary	B-pers
Fleming	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Headcloths	O
,	O
a	O
Ring	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
and	O
9	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
near	O
Grays	B-place
Inn	I-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
about	O
10	O
or	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
hit	O
her	O
on	O
her	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
B	O
-	O
h	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
glad	O
I	O
have	O
met	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
stopped	O
something	O
in	O
her	O
Mouth	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
her	O
down	O
against	O
something	O
that	O
hurt	O
her	O
Eye	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Sir	O
Hans	B-pers
Sloan	I-pers
,	O
to	O
be	O
cured	O
of	O
the	O
Hurt	O
she	O
had	O
received	O
.	O
Two	O
other	O
Evidences	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
saw	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
that	O
Night	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
did	O
appear	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
very	O
much	O
abus	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
was	O
malicious	O
,	O
on	O
Account	O
of	O
some	O
Proceedings	O
in	O
Law	O
between	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
call	O
'd	O
2	O
Evidences	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
their	O
Company	O
all	O
that	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
till	O
12	O
a-Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
threatned	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
damn	O
her	O
Soul	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
hang	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
upon	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Young	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Goodman	I-pers
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Woolcock	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
going	O
to	O
fetch	O
something	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
fetch	O
something	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
opened	O
a	O
Counter	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Silk	O
and	O
Stuff	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
her	O
Coats	O
,	O
she	O
staid	O
till	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
Notice	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
follow	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
dropp	O
'd	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
near	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
stood	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Canon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Magnus	I-place
the	I-place
Martyr	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
And	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gascoign	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sell	O
3	O
Parcels	O
of	O
Hemp	O
of	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
a	O
Hundred	O
each	O
Parcel	O
to	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Dier	O
's	O
Son	O
,	O
and	O
converted	O
the	O
Money	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
Use	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
now	O
and	O
then	O
a	O
Penny	O
to	O
keep	O
his	O
Secret	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
wherein	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
whole	O
Fact	O
.	O
However	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Susannah	B-pers
Downs	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Hutchinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
's	I-place
Queenhith	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Rings	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Dear	I-pers
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lay	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
which	O
was	O
Sunday	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
missing	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
after	O
his	O
Apprehension	O
confessed	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Rings	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hickinbottom	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mildred	I-place
Poultry	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Fitzgerald	I-pers
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Over	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Alhallows	B-place
Lombard	I-place
Street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
used	O
to	O
be	O
employed	O
as	O
a	O
Chair-woman	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
for	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Things	O
being	O
missing	O
,	O
were	O
found	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
them	O
with	O
a	O
felonious	O
Intent	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Williot	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Ethelburga	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
23	O
tann	O
'd	O
Sheep	O
Skins	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Person	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Carrier	O
that	O
was	O
to	O
carry	O
these	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Inn	O
,	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
rather	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
and	O
Fraud	O
than	O
a	O
Felony	O
,	O
therefore	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Court	O
allowed	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
bring	O
his	O
Action	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
the	O
Sheep-Skins	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
Debt	O
.	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Holms	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Quarts	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Mint	O
Water	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Walton	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Branch	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
.	I-place
Faith	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
this	O
present	O
July	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
attempting	O
to	O
pick	O
Pockets	O
in	O
the	O
Market	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
watch	O
'd	O
,	O
her	O
Hand	O
was	O
caught	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Pocket-Apron	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
could	O
not	O
positively	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
Sum	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Stutton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
,	I-place
Duke	I-place
's	I-place
Place	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
half	O
an	O
Ounce	O
of	O
Human	O
Hair	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
this	O
present	O
July	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Hutchins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dustan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
happening	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Company	O
and	O
Landlord	O
went	O
out	O
all	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Land-lady	O
taking	O
the	O
Tankards	O
,	O
set	O
them	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sitting	O
and	O
seeing	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
her	O
Return	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Tankards	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Back	O
Door	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
being	O
taxed	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
he	O
many	O
Times	O
promised	O
to	O
give	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
but	O
made	O
his	O
Escape	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
did	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ellix	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Ann	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
Iron	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Olive	I-pers
,	O
the	O
29th	O
Day	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
offered	O
them	O
to	O
sale	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
James	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
Outwitch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Body	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
's	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
5	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Merryweather	I-pers
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
pass	O
'd	O
thorough	O
Peter	O
's	O
Alley	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
drink	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
called	O
her	O
vile	O
Bitch	O
,	O
and	O
pushed	O
her	O
from	O
him	O
against	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
through	O
into	O
Grace-Church	B-place
Street	I-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
need	O
not	O
be	O
so	O
coy	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
so	O
constant	O
,	O
and	O
thrusting	O
her	O
Hand	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
he	O
lay	O
'd	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
5	O
s.	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
Grace-Church	O
Street	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Osbourn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Pheasants	O
,	O
Hens	O
,	O
Cocks	O
,	O
and	O
Rabbets	O
,	O
value	O
37	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Sayers	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Fowls	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
were	O
stolen	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Yard	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
bid	O
him	O
meet	O
him	O
at	O
2	O
a-Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
1st	O
or	O
2d	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
certain	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
of	O
him	O
3	O
Pheasants	O
,	O
Fowls	O
,	O
and	O
Rabbets	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
sold	O
them	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
a	O
Disagreement	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Time	O
the	O
Fowls	O
were	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Time	O
of	O
John	O
Ball	O
's	O
selling	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
defrauding	O
by	O
false	O
Pretences	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Haddoc	I-pers
,	O
of	O
148	O
Sword	O
Belts	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
l.	O
and	O
upwards	O
,	O
pretending	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
on	O
the	O
Account	O
of	O
his	O
former	O
Master	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Avon	I-pers
,	O
with	O
whom	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
Dealings	O
,	O
whereas	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Service	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Avon	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
not	O
sent	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
Goods	O
at	O
an	O
Under	O
rate	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
converted	O
the	O
Money	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
Use	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
also	O
owned	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Misdemeanour	O
.	O
Fined	O
5	O
Marks	O
.	O
Arthur	B-pers
Gilmore	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Marrying	O
a	O
second	O
Wife	O
,	O
his	O
first	O
Wife	O
being	O
alive	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Hackney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hamper	O
,	O
and	O
13	O
Geese	O
,	O
value	O
26	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hopewell	I-pers
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
lost	O
the	O
Hamper	O
and	O
Geese	O
,	O
And	O
Mr.	O
Taylor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Hamper	O
and	O
Geese	O
brought	O
into	O
a	O
Yard	O
on	O
Salt	O
Petre	O
Bank	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
bought	O
Six	O
of	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
Lee	B-pers
Hoy	I-pers
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Katherines	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Osbourn	I-pers
stole	O
the	O
Geese	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Barbara	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
2	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
May	I-pers
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
Lodgers	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
visited	O
by	O
some	O
Friends	O
,	O
they	O
making	O
merry	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
Mr.	O
May	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
very	O
merry	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
threw	O
him	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Rings	O
being	O
large	O
,	O
she	O
got	O
them	O
off	O
.	O
He	O
call	O
'd	O
two	O
Evidences	O
,	O
one	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Rings	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
on	O
his	O
Finger	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
.	O
It	O
appeard	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
compounded	O
the	O
Matter	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Husband	O
,	O
having	O
taken	O
a	O
Note	O
of	O
16	O
s.	O
for	O
the	O
Rings	O
,	O
which	O
not	O
being	O
paid	O
,	O
he	O
arrested	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Husband	O
had	O
indicted	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
in	O
the	O
Crown	O
Office	O
for	O
compounding	O
Felony	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
her	O
having	O
the	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
much	O
in	O
Drink	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Shuttle	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Money-Drawer	O
,	O
and	O
30	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
about	O
May	O
was	O
twelve	O
Months	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
who	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
apprehended	O
upon	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Shoebridge	I-pers
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
together	O
walking	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Mother	O
telling	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Drawer	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
himself	O
had	O
23	O
s.	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
for	O
his	O
Share	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Burrel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Westhal	I-pers
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Lodger	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
deliver	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
arrested	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
with	O
a	O
felonious	O
Intent	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Grimes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
who	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Strowd	I-pers
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Francis	B-pers
Emmerson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Picture	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
three	O
Guineas	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Bonny	I-pers
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
Picture	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
with	O
a	O
felonious	O
Intent	O
;	O
but	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Emma	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Linnen	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
to	O
the	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Rock	I-pers
.	O
But	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
also	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Henly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Smock	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Grace	B-pers
Hatton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Hutchings	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Marshal	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
one	O
Morning	O
before	O
the	O
Family	O
was	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Street-Door	O
was	O
lock	O
'd	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
a	O
spring	O
Lock	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
also	O
that	O
he	O
always	O
absconded	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
from	O
Francis	B-pers
Walters	I-pers
,	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
before	O
mentioned	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
clearly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Drake	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Deal	I-pers
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
having	O
forc	O
'd	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
when	O
her	O
Landlady	O
was	O
abroad	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
Countess	B-pers
Dowager	I-pers
of	I-pers
Oxford	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Day	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Stables	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bromfield	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Enfield	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Table	O
Cloth	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Linnen	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Bourn	I-pers
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Linnen	O
was	O
hang	O
'd	O
out	O
to	O
dry	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
both	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
seen	O
committing	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
apprehended	O
soon	O
after	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Hague	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Child	O
's	O
Cap	O
,	O
and	O
Skirt	O
of	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
d.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Deacon	I-pers
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Mother	O
could	O
not	O
hear	O
of	O
it	O
from	O
Wednesday	O
till	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
publishing	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
dropp	O
'd	O
near	O
London	O
Bridge	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Kelly	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
uttering	O
a	O
King	O
Edward	O
6th	O
Shilling	O
gilt	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
broad	O
Piece	O
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
Lucy	B-pers
Young	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
Shop	O
,	O
about	O
10	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
without	O
Hat	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
great	O
Haste	O
,	O
pretending	O
his	O
Lady	O
was	O
in	O
great	O
Haste	O
for	O
the	O
Tea	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Money	O
for	O
a	O
broad	O
Piece	O
,	O
but	O
pretending	O
not	O
to	O
know	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
23	O
s.	O
Piece	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
25	O
s.	O
Piece	O
,	O
that	O
thereupon	O
she	O
weigh	O
'd	O
it	O
against	O
a	O
23	O
s.	O
Piece	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
something	O
heavier	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
his	O
Lady	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
24	O
s.	O
Piece	O
,	O
that	O
then	O
she	O
offered	O
to	O
send	O
her	O
Maid	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
then	O
she	O
might	O
send	O
that	O
23	O
s.	O
Piece	O
of	O
her	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
would	O
convince	O
his	O
Lady	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
not	O
willing	O
to	O
do	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
might	O
give	O
him	O
Change	O
as	O
a	O
23	O
s.	O
Piece	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
his	O
Lady	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
25	O
s.	O
Piece	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
back	O
immediately	O
.	O
That	O
however	O
she	O
sent	O
her	O
Maid	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
had	O
gone	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
certain	O
House	O
he	O
pretended	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
,	O
he	O
bid	O
the	O
Maid	O
go	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Occasion	O
for	O
her	O
going	O
in	O
.	O
Patrick	B-pers
Norton	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
put	O
off	O
such	O
sort	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
South-Sea	O
Shillings	O
and	O
Six	O
Pences	O
gilt	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
used	O
a	O
House	O
on	O
Snow-Hill	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
got	O
that	O
Sort	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
never	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
thither	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
has	O
gone	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
stood	O
at	O
some	O
Distance	O
while	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
Shop	O
to	O
buy	O
something	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
throw	O
down	O
one	O
of	O
those	O
half	O
Guineas	O
or	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
would	O
ask	O
the	O
Price	O
,	O
and	O
object	O
against	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
demand	O
his	O
Money	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
that	O
Means	O
get	O
good	O
Money	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
very	O
well	O
tell	O
how	O
he	O
managed	O
it	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
this	O
Evidence	O
used	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
Shop	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
ask	O
this	O
Evidence	O
for	O
one	O
Piece	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
stay	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
off	O
,	O
waiting	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
And	O
also	O
,	O
that	O
sometimes	O
he	O
would	O
ask	O
him	O
to	O
change	O
Clothes	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
so	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Young	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
give	O
him	O
such	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
verily	O
believed	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
Piece	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
a	O
King	O
Edwards	O
Shilling	O
gilt	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Tonng	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
Tea	O
and	O
Sugar	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
him	O
what	O
Money	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
exchange	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
several	O
Persons	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
capable	O
of	O
giving	O
any	O
Account	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
much	O
to	O
his	O
Service	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
most	O
hearty	O
Friends	O
did	O
own	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
before	O
this	O
Time	O
been	O
reviled	O
for	O
putting	O
off	O
false	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
upon	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
Fin	O
'd	O
20	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
seven	O
Iron	O
Bars	O
of	O
a	O
Grate	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Armstrong	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Nails	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
or	O
Samuel	B-pers
Singleton	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
offered	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
sale	O
,	O
and	O
directed	O
to	O
a	O
Place	O
in	O
the	O
Mint	O
,	O
where	O
another	O
Part	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Hancock	I-pers
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
this	O
present	O
July	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
a	O
Man	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Shop	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
buying	O
Clothes	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Breeches	O
were	O
stolen	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Floyd	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Pancrass	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Veal	I-pers
the	O
21st	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
came	O
about	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
from	O
the	O
White-Swan	B-place
in	O
New-Street	B-place
,	O
and	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
stay	O
'd	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
Tottenham	B-place
Court	I-place
,	O
and	O
stay	O
'd	O
till	O
about	O
Five	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
sleep	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
waked	O
,	O
his	O
Watch	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
that	O
taxing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
Sarah	B-pers
Flute	I-pers
for	O
six	O
Shillings	O
.	O
Sarah	O
Flute	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
her	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
that	O
Morning	O
bring	O
her	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Watch	O
,	O
telling	O
her	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
drink	O
,	O
fearing	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
having	O
both	O
been	O
up	O
all	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
lent	O
her	O
no	O
Money	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
used	O
to	O
keep	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Company	O
,	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
her	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
frequently	O
coming	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
her	O
be	O
quiet	O
.	O
Upon	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Susan	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Cumpton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Griffith	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Gallon	O
Pot	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Guyneer	I-pers
the	O
26th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Sands	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Bellas	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Dun	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Wilks	I-pers
,	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
35	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Barren	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Club	O
Box	O
,	O
that	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
a	O
Club	O
,	O
kept	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Richard	O
Barron	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
Indictment	O
not	O
being	O
righty	O
laid	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
acquitted	O
,	O
but	O
will	O
be	O
again	O
indicted	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Lutterel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Robert	B-pers
Southwell	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
drawn	O
Sword	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
Part	O
of	O
his	O
Body	O
between	O
the	O
long	O
Ribs	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Breadth	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
six	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
immediately	O
dy	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
for	O
being	O
present	O
,	O
aiding	O
and	O
abetting	O
,	O
comforting	O
and	O
assisting	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Murther	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
also	O
both	O
indicted	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
Servant	O
at	O
the	O
Busy	B-place
Body	I-place
Tavern	I-place
,	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
Mistress	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
Voice	O
of	O
a	O
Woman	O
crying	O
our	O
Help	O
,	O
Help	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
thereupon	O
ran	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Ann	O
Butler	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Stair	O
Head	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
with	O
their	O
Swords	O
drawn	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Posture	O
of	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
interposed	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
get	O
hold	O
of	O
both	O
their	O
Swords	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
gotten	O
them	O
both	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
Hands	O
,	O
ran	O
down	O
Stairs	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
for	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sunderland	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
Cellar	O
Man	O
at	O
the	O
Busy	O
Body	O
Tavern	O
,	O
was	O
standing	O
near	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
a	O
Woman	O
's	O
Voice	O
crying	O
out	O
violently	O
,	O
Murther	O
,	O
Murther	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
ran	O
up	O
after	O
Sutton	O
,	O
but	O
Sutton	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
their	O
Swords	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
drawn	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
For	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
lead	O
me	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
stuck	O
in	O
the	O
Back	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
lead	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
could	O
not	O
speak	O
,	O
but	O
foamed	O
at	O
the	O
Mouth	O
.	O
Kenelm	B-pers
Buckworth	I-pers
said	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Busy	O
Body	O
Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
an	O
Out-cry	O
of	O
Murther	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
up	O
Stairs	O
and	O
met	O
the	O
Deceased	O
at	O
the	O
Stair	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
leading	O
him	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
he	O
mentioned	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
saying	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
stabb	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Back	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
faint	O
,	O
and	O
faltered	O
in	O
his	O
Speech	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
led	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
behind	O
the	O
Bar	O
.	O
He	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Butler	O
was	O
several	O
Yards	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Deceased	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hardesty	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
waited	O
at	O
the	O
said	O
Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
an	O
Opera	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
10	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
the	O
Deceased	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
show	O
a	O
Room	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
called	O
for	O
Arack	O
Punch	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
not	O
having	O
Arack	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
Punch	O
made	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Rum	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
Crust	O
of	O
Bread	O
;	O
that	O
some	O
Time	O
after	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Reckoning	O
;	O
which	O
of	O
them	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
other	O
reply	O
,	O
Why	O
should	O
he	O
do	O
that	O
?	O
when	O
the	O
Bowl	O
was	O
not	O
half	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
short	O
Time	O
after	O
,	O
the	O
Woman	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
Murther	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
enter	O
in	O
,	O
thinking	O
,	O
probably	O
,	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
might	O
be	O
fagging	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
immediately	O
the	O
Porter	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
their	O
Swords	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
going	O
in	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Ann	O
Butler	O
,	O
said	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Lutterel	O
,	O
My	O
dear	O
Harry	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
you	O
are	O
wounded	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
,	O
this	O
Evidence	O
,	O
to	O
search	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
but	O
found	O
only	O
a	O
slight	O
Scratch	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
believed	O
might	O
be	O
given	O
by	O
the	O
taking	O
away	O
of	O
his	O
Sword	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Flavers	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
at	O
the	O
said	O
Tavern	O
,	O
heard	O
a	O
Woman	O
cry	O
out	O
above	O
Stairs	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Rape	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Gentlewoman	O
at	O
the	O
Tavern	O
sent	O
one	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
brought	O
down	O
their	O
Swords	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
assisted	O
Mr.	O
Southwell	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Woman	O
held	O
him	O
while	O
Lutterel	O
run	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Back	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Southwell	O
said	O
these	O
Words	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Stair	O
Foot	O
;	O
and	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
afterwards	O
told	O
these	O
Words	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Southwell	O
to	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Pack	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Didier	I-pers
the	O
Surgeon	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
called	O
for	O
to	O
dress	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
him	O
held	O
up	O
by	O
two	O
Men	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Harts-Horn	O
held	O
at	O
his	O
Nose	O
;	O
that	O
having	O
found	O
the	O
Wound	O
,	O
he	O
probed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
went	O
upwards	O
and	O
downwards	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
Interstices	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Muscles	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
6th	O
and	O
7th	O
of	O
the	O
true	O
Ribs	O
,	O
called	O
the	O
Long	O
Ribs	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
spoke	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
calling	O
upon	O
him	O
very	O
loud	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Deceased	O
made	O
him	O
no	O
Answer	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
dress	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Colthart	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
did	O
not	O
live	O
above	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
Minutes	O
after	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
afterwards	O
opened	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
went	O
through	O
the	O
lower	O
Edge	O
of	O
the	O
left	O
Lung	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
;	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Position	O
of	O
the	O
Wound	O
his	O
Arm	O
was	O
up	O
when	O
he	O
receiv	O
'd	O
it	O
:	O
That	O
if	O
he	O
were	O
a	O
left	O
Handed	O
Man	O
,	O
he	O
believes	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
upon	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
might	O
easily	O
receive	O
the	O
Wound	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
believed	O
his	O
Hand	O
was	O
extended	O
when	O
he	O
received	O
the	O
Wound	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Halley	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
drinking	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
Room	O
to	O
where	O
the	O
Deceased	O
and	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
heard	O
no	O
Disturbance	O
or	O
Parrying	O
of	O
Swords	O
,	O
although	O
,	O
he	O
thinks	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
only	O
a	O
thin	O
Partition	O
between	O
them	O
.	O
Robert	O
Sutton	O
being	O
called	O
again	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Stair	O
Head	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
hear	O
the	O
Clashing	O
of	O
Swords	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
enter	O
'd	O
the	O
Room	O
.	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Swords	O
touch	O
each	O
other	O
.	O
That	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Stair	O
Head	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Butler	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
of	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
their	O
Swords	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
following	O
him	O
,	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
inside	O
of	O
the	O
Table	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Malice	O
against	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
together	O
most	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Marybone	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
return	O
'd	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Hay	O
Market	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Ann	O
Butler	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Southwel	O
would	O
have	O
have	O
had	O
him	O
gone	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
engage	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
refusing	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
forced	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
being	O
there	O
at	O
the	O
Tavern	O
,	O
a	O
drinking	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
talking	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Butler	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
the	O
Deceased	O
took	O
Exceptions	O
,	O
and	O
grew	O
very	O
Quarrelsome	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
meant	O
by	O
engrossing	O
her	O
all	O
to	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
her	O
Gloves	O
and	O
Fan	O
,	O
and	O
oblig	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
sit	O
next	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
she	O
should	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
lend	O
him	O
a	O
Guinea	O
.	O
That	O
thereupon	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
hard	O
he	O
should	O
force	O
a	O
Woman	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
whether	O
she	O
would	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
his	O
Rage	O
increased	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
bit	O
him	O
a	O
Slap	O
on	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
advanced	O
towards	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
oblig	O
'd	O
to	O
take	O
to	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
almost	O
fallen	O
down	O
in	O
getting	O
himself	O
ready	O
to	O
receive	O
his	O
Attack	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
received	O
a	O
Wound	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
in	O
the	O
Encounter	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Persons	O
of	O
Reputation	O
and	O
Honour	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
the	O
Deceased	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
quarrelsome	O
Person	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
they	O
gave	O
Instances	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
himself	O
was	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
quiet	O
and	O
peaceable	O
Disposition	O
and	O
civil	O
Behaviour	O
.	O
Ann	O
Butler	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
in	O
the	O
Hay	O
Market	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
clapping	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
swearing	O
that	O
she	O
should	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
excuse	O
her	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
pay	O
a	O
Visit	O
to	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
,	O
and	O
drink	O
a	O
Dish	O
of	O
Tea	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
But	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
Outragious	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
Mob	O
her	O
:	O
That	O
she	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
rather	O
than	O
her	O
self	O
and	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
exposed	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
drink	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
and	O
did	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Busy	O
Body	O
Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
there	O
drinking	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Lutterel	O
being	O
talking	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Southwel	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
quere	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
Fellow	O
to	O
engross	O
the	O
Woman	O
all	O
to	O
himself	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
Satisfaction	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Lutterel	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
Another	O
Time	O
would	O
be	O
better	O
;	O
the	O
Deceased	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
No	O
Time	O
like	O
the	O
present	O
,	O
and	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Lutterel	O
had	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
down	O
,	O
falling	O
backwards	O
before	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
his	O
Sword	O
drawn	O
,	O
and	O
himself	O
in	O
a	O
Posture	O
to	O
defend	O
himself	O
,	O
that	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
pacify	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
immediately	O
ran	O
to	O
the	O
Stair	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
out	O
violently	O
for	O
Help	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Servant	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
their	O
Swords	O
,	O
as	O
had	O
been	O
before	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
After	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
Henry	O
Lutterel	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
upon	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evedince	O
against	O
Ann	O
Butler	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Merry	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Reynolds	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Statute	O
made	O
in	O
the	O
12th	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
Queen	O
,	O
against	O
vending	O
and	O
selling	O
Dice	O
with	O
false	O
and	O
counterfeit	O
Stamps	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Garland	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
sell	O
her	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Dice	O
,	O
demanding	O
4	O
s.	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
telling	O
her	O
he	O
had	O
newly	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
White	O
Chapel	O
Prison	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Dice	O
being	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Rolloss	O
the	O
Engraver	O
to	O
the	O
Stamp	O
Office	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Stamps	O
these	O
Dice	O
were	O
stamp	O
'd	O
with	O
,	O
were	O
not	O
the	O
true	O
Stamps	O
,	O
made	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
the	O
only	O
Person	O
that	O
was	O
appointed	O
to	O
make	O
them	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Walpole	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
a	O
Man	O
bought	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
sell	O
her	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Dice	O
,	O
for	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
telling	O
her	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
Paper	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
Chancery	O
Lane	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
also	O
false	O
Dice	O
,	O
and	O
stamp	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
same	O
Stamp	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Saunders	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
having	O
notice	O
of	O
there	O
Dice	O
being	O
offered	O
to	O
sale	O
,	O
went	O
and	O
secured	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
brought	O
them	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
should	O
satisfy	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
who	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
from	O
one	O
that	O
stood	O
over	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
carry	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
catch	O
him	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
apprehend	O
him	O
afterwards	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Skeats	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
him	O
from	O
his	O
Work	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
Dice	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
allowing	O
him	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Pair	O
for	O
selling	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
such	O
a	O
Shop	O
,	O
at	O
St.	O
Dunstans	O
,	O
and	O
directed	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
any	O
Questions	O
were	O
ask	O
'd	O
of	O
him	O
whence	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
say	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
the	O
Groom	O
Porter	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Poultry	O
Compter	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Walraven	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
forging	O
and	O
counterfeiting	O
Stamps	O
,	O
and	O
stamping	O
Dice	O
,	O
with	O
these	O
false	O
Stamps	O
,	O
and	O
uttering	O
and	O
vending	O
the	O
Dice	O
stamped	O
with	O
these	O
counterfeit	O
Stamps	O
,	O
contrary	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Statute	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Love	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
apprehended	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Rolloss	O
,	O
who	O
among	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Tools	O
(	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Watch	O
Maker	O
)	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
a	O
Parcel	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
made	O
them	O
to	O
stamp	O
Buckles	O
and	O
Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
among	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
old	O
Tools	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Rolloss	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Purpose	O
,	O
and	O
produced	O
the	O
Tools	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
verily	O
believed	O
were	O
the	O
same	O
Stamps	O
where	O
with	O
those	O
counterfeit	O
Dice	O
,	O
that	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
received	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
were	O
Stamped	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
oftentimes	O
seen	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stamp	O
Dice	O
with	O
such	O
Sorts	O
of	O
Stamps	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Facts	O
of	O
counterfeiting	O
,	O
stamping	O
or	O
selling	O
the	O
said	O
Dice	O
with	O
false	O
Stamps	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
having	O
the	O
Tools	O
,	O
he	O
pretended	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
them	O
among	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
old	O
Tools	O
,	O
and	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Ivory	O
,	O
six	O
Years	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
Dice	O
among	O
the	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Ivory	O
;	O
But	O
having	O
no	O
Proof	O
of	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
seen	O
to	O
stamp	O
Dice	O
with	O
these	O
counterfeit	O
Stamps	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
made	O
those	O
Stamps	O
to	O
stamp	O
Buckles	O
and	O
Spoons	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
Purpose	O
they	O
were	O
of	O
no	O
Use	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
other	O
Use	O
but	O
stamping	O
of	O
Dice	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
forging	O
and	O
counterfeiting	O
the	O
Stamps	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
stamping	O
Dice	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
selling	O
and	O
vending	O
them	O
Death	O
.	O
His	O
Wife	O
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Walraven	I-pers
,	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
for	O
stamping	O
Dice	O
,	O
with	O
these	O
counterfeit	O
Stamps	O
;	O
but	O
considering	O
that	O
it	O
might	O
:	O
be	O
done	O
in	O
Subjection	O
to	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
they	O
thought	O
not	O
sit	O
to	O
go	O
through	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
whereupon	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ursula	B-pers
Gardener	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
wilful	O
and	O
corrupt	O
Perjury	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Prerogative	O
Court	O
,	O
concerning	O
a	O
Will	O
;	O
But	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Harman	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Brian	I-place
's	I-place
Barnet	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Nicol	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
High-Way	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
17	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
,	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Mr	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Reed	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High-Way	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
a	O
Moidore	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
broad	O
Piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
aforementioned	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Nicol	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Chair	O
,	O
two	O
Men	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
beyond	O
Muzzle	B-place
Hill	I-place
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
stop	O
,	O
held	O
Pistols	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
gave	O
them	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
17	O
s.	O
that	O
then	O
they	O
bid	O
him	O
give	O
them	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
told	O
them	O
he	O
had	O
none	O
;	O
then	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
bid	O
him	O
give	O
him	O
his	O
Pocket	O
Book	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
none	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
bid	O
him	O
pull	O
out	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
taking	O
out	O
some	O
Papers	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
were	O
of	O
no	O
value	O
to	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
desiring	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
them	O
alone	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
them	O
.	O
And	O
having	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Reed	O
,	O
they	O
rode	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
him	O
to	O
Prosecute	O
his	O
Journey	O
;	O
that	O
meeting	O
with	O
Captains	O
Parsons	O
.	O
they	O
acquainted	O
him	O
with	O
what	O
had	O
befallen	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
described	O
the	O
Men	O
and	O
Horses	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
rode	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
apprehended	O
at	O
Hackney	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
their	O
Faces	O
,	O
because	O
they	O
had	O
Masks	O
on	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Papers	O
that	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
from	O
Davis	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
were	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
swore	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
afterwards	O
saw	O
the	O
Horses	O
on	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
Horses	O
that	O
those	O
that	O
robbed	O
him	O
,	O
rid	O
on	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Reed	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Cony	O
Hatch	O
;	O
he	O
also	O
was	O
met	O
by	O
two	O
Men	O
on	O
Horse-back	O
,	O
who	O
drew	O
their	O
Pistols	O
,	O
told	O
him	O
they	O
wanted	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
them	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
a	O
Moidore	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
broad	O
Piece	O
:	O
That	O
they	O
then	O
rode	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
pursued	O
by	O
Captain	O
Parsons	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Nicols	O
Description	O
of	O
their	O
Persons	O
,	O
Clothes	O
and	O
Horses	O
,	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
their	O
Faces	O
,	O
they	O
being	O
mask	O
'd	O
.	O
Captain	O
Parsons	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
meeting	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
on	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
by	O
two	O
Men	O
on	O
Bay	O
Horses	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
being	O
a	O
little	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
wearing	O
a	O
Rug	O
Coat	O
:	O
He	O
pursu	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
by	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
desired	O
another	O
to	O
accompany	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
riding	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
heard	O
of	O
them	O
from	O
Place	O
to	O
Place	O
,	O
as	O
at	O
Hornsey	O
,	O
Edmonton	O
,	O
Stamford	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
at	O
last	O
pursued	O
them	O
to	O
Hackney	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
just	O
been	O
drinking	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Meremaid	O
Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
mounted	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
just	O
gone	O
,	O
but	O
were	O
overtaken	O
,	O
brought	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
apprehended	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Newson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Captain	O
Parsons	O
calling	O
at	O
the	O
Green	O
Man	O
,	O
at	O
Muzzle	O
Hill	O
,	O
and	O
desiring	O
Assistance	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
a	O
Horse	O
,	O
rode	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
overtook	O
him	O
about	O
Hornsey-Church	O
,	O
they	O
pursued	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
hearing	O
of	O
them	O
from	O
Place	O
to	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
Turnpikes	O
,	O
till	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
Hackney	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
first	O
got	O
Intelligence	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Green	O
Lane	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Turnpike	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
informed	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
haste	O
,	O
threw	O
the	O
Man	O
a	O
Shilling	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
Way	O
to	O
Epping	O
:	O
That	O
they	O
pursued	O
them	O
to	O
South-gate	O
,	O
to	O
Bore's-Farm	O
,	O
and	O
till	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
Edmonton	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
got	O
Notice	O
of	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
Turnpike	O
at	O
Stanford	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
pursued	O
them	O
to	O
and	O
fro	O
for	O
a	O
Journey	O
of	O
near	O
20	O
Miles	O
,	O
till	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
Hackney	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
heard	O
at	O
the	O
Meremaid	O
Tavern	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
,	O
changed	O
their	O
Coats	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
just	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
Man	O
that	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
that	O
had	O
led	O
their	O
Horses	O
,	O
he	O
lent	O
him	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
taking	O
a	O
Broom-stick	O
rode	O
after	O
,	O
overtook	O
,	O
and	O
stopped	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
afterwards	O
apprehended	O
,	O
he	O
catching	O
hold	O
of	O
Harman	O
's	O
Bridle	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
Davis	O
was	O
riding	O
away	O
,	O
his	O
Horse	O
threw	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
also	O
apprehended	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Billington	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
at	O
work	O
at	O
Hackney	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
Evidences	O
coming	O
with	O
a	O
Hue	O
and	O
Cry	O
,	O
he	O
mounted	O
one	O
of	O
their	O
Horses	O
,	O
rode	O
after	O
them	O
with	O
a	O
Stick	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
;	O
and	O
coming	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
stopped	O
them	O
,	O
threatning	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
they	O
offered	O
to	O
put	O
their	O
Hands	O
to	O
their	O
Pockets	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
knock	O
them	O
down	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
others	O
Evidences	O
that	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
at	O
searching	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
a	O
Mask	O
,	O
and	O
Pair	O
of	O
Pistols	O
in	O
Harman	O
's	O
Pocket	O
,	O
that	O
another	O
Mask	O
was	O
found	O
thrown	O
in	O
the	O
Chimney	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
where	O
Davis	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Pistols	O
hid	O
behind	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
changed	O
their	O
Coats	O
at	O
the	O
Meremaid	O
Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Nichols	O
's	O
Papers	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
Davis	O
's	O
Pocket	O
at	O
Justice	O
Holworthy	O
's	O
;	O
also	O
a	O
Purse	O
of	O
Money	O
was	O
found	O
on	O
them	O
that	O
had	O
such	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
had	O
lost	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
stiffly	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
Harman	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
with	O
the	O
Mask	O
that	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
a	O
Masquerade	O
;	O
but	O
gave	O
no	O
Account	O
where	O
was	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
his	O
Masquerading	O
Equipage	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cotterel	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
suborning	O
John	B-pers
Long	I-pers
,	O
to	O
make	O
Affidavit	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Pilot	O
,	O
had	O
,	O
piloted	O
the	O
Ship	O
Williams	O
Gully	O
safely	O
into	O
the	O
Downs	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
her	O
there	O
in	O
good	O
Condition	O
,	O
prosecuting	O
her	O
Voyage	O
to	O
Cales	O
,	O
whereas	O
the	O
said	O
William	B-pers
Long	I-pers
had	O
never	O
piloted	O
any	O
such	O
Ship	O
as	O
the	O
William	O
Gally	O
thither	O
;	O
and	O
also	O
for	O
suborning	O
one	O
Lee	O
,	O
alias	O
Pye	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
Affidavit	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Mariner	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Ship	O
William	O
Gally	O
,	O
bound	O
for	O
Cales	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
lost	O
near	O
the	O
Canaries	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
Men	O
but	O
himself	O
and	O
another	O
that	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Ship	O
drowned	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
Mariner	O
in	O
any	O
such	O
Ship	O
.	O
The	O
Council	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
having	O
opened	O
the	O
Cause	O
,	O
setting	O
forth	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pretending	O
to	O
be	O
sole	O
Owner	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Ship	O
,	O
called	O
the	O
William	O
Gally	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
one	O
Partridge	O
was	O
Master	O
,	O
had	O
upon	O
the	O
Affidavit	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
Long	O
had	O
made	O
,	O
of	O
his	O
having	O
piloted	O
the	O
Ship	O
William	O
Gally	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Downs	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
her	O
in	O
good	O
Case	O
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
prosecuting	O
her	O
Voyage	O
to	O
Cases	O
,	O
gotten	O
an	O
Assurance	O
made	O
by	O
several	O
Persons	O
for	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
650	O
l.	O
did	O
afterwards	O
upon	O
the	O
Affidavit	O
he	O
procured	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Lee	O
,	O
alias	O
Pye	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Ship	O
William	O
Gally	O
was	O
lost	O
near	O
the	O
Canaries	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
obtain	O
the	O
Money	O
so	O
insured	O
,	O
make	O
Affidavit	O
before	O
Sir	O
Francis	B-pers
Forbes	I-pers
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
sole	O
Owner	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Ship	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
had	O
cost	O
him	O
in	O
Ship	O
,	O
Apparel	O
,	O
sitting	O
out	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
to	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
600	O
l.	O
and	O
upwards	O
.	O
They	O
prov	O
'd	O
all	O
their	O
Changes	O
by	O
the	O
following	O
Evidences	O
.	O
The	O
Affidavits	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
Policy	O
of	O
Insurance	O
prov	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Persons	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
Insurance	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Subornation	O
proved	O
by	O
the	O
Persons	O
suborned	O
.	O
William	O
Long	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
Company	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
one	O
Blake	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
ply	O
'd	O
with	O
Liquor	O
,	O
an	O
Affidavit	O
was	O
drawn	O
up	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
make	O
and	O
sign	O
to	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Sollicitations	O
and	O
Promises	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
to	O
this	O
Purpose	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
pilot	O
the	O
Ship	O
William	O
Gally	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
one	O
Partridge	O
was	O
Master	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Downs	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
Pilot	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
ever	O
carry	O
any	O
such	O
Ship	O
to	O
the	O
Downs	O
,	O
nor	O
ever	O
knew	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
any	O
such	O
Ship	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
afterwards	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
considered	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
not	O
willing	O
to	O
stand	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Affidavit	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
threatned	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
pillory	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
promisory	O
Note	O
for	O
10	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
to	O
be	O
paid	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
received	O
his	O
Insurance	O
.	O
Lee	O
,	O
alias	O
Pye	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Woman	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
be	O
Bail	O
for	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
Prison	O
,	O
that	O
by	O
that	O
means	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
into	O
the	O
Company	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
ply	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
Liquor	O
,	O
kept	O
him	O
out	O
two	O
Days	O
and	O
Nights	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Guinea	O
to	O
make	O
an	O
Affidavit	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Mariner	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Ship	O
William	O
Gally	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
one	O
Partridge	O
was	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
lost	O
near	O
the	O
Canaries	O
;	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
never	O
on	O
board	O
any	O
such	O
Ship	O
as	O
a	O
Mariner	O
,	O
nor	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
her	O
being	O
lost	O
.	O
That	O
afterwards	O
being	O
concerned	O
in	O
his	O
Mind	O
for	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
go	O
back	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
lose	O
500	O
l.	O
and	O
threatned	O
to	O
put	O
the	O
Law	O
in	O
Execution	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
several	O
Affidavits	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Matter	O
so	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
guilty	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
fined	O
him	O
50	O
l.	O
and	O
sentenc	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
stand	O
on	O
the	O
Pillory	O
once	O
at	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
.	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgement	O
as	O
followeth	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
Seven	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Ramsey	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Breeden	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Merry	I-pers
alias	O
Reynolds	O
,	O
Anthony	B-pers
Walraven	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Harman	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Horn	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
,	O
Thirty	O
Nine	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Webster	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Mackdonald	I-pers
,	O
Chester	B-pers
Colson	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Montross	I-pers
,	O
Leonard	B-pers
Burk	I-pers
,	O
Ralph	B-pers
Crofts	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Pugh	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Tompkins	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Vickery	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Hutchinson	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Branch	I-pers
,	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Burrel	I-pers
,	O
Hannah	B-pers
Henley	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Drake	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bromfield	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Griffith	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Man	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Eyles	I-pers
,	O
Bacon	B-pers
Wynne	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Lack	I-pers
,	O
Anthony	B-pers
Lamb	I-pers
,	O
Michael	B-pers
Canon	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hickingbottom	I-pers
.	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Holms	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Ellix	I-pers
,	O
Michael	B-pers
Shuttle	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Grimes	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
alias	O
Emmerson	O
,	O
Martha	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
Susannah	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Hutchins	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
Four	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Lutterel	I-pers
,	O
Arthur	B-pers
Gilmore	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Strutton	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
a	O
former	O
Convict	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
,	O
One	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Skeaf	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Cotterel	I-pers
Fined	O
50	O
l.	O
to	O
stand	O
on	O
the	O
Pillory	O
once	O
at	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
Fined	O
5	O
Marks	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Kelly	I-pers
Fined	O
20	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
suffer	O
3	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Ramsey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Breeden	I-pers
,	O
pleaded	O
their	O
Bellies	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
being	O
impannelled	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
with	O
Quick	O
Child	O
.	O
