TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
'S	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Fail-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
7th	O
,	O
8th	O
,	O
9th	O
,	O
and	O
10th	O
Days	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Eleventh	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
GEORGE	B-pers
MERTTINS	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Tracy	O
,	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
Sergeant	O
at	O
Law	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
JURORS	O
Were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
The	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Emanuel	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
Nicolas	B-pers
Took	I-pers
,	O
Gabriel	B-pers
Sleath	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Petly	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Pickard	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Coombs	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bissen	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Bains	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hulm	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Gibbs	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
,	O
The	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Whitehurst	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wooton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Tyce	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Oaks	B-pers
Bickford	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Goreham	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
follows	O
,	O
viz	O
Ruth	B-pers
Springthorp	I-pers
of	O
Bishopsgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
smock	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
Yards	O
of	O
Callico	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Deborah	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Cassel	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
Henry	O
cassel	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
Night	O
in	O
which	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
leave	O
her	O
Service	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
just	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
(	O
Transp	O
.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Cornhill	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
three	O
Pair	O
of	O
Curtains	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
40	O
s.	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoos	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
Val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
How	O
's	O
Works	O
val	O
16	O
s.	O
seven	O
Quire	O
of	O
Paper	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
;	O
Eight	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Stockings	O
val	O
.	O
40s	O
and	O
three	O
Pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stocking	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
J.	O
Cook	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
:	O
The	O
prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
Joyner	O
,	O
Servant	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Barriet	I-pers
,	O
for	O
whom	O
he	O
worked	O
several	O
weeks	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
suspect	O
how	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
till	O
one	O
day	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
his	O
Pocket-Book	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
were	O
Memorandums	O
of	O
several	O
Things	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Manner	O
how	O
they	O
were	O
disposed	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
caused	O
,	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
apprehended	O
:	O
He	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
fact	O
and	O
that	O
Lewis	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
was	O
his	O
Confederate	O
and	O
went	O
Halves	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
Goods	O
at	O
the	O
Places	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket-Book	O
.	O
Wm	B-pers
Barret	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
served	O
him	O
for	O
seven	O
or	O
Eight	O
Years	O
past	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
which	O
Time	O
he	O
bore	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
val	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Joanna	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
of	O
Alhallows	B-place
Barkin	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Sheets	O
val	O
,	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
Smock	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
one	O
lb	O
of	O
Sugar	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Moses	B-pers
Vigevina	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
left	O
the	O
Goods	O
with	O
an	O
Acquaintance	O
,	O
who	O
made	O
a	O
Discovery	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Long	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
of	O
Queenhithe	B-place
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
Long	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sack	O
of	O
Malt	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Woodcock	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
and	O
Howard	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stoln	O
.	O
Howard	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Long	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Webster	I-pers
of	O
Aldgate	B-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
Henry	B-pers
Thyburn	I-pers
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
off	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Guilty	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bagford	I-pers
of	O
Silver-street	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
Two-Foot	O
Rule	O
val	O
.	O
12d	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Roan	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
March	O
Last	O
.	O
Guilty	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Halfpenny	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Poultry	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bedell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hanson	I-pers
of	O
S.	B-place
Katharine	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Peters	I-pers
,	O
her	O
Brother-in-Law	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
near	O
the	O
Right	O
Pap	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Length	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
Depth	O
of	O
three	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
Matthias	B-pers
Hanson	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
:	O
My	O
Wife	O
Martha	O
having	O
lately	O
miscarried	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
laying	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
by	O
her	O
between	O
and	O
8	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
,	O
when	O
her	O
Brother	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
fitting	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
)	O
called	O
me	O
to	O
supper	O
.	O
I	O
awaked	O
and	O
got	O
off	O
the	O
Bed	O
and	O
saw	O
my	O
sister	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
who	O
was	O
very	O
drunk	O
,	O
walking	O
about	O
the	O
Room	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
.	O
If	O
there	O
's	O
any	O
Victuals	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
have	O
it	O
.	O
Molly	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Deceased	O
base	O
but	O
Patience	O
,	O
and	O
here	O
's	O
enough	O
for	O
as	O
all	O
.	O
But	O
she	O
continuing	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
troublesome	O
,	O
he	O
added	O
,	O
If	O
you	O
wont	O
be	O
quiet	O
,	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
'll	O
turn	O
you	O
out	O
.	O
She	O
answered	O
,	O
If	O
Right	O
took	O
place	O
,	O
you	O
ought	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
first	O
.	O
He	O
perceiving	O
that	O
she	O
resolved	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Disturbance	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
put	O
her	O
out	O
and	O
she	O
immediately	O
stab	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Knife	O
:	O
He	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
died	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
.	O
There	O
had	O
been	O
no	O
former	O
Quarrel	O
betwixt	O
them	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Hanson	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
:	O
After	O
my	O
Husband	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Bed-side	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
Molly	O
,	O
I	O
wonder	O
you	O
'll	O
make	O
yourself	O
so	O
drunk	O
?	O
-	O
Are	O
you	O
troubled	O
at	O
it	O
?	O
says	O
she	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
.	O
Why	O
then	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
ye	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
's	O
no	O
Sin	O
to	O
cut	O
your	O
Throat	O
;	O
and	O
with	O
that	O
,	O
she	O
struck	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
with	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
But	O
presently	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
have	O
Meat	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
any	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
had	O
.	O
Molly	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
Consider	O
that	O
my	O
Sister	O
is	O
not	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
I	O
'll	O
have	O
no	O
Noise	O
.	O
Some	O
other	O
Words	O
passing	O
,	O
he	O
rose	O
up	O
and	O
strove	O
to	O
put	O
her	O
out	O
.	O
His	O
Wife	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
part	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
struggling	O
together	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stab	O
'd	O
him	O
over	O
his	O
Wife	O
's	O
Arm	O
:	O
He	O
sunk	O
his	O
Knees	O
,	O
and	O
died	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Peters	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Widow	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
confirmed	O
the	O
former	O
Depositions	O
,	O
and	O
thus	O
added	O
;	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
part	O
my	O
Husband	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
cut	O
me	O
across	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
struck	O
the	O
Knife	O
into	O
my	O
Husband	O
's	O
Breast	O
.	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
You	O
have	O
kill	O
'd	O
my	O
Husband	O
!	O
She	O
threw	O
the	O
Knife	O
against	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
wish	O
I	O
had	O
stab	O
'd	O
ye	O
all	O
.	O
A	O
Surgeon	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
came	O
too	O
late	O
.	O
Other	O
Witnesses	O
spoke	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Purpose	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Vincent	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Elizabeth	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
her	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
one	O
moral	O
Wound	O
in	O
the	O
Right	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Breast	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Length	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
;	O
and	O
Depth	O
of	O
three	O
Inches	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Tindell	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
(	O
the	O
Deceased	O
)	O
had	O
been	O
my	O
Lodgers	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
about	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Weeks	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
time	O
afterwards	O
his	O
Wife	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
her	O
Return	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
she	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
some	O
ill	O
Women	O
at	O
Roper	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
lewd	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
Pye-Corner	O
,	O
He	O
came	O
back	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
to	O
me	O
from	O
the	O
Stairs-foot	O
,	O
Is	O
my	O
Bitch	O
above	O
?	O
Says	O
he	O
.	O
If	O
she	O
is	O
,	O
send	O
her	O
down	O
with	O
a	O
Candle	O
.	O
She	O
beg	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
he	O
should	O
abuse	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
;	O
He	O
beat	O
her	O
,	O
damn	O
'd	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
Bitch	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
'd	O
murder	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
ran	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
after	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Sight	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
without	O
any	O
further	O
Hurt	O
.	O
Pray	O
,	O
Landlady	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
comes	O
again	O
,	O
tell	O
him	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
here	O
;	O
for	O
if	O
he	O
finds	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
'll	O
certainly	O
be	O
way	O
Death	O
.	O
I	O
hid	O
her	O
behind	O
my	O
Bed	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
;	O
I	O
deny	O
'd	O
her	O
;	O
he	O
swore	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
.	O
When	O
his	O
wife	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
asleep	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
his	O
Room	O
to	O
see	O
how	O
much	O
he	O
had	O
spent	O
of	O
the	O
Seven	O
Shillings	O
he	O
took	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
found	O
but	O
Three-Halfpence	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
he	O
'll	O
murder	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
has	O
found	O
his	O
Knife	O
that	O
I	O
hid	O
in	O
my	O
Box	O
;	O
it	O
lies	O
by	O
his	O
Bed-side	O
with	O
a	O
Bull	O
's	O
Pizzle	O
.	O
Next	O
Morning	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
his	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Bull	O
's	O
Pizzle	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Chair	O
.	O
He	O
jump	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
Bed	O
,	O
snatch	O
'd	O
it	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
that	O
he	O
valu	O
'd	O
his	O
Pizzle	O
as	O
he	O
valu	O
'd	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
'd	O
as	O
soon	O
lose	O
an	O
Inch	O
of	O
one	O
as	O
t'other	O
;	O
for	O
he	O
kept	O
it	O
on	O
purpose	O
to	O
pizzle	O
the	O
Bitch	O
his	O
Wife	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
dress	O
'd	O
himself	O
,	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Chamber	O
,	O
lock	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
His	O
Wife	O
between	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
persuaded	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
Py-Corner	O
:	O
We	O
went	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
as	O
good	O
as	O
his	O
Word	O
in	O
exercising	O
his	O
Bull	O
's	O
Pizzle	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
follow	O
'd	O
me	O
in	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
.	O
I	O
blamed	O
her	O
,	O
as	O
her	O
Life	O
was	O
in	O
Danger	O
,	O
for	O
not	O
securing	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
secured	O
before	O
in	O
New-prison	O
for	O
abusing	O
her	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
home	O
soon	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
will	O
make	O
you	O
,	O
know	O
,	O
you	O
Bitch	O
that	O
you	O
shall	O
follow	O
me	O
any	O
more	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
marry	O
'd	O
to	O
little	O
Jenny	O
.	O
Well	O
,	O
Davis	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
is	O
so	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
help	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
neverthless	O
,	O
let	O
us	O
drink	O
together	O
and	O
be	O
Friends	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
's	O
none	O
in	O
Heaven	O
,	O
or	O
Earth	O
beneath	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
love	O
better	O
than	O
you	O
;	O
and	O
therefore	O
be	O
married	O
to	O
who	O
you	O
will	O
there	O
's	O
nobody	O
shall	O
enjoy	O
you	O
has	O
myself	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Mutton	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Starkey	B-place
's	I-place
at	O
the	O
White	B-place
Horse	I-place
;	O
and	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
'd	O
go	O
thither	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
sup	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
long	O
before	O
she	O
came	O
back	O
with	O
her	O
Hand	O
bloody	O
,	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
cut	O
her	O
Fingers	O
,	O
and	O
beg	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
leave	O
my	O
Chamber	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
abuse	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
might	O
run	O
in	O
there	O
and	O
save	O
her	O
Life	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
his	O
usual	O
Language	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
his	O
Wife	O
to	O
bring	O
him	O
a	O
Candle	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
swearing	O
at	O
her	O
upon	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
she	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
begging	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
reconciled	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
Friends	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
she	O
ran	O
up	O
into	O
my	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
Butcher	O
's	O
Knife	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
Provocation	O
given	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
slab	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
Breast	O
.	O
I	O
jump	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
Bed	O
;	O
she	O
ran	O
down	O
Stairs	O
;	O
he	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
after	O
him	O
:	O
He	O
miss	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
at	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
died	O
about	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
the	O
received	O
the	O
Wound	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Jeffery	I-pers
this	O
depos	O
'd	O
:	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Tobacco-Roll	O
,	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Tindall	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
last	O
Evidence	O
;	O
)	O
there	O
's	O
only	O
a	O
thin	O
Partition	O
betwixt	O
their	O
Stair-Case	O
and	O
mine	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Bed	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Disturbance	O
in	O
her	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Noise	O
of	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
People	O
running	O
down	O
Stairs	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
down	O
too	O
,	O
and	O
open	O
'd	O
my	O
Door	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
.	O
The	O
Moon	O
shone	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
shaded	O
by	O
the	O
Houses	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Door	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Shade	O
,	O
crying	O
she	O
was	O
stab	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
beg	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
in	O
,	O
when	O
Immediately	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
run	O
from	O
the	O
shady	O
side	O
into	O
the	O
Moon-light	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
naked	O
Knife	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
then	O
thought	O
appear	O
'd	O
bloody	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Deceased	O
in	O
;	O
she	O
sat	O
down	O
upon	O
some	O
Leaf	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
and	O
show	O
'd	O
me	O
her	O
Wound	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
bear	O
to	O
look	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Tindall	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Neighbours	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
has	O
killed	O
me	O
;	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
Sake	O
,	O
call	O
somebody	O
to	O
seize	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
do	O
n't	O
let	O
my	O
Blood	O
lie	O
at	O
your	O
Doors	O
.	O
He	O
runs	O
about	O
(	O
says	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
)	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
swears	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
'll	O
kill	O
the	O
first	O
Man	O
that	O
touches	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
soon	O
after	O
by	O
the	O
Comfortable	O
and	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
upon	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
Ha	O
!	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
not	O
dead	O
yet	O
.	O
-	O
Betty	O
!	O
speak	O
to	O
me	O
!	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
'll	O
find	O
to	O
your	O
Sorrow	O
that	O
she	O
will	O
not	O
live	O
much	O
longer	O
:	O
The	O
Lord	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
Heart	O
to	O
repent	O
.	O
Well	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
as	O
live	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
for	O
her	O
as	O
for	O
any	O
body	O
.	O
A	O
Surgeon	O
was	O
called	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
no	O
purpose	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
died	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
.	O
Gill	O
the	O
constable	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
New-Prison	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
kill	O
'd	O
the	O
best	O
Wife	O
that	O
ever	O
Man	O
lay	O
by	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
for	O
God	O
'd	O
Sake	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
let	O
me	O
be	O
Anatomized	O
.	O
Kilpatrick	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
searched	O
the	O
Wound	O
,	O
and	O
believed	O
it	O
be	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
her	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
brought	O
in	O
their	O
Verdict	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Which	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
heard	O
,	O
he	O
trun	O
'd	O
about	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
D	O
-	O
ye	O
all	O
together	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Rachel	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Katharine	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Suits	O
of	O
Laced	O
Head-Cloaths	O
val	O
20l	O
.	O
four	O
Pair	O
of	O
Laced	O
Ruffles	O
val	O
6	O
l.	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Pinners	O
val	O
.	O
50	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Dallington	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
in	O
Burr-street	B-place
;	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Scrutore	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
staid	O
a	O
Month	O
and	O
before	O
they	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
away	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
the	O
Lord	O
Exeter	O
's	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
confess	O
'd	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
Guilty	O
val	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Enfield	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bay	O
Gelding	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
evident	O
that	O
the	O
Horse	O
was	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Woodham	I-pers
's	O
Ground	O
at	O
Enfield	B-place
,	O
whither	O
it	O
was	O
sent	O
by	O
Henry	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
(	O
who	O
keeps	O
the	O
Peacock	O
Brew-house	O
in	O
White-Cross-street	O
.	O
)	O
Walker	O
advertised	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
he	O
received	O
Information	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Possession	O
of	O
-	O
Batts	O
near	O
Beckenham	O
.	O
-	O
Batts	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
Mark	B-pers
Hatton	I-pers
;	O
Mark	O
Hatton	O
of	O
Gilbert	O
the	O
Farrier	O
;	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Plat	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Plat	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
Forrest-Row-Fair	O
in	O
East	O
Grindstead	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Horse	O
at	O
the	O
Talbot-Inn	O
in	O
the	O
Borough	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
People	O
there	O
being	O
all	O
Strangers	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
who	O
to	O
subpoena	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
among	O
his	O
Neighbours	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Susan	B-pers
Fan	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Katharine	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Blanket	O
,	O
a	O
sheet	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pillow	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
April	O
.	O
Guilty	O
val	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Case	O
of	O
Drawers	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Silver	O
Snuff-Box	O
val	O
7	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
val	O
.	O
5s	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
val	O
5	O
s.	O
2	O
Moidores	O
,	O
9	O
Guineas	O
,	O
25	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Richard	O
Andrews	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
kept	O
the	O
Py	B-place
'd	I-place
Bull	I-place
Alehouse	I-place
in	O
Vine	B-place
street	I-place
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
her	O
Husband	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Barber	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
)	O
were	O
drinking	O
there	O
with	O
other	O
Company	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
abroad	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
left	O
them	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
.	O
They	O
thought	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
;	O
but	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Company	O
heard	O
her	O
cough	O
as	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
hear	O
me	O
cough	O
?	O
Yes	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
so	O
;	O
and	O
yet	O
I	O
stuff	O
'd	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
into	O
my	O
Mouth	O
to	O
prevent	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
crept	O
in	O
upon	O
my	O
Hands	O
and	O
Knees	O
.	O
The	O
Company	O
could	O
not	O
imagine	O
what	O
the	O
Woman	O
meant	O
by	O
such	O
odd	O
Expressions	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
home	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Nest	O
of	O
drawers	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
examined	O
,	O
and	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
carried	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
.	O
Guilty	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Camell	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Islington	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
open	O
Field	O
near	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
Hannah	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
now	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Bass	I-pers
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Field	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
Geo	B-pers
Bass	I-pers
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
val	O
.	O
6s	O
.	O
a	O
Forth	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
s	O
and	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Geo	O
.	O
Bass	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
3d	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
for	O
assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Lush	I-pers
in	O
an	O
open	O
Field	O
near	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
9s	O
6d	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
:	O
On	O
Sunday	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
8	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
Husband	O
(	O
that	O
is	O
now	O
)	O
coming	O
from	O
(	O
Islington	B-place
,	O
turned	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
Queen's-Head	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
went	O
along	O
by	O
the	O
Alms	O
Houses	O
into	O
the	O
first	O
Field	O
,	O
where	O
,	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
walking	O
Arm	O
in	O
Arm	O
,	O
Camell	O
and	O
Marshall	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
us	O
:	O
Camell	O
collar	O
'd	O
my	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
m	O
ye	O
,	O
deliver	O
your	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
frighted	O
,	O
let	O
go	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
Camell	O
bid	O
Marshall	O
seize	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
accordingly	O
follow	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
pull	O
'd	O
my	O
Hood	O
back	O
,	O
clapt	O
a	O
Knife	O
to	O
my	O
Throat	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
if	O
I	O
made	O
any	O
Noise	O
,	O
he	O
'd	O
kill	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
fell	O
down	O
.	O
He	O
perceived	O
I	O
was	O
frighted	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
'd	O
do	O
me	O
no	O
Hurt	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
but	O
be	O
quiet	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
my	O
Handkerchief	O
off	O
my	O
Neck	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
Shillings	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Soon	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
four	O
Gentlemen	O
came	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
guarded	O
us	O
to	O
Sam	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
's	O
Cake	O
house	O
at	O
the	O
Shepherd	O
and	O
Shepherdess	O
near	O
the	O
Pest	O
House	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Bass	I-pers
confirm	O
'd	O
his	O
Wife	O
's	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
Camell	O
took	O
his	O
Frock	O
,	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
7s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Drury	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
:	O
I	O
sometimes	O
draw	O
Drink	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Allen	O
's	O
and	O
was	O
there	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Bass	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
came	O
in	O
:	O
They	O
described	O
the	O
Men	O
that	O
robbed	O
them	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Allen	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Couple	O
of	O
Fellows	O
that	O
we	O
had	O
seen	O
loitering	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
thereabout	O
,	O
and	O
concluded	O
that	O
Moorfields	O
was	O
a	O
likely	O
Place	O
to	O
find	O
them	O
in	O
.	O
Thither	O
I	O
went	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
good	O
Luck	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
at	O
Bowls	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
nothing	O
then	O
,	O
but	O
fetch	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Ward	O
presently	O
pointed	O
out	O
Marshall	O
from	O
a	O
great	O
Number	O
of	O
People	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
believed	O
Camell	O
(	O
whose	O
Back	O
was	O
towards	O
her	O
)	O
was	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
be	O
certain	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
heard	O
him	O
speak	O
.	O
The	O
Words	O
were	O
hardly	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Mouth	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
swore	O
to	O
one	O
that	O
stood	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
'd	O
toss	O
up	O
who	O
should	O
go	O
next	O
She	O
presently	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
's	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
We	O
fetch	O
'd	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
which	O
Marshall	O
perceiving	O
,	O
ran	O
off	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
quickly	O
stopt	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
another	O
Place	O
when	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
their	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
Wilkinson	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Jack	O
of	O
Newberry	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Grub-street	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Sunday	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Winsmore-Hill	O
,	O
and	O
returning	O
at	O
7	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
drinking	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
Bed	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
them	O
there	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Limeham	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bell	O
and	O
Three	O
Adzes	O
in	O
Grub-street	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
at	O
Eight	O
o'Clock	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Tankard	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
till	O
Nine	O
.	O
That	O
his	O
House	O
is	O
near	O
a	O
Mile	O
,	O
or	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
's	O
Walk	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
a	O
Furlong	O
further	O
from	O
it	O
than	O
the	O
Jack	O
of	O
Newberry	O
is	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
along	O
Mugwell-street	O
,	O
(	O
in	O
Noble-Street	O
)	O
Cripplegate	O
Chimes	O
went	O
for	O
Eight	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
From	O
thence	O
he	O
went	O
directly	O
thro	O
'	O
Cripplegate	O
,	O
and	O
along	O
Grub-Street	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
coming	O
as	O
from	O
the	O
Fields	O
towards	O
Cripplegate	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Eale	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
that	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
,	O
her	O
Mistress	O
sent	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Jack	O
of	O
Newberry	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
her	O
see	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
past	O
Seven	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
then	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
Wilkinson	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
Stairs	O
(	O
as	O
she	O
supposed	O
)	O
to	O
Bed	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Turner	O
and	O
Pump-maker	O
,	O
in	O
Chissel-street	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Camell	O
had	O
work	O
'd	O
Labouring-Work	O
for	O
him	O
at	O
several	O
Gentlemen	O
's	O
Houses	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
never	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
dishonest	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Drury	I-pers
then	O
deposed	O
again	O
thus	O
:	O
When	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
Upper	O
Moorfields	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
between	O
Three	O
and	O
Four	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
we	O
carry	O
'd	O
'em	O
to	O
the	O
Green	O
Dragon	O
:	O
and	O
there	O
they	O
told	O
us	O
,	O
that	O
that	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
Wilkinson	O
's	O
(	O
the	O
Jack	O
of	O
Newberry	O
)	O
all	O
Day	O
,	O
till	O
Six	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
the	O
Raven	O
and	O
Bell	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
staid	O
till	O
Nine	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Jack	O
of	O
Newberry	O
again	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
not	O
try	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sattin	O
Gown	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Carolus	O
,	O
9	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Henly	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
a	O
Chair-Woman	O
)	O
to	O
take	O
Care	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
:	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
;	O
some	O
'em	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Isabel	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
set	O
with	O
Diamonds	O
,	O
val	O
20	O
s.	O
2	O
Moidores	O
,	O
36	O
Guineas	O
and	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
12	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wilmar	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
John	O
Wilmar	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
with	O
nine	O
Horses	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
seven	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
all	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
being	O
betwixt	O
40	O
and	O
50	O
l.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
Borough	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
Lodging	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Hyde-Park	O
:	O
It	O
was	O
then	O
about	O
Eight	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
enquired	O
the	O
Way	O
as	O
I	O
went	O
along	O
;	O
and	O
somewhere	O
about	O
the	O
Strand	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
'd	O
shew	O
me	O
the	O
Way	O
if	O
I	O
'd	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
together	O
to	O
the	O
Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
instead	O
of	O
one	O
Pint	O
we	O
had	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
.	O
About	O
Eleven	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
pretty	O
well	O
tired	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
fell	O
asleep	O
.	O
The	O
Drawer	O
awaked	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
me	O
feel	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
lost	O
my	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
felt	O
,	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
a	O
great	O
Part	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Bernard	B-pers
Armstrong	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
Drawer	O
at	O
the	O
Harp	B-place
and	I-place
Crown	I-place
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Martin's-Lane	I-place
.	O
About	O
Eight	O
at	O
Night	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Room	O
.	O
My	O
Master	O
do	O
n't	O
allow	O
Women	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
Stairs	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
looking	O
like	O
civil	O
People	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
there	O
might	O
be	O
no	O
Hurt	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
They	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
three	O
Pints	O
of	O
Wine	O
;	O
by	O
which	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
enough	O
in	O
their	O
Behaviour	O
to	O
convince	O
me	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Woman	O
of	O
the	O
Town	O
.	O
The	O
Man	O
grew	O
drowsy	O
.	O
Honest	O
Friend	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
have	O
a	O
Care	O
what	O
you	O
do	O
;	O
and	O
have	O
a	O
Care	O
of	O
your	O
Money	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
have	O
any	O
about	O
you	O
Money	O
!	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
40	O
l.	O
and	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
let	O
us	O
have	O
t'other	O
Pint	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
another	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
brought	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
interim	O
,	O
I	O
made	O
several	O
Excuses	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
might	O
have	O
as	O
little	O
Opportunity	O
as	O
possible	O
of	O
being	O
too	O
free	O
with	O
either	O
his	O
Person	O
or	O
Pocket	O
.	O
She	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
pay	O
.	O
The	O
Reckoning	O
was	O
5	O
s.	O
2	O
d.	O
The	O
Man	O
was	O
asleep	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
27	O
s.	O
(	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
Silver	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
thought	O
she	O
had	O
made	O
some	O
mistake	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
knew	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
me	O
.	O
Pish	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
a	O
Fool	O
?	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
and	O
wink	O
'd	O
upon	O
me	O
;	O
Do	O
n't	O
you	O
know	O
your	O
Business	O
Ca	O
n't	O
you	O
take	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
be	O
quiet	O
?	O
I	O
still	O
refused	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
her	O
pressing	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
strong	O
suspicion	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
pick	O
'd	O
the	O
Countryman	O
's	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
:	O
She	O
grew	O
angry	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
gone	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
resolved	O
to	O
keep	O
her	O
till	O
I	O
had	O
awaked	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
him	O
examine	O
his	O
Pockets	O
;	O
which	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
pretty	O
well	O
emptied'em	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
a	O
Porter	O
for	O
the	O
Beadle	O
,	O
who	O
carry	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Round-House	O
.	O
-	O
Halliwell	O
the	O
Constable	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
I	O
stript	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
Round-House	O
,	O
and	O
search	O
'd	O
her	O
in	O
every	O
Place	O
.	O
Two	O
Crowns	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Stockings	O
,	O
two	O
Moidores	O
in	O
her	O
Hands	O
,	O
several	O
Guineas	O
,	O
a	O
Half-Guinea	O
,	O
a	O
Half-Crown	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Ring	O
with	O
a	O
Stone	O
and	O
six	O
Sparks	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
many	O
other	O
Guineas	O
in	O
her	O
Bosom	O
,	O
as	O
made	O
up	O
20	O
l.	O
13	O
s.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
thus	O
made	O
her	O
Defence	O
:	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
go	O
and	O
take	O
a	O
Glass	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
refus	O
'd	O
and	O
got	O
past	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
Hopes	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
troubled	O
with	O
him	O
no	O
more	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
follow	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
Temple-Bar	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
,	O
with	O
great	O
Importunity	O
,	O
and	O
much	O
against	O
my	O
Will	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Tavern	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
had	O
five	O
Pints	O
of	O
Wine	O
.	O
He	O
press	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
House	O
in	O
Piccadilly	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
with	O
him	O
all	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
with	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
was	O
no	O
such	O
Person	O
.	O
My	O
Dear	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
but	O
go	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
want	O
for	O
nothing	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
Money	O
enough	O
,	O
and	O
do	O
n't	O
value	O
30	O
or	O
40	O
l.	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
think	O
I	O
wo	O
n't	O
be	O
as	O
good	O
as	O
my	O
Word	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
give	O
it	O
you	O
now	O
.	O
And	O
so	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
his	O
money	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
into	O
my	O
Lap	O
.	O
And	O
I	O
am	O
so	O
far	O
from	O
being	O
guilty	O
of	O
this	O
that	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
charged	O
with	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
an	O
ill	O
thing	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
-	O
Rimmington	O
,	O
a	O
Barber	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Mother	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Perriwig	O
in	O
Black-Fryers	O
,	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
We	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ever	O
since	O
she	O
came	O
from	O
Sunderland	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
above	O
twelve	O
Years	O
ago	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
our	O
House	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
had	O
three	O
Husbands	O
;	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
are	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
saw	O
her	O
marry	O
'd	O
to	O
this	O
third	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
now	O
living	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Taylor	O
and	O
a	O
Soldier	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
two	O
Children	O
alive	O
:	O
She	O
has	O
been	O
an	O
industrious	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
to	O
assist	O
her	O
Husband	O
in	O
his	O
Business	O
.	O
She	O
always	O
behaved	O
herself	O
civilly	O
;	O
no	O
Company	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
never	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Lodging	O
after	O
Ten	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Snelson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Whitechappel	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
Yards	O
of	O
Lace	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
Pound	O
of	O
Pepper	O
val	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
four	O
Nutmegs	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Geo	B-pers
.	I-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Myers	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Aldgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
Haddock	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Spoon	O
val	O
.	O
9	O
s.	O
a	O
Ring	O
val	O
6	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Pinners	O
val	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	O
Johnson	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
April	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
val	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Golding	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Covent-Garden	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coach	O
Seat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Lilly	I-pers
Guilty	O
.	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Peterson	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hyat	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
thence	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Socks	O
val	O
2	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
.	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
twenty	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
30s	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
and	O
S.	O
Hyat	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Shellam	I-pers
of	O
Whitechappel	B-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Pound	O
of	O
Yarn	O
,	O
val	O
4s	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
Jan	O
.	O
last	O
;	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
and	O
Susan	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stoln	O
.	O
The	O
Accessaries	O
were	O
acquitted	O
;	O
but	O
Shellam	O
the	O
Principal	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Whipt	O
.	O
Olive	B-pers
Searle	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
val	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Lewis	B-pers
Jetsam	I-pers
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Kenniston	I-pers
of	O
S.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Curtain	O
,	O
val	O
2.	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Avery	I-pers
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
of	O
S.	B-place
Sepulchre	I-place
's	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Evilhay	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Wig	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Coat	O
val	O
.	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Wastecoat	O
val	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
Shirt	O
and	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
val	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	O
Evilhay	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Evilhay	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
,	O
about	O
Nine	O
o'Clock	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
thro	O
'	O
Chartreux-Lane	B-place
with	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Cloaths	O
in	O
his	O
Arms	O
,	O
his	O
Heels	O
were	O
tript	O
up	O
;	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
fell	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
lost	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
very	O
dark	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
who	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
had	O
served	O
him	O
so	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hoskins	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
next	O
after	O
Mr.	O
Evilhay	O
was	O
robbed	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
Queen's-street	O
;	O
Lincoln's-Inn-Fields	O
and	O
talking	O
of	O
his	O
Loss	O
he	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
a	O
Pattern	O
of	O
the	O
Cloth	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
I	O
Called	O
to	O
mind	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Loitering	O
about	O
Lincoln's-Inn-Fields	O
with	O
such	O
a	O
coloured	O
Suit	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
big	O
for	O
him	O
Mr.	O
Evilhay	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
examine	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
again	O
which	O
I	O
think	O
was	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
he	O
then	O
had	O
only	O
the	O
Waste	O
coat	O
and	O
Breeches	O
on	O
for	O
the	O
Coat	O
as	O
I	O
afterwards	O
heard	O
,	O
was	O
at	O
Pawn	O
.	O
I	O
presently	O
stopt	O
him	O
and	O
demanded	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
chose	O
Cloths	O
?	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
were	O
sent	O
him	O
by	O
his	O
Friends	O
from	O
Coventry	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
they	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
so	O
?	O
says	O
I	O
.	O
Because	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
growing	O
.	O
Afterwards	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
the	O
Lady	O
Child	O
gave	O
them	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
another	O
time	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
be	O
won	O
them	O
at	O
Tossing-up	O
in	O
Moorfields	O
one	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
.	O
Eliz	B-pers
Hysham	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
Monday	O
after	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
Coat	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
three	O
Shillings	O
;	O
he	O
fetch	O
'd	O
it	O
out	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
it	O
again	O
Night	O
for	O
5	O
Shillings	O
.	O
He	O
clear	O
'd	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
afterwards	O
have	O
had	O
7	O
Shillings	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
began	O
to	O
suspect	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
in	O
any	O
more	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
himself	O
,	O
Bob	B-pers
Dowland	I-pers
and	O
another	O
,	O
committed	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
That	O
Dowland	O
had	O
the	O
Shoes	O
and	O
Stockings	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
had	O
the	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
himself	O
the	O
Coat	O
,	O
Wastecoat	O
and	O
Breeches	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
stumbled	O
over	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Moorfields	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
into	O
Smithfield	O
Rounds	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
stript	O
himself	O
,	O
put	O
them	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
his	O
old	O
Rags	O
behind	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Susan	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Covent	B-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
7	O
Yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
striped	O
Cotton	O
,	O
4	O
Yards	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
2	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Flude	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Dish	O
and	O
7	O
Plates	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Gladdell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
March	O
last	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Jenks	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S	B-place
Gile	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Latter	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
val	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Lewis	B-pers
Win	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
On	O
which	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Prosecution	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Fitchet	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Dish	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Chamber-Pot	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Guilty	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Judith	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
of	O
S.	B-place
Bennet	I-place
Gracechurch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Seal	O
with	O
an	O
Amethyst	O
set	O
in	O
Gold	O
,	O
val	O
3	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Ashew	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
,	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
:	O
Between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
the	O
Hole	O
in	O
the	O
Wall	O
in	O
Jerusalem-Alley	B-place
,	O
in	O
Gracechruch-Street	B-place
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
.	O
He	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
of	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Silver	O
.	O
I	O
search	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Watch	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
his	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
appearing	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Susan	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Bride	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Watch	O
.	O
val	O
.	O
35	O
s.	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Odell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Odell	I-pers
,	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
part	O
of	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Pints	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
besides	O
other	O
Liquors	O
,	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Lewis	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
Bull-Head	O
at	O
Tottenham	O
Court	O
;	O
from	O
whence	O
,	O
about	O
Three	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
Shoo-Lane	B-place
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lived	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
her	O
several	O
times	O
before	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
made	O
me	O
promise	O
to	O
call	O
upon	O
her	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
that	O
Way	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
be	O
as	O
good	O
as	O
my	O
Word	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
more	O
Women	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
felt	O
her	O
Hand	O
about	O
my	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
pick	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
We	O
drank	O
Brandy	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
at	O
Five	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
my	O
Watch	O
till	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Smithfield	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
and	O
demanded	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
began	O
to	O
call	O
me	O
Names	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
for	O
pushing	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
.	O
I	O
consider	O
'd	O
that	O
it	O
grew	O
late	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
eight	O
Miles	O
home	O
to	O
Whetstone	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
left	O
her	O
for	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
again	O
next	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
threatned	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
Constable	O
and	O
send	O
her	O
to	O
Newgate	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
'd	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
she	O
'd	O
help	O
me	O
to	O
it	O
again	O
;	O
But	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
comply	O
to	O
that	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
Course	O
to	O
take	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
tell	O
any	O
body	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
my	O
Wife	O
should	O
hear	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
and	O
consider	O
'd	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
again	O
next	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Eagle	O
and	O
Child	O
,	O
where	O
Lewis	B-pers
Lefevre	I-pers
,	O
her	O
pretended	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
more	O
Women	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
in	O
Pawn	O
for	O
a	O
Guinea	O
;	O
and	O
except	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
never	O
have	O
it	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
treat	O
'em	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
without	O
my	O
Watch	O
too	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
very	O
well	O
pleas	O
'd	O
withall	O
.	O
Whereupon	O
,	O
I	O
began	O
to	O
think	O
with	O
myself	O
,	O
This	O
wicked	O
Jade	O
puts	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
sees	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
Tears	O
,	O
and	O
do	O
n't	O
much	O
care	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
thing	O
known	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
sha	O
n't	O
save	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
'll	O
tell	O
my	O
Wife	O
of	O
it	O
myself	O
.	O
So	O
home	O
I	O
goes	O
,	O
and	O
tells	O
her	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
committed	O
a	O
great	O
Fault	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
for	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
make	O
her	O
Amends	O
for	O
time	O
to	O
come	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
let	O
her	O
know	O
the	O
whole	O
Concern	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Odell	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
my	O
Husband	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
his	O
Watch	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
Pawn	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
'd	O
give	O
a	O
Guinea	O
to	O
redeem	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
otherwise	O
,	O
not	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
Confession	O
,	O
and	O
Refusal	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
Charge	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
the	O
Constable	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
that	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
pawn	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
spent	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
needs	O
call	O
in	O
at	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
where	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
had	O
sat	O
down	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
,	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
something	O
wrapt	O
in	O
a	O
Paper	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
again	O
.	O
We	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Paper	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Watch	O
.	O
Guilty	O
val	O
.	O
10d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Walter	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Aldgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
43	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Radbourn	I-pers
,	O
and	O
20	O
Guineas	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Stanfield	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Stanfield	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
:	O
Mr.Radbourn	O
kept	O
a	O
Compting-House	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Lucas	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
Packer	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
a	O
Bag	O
in	O
the	O
Desk	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
'Change	O
;	O
and	O
returning	O
in	O
Half	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
enquired	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Lucas	O
it	O
any	O
body	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
no	O
body	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Radbourn	O
's	O
Footman	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
who	O
was	O
just	O
then	O
gone	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
Press-Room	O
.	O
We	O
followed	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
bid	O
behind	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Presses	O
,	O
I	O
pulled	O
him	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
dropt	O
the	O
Bag	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
corroborated	O
by	O
the	O
Deposition	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Lucas	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Stainbank	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Clouts	O
and	O
three	O
Napkins	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
'	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Dicks	I-pers
:	O
Two	O
smocks	O
and	O
two	O
Caps	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Simson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
April	O
.	O
Guilty	O
value	O
10d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Field	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Katherine	I-place
's	I-place
Cree-church	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Branch	O
Candlestick	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
l.	O
two	O
Wigs	O
val	O
.	O
11	O
l.	O
a	O
Sheet	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Cambrick	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Mendez	I-pers
.	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
And	O
William	B-pers
Field	I-pers
,	O
Senior	O
,	O
of	O
Bishopsgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
said	O
Sheet	O
and	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
Knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stoln	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Mendez	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Jew	O
,	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Sarah	O
had	O
been	O
my	O
Servant	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Months	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Strict	O
Charge	O
never	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
Parlour	O
Windows	O
in	O
a	O
Morning	O
before	O
some	O
other	O
of	O
the	O
Family	O
were	O
come	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
some	O
valuable	O
Goods	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
there	O
might	O
be	O
lost	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Morning	O
in	O
which	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
she	O
got	O
up	O
earlier	O
than	O
ordinary	O
,	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
Parlour	O
Windows	O
betwixt	O
5	O
and	O
6	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
soon	O
after	O
the	O
Watchman	O
went	O
off	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
little	O
black	O
Girl	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sent	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
to	O
light	O
a	O
Fire	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
not	O
usual	O
.	O
My	O
Daughter	O
coming	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
heard	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
Thieves	O
!	O
The	O
House	O
is	O
robb	O
'd	O
!	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Slashes	O
was	O
thrown	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Window	O
Cushion	O
was	O
sandy	O
,	O
but	O
seemed	O
rather	O
to	O
be	O
thrown	O
on	O
for	O
a	O
Pretence	O
,	O
than	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
real	O
Mark	O
of	O
a	O
Foot	O
that	O
had	O
entred	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
.	O
Most	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Sarah	O
's	O
Cloaths	O
were	O
sent	O
away	O
just	O
before	O
this	O
Robbery	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
William	O
being	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
brought	O
Sarah	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
pass	O
'd	O
for	O
her	O
Father	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
an	O
Officer	O
and	O
searched	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
Cambrick	O
Handkerchief	O
and	O
a	O
Sheet	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
but	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
lost	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
as	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
Candlestick	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Mendez	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Purpose	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Constable	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
finding	O
of	O
the	O
Sheet	O
and	O
Handkerchief	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Sarah	O
thus	O
defended	O
herself	O
.	O
My	O
Master	O
bade	O
me	O
get	O
up	O
earlier	O
than	O
usual	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
Parlour	O
Windows	O
,	O
not	O
thinking	O
any	O
Hurt	O
.	O
I	O
ordered	O
the	O
Black	O
Girl	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Fire	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
being	O
awkward	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
Half	O
an	O
Hour	O
to	O
instruct	O
her	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Silver	O
Branch	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Parlour	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
frightned	O
,	O
and	O
screamed	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
at	O
that	O
instant	O
my	O
young	O
Mistress	O
came	O
down	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Field	I-pers
called	O
several	O
Creditable	O
Persons	O
to	O
speak	O
in	O
his	O
Behalf	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
,	O
industrious	O
Man	O
,	O
but	O
unfortunate	O
in	O
his	O
Children	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Shoomaker	O
by	O
Trade	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
Clerk	O
of	O
a	O
Dissenting	O
Meeting	O
.	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Aldgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
val.5l	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Walden	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Leaper	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
sell	O
me	O
a	O
Tankard	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
at	O
Newcastle	O
three	O
Weeks	O
ago	O
;	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
afterwards	O
heard	O
that	O
it	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
lost	O
above	O
one	O
Week	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
formerly	O
,	O
by	O
means	O
of	O
an	O
Advertsement	O
,	O
stop	O
a	O
Tankard	O
that	O
was	O
stolen	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Walden	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Tuns	O
in	O
Portsmouth	O
;	O
and	O
finding	O
the	O
Initial	O
Letters	O
of	O
his	O
Name	O
upon	O
this	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
,	O
I	O
suspected	O
that	O
it	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
Place	O
.	O
I	O
question	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
I	O
was	O
uneasy	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
quickly	O
bring	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Neighbours	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
lived	O
but	O
hard-by	O
.	O
In	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
he	O
returned	O
with	O
two	O
Women	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
Business	O
to	O
buy	O
old	O
Silver	O
.	O
This	O
did	O
not	O
satisfy	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
charged	O
a	O
Constable	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
forthwith	O
wrote	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Walden	O
,	O
advising	O
him	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
stopt	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Plate	O
,	O
but	O
neither	O
mentioned	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Tankard	O
,	O
nor	O
what	O
Marks	O
it	O
had	O
.	O
He	O
returned	O
me	O
an	O
Answer	O
the	O
next	O
Post	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
Tankard	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
Weight	O
,	O
such	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
described	O
the	O
suspected	O
Person	O
:	O
All	O
which	O
Particulars	O
agreed	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
this	O
Tankard	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Batchelor	I-pers
,	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
whom	O
we	O
never	O
saw	O
before	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Tankard	O
of	O
Beer	O
and	O
a	O
Pipe	O
;	O
he	O
empty	O
'd	O
them	O
both	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
Next	O
Morning	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
drank	O
and	O
smoak	O
'd	O
as	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
t'other	O
Tankard	O
and	O
Pipe	O
.	O
Soon	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
we	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
saw	O
after	O
him	O
any	O
more	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Tankard	O
for	O
2	O
s.	O
l5	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
Road	O
from	O
Portsmouth	O
near	O
Port	O
Down	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Colstock	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Chandler	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Harmon	B-pers
Smalt	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
March	O
-Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Queenhithe	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
7s	O
.	O
15s	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Crick	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Pearson	I-pers
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Michael	I-place
Bassishaw	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Human	O
Hair	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
3	O
Moidores	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Storer	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Storer	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
Guilty	O
val	O
.	O
39s	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Larkin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Billingsgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
fourteen	O
Cod-Fish	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sam	B-pers
.	I-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ingram	I-pers
of	O
Ludgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
Value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wall	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dashwood	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Landis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Cornhill	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
96	O
Yards	O
of	O
Callimanco	O
,	O
Value	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Delahaye	I-pers
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
in	O
defrauding	O
Charles	B-pers
Delahaye	I-pers
of	O
the	O
said	O
Callimanco	O
,	O
under	O
a	O
Pretence	O
of	O
shewing	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
Customer	O
.	O
He	O
Pleaded	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Prosecution	O
on	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
Fined	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Barrance	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Aldgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
Sylvester	B-pers
Davy	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Bryan	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Covent-Garden	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
being	O
an	O
Evil-disposed	O
Person	O
,	O
greedy	O
of	O
Gain	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
regarding	O
the	O
Laws	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
did	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
1723.	O
that	O
is	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
knowingly	O
,	O
wilfully	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
send	O
a	O
written	O
Letter	O
,	O
dated	O
Jan.	O
27	O
.	O
1724-5	O
,	O
and	O
signed	O
by	O
the	O
fictitious	O
Name	O
of	O
John	O
Brown	O
,	O
to	O
Antonio	B-pers
Lopez	I-pers
Suasso	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
commonly	O
called	O
Baron	O
Suasso	O
,	O
demanding	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
27	O
l.	O
and	O
on	O
Refusal	O
thereof	O
,	O
threatning	O
to	O
burn	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
or	O
take	O
away	O
the	O
life	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Antonio	O
Lopez	O
Suosso	O
Esq	O
;	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brady	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
Before	O
I	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
my	O
Lodging	O
was	O
at	O
Philip	B-pers
Godfrey	I-pers
's	O
in	O
King's-Court	O
in	O
Russel-street	O
,	O
Convent-Garden	O
.	O
My	O
first	O
Acquaintance	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
by	O
the	O
Means	O
of	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Brady	I-pers
,	O
who	O
being	O
since	O
Michaelmas	O
last	O
convicted	O
in	O
this	O
Court	O
of	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
at	O
the	O
White-Lion	O
Tavern	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Cornhill	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
back	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
lay	O
in	O
Expectation	O
of	O
being	O
transported	O
.	O
Hereupon	O
Bryan	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
writes	O
a	O
Letter	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
Jackson	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
afterwards	O
read	O
over	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
can	O
neither	O
write	O
nor	O
read	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
call	O
to	O
mind	O
the	O
Particulars	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
remember	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Mischief	O
threatned	O
to	O
Jackson	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
use	O
Means	O
to	O
prevent	O
the	O
Transportation	O
of	O
Batt	O
.	O
Brady	O
.	O
Whether	O
or	O
no	O
Jackson	O
made	O
any	O
Application	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
in	O
Behalf	O
of	O
Batt	O
.	O
is	O
more	O
than	O
I	O
can	O
tell	O
:	O
But	O
it	O
happening	O
that	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Forward	I-pers
left	O
him	O
behind	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
persuading	O
Smith	O
but	O
that	O
his	O
Letter	O
was	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
grew	O
very	O
much	O
elevated	O
,	O
and	O
valued	O
himself	O
mightily	O
upon	O
his	O
Ingenuity	O
and	O
Management	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
soon	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
resolved	O
to	O
try	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
procure	O
a	O
sum	O
of	O
Money	O
by	O
the	O
same	O
Means	O
.	O
He	O
consulted	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
a	O
proper	O
Person	O
,	O
and	O
or	O
last	O
we	O
pitched	O
upon	O
Baron	O
Suosso-Accordingly	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
he	O
sends	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Sum	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
King's-Court	O
,	O
where	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
,	O
he	O
agreed	O
to	O
write	O
a	O
Letter	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Baron	O
,	O
demanding	O
27	O
l.	O
to	O
be	O
paid	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
called	O
for	O
Pen	O
,	O
Ink	O
and	O
Paper	O
,	O
and	O
began	O
to	O
write	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
wrote	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Words	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
the	O
Ink	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
yellow	O
.	O
Whereupon	O
I	O
steps	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
Landlord	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
some	O
that	O
was	O
blacker	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
he	O
finish	O
'd	O
the	O
Letter	O
.	O
He	O
read	O
it	O
over	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
remember	O
that	O
in	O
it	O
he	O
desired	O
the	O
Baron	O
to	O
pay	O
27	O
l.	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
Lodgers	O
.	O
or	O
else	O
he	O
swore	O
he	O
'd	O
be	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
or	O
burn	O
his	O
Country	O
Seat	O
,	O
and	O
concluded	O
with	O
some	O
such	O
Words	O
as	O
these	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
shamm	O
'd	O
it	O
with	O
any	O
body	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Name	O
is	O
John	O
Brown	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
directed	O
it	O
as	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
To	O
my	O
Lord	O
Baron	O
Suass	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Jury	O
.	O
He	O
sealed	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
the	O
Penny	O
Post	O
Office	O
.	O
I	O
accordingly	O
carry	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Tenant	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
Distiller	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Bridges-Street	O
,	O
in	O
Russel-street	O
.	O
Since	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
enquired	O
of	O
me	O
several	O
time	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
received	O
no	O
Answer	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
heard	O
nothing	O
.	O
But	O
not	O
long	O
after	O
,	O
a	O
Man	O
came	O
about	O
Noon	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
being	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
Debt	O
,	O
was	O
afraid	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Balliff	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
slipt	O
out	O
and	O
went	O
home	O
.	O
The	O
Man	O
came	O
again	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
met	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
John	O
Brown	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
meet	O
me	O
next	O
day	O
about	O
Three	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
at	O
the	O
Kings's-Arms	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Covent-Garden	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
Money	O
to	O
pay	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
Account	O
of	O
John	O
Brown	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
thither	O
,	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
committed	O
to	O
Newgate	O
.	O
While	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
fear	O
nothing	O
;	O
for	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
There	O
's	O
no	O
Langer	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
can	O
but	O
1keep	O
your	O
own	O
Counsel	O
,	O
you	O
'll	O
come	O
off	O
well	O
enough	O
.	O
The	O
Letter	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
;	O
and	O
this	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
verily	O
believed	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
Line	O
,	O
being	O
wrote	O
with	O
a	O
yellow	O
luk	O
,	O
very	O
different	O
from	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
Benj	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Penny	O
Post	O
Man	O
,	O
being	O
shew	O
'd	O
the	O
Letter	O
,	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
by	O
the	O
Date	O
of	O
this	O
Letter	O
,	O
and	O
Tenant	O
C	O
being	O
wrote	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
I	O
know	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
own	O
Hand	O
)	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
that	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
January	O
I	O
took	O
this	O
Letter	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Tenant	O
C	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
proper	O
Office	O
at	O
Charing-Cross	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
write	O
Tenant	O
C	O
upon	O
all	O
the	O
Letters	O
that	O
I	O
take	O
from	O
thence	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Curiel	I-pers
Abasse	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Baron	O
Suasso	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
received	O
the	O
Letter	O
,	O
now	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
Penny-Postman	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
about	O
Ten	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
:	O
The	O
Baron	O
was	O
then	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
;	O
but	O
coming	O
home	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
then	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
read	O
it	O
myself	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
.	O
Antonio	B-pers
Lopez	I-pers
Suasso	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
received	O
this	O
Letter	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Abasse	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
began	O
to	O
read	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
for	O
no	O
other	O
than	O
a	O
Petition	O
for	O
Charity	O
;	O
but	O
coming	O
higher	O
the	O
End	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
to	O
find	O
such	O
imprecations	O
and	O
Threatening	O
as	O
I	O
there	O
met	O
with	O
.	O
I	O
advertised	O
a	O
Reward	O
to	O
any	O
out	O
that	O
would	O
discover	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
sent	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
being	O
unsuccessful	O
,	O
I	O
employ	O
'd	O
a	O
proper	O
Person	O
to	O
feign	O
a	O
Compliance	O
with	O
the	O
Proposals	O
in	O
the	O
Letter	O
;	O
by	O
which	O
Means	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
detected	O
.	O
The	O
Letter	O
to	O
Jackson	O
was	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
appeared	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Hand-Writing	O
,	O
Irish	O
Blunders	O
,	O
Imprecations	O
,	O
and	O
Spelling	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
genuine	O
Work	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Author	O
that	O
wrote	O
the	O
other	O
to	O
Baron	O
suasso	O
:	O
Which	O
last	O
was	O
openly	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
literally	O
as	O
follows	O
:	O
Janry	O
the	O
27th	O
1724/5	O
.	O
Me	O
Lord	O
THis	O
is	O
to	O
let	O
your	O
Lordship	O
Know	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
A	O
poor	O
unfortuneate	O
Gentellman	O
that	O
I	O
is	O
Indept	O
Indepted	O
to	O
my	O
Tealer	O
the	O
sum	O
of	O
Seven	O
And	O
Twenty	O
pound	O
and	O
should	O
not	O
Give	O
your	O
Lordship	O
this	O
Truble	O
onely	O
that	O
present	O
nesesary	O
Compeells	O
me	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
I	O
am	O
soe	O
hared	O
Pursud	O
for	O
this	O
mony	O
that	O
I	O
dare	O
not	O
Show	O
my	O
Face	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
thime	O
and	O
baveing	O
of	O
Your	O
Lordships	O
Goodness	O
noeing	O
that	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
parson	O
that	O
dus	O
not	O
vallue	O
suoh	O
a	O
small	O
matters	O
that	O
to	O
Releve	O
a	O
person	O
in	O
Great	O
Distress	O
which	O
Dept	O
shall	O
be	O
Return	O
'd	O
Honourably	O
In	O
a	O
little	O
Time	O
to	O
Your	O
Lordship	O
this	O
person	O
that	O
I	O
Owe	O
this	O
Money	O
to	O
is	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brady	I-pers
Liveing	I-pers
in	O
Kings-Court	O
in	O
Russel	O
Street	O
be	O
Drury	O
lane	O
pleahouse	O
and	O
if	O
Your	O
Lordship	O
pleases	O
to	O
pay	O
this	O
mony	O
to	O
my	O
Creditor	O
thomas	O
Brady	O
I	O
shall	O
Be	O
for	O
Ever	O
oblidge	O
to	O
your	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
other	O
Dependence	O
other	O
wise	O
Your	O
Lordship	O
may	O
Depend	O
upon	O
it	O
if	O
this	O
money	O
be	O
not	O
paid	O
to	O
this	O
Mr.	O
Brad	O
liveing	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Godfrees	O
In	O
the	O
Court	O
aforesaid	O
God	O
Dam	O
my	O
Blood	O
if	O
I	O
donte	O
be	O
Revengd	O
upon	O
your	O
Carkicees	O
and	O
speedily	O
and	O
if	O
this	O
money	O
be	O
not	O
paid	O
be	O
Monday	O
next	O
God	O
Etternally	O
Dam	O
my	O
Blood	O
if	O
I	O
doubt	O
murther	O
you	O
some	O
time	O
or	O
on	O
other	O
Either	O
in	O
town	O
or	O
in	O
Contrey	O
or	O
if	O
I	O
cont	O
'	O
not	O
meet	O
with	O
your	O
or	O
gett	O
any	O
oportunity	O
by	O
God	O
that	O
made	O
me	O
Ill	O
Burn	O
your	O
Contry	O
Seat	O
You	O
need	O
not	O
ln	O
Sist	O
upon	O
any	O
other	O
Teerms	O
but	O
wthat	O
is	O
In	O
this	O
letter	O
I	O
desire	O
you	O
may	O
not	O
Let	O
mr.	O
Brady	O
Know	O
of	O
this	O
writting	O
or	O
Devowlge	O
it	O
to	O
any	O
Person	O
what	O
Sum	O
Ever	O
this	O
it	O
all	O
from	O
me	O
that	O
never	O
Shamd	O
with	O
any	O
Body	O
Yet	O
my	O
Name	O
is	O
John	O
Brown	O
.	O
Your	O
Lordships	O
most	O
obedt	O
Servant	O
in	O
Distress	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
neither	O
knew	O
Baron	O
Suasso	O
's	O
City-House	O
nor	O
his	O
Country-House	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Evidence	O
Brady	O
was	O
a	O
Fellow	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
scandalous	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
for	O
begging	O
with	O
a	O
false	O
Brief	O
.	O
He	O
farther	O
desired	O
,	O
that	O
Brady	O
might	O
be	O
ask	O
'd	O
who	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
wrote	O
the	O
Taylor	O
's	O
Bill	O
for	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
John	O
Brown	O
?	O
In	O
Answer	O
to	O
which	O
,	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Plunket	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
That	O
Day	O
that	O
Brady	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
Hurry	O
,	O
and	O
begg	O
'd	O
of	O
me	O
to	O
write	O
a	O
Bill	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
his	O
Work-Shop	O
,	O
and	O
wrote	O
as	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Men	O
dictated	O
.	O
John	O
Brown	O
's	O
Bell	O
,	O
For	O
two	O
Suits	O
of	O
Duroy	O
,	O
one	O
Suit	O
of	O
Cloth	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Articles	O
,	O
that	O
came	O
to	O
about	O
27l	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
round	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Claude	B-pers
Anjou	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
our	O
Sovereign	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	B-pers
,	O
called	O
S.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Palace	I-place
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Brilliant	O
Ear-Rings	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
one	O
Cross	O
with	O
five	O
Diamonds	O
value	O
42	O
s.	O
ten	O
Gold	O
Medals	O
value	O
30	O
l.	O
five	O
Silver	O
Medals	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
fifteen	O
Ducats	O
in	O
a	O
Purse	O
,	O
a	O
Bodkin	O
let	O
with	O
Diamonds	O
,	O
a	O
great	O
Number	O
of	O
Lockets	O
,	O
Snuff-Boxes	O
,	O
and	O
Rings	O
set	O
with	O
Diamonds	O
,	O
Emeralds	O
,	O
and	O
Sapphyres	O
,	O
several	O
Bracelets	O
,	O
Pearls	O
,	O
and	O
Red	O
and	O
Green	O
Stones	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Equipage	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
other	O
Things	O
of	O
great	O
value	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
One	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
The	O
Council	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
open	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
frequently	O
at	O
the	O
Lodgings	O
where	O
the	O
Robbery	O
and	O
Burglary	O
were	O
committed	O
,	O
had	O
from	O
thence	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
of	O
learning	O
not	O
only	O
in	O
what	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Lodgings	O
it	O
was	O
most	O
likely	O
to	O
meet	O
with	O
extraordinary	O
Booty	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
Time	O
and	O
which	O
Way	O
were	O
most	O
eligible	O
for	O
his	O
Entrance	O
.	O
That	O
after	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
suspected	O
,	O
by	O
being	O
observed	O
to	O
have	O
several	O
Medals	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
John	B-pers
Graves	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
,	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
:	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
Night	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
Sadler's-Wells	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
seized	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
clapt	O
his	O
Hand	O
to	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
feeling	O
for	O
a	O
Pistol	O
;	O
but	O
instead	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
dropt	O
this	O
Purse	O
with	O
these	O
two	O
Gold	O
Medals	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
has	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
Hamburg	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
the	O
Effigy	O
of	O
the	O
Princess	O
Sophia	O
;	O
this	O
Silver	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
this	O
Toothpick-Case	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Jewels	O
.	O
Lucretia	B-pers
La	I-pers
Vienna	I-pers
and	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Schroder	I-pers
,	O
(	O
by	O
a	O
sworn	O
Interpreter	O
)	O
proved	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Constable	O
then	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
between	O
Friday	O
and	O
Saturday	O
;	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Ground-Room	O
where	O
the	O
Entrance	O
was	O
made	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
Eight	O
o'Clock	O
that	O
Friday	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Sash	O
of	O
that	O
Room	O
was	O
left	O
shut	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Window-Shutters	O
without	O
were	O
pulled	O
to	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
barr	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
Seven	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
they	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Sash	O
open	O
.	O
His	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
this	O
Effect	O
:	O
Between	O
One	O
and	O
Two	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
over	O
a	O
Door	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Lodgings	O
where	O
I	O
committed	O
the	O
Robbery	O
:	O
I	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Shutters	O
,	O
threw	O
up	O
the	O
Sash	O
,	O
and	O
enter	O
'd	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Window	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
little	O
Fire	O
in	O
the	O
Chimney	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
I	O
lighted	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Wax-Candle	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
I	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
Scrutere	O
with	O
my	O
Knife	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
effect	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
about	O
for	O
something	O
else	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
a	O
Key	O
hang	O
by	O
the	O
Looking-Glass	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
answer	O
'd	O
my	O
With	O
.	O
I	O
stole	O
from	O
thence	O
all	O
the	O
Goods	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
accused	O
at	O
:	O
Some	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
I	O
dropt	O
two	O
Medals	O
into	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Barr	I-pers
,	O
but	O
without	O
his	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Others	O
I	O
disposed	O
of	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Fairfield	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Alchouse-keeper	O
in	O
Black-Fryars	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
lodged	O
.	O
The	O
rest	O
I	O
left	O
there	O
unknown	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
's	O
Head	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Advertisement	O
in	O
the	O
Daily-Courrant	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
resolved	O
to	O
go	O
for	O
Holland	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Constable	O
prevented	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
according	O
to	O
his	O
Confession	O
,	O
and	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Vincent	I-pers
,	O
Senior	O
,	O
of	O
Fulham	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
nine	O
Ducks	O
,	O
value	O
9s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
Pitts	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
1723	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2	O
d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
Cocks	O
,	O
eight	O
Hens	O
,	O
five	O
Ducks	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Drake	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hobart	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1	O
st	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
1723	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Vincent	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Cocks	O
,	O
twelve	O
Hens	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Geese	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Ormarod	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
1723	O
.	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Vincent	I-pers
,	O
Senior	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stoln	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
but	O
Ben	O
.	O
Rand	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Confederate	O
with	O
them	O
ing	O
he	O
Facts	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
two	O
Years	O
ago	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
this	O
Prosecution	O
was	O
the	O
Consequence	O
of	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
betwixt	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Drake	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Holborn	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tompkins	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
6	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoos	O
,	O
3	O
Pair	O
of	O
Boots	O
,	O
5	O
Pair	O
of	O
Spatterdashes	O
,	O
2	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Tho	O
.	O
Tompkins	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Prosecutor	O
were	O
both	O
Cobler	O
s	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
former	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Stall	O
of	O
the	O
latter	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
of	O
his	O
Effects	O
.	O
Guilty	O
val	O
.	O
4s	O
.	O
10d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Arthur	B-pers
Kenly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Shirts	O
val	O
.	O
40s	O
.	O
and	O
1	O
Cane	O
with	O
a	O
Gold-Head	O
val	O
.	O
40s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Archer	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
April	O
.	O
Guilty	O
val	O
.	O
39s	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
,	O
Katharine	B-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
Katharine	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Thistleworth	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Clements	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
a	O
Sattin	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
val	O
4l	O
.	O
2	O
Crape	O
Gown	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
a	O
Coral	O
val	O
.	O
10s	O
.	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
9Mobs	O
,	O
6	O
Yards	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
30l	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Clements	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
J.	O
Clements	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Mary	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
had	O
been	O
my	O
Servant	O
about	O
3	O
Months	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
my	O
Wife	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Uxbridge	O
Market	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
better	O
Security	O
,	O
desired	O
Mary	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
(	O
who	O
worked	O
in	O
my	O
Ground	O
)	O
to	O
stay	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
all	O
Night	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
about	O
7	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
I	O
left	O
Work	O
in	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
Garden	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
saw	O
Lloyd	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
with	O
Mary	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
he	O
making	O
a	O
Kite	O
for	O
the	O
Children	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
Stevens	O
that	O
my	O
Master	O
would	O
be	O
angry	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
that	O
she	O
let	O
any	O
Men	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
abroad	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
hard	O
if	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
speak	O
to	O
a	O
Friend	O
.	O
About	O
Ten	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
she	O
persuaded	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
Child	O
would	O
be	O
frightned	O
to	O
lie	O
alone	O
;	O
and	O
for	O
her	O
part	O
,	O
she	O
intended	O
to	O
set	O
up	O
all	O
Night	O
and	O
wash	O
.	O
So	O
about	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
I	O
fastned	O
all	O
,	O
the	O
Doors	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
leaving	O
the	O
three	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
2	O
young	O
Son	O
of	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
and	O
my	O
Daughter	O
,	O
(	O
Whose	O
Name	O
is	O
likewise	O
Mary	O
Stevens	O
)	O
all	O
together	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
When	O
my	O
Mother	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
Mary	O
Stevens	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
down	O
a	O
Bundle	O
in	O
her	O
Arms	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Wash	O
-house	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
Kate	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
;	O
and	O
they	O
unbolted	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
both	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
,	O
Stevens	O
having	O
the	O
Bundle	O
.	O
In	O
about	O
four	O
Minutes	O
after	O
,	O
Tom	O
.	O
Lloyd	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
bolt	O
the	O
Dear	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
too	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
only	O
gone	O
to	O
make	O
Water	O
;	O
but	O
staying	O
longer	O
than	O
I	O
expected	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
bolted	O
the	O
Door	O
myself	O
;	O
and	O
neither	O
of	O
em	O
came	O
there	O
any	O
more	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Stuck	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
;	O
An	O
Advertisement	O
being	O
left	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Clements	O
,	O
I	O
Soon	O
after	O
heard	O
that	O
such	O
Persons	O
as	O
were	O
therein	O
describ	O
'd	O
were	O
seen	O
at	O
the	O
Barr's-Head	O
Inn	O
in	O
Braintree	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
Lloyd	O
and	O
his	O
Wise	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
but	O
Stevens	O
got	O
away	O
into	O
the	O
Field	O
.	O
However	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Directions	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Manning	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
hid	O
in	O
a	O
Ditch	O
among	O
some	O
Bushes	O
.	O
Oh	O
!	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
she	O
saw	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
deserve	O
to	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
,	O
for	O
wronging	O
such	O
a	O
Master	O
.	O
Several	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
'em	O
.	O
They	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
committed	O
to	O
Chelmsford	O
Jail	O
;	O
but	O
afterwards	O
removed	O
by	O
a	O
Habeas	O
Corpus	O
to	O
Newgate	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
that	O
Katharine	O
Lloyd	O
was	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
that	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
inform	O
'd	O
the	O
Jury	O
that	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Laws	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
the	O
Wife	O
is	O
entirely	O
under	O
the	O
Power	O
,	O
Direction	O
,	O
and	O
Influence	O
of	O
her	O
Husband	O
;	O
and	O
therefore	O
,	O
whatever	O
she	O
shall	O
act	O
by	O
his	O
Direction	O
,	O
or	O
with	O
his	O
Knowledge	O
,	O
the	O
otherwise	O
of	O
a	O
Capital	O
Nature	O
,	O
yet	O
it	O
must	O
not	O
be	O
imputed	O
to	O
her	O
as	O
a	O
Crime	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
must	O
be	O
acquitted	O
.	O
For	O
as	O
the	O
Law	O
gives	O
Privileges	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
,	O
it	O
very	O
justly	O
grants	O
Indulgences	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
hard	O
,	O
if	O
a	O
Woman	O
must	O
suffer	O
for	O
acting	O
in	O
Obedience	O
to	O
a	O
Power	O
that	O
she	O
can	O
not	O
resist	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
Kath-Lloyd	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Wibrow	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
a	O
Napkin	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
and	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Hanson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
granted	O
her	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
her	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Enfield	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
Trusses	O
of	O
Hay	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Sams	I-pers
;	O
and	O
three	O
Trusses	O
of	O
Hay	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sir	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Sambrook	I-pers
Bart	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
;	O
and	O
three	O
Trusses	O
of	O
Hay	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Caswel	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Coach-Wheel	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Val	O
.	O
10d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
Anthony	B-pers
Ellens	I-pers
,	O
three	O
Guineas	O
and	O
fifteen	O
Shillings	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
his	O
Money	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
asleep	O
in	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
at	O
Lime-House	B-place
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
awaked	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Poof	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Purchase	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Shadwell	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
15	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cloth	O
,	O
Value	O
9	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Cowen	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
William	O
Cowen	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
:	O
I	O
carry	O
Cloth	O
to	O
sell	O
about	O
Streets	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Husband	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
my	O
Ship-mate	O
:	O
He	O
bade	O
me	O
call	O
upon	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
she	O
wanted	O
nothing	O
in	O
my	O
Way	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
I	O
afterwards	O
miss	O
'd	O
a	O
Piece	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
found	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
thus	O
made	O
her	O
Defence	O
:	O
When	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
rude	O
,	O
threw	O
me	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
so	O
and	O
so	O
,	O
whereof	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Cloth	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
spend	O
all	O
the	O
Money	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
merry	O
,	O
and	O
do	O
so	O
and	O
so	O
;	O
whereof	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
Cloth	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
spent	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
do	O
so	O
and	O
so	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
swear	O
a	O
Robbery	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
whereof	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
contradicted	O
by	O
his	O
own	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
Linneke	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
three	O
Neckcloths	O
,	O
and	O
six	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Kellar	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Peirce	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Whitechappel	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Table-Cloth	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Hugh	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sheet	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Seymour	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
value	O
35	O
s.	O
a	O
Smock	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
three	O
Aprons	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Dobbs	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Guy	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Tuddington	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
1723.	O
that	O
is	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
did	O
feloniously	O
hunt	O
and	O
kill	O
three	O
fallow	O
Deer	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
in	O
a	O
Paddock	O
or	O
inclosed	O
Ground	O
where	O
Deer	O
are	O
usually	O
kept	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
Anthony	B-pers
Duncomb	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
Charler	B-pers
George	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
As	O
I	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
Lodge	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
Park	O
like	O
the	O
Squeaking	O
of	O
Deer	O
,	O
about	O
Five	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Biddesford	O
(	O
an	O
old	O
Man	O
)	O
standing	O
together	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
whether	O
they	O
saw	O
me	O
or	O
no	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
presently	O
parted	O
and	O
went	O
towards	O
the	O
Pales	O
.	O
I	O
slipt	O
on	O
my	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
follow	O
'd	O
with	O
my	O
Gun	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
stept	O
to	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
Pistol	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
back	O
,	O
he	O
'd	O
shoot	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
sure	O
that	O
my	O
Piece	O
would	O
go	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
retreated	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
two	O
Deer	O
lying	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
look	O
'd	O
as	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
torne	O
by	O
Dogs	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Biddesford	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
Pales	O
.	O
It	O
fell	O
out	O
that	O
some	O
Countrymen	O
were	O
coming	O
by	O
soon	O
after	O
without-side	O
the	O
Pales	O
,	O
(	O
for	O
there	O
's	O
no	O
Foot-Path	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Park	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
Thieves	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
join	O
'd	O
together	O
to	O
assist	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
Pales	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
found	O
another	O
Deer	O
with	O
his	O
Throat	O
cut	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
quite	O
cold	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
old	O
Biddesford	O
took	O
their	O
Way	O
towards	O
Roger	O
's	O
Ferry	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
pursued	O
them	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Ferry	O
,	O
they	O
turned	O
about	O
,	O
presented	O
their	O
Pistols	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
we	O
were	O
dead	O
Men	O
,	O
if	O
we	O
came	O
a	O
Foot	O
nearer	O
.	O
However	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
off	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
a	O
Boat	O
after	O
them	O
:	O
They	O
landed	O
at	O
the	O
Half-Mile	O
Tree	O
,	O
(	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
Mile	O
from	O
Kingston	O
)	O
and	O
we	O
were	O
not	O
far	O
behind	O
them	O
.	O
Biddesford	O
was	O
shot	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
Kingston	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Powder-Horn	O
and	O
naked	O
Knife	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
latter	O
Part	O
of	O
this	O
Deposition	O
was	O
confirmed	O
by	O
the	O
three	O
Countrymen	O
that	O
assisted	O
C.George	O
in	O
the	O
Pursuit	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bullock	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Shoreditch	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
Lamb-Skins	O
and	O
four	O
Sheep-Skins	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Baynham	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Shadwell	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Iron	O
Crow	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Gallon	O
Pot	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bortene	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Sepulchre	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
29	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Shotbolt	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Whiteside	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Doyle	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
returning	O
from	O
Transportation	O
within	O
the	O
Term	O
of	O
seven	O
Years	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
full	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hands	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Wapping	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hitchen	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Ridinghood	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Hat	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Counter-Cloth	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hitchen	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Val	O
.	O
of	O
4	O
s	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Sims	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Black-Hood	O
,	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Head-Cloaths	O
,	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Smocks	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Tilly	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Hendrick	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Holloway	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Whitechappel	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Drugget	O
val	O
.	O
45	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Tea-Pot	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Susan	B-pers
Grimes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Watch	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
25	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Fitzgerald	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Fitzgerald	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
this	O
Effect	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
O	O
'	O
my	O
Shoul	O
,	O
I	O
wash	O
got	O
pretty	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
wash	O
going	O
very	O
shoberly	O
along	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Preeshoner	O
upon	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
wash	O
going	O
before	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
wash	O
after	O
asking	O
her	O
which	O
Way	O
she	O
wash	O
walking	O
:	O
And	O
she	O
made	O
a	O
Laugh	O
upon	O
my	O
Faush	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
to	O
Newtoner's-Lane	O
.	O
Arrah	O
Joy	O
,	O
(	O
shaid	O
I	O
)	O
you	O
should	O
always	O
have	O
Somebody	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
go	O
sho	O
far	O
alone	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
would	O
be	O
after	O
taking	O
me	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
any	O
Thing	O
.	O
Arrah	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
Shoul	O
,	O
(	O
said	O
I	O
)	O
you	O
shall	O
never	O
fear	O
but	O
I	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
shome	O
thing	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
nothing	O
myself	O
.	O
Sho	O
we	O
went	O
together	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
having	O
any	O
Deshign	O
to	O
be	O
consherned	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
paid	O
her	O
Landlady	O
a	O
Shilling	O
for	O
a	O
Bed	O
.	O
For	O
it	O
ish	O
my	O
Way	O
to	O
make	O
Love	O
upon	O
a	O
Woman	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
whenshoever	O
I	O
intend	O
to	O
lie	O
alone	O
.	O
But	O
ash	O
to	O
the	O
Preceshoner	O
,	O
she	O
wash	O
after	O
making	O
me	O
shit	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
sho	O
tumble	O
together	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
wash	O
after	O
shitting	O
in	O
the	O
Chair	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
was	O
coming	O
to	O
shit	O
in	O
my	O
Lap	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
sho	O
she	O
shit	O
beside	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
wash	O
hoping	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
be	O
eashy	O
;	O
but	O
for	O
all	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
shit	O
at	O
quiet	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
wash	O
after	O
being	O
concerned	O
with	O
my	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
away	O
my	O
Watch	O
whether	O
I	O
would	O
or	O
no	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
pulled	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
pulled	O
;	O
and	O
sho	O
for	O
fear	O
she	O
should	O
get	O
it	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
let	O
go	O
my	O
Hold	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
carried	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Watch	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Watch	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
He	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
Plaushe	O
that	O
my	O
Modesty	O
wo	O
n't	O
suffer	O
me	O
to	O
name	O
;	O
for	O
ash	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
living	O
Chreestian	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
put	O
into	O
her	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Watch	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
thus	O
made	O
her	O
Defence	O
:	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
under	O
Newgate	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
to	O
my	O
Lodging	O
in	O
Charles-Street	B-place
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
about	O
his	O
Business	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
follow	O
me	O
home	O
.	O
My	O
Landlady	O
opened	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
leave	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
catch	O
'd	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
in	O
and	O
drink	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
as	O
well	O
acquainted	O
there	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
So	O
he	O
called	O
for	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Quatterns	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
no	O
Money	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
pawn	O
'd	O
his	O
Watch	O
to	O
her	O
for	O
5	O
s.	O
He	O
was	O
so	O
impudent	O
,	O
that	O
we	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
to	O
fall	O
upon	O
cut	O
Knees	O
to	O
keep	O
his	O
Hands	O
from	O
under	O
our	O
Petticoats	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
gone	O
up	O
to	O
Bed	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
which	O
I	O
refusing	O
,	O
he	O
threatned	O
to	O
swear	O
my	O
Life	O
away	O
;	O
for	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
Irishman	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
swear	O
farther	O
than	O
ten	O
Englishmen	O
.	O
Whereupon	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
in	O
a	O
Watchman	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
were	O
both	O
taken	O
into	O
Custody	O
.	O
It	O
appearing	O
upon	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Oath	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Watch	O
from	O
him	O
violently	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
his	O
Knowledge	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
being	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
it	O
privately	O
,	O
and	O
without	O
his	O
Knowledge	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Scurrier	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
