TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
For	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
AND	O
ON	O
The	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
ON	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
,	O
Monday	O
,	O
and	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
13th	O
,	O
14th	O
,	O
16th	O
and	O
18th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
1727	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Thirteenth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
EYLES	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
and	O
Bart	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pengelly	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	O
of	O
the	O
Exchequer	O
,	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Reynolds	O
,	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Denton	O
,	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Roby	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
,	O
Serjeant	O
at	O
Law	O
;	O
and	O
other	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
aforesaid	O
:	O
Together	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Sabin	I-pers
William	B-pers
Tomlinson	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Packer	I-pers
George	B-pers
Lawley	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
James	B-pers
Crockett	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Wootton	I-pers
John	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
John	B-pers
Shuckbrook	I-pers
James	B-pers
Lacy	I-pers
Joel	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Prater	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Gouge	I-pers
William	B-pers
Gilmore	I-pers
John	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
West	I-pers
James	B-pers
Sharpless	I-pers
William	B-pers
Sudbury	I-pers
John	B-pers
Gouge	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Wren	I-pers
John	B-pers
Arnott	I-pers
John	B-pers
Power	I-pers
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Gold	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
24	O
Yards	O
of	O
Taffaty	O
Ribband	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Towers	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Buttolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
Decemb	O
.	O
the	O
10th	O
.	O
John	O
Towers	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Son	O
shew	O
'd	O
her	O
some	O
Ribbands	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Cherry	O
colour	O
'd	O
Ribband	O
,	O
and	O
taxed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
found	O
several	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Ribband	O
upon	O
her	O
John	B-pers
Towers	I-pers
Jun	O
.	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
their	O
Shop	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
see	O
some	O
Ribband	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
fix	O
'd	O
upon	O
a	O
Colour	O
,	O
she	O
conveyed	O
the	O
Piece	O
of	O
Cherry	O
colour	O
'd	O
Ribband	O
away	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
immediately	O
missed	O
,	O
having	O
but	O
one	O
Piece	O
of	O
that	O
Colour	O
in	O
the	O
Box	O
:	O
Whereupon	O
he	O
taxed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
into	O
another	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
his	O
Mother	O
,	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Towers	O
,	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
.	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Towers	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
upon	O
searching	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
Piece	O
of	O
Cherry	O
colour	O
'd	O
Ribband	O
under	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Stays	O
;	O
and	O
likewise	O
another	O
Piece	O
of	O
a	O
Blue	O
green	O
band	O
,	O
which	O
her	O
Son	O
knew	O
to	O
be	O
theirs	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
cut	O
a	O
Yard	O
off	O
but	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
by	O
Candle-light	O
for	O
blue	O
Ribband	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
return	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
same	O
Block	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Ribband	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Pair	O
of	O
Women	O
's	O
Leather	O
Shoes	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hyram	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Towers	I-pers
Sen.	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
2	O
Pair	O
of	O
Women	O
's	O
new	O
Shoes	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
they	O
might	O
be	O
stole	O
likewise	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
sent	O
a	O
Shoe	O
of	O
each	O
Pair	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Neighbour	O
's	O
(	O
a	O
Shoemaker	O
)	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
such	O
Goods	O
,	O
his	O
Neighbour	O
said	O
they	O
was	O
not	O
his	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
believed	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
Mr.	O
Hyram	O
's	O
in	O
Dukes-Place	B-place
:	O
The	O
Shoes	O
were	O
sent	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hyram	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
Goods	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Hyram	O
's	O
Man	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
their	O
Shop	O
and	O
wanted	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
trying	O
several	O
Pairs	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
too	O
long	O
,	O
another	O
Pair	O
was	O
too	O
short	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
Pair	O
that	O
fitted	O
her	O
exactly	O
,	O
but	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
disliked	O
the	O
Heels	O
;	O
and	O
whilst	O
he	O
was	O
looking	O
for	O
another	O
Pair	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
conveyed	O
the	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
away	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
mist	O
the	O
Shoes	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
positive	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
whom	O
the	O
Shoes	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
at	O
Mr	O
.	O
Towers	O
's	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
was	O
so	O
difficult	O
to	O
please	O
at	O
their	O
Shop	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
'd	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Ribband	O
,	O
but	O
denied	O
the	O
Shoes	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
Boy	O
)	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Christ-Church	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Ward	I-place
of	I-place
Farringdon	I-place
within	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Velvet	O
Cap	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Fenton	I-pers
,	O
December	O
17	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
been	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Olive	I-place
's	I-place
Silver-street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
blue	O
Shag	O
Coat	O
belonging	O
to	O
Isaac	B-pers
Mead	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
8	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Forbes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Magnus	I-place
,	I-place
Bridge	I-place
Ward	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Yalding	I-pers
,	O
Decemb	O
.	O
16	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Fork	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Grubar	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Undershaft	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Ward	I-place
of	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
Decemb	O
.	O
10	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
second	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Caples	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Buttolph	I-place
without	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Cloth	O
Coach	O
Cushions	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Walson	I-pers
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
Defect	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Travers	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pistole	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
Sen.	O
Decemb	O
.	O
20	O
.	O
William	O
Martin	O
,	O
Sen.	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
Wash	O
one	O
Day	O
in	O
a	O
Week	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
Iron	O
another	O
Day	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
two	O
Days	O
in	O
a	O
Week	O
constantly	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Victualler	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
before	O
Christmas	O
Day	O
I	O
started	O
some	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
over-haul	O
my	O
Books	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
Money	O
short	O
for	O
Payment	O
of	O
my	O
Brewer	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
answer	O
the	O
Draught	O
I	O
made	O
of	O
Liquor	O
;	O
which	O
made	O
me	O
suspect	O
some	O
Body	O
had	O
Recourse	O
to	O
my	O
Money	O
besides	O
myself	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
help	O
Wash	O
as	O
usual	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
,	O
was	O
for	O
going	O
up	O
Stairs	O
;	O
whereupon	O
my	O
Wife	O
bid	O
her	O
keep	O
to	O
the	O
Washing-Tub	O
:	O
In	O
a	O
little	O
Time	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
attempts	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
Stairs	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Wife	O
desired	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
Business	O
she	O
had	O
up	O
Stairs	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
some	O
foul	O
Linen	O
;	O
my	O
Wife	O
told	O
her	O
the	O
Maid	O
could	O
fetch	O
that	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
her	O
keep	O
to	O
washing	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
making	O
such	O
Excuses	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
made	O
my	O
Wife	O
suspect	O
that	O
she	O
must	O
be	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
came	O
at	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
upon	O
that	O
I	O
goes	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
unlocks	O
my	O
Draw	O
where	O
I	O
kept	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
counts	O
it	O
over	O
very	O
carefully	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
Twenty	O
three	O
Guineas	O
in	O
one	O
Bag	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
that	O
at	O
the	O
Bottom	O
of	O
the	O
Drawer	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
Moidores	O
,	O
some	O
half	O
Broads	O
and	O
a	O
new	O
French	O
Pistole	O
in	O
another	O
Bag	O
,	O
and	O
lays	O
that	O
near	O
the	O
Top	O
of	O
the	O
Drawer	O
,	O
then	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Wife	O
sends	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
up	O
Stairs	O
with	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
that	O
was	O
below	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
carried	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
comes	O
down	O
again	O
presently	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
goes	O
up	O
Stairs	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
Drawer	O
lockt	O
as	O
usual	O
,	O
I	O
unlockt	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Bag	O
which	O
had	O
the	O
odd	O
Gold	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
mist	O
the	O
new	O
Pistole	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
other	O
Bag	O
and	O
told	O
over	O
the	O
Guineas	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
found	O
exactly	O
right	O
:	O
I	O
acquainted	O
my	O
Wife	O
and	O
my	O
Son	O
how	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
order	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
Stairs	O
and	O
brush	O
her	O
young	O
Master	O
's	O
Cloths	O
;	O
my	O
Son	O
taxed	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Theft	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
be	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
first	O
put	O
her	O
Hand	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Pistole	O
,	O
and	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
conceal	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
Son	O
perceiving	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
her	O
little	O
Finger	O
being	O
closed	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Pistole	O
under	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
Passion	O
,	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
lying	O
B	O
-	O
h	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Drawer	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Martin	O
,	O
Jun	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
Father	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
up	O
to	O
brush	O
his	O
Cloths	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
frequently	O
did	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
Stairs	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
Gown	O
,	O
she	O
desired	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
wanted	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
taxed	O
her	O
with	O
robbing	O
his	O
Father	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
searched	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
trembled	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
great	O
Confusion	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
upon	O
searching	O
her	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Pistole	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
as	O
set	O
forth	O
in	O
the	O
former	O
Deposition	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cable	O
,	O
Value	O
20.	O
d.	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
an	O
Iron	O
Anchor	O
,	O
Value	O
19	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Start	I-pers
,	O
Decemb	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Barnaby	B-pers
Phinks	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
Boy	O
)	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
10	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
:	O
And	O
Christian	B-pers
Phinks	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Boy	O
's	O
Mother	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Catherine	I-place
's	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Velvet	O
Hood	O
,	O
a	O
Velvet-back	O
Scarf	O
.	O
2	O
Silk	O
Gowns	O
,	O
2	O
Silk	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
Decemb	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
)	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Cloths	O
which	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
were	O
here	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Confession	O
taken	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
being	O
read	O
,	O
she	O
making	O
no	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Chou	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Choun	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Goss	I-pers
,	O
Decemb	O
.	O
21	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Bustock	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Allhallows	I-place
Lombard	I-place
Street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
2	O
Guineas	O
,	O
from	O
James	B-pers
Lawson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
James	O
Lawson	O
,	O
Decemb	O
,	O
19	O
.	O
James	O
Lawson	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
December	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Cornhill	O
between	O
Eleven	O
and	O
Twelve	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
drink	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Salutation	B-place
Alehouse	I-place
in	O
Bell-Yard	B-place
,	O
and	O
going	O
up	O
Stairs	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sate	O
down	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
sate	O
down	O
at	O
the	O
Side	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Money	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
Left	O
Pocket	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
right	O
side	O
Pocket	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Left	O
after	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
only	O
some	O
Farthings	O
in	O
my	O
right	O
Pocket	O
,	O
but	O
after	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
Drinking	O
and	O
-	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
change	O
a	O
Guinea	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
indeed	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
so	O
drunk	O
neither	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
be	O
sure	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
pickt	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
for	O
my	O
Guineas	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
desired	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
them	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
stopt	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
spoke	O
to	O
the	O
Landlord	O
to	O
call	O
a	O
Constable	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Blee	I-pers
the	O
Constable	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
Between	O
Eleven	O
and	O
Twelve	O
o'Clock	O
the	O
Man	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
from	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
denied	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
Impudence	O
enough	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
;	O
however	O
,	O
afterwards	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
Stairs	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
shewed	O
me	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
Half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
that	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
Cribb	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
have	O
it	O
here	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
thus	O
made	O
her	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Cornhill	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Royal-Exchange	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
drink	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
denied	O
him	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
this	O
Alehouse	O
;	O
I	O
own	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
unfortunate	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
by	O
keeping	O
Company	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
wronged	O
Man	O
,	O
Woman	O
or	O
Child	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
what	O
Gentlemen	O
please	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
(	O
and	O
what	O
can	O
be	O
freer	O
than	O
Gift	O
?	O
)	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
Constable	O
came	O
I	O
offered	O
to	O
be	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
such	O
Money	O
about	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
must	O
give	O
it	O
me	O
among	O
some	O
Half-pence	O
which	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Bunch	O
of	O
Rods	O
,	O
for	O
we	O
were	O
both	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
mind	O
what	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
the	O
Rods	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
be	O
Flogg	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Man	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
suffer	O
any	O
such	O
doings	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
who	O
carried	O
us	O
both	O
to	O
the	O
computer	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Huntley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linen	O
Sheet	O
,	O
Value	O
3	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Feather	O
Bolster	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Nevil	I-pers
,	O
Decemb	O
,	O
21	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Michael	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
and	O
Luke	B-pers
Wall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Clement	I-place
Dane	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
Shillings	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Jan	O
8	O
.	O
James	O
James	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
Lodges	O
at	O
John	O
williams	O
's	O
in	O
Clement	B-place
's	I-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
about	O
9	O
0	O
'	O
Clock	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
last	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Anderson	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
one	O
Cuel	O
a	O
Cook	O
Maid	O
,	O
that	O
had	O
lived	O
formerly	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
Servant	O
;	O
that	O
going	O
up	O
Stairs	O
after	O
Anderson	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
he	O
cried	O
,	O
Landlord	O
,	O
some	O
Body	O
has	O
been	O
at	O
my	O
Box	O
,	O
his	O
Landlord	O
told	O
him	O
no	O
Body	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
it	O
his	O
Business	O
to	O
find	O
out	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodged	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
accomplished	O
by	O
7	O
O'Clock	O
that	O
Evening	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
but	O
going	O
again	O
about	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
he	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
charged	O
a	O
Constable	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
searched	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
his	O
Coat	O
under	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Direction	O
found	O
out	O
Luke	O
Wall	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
his	O
Shirt	O
on	O
his	O
Back	O
and	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
about	O
his	O
Neck	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Coat	O
from	O
under	O
Anderson	O
's	O
Bed	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
Sacking	O
and	O
the	O
Bed	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Coat	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
Anderson	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
by	O
his	O
Direction	O
they	O
found	O
Wall	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shirt	O
on	O
his	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
about	O
his	O
Neck	O
:	O
The	O
Coat	O
and	O
Handkerchief	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Hains	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
drawn	O
Sword	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Breast	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
short	O
Ribs	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Breadth	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
and	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
12	O
Inches	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
Decemb	O
.	O
of	O
which	O
Wound	O
he	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
10th	O
Day	O
of	O
January	O
following	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
Stabbing	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
Time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
Murther	O
.	O
Humphrey	B-pers
Toms	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
Edward	O
Perry	O
(	O
the	O
Deceased	O
)	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
were	O
going	O
cross	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Park	I-place
on	O
Wednesday	O
was	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
,	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
Mary	B-pers
Pool	I-pers
a	O
little	O
Way	O
home	O
;	O
Edward	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
and	O
I	O
were	O
foremost	O
about	O
20	O
or	O
30	O
Yards	O
when	O
we	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
past	O
us	O
and	O
meddled	O
with	O
Mary	O
Pool	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
Mrs.	O
Perry	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
Edward	O
Perry	O
asked	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
why	O
he	O
meddled	O
with	O
the	O
Women	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
and	O
stuck	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Pass	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Push	O
given	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
within	O
a	O
Yard	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
when	O
he	O
fell	O
,	O
crying	O
out	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
;	O
neither	O
the	O
Deceased	O
or	O
my	O
self	O
had	O
either	O
Sword	O
or	O
Stick	O
,	O
nor	O
was	O
there	O
any	O
Offence	O
given	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
only	O
the	O
Deceased	O
asked	O
him	O
why	O
he	O
meddled	O
with	O
the	O
Women	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
once	O
lifted	O
up	O
his	O
Hand	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mr.	O
James	B-pers
Pringle	I-pers
the	O
Surgeon	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Deceased	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
after	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
given	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
mortal	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
which	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
5th	O
Rib	O
on	O
the	O
Right	O
Side	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
out	O
between	O
the	O
6th	O
and	O
7th	O
Rib	O
on	O
the	O
Left	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
had	O
all	O
the	O
Symptoms	O
of	O
being	O
mortal	O
,	O
insomuch	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
expect	O
the	O
Deceased	O
could	O
have	O
lived	O
Forty	O
eight	O
Hours	O
,	O
notwithstanding	O
he	O
lived	O
14	O
Days	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
dead	O
he	O
opened	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
had	O
penetrated	O
the	O
Diaphragma	O
,	O
or	O
Midriff	O
,	O
and	O
through	O
the	O
Left	O
Lobe	O
of	O
the	O
Lungs	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
Going	O
over	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
Park	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
my	O
Husband	O
and	O
Humphrey	B-pers
Tonis	I-pers
were	O
before	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Pool	I-pers
and	O
I	O
followed	O
at	O
a	O
little	O
Distance	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
passed	O
my	O
Husband	O
and	O
Humphry	O
Toms	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
us	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
Mary	O
Pool	O
about	O
the	O
Neck	O
and	O
Throat	O
,	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Manner	O
as	O
it	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
strangle	O
her	O
,	O
more	O
than	O
to	O
salute	O
her	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
my	O
Husband	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
only	O
ask	O
'd	O
why	O
he	O
did	O
so	O
?	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
no	O
Answer	O
but	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
thrust	O
it	O
through	O
my	O
Husband	O
's	O
Body	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
violent	O
Manner	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Point	O
of	O
the	O
Sword	O
penetrated	O
my	O
Thumb	O
so	O
that	O
it	O
festred	O
for	O
near	O
a	O
Week	O
afterwards	O
;	O
my	O
Husband	O
had	O
neither	O
Stick	O
nor	O
Sword	O
,	O
nor	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
offered	O
to	O
lift	O
up	O
his	O
Hand	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
cried	O
out	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
Centry	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
stop	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Pool	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
having	O
been	O
at	O
Edward	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
's	O
House	O
in	O
Long-ditch	O
in	O
Corkcutter	O
's	O
Alley	O
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Humphrey	B-pers
Toms	I-pers
,	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
Part	O
of	O
my	O
Way	O
home	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
we	O
came	O
near	O
Story's-Gate	O
,	O
the	O
Men	O
being	O
before	O
us	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
and	O
almost	O
choak	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
his	O
Mouth	O
to	O
mine	O
;	O
what	O
he	O
intended	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
much	O
frighted	O
that	O
the	O
first	O
Words	O
I	O
heard	O
was	O
from	O
Edward	O
Perry	O
;	O
who	O
cried	O
out	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Perks	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
cross	O
the	O
Park	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Chapel	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
great	O
Noise	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Person	O
say	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
:	O
I	O
assisted	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
Deceased	O
to	O
the	O
Angel	O
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
taking	O
him	O
by	O
one	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
unable	O
to	O
walk	O
;	O
I	O
staid	O
there	O
and	O
saw	O
his	O
Wounds	O
dressed	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Doctor	O
did	O
not	O
search	O
both	O
Wounds	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
said	O
her	O
Husband	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
.	O
The	O
Serjeant	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
when	O
he	O
heard	O
what	O
had	O
happened	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
Dr.	O
Pringle	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
their	O
own	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
Deceased	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Speech	O
,	O
he	O
declared	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Sword	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
draw	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
Toms	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
assaulted	O
him	O
and	O
beat	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Perry	O
gave	O
him	O
several	O
Strokes	O
with	O
a	O
Stick	O
.	O
Bryan	B-pers
Higgins	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
was	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
he	O
coming	O
from	O
their	O
Quarters	O
to	O
their	O
Lodgings	O
in	O
Thieving-Lane	O
,	O
Westminster	O
,	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
eight	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
they	O
met	O
some	O
Soldiers	O
and	O
pass	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
met	O
the	O
Women	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
to	O
kiss	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Man	O
which	O
is	O
dead	O
turned	O
about	O
and	O
struck	O
him	O
cross	O
the	O
Head	O
and	O
Shoulders	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
his	O
Soul	O
he	O
would	O
see	O
him	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
pushed	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Times	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
near	O
Story's-Gate	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
retreated	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Toms	O
had	O
no	O
Sword	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Stick	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Perry	O
had	O
a	O
Sword	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
Deponent	O
having	O
neither	O
Sword	O
nor	O
Stick	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
go	O
between	O
two	O
drawn	O
Swords	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
long	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Osborn	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
Coming	O
home	O
from	O
my	O
Quarters	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
we	O
met	O
the	O
Deceased	O
and	O
Toms	O
and	O
pass	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
met	O
the	O
Women	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
they	O
belonged	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
called	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
Toms	O
came	O
back	O
and	O
gave	O
Hains	O
a	O
Stroke	O
over	O
the	O
Back	O
with	O
a	O
Stick	O
,	O
then	O
struck	O
him	O
over	O
the	O
Head	O
and	O
made	O
him	O
reel	O
:	O
Hains	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
that	O
was	O
for	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
Sword	O
drawn	O
on	O
either	O
Side	O
,	O
but	O
Toms	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
see	O
him	O
out	O
.	O
Corporal	O
Davis	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
second	O
Night	O
after	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
wounded	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
who	O
answer	O
'd	O
but	O
indifferent	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
weak	O
;	O
then	O
asked	O
his	O
Wife	O
how	O
this	O
Affair	O
happened	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Woman	O
about	O
the	O
Neck	O
and	O
almost	O
strangled	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
that	O
she	O
called	O
to	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
wounded	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
most	O
barbarous	O
Manner	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
,	O
hold	O
your	O
Tongue	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
believe	O
we	O
were	O
all	O
fuddled	O
,	O
and	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
hoped	O
he	O
should	O
recover	O
for	O
his	O
own	O
Sake	O
and	O
for	O
the	O
young	O
Man	O
's	O
Sake	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
forgave	O
him	O
although	O
he	O
had	O
neither	O
Stick	O
nor	O
Sword	O
.	O
Serjeant	O
Hare	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Night	O
the	O
Quarrel	O
happened	O
they	O
had	O
pursued	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
naked	O
Sword	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
killed	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Sword	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Tilt-Yard	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
his	O
Regimental	O
Coat	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Hole	O
in	O
the	O
Right	O
Side	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Thumb	O
was	O
cut	O
and	O
all	O
bloody	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
complained	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
with	O
the	O
Deceased	O
;	O
his	O
Sword	O
I	O
delivered	O
to	O
Charles	B-pers
Moody	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Drum	O
in	O
the	O
Company	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
has	O
lodged	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
near	O
five	O
Months	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Osborn	I-pers
and	O
Bryan	B-pers
Higgins	I-pers
;	O
he	O
always	O
kept	O
good	O
Hours	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
not	O
given	O
to	O
Quarrel	O
.	O
Corporal	O
Smith	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
During	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Confinement	O
in	O
the	O
Tilt-Yard	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
Coat	O
and	O
Wastecoat	O
,	O
which	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
run	O
through	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
I	O
likewise	O
saw	O
his	O
Thumb	O
bound	O
up	O
with	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
Curiosity	O
to	O
see	O
in	O
what	O
Manner	O
it	O
was	O
wounded	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
8	O
Months	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Barracks	O
in	O
the	O
Tower	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
always	O
a	O
quiet	O
Fellow	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
declined	O
and	O
avoided	O
Quarrels	O
.	O
Colonel	O
Williamson	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
Son	O
of	O
an	O
old	O
Soldier	O
that	O
is	O
now	O
disabled	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Father	O
requested	O
me	O
to	O
do	O
something	O
for	O
his	O
Son	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
at	O
present	O
,	O
but	O
recommended	O
him	O
to	O
Colonel	O
Price	O
's	O
Regiment	O
,	O
but	O
advised	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
no	O
Bounty	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
when	O
any	O
Thing	O
better	O
offer	O
'd	O
he	O
might	O
the	O
easier	O
get	O
a	O
Discharge	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
pretty	O
good	O
Scholar	O
,	O
and	O
understands	O
Latin	O
,	O
and	O
during	O
his	O
being	O
at	O
the	O
Tower	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
near	O
a	O
Year	O
,	O
he	O
behaved	O
so	O
well	O
that	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
liberty	O
to	O
come	O
into	O
my	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
always	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
modest	O
Fellow	O
;	O
and	O
for	O
wearing	O
a	O
Sword	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
standing	O
Order	O
,	O
that	O
no	O
Soldier	O
shall	O
be	O
Seen	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
without	O
his	O
Sword	O
on	O
,	O
which	O
makes	O
me	O
believe	O
the	O
Deceased	O
might	O
have	O
a	O
Sword	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
the	O
Evidences	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
directly	O
contradicting	O
what	O
had	O
been	O
sworn	O
in	O
favour	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
thought	O
it	O
necessary	O
to	O
ask	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
some	O
further	O
Questions	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
Ann	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
declared	O
,	O
She	O
saw	O
no	O
Body	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
not	O
any	O
Company	O
pass	O
by	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
stragling	O
or	O
single	O
Persons	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
neither	O
saw	O
Osborn	O
or	O
Higgins	O
to	O
her	O
Knowledge	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Violence	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
neither	O
did	O
Toms	O
give	O
any	O
Blow	O
.	O
Humphrey	B-pers
Toms	I-pers
declared	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
no	O
Person	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
Higgins	O
and	O
Osborn	O
by	O
fight	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
there	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Perks	I-pers
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
help	O
'd	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
Deceased	O
to	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
neither	O
Sword	O
nor	O
Stick	O
,	O
nor	O
had	O
the	O
Deceased	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
his	O
Sword	O
Belt	O
on	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Coat	O
and	O
Wastcoat	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
and	O
shown	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
Examination	O
,	O
the	O
Holes	O
in	O
the	O
Coat	O
and	O
Wastcoat	O
did	O
not	O
correspond	O
,	O
being	O
on	O
contrary	O
sides	O
of	O
the	O
Body	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
guilty	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Morley	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mildred	I-place
Breadstreet	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
30	O
Guineas	O
,	O
1	O
Half	O
Guinea	O
,	O
13	O
Moidores	O
,	O
a	O
Quarter	O
Moidore	O
,	O
2	O
Broad	O
Pieces	O
value	O
23	O
Shillings	O
each	O
,	O
one	O
Half	O
Broad	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
Shillings	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
seven	O
Pounds	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Humphrey	B-pers
Brearly	I-pers
Decemb	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
Humphrey	B-pers
Brearly	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Crown	B-place
and	I-place
Cushion	I-place
Tavern	I-place
in	O
Breadstreet	B-place
,	O
and	O
having	O
occasion	O
to	O
sit	O
up	O
late	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
all	O
the	O
Servants	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
3	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
Money	O
into	O
a	O
little	O
Drawer	O
and	O
locked	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Side	O
Cupboard	O
that	O
is	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
behind	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
then	O
lock	O
'd	O
the	O
Room	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
;	O
about	O
eight	O
o'Clock	O
my	O
Maid	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
Room	O
behind	O
the	O
Bar	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
true	O
,	O
then	O
goes	O
to	O
the	O
Side	O
Cupboard	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
gone	O
but	O
Six-pence	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
my	O
Porter	O
,	O
had	O
double	O
locked	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
threw	O
away	O
the	O
Key	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
strange	O
Porter	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
let	O
us	O
out	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
advertised	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
several	O
News	O
Papers	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
an	O
Advertisement	O
in	O
the	O
Gazette	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
at	O
Guilford	O
,	O
and	O
confined	O
there	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
before	O
the	O
Mayor	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
and	O
signed	O
his	O
own	O
Confession	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Brearly	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
Decemb	O
.	O
3.	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
the	O
Porter	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
,	O
the	O
Iron	O
Bar	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
taken	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
double	O
locked	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
out	O
till	O
a	O
Porter	O
who	O
found	O
the	O
Key	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
opened	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
the	O
Room	O
behind	O
the	O
Bar	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
lay	O
a	O
little	O
Key	O
and	O
2	O
Iron	O
Skewers	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
frighted	O
,	O
called	O
my	O
Master	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Key	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
found	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
.	O
Radcliff	B-pers
West	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Brearly	O
to	O
Guilford	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
before	O
the	O
Mayor	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
his	O
Master	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
upwards	O
of	O
Sixty	O
Pounds	O
,	O
which	O
Money	O
was	O
told	O
over	O
there	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Scullard	O
to	O
the	O
New	O
Goal	O
in	O
Southwark	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
any	O
other	O
Person	O
advised	O
him	O
to	O
commit	O
this	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
no	O
Person	O
advised	O
him	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
he	O
think	O
of	O
doing	O
it	O
when	O
he	O
first	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
believed	O
the	O
Devil	O
put	O
him	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Buttolph	I-place
without	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Cloth	O
Coats	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
Shillings	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
6	O
Shillings	O
,	O
a	O
Wastcoat	O
2	O
Shillings	O
,	O
2	O
Hats	O
,	O
2	O
Shillings	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Bick	I-pers
,	O
Decemb	O
.	O
22	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Laylor	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Christ-Church	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Ward	I-place
of	I-place
Farringdon	I-place
within	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Downs	I-pers
,	O
Decemb	O
.	O
the	O
19th	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Burgis	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
eighteen	O
Pounds	O
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Chain	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
Pounds	O
,	O
a	O
Cornelian	O
Seal	O
set	O
in	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
an	O
Orange	O
Woman	O
at	O
the	O
Old	O
Play-house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
often	O
bought	O
Oranges	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
invited	O
her	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
drink	O
Tea	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
used	O
to	O
talk	O
of	O
a	O
pretty	O
Child	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
she	O
might	O
bring	O
her	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
might	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
,	O
five	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
Child	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
come	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
before	O
she	O
desired	O
to	O
see	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
might	O
know	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
must	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Play-house	O
early	O
,	O
because	O
there	O
would	O
be	O
a	O
full	O
House	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
Maid	O
for	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
told	O
her	O
what	O
a	O
Clock	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
then	O
asked	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
burnt	O
she	O
should	O
approve	O
of	O
it	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
ordered	O
my	O
Maid	O
to	O
burn	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
drank	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Glasses	O
and	O
then	O
was	O
for	O
going	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
the	O
Child	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
troublesome	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
leave	O
her	O
with	O
me	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
not	O
at	O
all	O
:	O
She	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
returned	O
again	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
my	O
Watch	O
still	O
lying	O
upon	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
sate	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
Table	O
where	O
the	O
Watch	O
lay	O
;	O
after	O
a	O
short	O
Stay	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
must	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
leave	O
the	O
Child	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
no	O
sooner	O
gone	O
but	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
my	O
Maid	O
came	O
,	O
who	O
I	O
had	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Knot	O
and	O
a	O
Tart	O
for	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
we	O
searched	O
the	O
Room	O
but	O
could	O
find	O
no	O
Watch	O
;	O
her	O
Child	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
six	O
Years	O
old	O
said	O
,	O
Do	O
n't	O
be	O
frighted	O
,	O
Mamma	O
put	O
your	O
Watch	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
will	O
give	O
it	O
you	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
my	O
Maid	O
for	O
Mrs.	O
Burgis	O
,	O
to	O
tell	O
her	O
I	O
must	O
speak	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
about	O
7	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
why	O
she	O
had	O
played	O
the	O
Rogue	O
with	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
she	O
denied	O
having	O
meddled	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
should	O
go	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
desired	O
she	O
might	O
send	O
for	O
a	O
Cloak	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Hoop-petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
whispered	O
to	O
a	O
Person	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
came	O
in	O
without	O
being	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
and	O
fetched	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
wanted	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
pretty	O
while	O
in	O
putting	O
them	O
on	O
just	O
at	O
a	O
Corner	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
near	O
which	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
old	O
Pattens	O
,	O
she	O
pretended	O
her	O
Shoe	O
was	O
unbuckled	O
,	O
or	O
her	O
Garter	O
untied	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
stooped	O
down	O
for	O
a	O
little	O
Time	O
:	O
And	O
after	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
knocked	O
up	O
all	O
the	O
Pawnbrokers	O
thereabout	O
to	O
enquire	O
if	O
the	O
Watch	O
had	O
been	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
could	O
hear	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
found	O
under	O
an	O
old	O
Patten	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Cristial	O
downward	O
,	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
an	O
Excuse	O
to	O
stoop	O
,	O
notwithstanding	O
that	O
the	O
Pattens	O
had	O
been	O
removed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Place	O
strictly	O
searched	O
before	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
thus	O
made	O
her	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
invited	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
Tea	O
and	O
Breakfast	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
bring	O
my	O
Girl	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
one	O
Morning	O
about	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
Maid	O
if	O
her	O
Mistress	O
was	O
within	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
yes	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
Bed	O
with	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
another	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Footman	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
suppose	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
Bed	O
with	O
his	O
Master	O
.	O
So	O
hearing	O
she	O
kept	O
such	O
bad	O
Hours	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
seldom	O
got	O
up	O
before	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
about	O
Five	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
dressing	O
of	O
her	O
Head	O
,	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
might	O
drink	O
two	O
Glasses	O
of	O
French	O
Wine	O
burnt	O
,	O
I	O
enquired	O
what	O
a	O
Clock	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
fetched	O
and	O
said	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
long	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
if	O
my	O
Child	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
thought	O
troublesome	O
I	O
would	O
leave	O
her	O
while	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Playhouse	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
seemed	O
very	O
well	O
pleased	O
with	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
some	O
Time	O
Mrs.	O
Cooper	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
from	O
the	O
Playhouse	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
why	O
I	O
had	O
played	O
the	O
Rogue	O
with	O
her	O
Watch	O
,	O
I	O
,	O
as	O
very	O
well	O
I	O
might	O
,	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
for	O
searching	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
leave	O
to	O
strip	O
me	O
naked	O
(	O
the	O
Constable	O
promising	O
to	O
look	O
out	O
at	O
Window	O
)	O
this	O
was	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
did	O
search	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
so	O
done	O
and	O
carried	O
me	O
before	O
the	O
Justices	O
I	O
was	O
admitted	O
to	O
Bail	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
that	O
was	O
then	O
charged	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
came	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
News	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
further	O
Proceedings	O
would	O
be	O
stopt	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Colebrook	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Woman	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Ill	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
confin	O
'd	O
,	O
Whitehead	O
,	O
declared	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
a	O
strict	O
Search	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Room	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
find	O
no	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
staid	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
till	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
Colonel	O
Ridley	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sold	O
Oranges	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
:	O
but	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
great	O
Reason	O
to	O
believe	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
Cooper	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
lewd	O
infamous	O
Woman	O
and	O
a	O
common	O
Street-walker	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Barrowford	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Johnson	B-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
Black	O
,	O
Servant	O
to	O
Colonel	O
Johnson	O
)	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
Forty	O
Shillings	O
,	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6d	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Thread	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
his	O
Master	O
Colonel	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holhorn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pea-Jacket	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Amps	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
7	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
a	O
Poor	O
and	O
trifling	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Body	O
appeared	O
to	O
his	O
Character	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Coventry	I-pers
,	O
Labourer	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
an	O
Assault	O
on	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Catherine	B-pers
Southall	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
and	O
carnally	O
knowing	O
her	O
against	O
her	O
Will	O
,	O
Jan.	O
5	O
.	O
Catherine	O
Southall	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
courted	O
me	O
for	O
Marriage	O
,	O
and	O
persuaded	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
Salisbury	O
Street	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
Wedding	O
Ring	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
7	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
when	O
he	O
deluded	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
haul	O
'd	O
me	O
into	O
a	O
dirty	O
Place	O
at	O
lvy-Bridge	B-place
,	O
and	O
laid	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
laid	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
unlace	O
me	O
,	O
then	O
took	O
up	O
my	O
Coats	O
and	O
laid	O
with	O
me	O
-	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
me	O
and	O
entered	O
my	O
Body	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Manner	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
well	O
enough	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
been	O
got	O
with	O
Child	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
desire	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
hurt	O
me	O
-	O
and	O
he	O
lay	O
upon	O
me	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
stirr	O
'd	O
or	O
spoke	O
a	O
Word	O
he	O
would	O
knock	O
my	O
Brains	O
out	O
-	O
I	O
lived	O
about	O
twice	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
off	O
the	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
Home	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
Mistress	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
a	O
Man	O
who	O
deluded	O
me	O
away	O
;	O
then	O
my	O
Mistress	O
sent	O
for	O
my	O
Mother	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
till	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
see	O
what	O
a	O
Condition	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
we	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
he	O
lived	O
before	O
at	O
the	O
next	O
Cellar	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
away	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
there	O
no	O
more	O
:	O
We	O
had	O
been	O
acquainted	O
about	O
a	O
Week	O
-	O
indeed	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
made	O
any	O
Enquiry	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
Mistress	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
heard	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Rank	O
with	O
the	O
Hackney	O
Coachmen	O
every	O
Night	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Kinerly	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
Katherine	B-pers
Southall	I-pers
was	O
my	O
Servant	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
within	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
vile	O
Condition	O
all	O
over	O
dirty	O
-	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Cheese	O
:	O
However	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
this	O
Fellow	O
's	O
Mistress	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
Girl	O
into	O
a	O
private	O
Room	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
examined	O
her	O
very	O
strictly	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
her	O
undress	O
herself	O
;	O
and	O
observing	O
what	O
a	O
Condition	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
(	O
crying	O
before	O
his	O
Mistress	O
and	O
my	O
self	O
)	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
Ivy	O
Bridge	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
dirty	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
her	O
against	O
her	O
Will	O
-	O
;	O
about	O
Half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Cellar	O
where	O
my	O
Husband	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
,	O
(	O
not	O
the	O
Cellar	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
frequent	O
)	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
some	O
Man	O
had	O
done	O
something	O
to	O
our	O
Girl	O
which	O
he	O
ought	O
to	O
be	O
punished	O
for	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
there	O
drinking	O
Geneva	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
it	O
when	O
I	O
spoke	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
telling	O
some	O
Soldiers	O
that	O
he	O
longed	O
for	O
a	O
Maidenhead	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
the	O
Girl	O
was	O
16	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
fit	O
for	O
Business	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
;	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
from	O
Justice	O
Harper	O
,	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
Constable	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Kinman	I-pers
(	O
Midwife	O
)	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
When	O
this	O
Girl	O
's	O
Mother	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
Daughter	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
searching	O
her	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
Man	O
had	O
had	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
that	O
her	O
Condition	O
was	O
any	O
otherways	O
than	O
what	O
it	O
might	O
have	O
been	O
upon	O
such	O
an	O
Occasion	O
,	O
if	O
no	O
Violence	O
had	O
been	O
used	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
for	O
my	O
Part	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
never	O
have	O
been	O
persuaded	O
or	O
deluded	O
to	O
it	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
dirty	O
Place	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
thus	O
made	O
his	O
Defence	O
.	O
Katherine	O
Southall	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
after	O
me	O
to	O
our	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
be	O
always	O
giving	O
me	O
Apples	O
or	O
Oranges	O
,	O
or	O
one	O
Thing	O
or	O
another	O
:	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
to	O
lend	O
me	O
Six-pence	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
sent	O
it	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Gin	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
hang	O
her	O
Windows	O
on	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
it	O
,	O
then	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
drink	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
out	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
to	O
lie	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
consented	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
her	O
Gown	O
Tail	O
that	O
it	O
might	O
not	O
be	O
dirty	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
over	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
to	O
send	O
me	O
a	O
Shilling	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
lent	O
it	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
shall	O
I	O
say	O
to	O
my	O
Mistress	O
that	O
my	O
Cap	O
is	O
so	O
dirty	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
not	O
tell	O
her	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
will	O
tell	O
her	O
that	O
a	O
drunken	O
Man	O
run	O
against	O
me	O
and	O
threw	O
me	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
Dirt	O
;	O
the	O
Place	O
is	O
not	O
above	O
five	O
Yards	O
distance	O
from	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
People	O
passing	O
by	O
in	O
the	O
Time	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gripp	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
13	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
Shillings	O
,	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Table-cloath	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
Shillings	O
;	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Audley	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
2	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sarsnet	O
Hood	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Susanna	B-pers
Legget	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
1	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Audley	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Chandlers	O
Shop	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
of	O
January	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Dukes	I-pers
came	O
to	O
my	O
Shop	O
and	O
offered	O
a	O
Sarsnet-Hood	O
and	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
to	O
Sale	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
bargaining	O
with	O
Gripp	O
for	O
the	O
Hood	O
and	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
Hill	O
and	O
Dukes	O
went	O
into	O
my	O
Room	O
backward	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Gin	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
gone	O
I	O
mist	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
caused	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
to	O
be	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
John	O
Hill	O
confessed	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
pawned	O
the	O
Table-Cloth	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dukes	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
was	O
Fortnight	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
carry	O
out	O
some	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
returned	O
home	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Sarsnet-Hood	O
and	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
in	O
Vine-street	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
shewed	O
them	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gripp	I-pers
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
I	O
should	O
do	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
might	O
sell	O
them	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Audley	O
;	O
so	O
on	O
Monday	O
Night	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Audley	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
Gripp	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
;	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
bargaining	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Audley	O
,	O
Hill	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
backwards	O
and	O
drank	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Gin	O
,	O
and	O
Hill	O
gets	O
up	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
busy	O
forwards	O
,	O
and	O
pulls	O
out	O
a	O
Drawer	O
,	O
takes	O
out	O
a	O
little	O
Key	O
and	O
unlocks	O
the	O
Drawer	O
where	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
takes	O
it	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
:	O
Upon	O
which	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
know	O
where	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
answered	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
there	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
Andley	O
wanted	O
some	O
Money	O
and	O
he	O
see	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
that	O
Drawer	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
Key	O
into	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
Gripp	O
came	O
backwards	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
Hill	O
sent	O
him	O
forwards	O
again	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Herrings	O
,	O
and	O
whilst	O
Gripp	O
was	O
buying	O
the	O
Herrings	O
,	O
Hill	O
stole	O
the	O
Table-Cloth	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
perceive	O
that	O
Gripp	O
knew	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
from	O
any	O
Conversation	O
they	O
had	O
afterwards	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
Gripp	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Hill	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Castle	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Frock	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
Shillings	O
,	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Duffield	I-pers
,	O
Decemb	O
.	O
27	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Black	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Saucepan	O
and	O
a	O
Copper	O
Pot	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
Shillings	O
each	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Pincard	I-pers
,	O
Jan.2	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Pincard	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Abraham	B-pers
Preston	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Leather	O
Saddle	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Blagden	I-pers
.	O
Jan.	O
3	O
.	O
Humphry	B-pers
Porken	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Saddle	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
Custody	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
my	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
thence	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kingham	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
House	O
off	O
the	O
Saddle	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
mean	O
the	O
Saddle	O
off	O
the	O
Horse	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Blagden	O
's	O
Saddle	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Road	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Fretts	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchre	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Gown	O
,	O
2	O
Mobs	O
,	O
2	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
18	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
Decemb	O
.	O
21	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Dutton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Chelsea	I-place
,	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Brass	O
Tops	O
for	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Plate	O
with	O
a	O
Coat	O
of	O
Arms	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
:	O
Decemb.24	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Bryan	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
Hats	O
,	O
Value	O
35	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
Shillings	O
,	O
a	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Iron	O
Grate	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
Shillings	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Sellon	I-pers
,	O
January	O
10	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Salis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cotton	O
Gown	O
and	O
Cap	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cover	I-pers
.	O
Decemb.14	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Mukes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
John	I-place
's	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
,	O
with	O
Jane	B-pers
Dennis	I-pers
and	O
another	O
Person	O
,	O
did	O
rob	O
Isaac	B-pers
Estwick	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
of	O
3	O
Guineas	O
,	O
a	O
Half	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
Pounds	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
.	O
Jan.	O
2	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Estwick	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
Between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
on	O
Monday	O
Night	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Nightingale-Lane	B-place
,	O
a	O
Woman	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
a	O
Door	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
not	O
being	O
willing	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
Cholar	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
two	O
of	O
my	O
Acquaintance	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
beat	O
and	O
turned	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
bolted	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Jane	O
Dennis	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Person	O
seized	O
me	O
and	O
pulled	O
me	O
down	O
with	O
such	O
Violence	O
that	O
I	O
shriek	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
begg	O
'd	O
they	O
would	O
spare	O
my	O
Life	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
my	O
Money	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Bag	O
altogether	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
so	O
frighted	O
that	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
which	O
of	O
them	O
took	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Jane	O
Dennis	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
only	O
a	O
Woman	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
till	O
my	O
Friends	O
came	O
back	O
and	O
got	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Carrel	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
Going	O
along	O
Nightingale-Lane	O
Jane	O
Dennis	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
a	O
Door	O
,	O
(	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Gin	O
Shop	O
)	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
any	O
Thing	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
my	O
Cousin	O
Estwick	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
not	O
willing	O
to	O
come	O
in	O
,	O
but	O
Jane	B-pers
Dennis	I-pers
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
pass	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
but	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
him	O
in	O
by	O
Force	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
we	O
had	O
drank	O
some	O
of	O
their	O
Liquors	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
my	O
Cousin	O
come	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
Poker	O
and	O
beat	O
one	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
my	O
Cousin	O
come	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
his	O
own	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
go	O
by	O
and	O
by	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
when	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
come	O
away	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
pull	O
'd	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
stay	O
there	O
;	O
indeed	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
informed	O
us	O
what	O
Money	O
he	O
had	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
Seven	O
Pounds	O
fifteen	O
Shillings	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
nor	O
see	O
any	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
excepting	O
18	O
Pence	O
which	O
he	O
paid	O
her	O
for	O
Liquors	O
;	O
and	O
called	O
one	O
Edward	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
who	O
being	O
sworn	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
this	O
House	O
about	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
that	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
there	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
Seven	O
Pounds	O
fifteen	O
Shillings	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
charge	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Women	O
that	O
were	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
two	O
Men	O
that	O
were	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
his	O
Evidence	O
next	O
Morning	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Dennis	I-pers
,	O
(	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
admitted	O
to	O
Bail	O
,	O
surrended	O
herself	O
some	O
Hours	O
after	O
this	O
Trial	O
was	O
over	O
)	O
and	O
was	O
indicted	O
in	O
the	O
like	O
Manner	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
same	O
Evidence	O
being	O
produced	O
against	O
her	O
as	O
against	O
the	O
former	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Eccles	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
George	I-place
the	I-place
Martyr	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
three	O
other	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
did	O
in	O
a	O
riotous	O
Manner	O
meet	O
together	O
about	O
one	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Benson	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
did	O
strive	O
to	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
Goods	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
three	O
Hundred	O
Pounds	O
;	O
and	O
for	O
assaulting	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Benson	I-pers
with	O
a	O
drawn	O
Sword	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
conspiring	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Cunningham	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
the	O
Wife	O
and	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Benson	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Benson	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
17th	O
of	O
November	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
to	O
my	O
Office	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
Letter	O
directed	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
very	O
well	O
read	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
it	O
related	O
to	O
some	O
unwarrantable	O
Proceedings	O
in	O
my	O
Family	O
;	O
and	O
going	O
home	O
about	O
5	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
Wife	O
's	O
two	O
Sisters	O
,	O
then	O
asked	O
the	O
Maid	O
where	O
her	O
Mistress	O
was	O
,	O
she	O
answered	O
,	O
gone	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Middleton	O
's	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Middleton	O
's	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
Dine	O
at	O
home	O
that	O
Day	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
called	O
there	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Cunningham	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
Morning	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
Word	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
come	O
home	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
came	O
home	O
sooner	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Stables	O
saw	O
two	O
strange	O
Fellows	O
:	O
And	O
there	O
used	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
many	O
Irishmen	O
about	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
ordered	O
that	O
no	O
Body	O
should	O
come	O
there	O
without	O
my	O
Knowledge	O
;	O
my	O
Wife	O
complained	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
strange	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
nor	O
her	O
Sisters	O
must	O
have	O
no	O
Body	O
come	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
stay	O
'd	O
at	O
home	O
all	O
Day	O
on	O
Sunday	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Supper	O
with	O
my	O
Wife	O
and	O
her	O
Sister	O
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
my	O
Groom	O
,	O
desired	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
my	O
self	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
murthered	O
to	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Stable	O
I	O
should	O
find	O
Mary	B-pers
Walthoe	I-pers
,	O
my	O
Wife	O
's	O
Maid	O
who	O
would	O
tell	O
me	O
more	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
murthered	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
Mistress	O
had	O
a	O
Pistol	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
now	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
Cloaths	O
were	O
all	O
packed	O
up	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
for	O
her	O
going	O
away	O
between	O
Twelve	O
and	O
Two	O
:	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
packt	O
up	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
my	O
Coachman	O
,	O
Richard	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
stand	O
by	O
me	O
?	O
He	O
answered	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
to	O
desire	O
his	O
assistance	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
my	O
own	O
Pistols	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
carried	O
away	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Cunningham	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
sent	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Harcourt	O
of	O
the	O
Crown	O
Office	O
,	O
and	O
begg	O
'd	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
immediately	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Parlour	O
,	O
where	O
was	O
my	O
Mother	O
,	O
Sisters	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
seized	O
a	O
Pistol	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
the	O
Story	O
,	O
and	O
fetched	O
her	O
packt	O
up	O
Cloths	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
sent	O
into	O
Shoreditch	O
to	O
Robert	O
Dug	O
's	O
,	O
desiring	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
my	O
Assistance	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
bring	O
what	O
Arms	O
he	O
could	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
murthered	O
:	O
Robert	B-pers
Dags	I-pers
came	O
about	O
one	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Maids	O
I	O
sent	O
to	O
watch	O
above	O
Stairs	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
come	O
;	O
and	O
presently	O
after	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Noise	O
at	O
my	O
Door	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
some	O
Body	O
had	O
been	O
unlocking	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
rush	O
'd	O
our	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
about	O
eight	O
Foot	O
from	O
my	O
Door	O
,	O
making	O
haste	O
over	O
the	O
Ways	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
and	O
seized	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Collar	O
,	O
and	O
turning	O
his	O
Face	O
to	O
a	O
Light	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
pushed	O
him	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
Villain	O
I	O
wanted	O
,	O
(	O
had	O
it	O
been	O
Cunninghams	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
shot	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Pistol	O
charged	O
in	O
my	O
Hand	O
)	O
turning	O
back	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
thought	O
,	O
saw	O
Cunningham	O
go	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
down	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
him	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
my	O
Coachman	O
had	O
seized	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
come	O
back	O
to	O
my	O
Door	O
and	O
drawn	O
his	O
Sword	O
then	O
he	O
talked	O
of	O
having	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
the	O
little	O
Man	O
in	O
black	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
before	O
.	O
Pheby	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ashton	I-pers
a	O
Porter	O
lodged	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
little	O
Girl	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
,	O
who	O
hearing	O
Ashton	O
tell	O
his	O
Wife	O
what	O
Letters	O
he	O
carried	O
to	O
'Squire	O
Benson	O
's	O
Lady	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
Mr.	O
Cunninghams	O
visited	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
at	O
Supper	O
there	O
one	O
Night	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Benson	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
they	O
put	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
Closet	O
;	O
the	O
Girl	O
telling	O
this	O
Story	O
,	O
induced	O
this	O
Deponent	O
to	O
send	O
Mr.	O
Benson	O
the	O
Letter	O
he	O
received	O
concerning	O
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
Family	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Walthoe	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
knew	O
of	O
Mr.	O
-	O
Cunningham	O
's	O
coming	O
to	O
her	O
Mistress	O
a	O
Nights	O
after	O
her	O
Master	O
was	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Cunningham	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
intended	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
take	O
away	O
her	O
Mistress	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
Hours	O
of	O
12	O
and	O
2	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
loaded	O
Pistol	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
Mistress	O
at	O
her	O
own	O
Desire	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
Resistance	O
he	O
would	O
gag	O
and	O
tie	O
all	O
the	O
Servants	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
murthered	O
them	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
never	O
a	O
Servant	O
at	O
home	O
at	O
present	O
,	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Russel	O
was	O
not	O
come	O
home	O
from	O
hiring	O
the	O
Yacht	O
that	O
was	O
to	O
carry	O
her	O
Mistress	O
away	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
this	O
Deponent	O
was	O
very	O
uneasy	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
there	O
should	O
be	O
Murther	O
committed	O
in	O
Case	O
of	O
Resistance	O
;	O
and	O
intended	O
to	O
acquaint	O
her	O
Master	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
having	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
the	O
Coachman	O
and	O
Groom	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
how	O
the	O
delivered	O
her	O
Mistress	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Canningham	O
;	O
which	O
Pistol	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
She	O
further	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
knew	O
her	O
Mistress	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
had	O
frequently	O
brought	O
Letters	O
for	O
her	O
Mistress	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Cunningham	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
our	O
House	O
often	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
down	O
to	O
Tunbridge	O
on	O
Mr.	O
Cunningham	O
's	O
Account	O
,	O
and	O
spoke	O
to	O
my	O
Mistress	O
there	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Delauny	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
made	O
the	O
Pistol	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Servant	O
sold	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Cunningham	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
Mr.	O
Russel	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
Mr.	O
Cunningham	O
's	O
Companion	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
his	O
Servant	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Keneday	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Knowledge	O
I	O
had	O
of	O
this	O
Affair	O
was	O
but	O
about	O
a	O
Week	O
before	O
this	O
happened	O
;	O
for	O
going	O
into	O
Hertfordshire	O
with	O
my	O
Mistress	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Benson	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
we	O
came	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Crown	O
at	O
Ware	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
strange	O
Horses	O
in	O
the	O
Stable	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
Supper-time	O
,	O
sitting	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
one	O
Clouds	O
,	O
who	O
I	O
mistrusted	O
was	O
Cunningham	O
's	O
Servant	O
;	O
and	O
we	O
drank	O
Wine	O
together	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
pay	O
any	O
Thing	O
:	O
In	O
the	O
Morning	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
Mistress	O
forward	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
baited	O
at	O
the	O
Old	O
Bell	O
at	O
Edmonton	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
we	O
got	O
there	O
comes	O
Mr.	O
Cunningham	O
and	O
Clouds	O
;	O
Cunningham	O
goes	O
in	O
a	O
Doors	O
,	O
and	O
Clouds	O
comes	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
we	O
drank	O
Wine	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ordered	O
the	O
Foot-Boy	O
might	O
not	O
come	O
into	O
our	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
pay	O
any	O
Thing	O
:	O
When	O
I	O
got	O
upon	O
my	O
Box	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
10	O
Shillings	O
,	O
I	O
thanked	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
for	O
.	O
And	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
Mary	B-pers
Walthoe	I-pers
carry	O
out	O
several	O
Bundles	O
on	O
Sunday	O
,	O
I	O
threatned	O
her	O
.	O
He	O
further	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Time	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Walthoe	I-pers
told	O
us	O
they	O
would	O
come	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Ashton	O
the	O
Porter	O
by	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
out	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
a	O
Night	O
?	O
And	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
,	O
he	O
thought	O
;	O
just	O
after	O
he	O
left	O
him	O
,	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Clock	O
struck	O
One	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
in	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
before	O
the	O
Waits	O
came	O
and	O
played	O
at	O
our	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Cook	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
placed	O
in	O
the	O
Drawing-Room	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Men	O
looking	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Iron	O
Rails	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
I	O
saw	O
several	O
People	O
,	O
but	O
knew	O
none	O
but	O
Russel	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
there	O
were	O
four	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
Waits	O
.	O
That	O
Russel	O
,	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
threatened	O
Mr.	O
Benson	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
had	O
Fire	O
Arms	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
him	O
surrender	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
seized	O
him	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
not	O
to	O
know	O
Mrs.	O
Benson	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
Window	O
on	O
the	O
Iron	O
Rails	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
,	O
Who	O
is	O
the	O
Lady	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
save	O
her	O
Honour	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
her	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Ramshaw	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
Mr.	O
Cunningham	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
see	O
Mr.	O
Russel	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
black	O
Cloaths	O
on	O
and	O
white	O
Stockings	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
walking	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
the	O
Street	O
twice	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
once	O
by	O
their	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Rails	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
her	O
Mistress	O
got	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Parlour	O
Window	O
upon	O
the	O
Iron	O
Rails	O
,	O
Russel	O
said	O
,	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
,	O
what	O
makes	O
you	O
out	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
make	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
you	O
sha	O
n't	O
be	O
hurt	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Hand	O
from	O
her	O
Mistress	O
's	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Coachman	O
took	O
her	O
down	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Benson	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Brother	O
)	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
My	O
Brother	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
Shoreditch	O
for	O
Robert	B-pers
Dag	I-pers
,	O
and	O
we	O
were	O
come	O
out	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
before	O
this	O
happened	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
cross	O
the	O
Way	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
Mrs.	O
Benson	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
Rails	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
his	O
Sword	O
drawn	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
first	O
that	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dags	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
see	O
Mistress	O
Benson	O
on	O
the	O
Rails	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
save	O
her	O
Honour	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
his	O
Sword	O
drawn	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Keet	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
packt	O
up	O
and	O
a	O
Diamond	O
Buckle	O
had	O
been	O
sent	O
before	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Cunningham	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
sister	O
designed	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
that	O
Night	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Cunningham	O
,	O
who	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
with	O
my	O
Sister	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
once	O
in	O
the	O
Chamber	O
where	O
my	O
Sister	O
lay	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
ordered	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
Times	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Benson	O
's	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
delivered	O
Letters	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Cunningham	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Letters	O
read	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
contained	O
professions	O
of	O
Love	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
never	O
delivered	O
any	O
Message	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Walthoe	I-pers
;	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
at	O
Tunbridge	O
at	O
my	O
Sister	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Cunningham	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Benson	O
's	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
but	O
once	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
return	O
him	O
Thanks	O
for	O
some	O
Favour	O
done	O
him	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Hammond	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
the	O
Monday	O
before	O
this	O
happened	O
,	O
and	O
agreed	O
with	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
Lodging	O
for	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
that	O
would	O
be	O
private	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
above	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Persons	O
come	O
to	O
him	O
:	O
And	O
I	O
insisted	O
that	O
no	O
Woman	O
should	O
come	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
being	O
cautious	O
in	O
that	O
respect	O
for	O
the	O
Reputation	O
of	O
my	O
House	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
after	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
came	O
,	O
he	O
invited	O
me	O
to	O
Dine	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Debt	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
any	O
Bailiff	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
be	O
with	O
him	O
every	O
Night	O
.	O
She	O
swore	O
she	O
was	O
awaked	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Sleep	O
at	O
One	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
by	O
the	O
opening	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
she	O
put	O
on	O
her	O
Cloaths	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
cloud	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Entry	O
,	O
and	O
Cunningham	O
and	O
Ashton	O
above	O
Stairs	O
.	O
Margaret	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Hammond	O
's	O
Maid	O
swore	O
.	O
About	O
One	O
o'Clock	O
she	O
let	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
House	O
,	O
that	O
Ashton	O
the	O
Potter	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
House	O
till	O
after	O
Two	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
positively	O
contradicted	O
by	O
Keneday	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Benson	O
's	O
Coachman	O
)	O
and	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Cunningham	O
and	O
Cloud	O
his	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
Ashton	O
were	O
all	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
their	O
House	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
Time	O
of	O
the	O
Disturbance	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
.	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Gother	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Cunningham	O
was	O
indebted	O
to	O
several	O
Persons	O
very	O
considerably	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
advised	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Holland	O
about	O
3	O
Weeks	O
before	O
this	O
happened	O
,	O
for	O
his	O
own	O
Safety	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Benson	O
was	O
examin	O
'd	O
by	O
Consent	O
of	O
both	O
Sides	O
,	O
she	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
positive	O
that	O
Mr	O
Russel	O
was	O
privy	O
to	O
her	O
going	O
away	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Cunningham	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
resolved	O
to	O
carry	O
her	O
away	O
as	O
had	O
been	O
mentioned	O
;	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
name	O
particularly	O
who	O
should	O
assist	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
Iron	O
Rails	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
said	O
no	O
Body	O
should	O
hurt	O
her	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
brought	O
Letters	O
and	O
Messages	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Cunningham	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
her	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
several	O
Times	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Cunningham	O
,	O
at	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
;	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Hammond	O
see	O
her	O
and	O
knew	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Waits	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
one	O
of	O
their	O
Company	O
had	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
given	O
them	O
to	O
play	O
a	O
Tune	O
under	O
Mr.	O
Benson	O
's	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
repulsed	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Benson	O
's	O
Servants	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prissoner	O
followed	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
them	O
go	O
back	O
and	O
play	O
there	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Anne	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
72	O
Calve-Skins	O
,	O
Value	O
14	O
Pounds	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Morocco	O
Leather	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
40	O
Shillings	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Biggins	I-pers
,	O
Octob	O
.	O
29	O
.	O
and	O
Francis	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Leather	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Heymore	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
pursue	O
Thomas	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Bull	O
at	O
Dunstable	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Room	O
up	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
in	O
Cranbone	O
Alley	O
,	O
his	O
Brother	O
lodging	O
at	O
next	O
Door	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
Leads	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
at	O
several	O
Times	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Biggins	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
Pursuit	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
to	O
us	O
how	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
most	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
Waggon	O
going	O
to	O
Chester	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
having	O
secured	O
him	O
we	O
pursued	O
the	O
Waggon	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
by	O
his	O
Direction	O
:	O
There	O
were	O
others	O
that	O
corroborated	O
this	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
in	O
Court	O
but	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Brother	O
Francis	O
was	O
entirely	O
ignorant	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
Francis	O
Morris	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Thomas	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Newel	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
3	O
Guineas	O
,	O
a	O
half	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
Pounds	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
James	B-pers
Grimes	I-pers
,	O
Decemb	O
.	O
12	O
.	O
James	O
Grimes	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Tindel	I-pers
's	O
in	O
Bridge's-street	B-place
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
Room	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Quarterns	O
of	O
Gin	O
,	O
I	O
pulled	O
out	O
my	O
Money	O
before	O
my	O
Sister	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Sister	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
me	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
drank	O
till	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
Nod	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
lost	O
my	O
Money	O
.	O
His	O
Sister	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
asked	O
my	O
Brother	O
to	O
treat	O
her	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
consented	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
Brother	O
and	O
the	O
young	O
Woman	O
together	O
about	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
my	O
Brother	O
said	O
his	O
Money	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Grimes	O
came	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Tindal	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
not	O
within	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Back	O
Room	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
they	O
bolted	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
was	O
together	O
near	O
an	O
Hour	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Crouch	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
lodged	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
drinking	O
that	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
very	O
merry	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
two	O
Crown	O
Pieces	O
,	O
four	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
Half	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
other	O
Money	O
in	O
her	O
Apron	O
,	O
or	O
something	O
that	O
sounded	O
like	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
snapt	O
her	O
Fingers	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
bit	O
a	O
Man	O
out	O
of	O
so	O
much	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
live	O
,	O
where	O
some	O
B	O
-	O
s	O
would	O
starve	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Patrick	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Steel	O
Saws	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Beaton	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
2	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Frances	B-pers
Hand	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Uxbridge	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
Pounds	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Darey	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
21	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Randall	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Davies	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Murfey	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Parish	O
;	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
seventeen	O
Yards	O
and	O
a	O
Half	O
of	O
printed	O
Linnen	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
thirteen	O
Ells	O
of	O
Garlick	O
Holland	O
,	O
value	O
17	O
Shillings	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
,	O
January	O
the	O
10th	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Shop	O
about	O
4	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
some	O
printed	O
Linnen	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
my	O
Wife	O
,	O
being	O
engaged	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
;	O
afterwards	O
I	O
came	O
and	O
relieved	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
very	O
difficult	O
,	O
as	O
most	O
such	O
Customers	O
are	O
,	O
I	O
shewed	O
them	O
some	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
liked	O
the	O
Fancy	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Cloth	O
was	O
too	O
thin	O
.	O
Randall	O
said	O
they	O
should	O
do	O
no	O
good	O
to	O
Night	O
,	O
so	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
Murfey	O
followed	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
Wife	O
I	O
did	O
n't	O
like	O
the	O
Customers	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
amongst	O
my	O
Goods	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
printed	O
Linnen	O
:	O
Murfey	O
came	O
back	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
one	O
Penny	O
a	O
Yard	O
more	O
;	O
whereupon	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
and	O
secured	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Randall	O
standing	O
over	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
who	O
observing	O
me	O
coming	O
towards	O
her	O
,	O
avoided	O
me	O
by	O
going	O
into	O
an	O
House	O
;	O
I	O
afterwards	O
meeting	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
stopt	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
Goods	O
I	O
had	O
then	O
mist	O
in	O
her	O
Custody	O
;	O
at	O
which	O
Time	O
another	O
Piece	O
dropt	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
a	O
Boy	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
took	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
Goods	O
also	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Mob	O
arising	O
,	O
some	O
Body	O
said	O
they	O
believed	O
she	O
had	O
more	O
Goods	O
about	O
her	O
:	O
However	O
,	O
having	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
her	O
and	O
Murfey	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
had	O
them	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
;	O
when	O
as	O
Randall	O
was	O
stepping	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
she	O
chanced	O
to	O
drop	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Garlick	O
Holland	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
mine	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
but	O
small	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
having	O
shewed	O
them	O
none	O
when	O
in	O
my	O
Shop	O
;	O
but	O
looking	O
upon	O
it	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
own	O
Mark	O
on	O
it	O
:	O
But	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
he	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
indisposed	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
take	O
their	O
Examination	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
them	O
committed	O
by	O
another	O
Justice	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Devon	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
my	O
Father	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
Mr.	O
Atkinson	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
I	O
and	O
another	O
stopped	O
Randall	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
,	O
she	O
answered	O
what	O
's	O
that	O
to	O
you	O
;	O
at	O
which	O
Time	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Goods	O
drop	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Davies	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
found	O
the	O
Linnen	O
he	O
had	O
miss	O
'd	O
upon	O
Randall	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
the	O
other	O
Piece	O
which	O
dropt	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hooker	I-pers
the	O
Constable	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
having	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Orders	O
to	O
secure	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
had	O
them	O
before	O
Justice	O
Railton	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
observ	O
'd	O
Randall	O
to	O
have	O
something	O
under	O
her	O
Petticoats	O
very	O
stiff	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
happened	O
to	O
prove	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Garlick	O
Holland	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
.	O
Randall	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fast	O
and	O
said	O
Murfey	O
was	O
innocent	O
.	O
Murfey	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
thus	O
alledged	O
.	O
I	O
having	O
the	O
Curiosity	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Rabbit	O
Woman	O
,	O
Randall	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
she	O
wanted	O
some	O
printed	O
Linnen	O
;	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
buy	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
altogether	O
ignorant	O
of	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Whole	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
Murfey	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Randall	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Steel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
Chapman	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
being	O
declared	O
Bankrupt	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
Surrender	O
himself	O
according	O
to	O
Notice	O
for	O
that	O
Purpose	O
given	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
conforming	O
himself	O
to	O
the	O
Direction	O
of	O
the	O
Statute	O
in	O
that	O
Case	O
made	O
and	O
provided	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
legally	O
declared	O
a	O
Bankrupt	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Notice	O
for	O
Surrendering	O
himself	O
was	O
not	O
duly	O
served	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Levy	B-pers
Joshua	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
value	O
four	O
Pounds	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Gabriel	I-pers
Bowman	I-pers
,	O
Novemb	O
.	O
14	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
and	O
Ruben	B-pers
Winfield	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
John	I-place
's	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
with	O
Edward	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
a	O
Lighter	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
Pounds	O
,	O
and	O
Coals	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
Value	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
George	I-place
's	I-place
Hanover-Square	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Hats	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Mackweaver	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wooll	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
Shillings	O
,	O
a	O
Fustian	O
Frock	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Radford	I-pers
,	O
Decemb	O
.	O
18	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
,	O
Jun	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
John	I-place
's	I-place
Hackney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Purse	O
,	O
3	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
seven	O
Pounds	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Surteys	I-pers
,	O
Octob	O
.	O
20	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Husey	I-pers
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Bivan	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
8	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
and	O
a	O
Holland	O
Frock	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Dye	I-pers
,	O
Decemb	O
.	O
24	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
Bivan	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Husey	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Black-Fryers	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
7	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Silver	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Moyden	I-pers
,	O
Decemb	O
.	O
31	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
Shillings	O
and	O
10	O
Pence	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Copes	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
eleven	O
Pounds	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
,	O
Decemb	O
31	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Dunn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Bartholomew	I-place
,	I-place
near	O
the	B-place
Royal	I-place
Exchange	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
an	O
Assault	O
on	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Hurst	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
and	O
Carnally	O
knowing	O
her	O
against	O
her	O
Will	O
,	O
Sept.	O
29	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Foulks	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Diaper	O
Table-cloth	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Linnen	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
6	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4s	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Forse	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
one	O
Moidore	O
,	O
5	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
Half	O
Guinea	O
,	O
from	O
Francis	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
Decemb	O
.	O
9	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Porch	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
9	O
Yards	O
of	O
Callico	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Rice	I-pers
,	O
Decemb	O
.	O
22	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Chiswell	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Damsel	I-pers
,	O
Decem	O
.	O
10	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Darby	B-pers
Eley	I-pers
and	O
Susanna	B-pers
Hutchinson	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Silk	O
and	O
Cotton	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
12	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Petticoats	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
January	O
7	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Yaul	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
Pounds	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Chaldron	O
of	O
Coals	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
.	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Lye	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Quart	O
Pots	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Hercules	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
August	O
10	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cousins	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Mackmillion	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
20	O
Shillings	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Godfrey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Suits	O
of	O
Head-cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Buck	I-pers
,	O
Decemb	O
.	O
15	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
ended	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgement	O
as	O
follows	O
:	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
5.	O
John	B-pers
Margan	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Marley	O
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Hains	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Roudall	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Newl	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Randall	O
,	O
pleaded	O
her	O
Belly	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
being	O
impanelled	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
her	O
Pregnant	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
2.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Preston	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
.	O
Transportation	O
26.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Travers	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Chous	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Antly	I-pers
,	O
Micheal	O
Auderson	O
,	O
Lake	O
Wall	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Foulks	I-pers
,	O
Patrick	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Gold	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Forbes	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Cope	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Husey	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
