TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KINGS	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX.HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
.	O
During	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
the	O
Rt	O
.	O
Honble	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Baylis	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
2d	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
1729	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
E.	O
Symon	O
,	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
,	O
and	O
Sold	O
by	O
J.	O
Roberts	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Oxford	O
Arms	O
,	O
in	O
Warwick	O
Lane	O
.	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
For	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
AND	O
ON	O
The	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
4th	O
,	O
5th	O
,	O
6th	O
,	O
and	O
7th	O
,	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
1728	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Second	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
ROBERT	B-pers
BAYLIS	I-pers
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
;	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Page	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
Raby	O
,	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
;	O
with	O
other	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
aforesaid	O
;	O
Together	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Field	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Yarroway	I-pers
,	O
Drew	B-pers
Drury	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Ives	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Farrow	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Siddal	I-pers
,	O
Brandon	B-pers
Hatch	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stent	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Beck	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Duffin	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Brightliff	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Welsh	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
,	O
Ambrose	B-pers
Stevenson	I-pers
,	O
Cornelius	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
,	O
Josiah	B-pers
Wallis	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Witherington	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fogg	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Rawlingson	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
black	O
Ribband	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
white	O
Forret	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nowell	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nowell	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Oath	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pickering	I-pers
,	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Shop	O
and	O
bought	O
several	O
Remnants	O
of	O
Ribband	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
missing	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
fetched	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
who	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Leaden	O
Weights	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Sceney	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Goodfellow	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
fall	O
with	O
the	O
Weights	O
near	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
presently	O
after	O
he	O
being	O
stopp	O
'd	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
people	O
coming	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
given	O
him	O
by	O
a	O
Man	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
only	O
an	O
idle	O
Tale	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bow	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Thetford	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
walking	O
along	O
Cheapside	B-place
he	O
was	O
inform	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
pursuing	O
him	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Kennet	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
30	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
Copper	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Franco	I-pers
,	O
Moses	B-pers
Franco	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Jacob	B-pers
Franco	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
Porter	O
at	O
the	O
Keys	O
,	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
thence	O
in	O
a	O
clandestine	O
Manner	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Broadstreet	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Tidmarsh	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
two	O
Girls	O
having	O
Din	O
'd	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Spoon	O
,	O
they	O
suspected	O
him	O
or	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
stolen	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
Girls	O
up	O
,	O
who	O
brought	O
out	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
yet	O
he	O
for	O
some	O
Time	O
denied	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
length	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
directed	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Spoon	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
appearing	O
by	O
the	O
Mark	O
and	O
Number	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Paul	B-pers
Hubbard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bottolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hardey	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
under	O
Pretence	O
of	O
wanting	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Buckles	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
shewing	O
him	O
several	O
pair	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
two	O
pair	O
into	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
conceal	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
Method	O
they	O
call	O
Palming	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
look	O
'd	O
very	O
narrowly	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Buckles	O
in	O
the	O
Lining	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Coat	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
Pair	O
he	O
before	O
conceaeld	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Gowen	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bottolph	I-place
without	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Kedger	I-pers
the	O
22d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
3	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Camblet	O
Coat	O
,	O
two	O
Suits	O
of	O
Finners	O
,	O
a	O
black	O
Silk	O
Hood	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
six	O
Suits	O
of	O
Night	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
eight	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
:	O
But	O
as	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
plain	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
only	O
guilty	O
of	O
single	O
Felony	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Taverner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Gregory	I-place
's	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Camblet	O
Cloaks	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Damask	O
Gown	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Bellows	O
,	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Bed	O
Curtains	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Newbury	I-pers
;	O
and	O
it	O
plainly	O
appearing	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
found	O
their	O
Goods	O
by	O
the	O
Direction	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
at	O
several	O
Places	O
were	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
single	O
Felony	O
on	O
each	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Ives	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Uxbridge	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Walker	B-pers
Norwood	I-pers
,	O
which	O
appearing	O
very	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Rodham	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Squire	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Prescot	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
6	O
Books	O
,	O
entituled	O
,	O
Chamberlain	O
's	O
present	O
State	O
of	O
Great-Britain	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
very	O
weak	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
4	O
pound	O
Brass	O
Weight	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Hepsibe	B-pers
Mirlea	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Patrick	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
30	O
Yards	O
of	O
fine	O
Cotton	O
Check	O
,	O
Value	O
40	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Otway	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Minnis	I-pers
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
the	O
Breadth	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
4	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languish	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
November	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
slaying	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Mr	O
William	B-pers
Minnis	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Turner	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
this	O
unhappy	O
Accident	O
happen	O
'd	O
,	O
himself	O
with	O
Captain	O
Otway	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
together	O
at	O
the	O
Cherry-Tree	O
in	O
Plumbtree-street	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
staid	O
till	O
One	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
ask	O
'd	O
them	O
if	O
they	O
should	O
not	O
Drink	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Wine	O
to	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Health	O
,	O
that	O
several	O
Houses	O
were	O
propos	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
length	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Feather	O
's	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
it	O
was	O
much	O
against	O
the	O
Mind	O
of	O
Captain	O
Otway	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
saying	O
they	O
should	O
have	O
bad	O
Wine	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
Deponent	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
took	O
him	O
under	O
the	O
Arms	O
,	O
and	O
oblig	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
there	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
which	O
Captain	O
Otway	O
said	O
was	O
bad	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
good	O
;	O
that	O
Captain	O
Otway	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
scrub	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
fit	O
for	O
none	O
but	O
Scrubs	O
;	O
that	O
presently	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
some	O
Time	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
seem	O
'd	O
as	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
quarreling	O
,	O
but	O
then	O
both	O
of	O
them	O
seem	O
'd	O
satisfied	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
then	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Wine	O
;	O
that	O
Captain	O
Otway	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
Scrub	O
and	O
Coward	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
no	O
Coward	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
Soldier	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
Deponent	O
falling	O
asleep	O
behind	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
any	O
more	O
of	O
their	O
Proceedings	O
that	O
Night	O
:	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
both	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
perceive	O
any	O
Malice	O
between	O
them	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
who	O
keeps	O
the	O
Feather	B-place
's	I-place
Tavern	I-place
in	O
Drury-lane	B-place
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
drank	O
3	O
Pints	O
of	O
Wine	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
had	O
drank	O
only	O
one	O
Pint	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
paid	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
go	O
,	O
saying	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Turner	O
should	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Scrub	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Deponent	O
would	O
have	O
persuaded	O
him	O
to	O
stay	O
,	O
fearing	O
there	O
might	O
be	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
Quarrel	O
,	O
but	O
go	O
and	O
get	O
him	O
a	O
Coach	O
or	O
a	O
Chair	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
sent	O
a	O
Drawer	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Drawer	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
soon	O
return	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
Captain	O
Otway	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
drink	O
another	O
Glass	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
out	O
again	O
and	O
left	O
Mr.	O
Turner	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
heard	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ducas	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
followed	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Feather	O
's	O
Tavern	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
saw	O
none	O
of	O
what	O
follow	O
'd	O
after	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
through	O
Banbury	O
Court	O
in	O
Long	O
Acre	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
their	O
Swords	O
drawn	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
on	O
his	O
Knees	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
standing	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
very	O
Dirty	O
,	O
and	O
seem	O
'd	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
both	O
begg	O
'd	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
leave	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
said	O
he	O
fear	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
hurt	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
a	O
Watchman	O
coming	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
both	O
very	O
readily	O
delivered	O
him	O
their	O
Swords	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
put	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
and	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Mufled	O
Bear	O
in	O
Covent-Garden	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Captain	O
begg	O
'd	O
an	O
able	O
Surgeon	O
might	O
be	O
provided	O
for	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
received	O
two	O
Wounds	O
in	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
in	O
his	O
Face	O
;	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
following	O
this	O
Deponent	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
Drink	O
was	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
seem	O
'd	O
very	O
sorry	O
when	O
he	O
heard	O
that	O
Captain	O
Otway	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
New	O
Prison	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
the	O
Watchman	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
both	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
were	O
upon	O
their	O
Legs	O
,	O
bemoaning	O
themselves	O
,	O
and	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
being	O
then	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
Dirty	O
,	O
their	O
Hats	O
and	O
Wigs	O
laying	O
at	O
a	O
considerable	O
Distance	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
both	O
surrender	O
'd	O
their	O
Swords	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
begg	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
might	O
be	O
taken	O
Care	O
of	O
by	O
an	O
able	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
got	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
into	O
a	O
Chair	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
provided	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
begg	O
'd	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
Care	O
of	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
four	O
Guineas	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
careful	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Coldham	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
dress	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Wound	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
;	O
that	O
Captain	O
Otway	O
gave	O
him	O
four	O
Guineas	O
to	O
take	O
Care	O
of	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
dress	O
'd	O
two	O
Wounds	O
in	O
Captain	O
Otway	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
in	O
his	O
Face	O
.	O
Captain	O
Otway	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Malice	O
against	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Banbury-Court	O
lay	O
in	O
his	O
way	O
Home	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
Way	O
of	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
their	O
Quarrelling	O
.	O
Several	O
Persons	O
of	O
Honour	O
appear	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
an	O
extraordinary	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
peaceable	O
,	O
honest	O
,	O
good-natur	O
'd	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Dart	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Pedder	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
's	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
;	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Pedder	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Dart	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Pedder	I-pers
,	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Tankard	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
fell	O
into	O
Discourse	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
another	O
kept	O
his	O
Wife	O
in	O
Discourse	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Third	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Tankard	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
swore	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
very	O
rudely	O
before	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
miss	O
'd	O
it	O
they	O
pursu	O
'd	O
and	O
took	O
Russel	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
be	O
easy	O
they	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
hang	O
Dart	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Pedder	I-pers
.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
there	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
perceived	O
Russel	O
kept	O
the	O
Landlord	O
in	O
Discourse	O
,	O
Pedder	O
kept	O
the	O
Landlady	O
in	O
Discourse	O
,	O
and	O
Dart	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Tankard	O
:	O
The	O
Fact	O
likewise	O
appeared	O
plain	O
by	O
several	O
other	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
particularly	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
offered	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
committed	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
them	O
a	O
Bond	O
of	O
40	O
l.	O
not	O
to	O
prosecute	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
procure	O
his	O
Tankard	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
William	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Dart	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Pedder	I-pers
,	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
Shillings	O
each	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Mary	B-pers
Pedder	I-pers
,	O
nor	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
her	O
Name	O
mentioned	O
by	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
North	I-pers
and	O
Ann	B-pers
North	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Chamber-pot	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Timothy	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
plain	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Bentley	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
with	O
others	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
privately	O
steal	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
Ten	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Moreton	I-pers
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
fix	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
several	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
to	O
a	O
Funeral	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
his	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
Maid	O
,	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
return	O
'd	O
he	O
found	O
his	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
his	O
Maid	O
gone	O
,	O
his	O
Man	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Candle	O
burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Socket	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
fear	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
found	O
it	O
so	O
;	O
It	O
further	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
Justice	O
Blagney	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
Fowler	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bottolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
40	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Paul	B-pers
Osbourn	I-pers
;	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
plain	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Emery	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
two	O
Aprons	O
,	O
three	O
Shirts	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Bernard	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
and	O
Walter	B-pers
Beal	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Kellet	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Rambet	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Clasps	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Colonel	O
Henry	B-pers
Cornwell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Elliot	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
for	O
Money	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Doctor	O
's	O
Dues	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
Hammer	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
B	O
-	O
h	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
murder	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
fearing	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
her	O
some	O
Mischief	O
,	O
bade	O
him	O
get	O
away	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
taken	O
,	O
that	O
soon	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
who	O
stood	O
below	O
to	O
receive	O
the	O
Doctor	O
's	O
Dues	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
got	O
in	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
by	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
search	O
'd	O
and	O
the	O
Silver	O
Clasps	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Buroe	O
above	O
Stairs	O
;	O
his	O
being	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
confessing	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
Silver	O
Clasps	O
out	O
of	O
Colonel	O
Cornwell	O
's	O
Buroe	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Chedrue	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
17	O
joint	O
Bearers	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Tops	O
and	O
Bottoms	O
of	O
Mother	O
of	O
Pearl	O
Snuff-Boxes	O
,	O
with	O
5	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Silver	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Dubeck	I-pers
,	O
which	O
appearing	O
plain	O
by	O
the	O
Deposition	O
of	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Plow-Coulter	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Rooks	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Farmer	O
,	O
keeps	O
a	O
Boy	O
to	O
scare	O
away	O
the	O
Crows	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Boy	O
inform	O
'd	O
him	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Plow-Coulter	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
Information	O
he	O
pursu	O
'd	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Coulter	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
the	O
Scare	O
Crow	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
Plow-Coulter	O
from	O
the	O
Plow	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
about	O
9	O
or	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
in	O
at	O
his	O
own	O
Door	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
snatch	O
'd	O
his	O
Hat	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
running	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
soon	O
apprehended	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bease	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
pursu	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
flung	O
it	O
away	O
soon	O
after	O
,	O
whereupon	O
this	O
Deponent	O
secur	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
James	O
Glonfield	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
off	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
pursuing	O
him	O
,	O
saw	O
him	O
fall	O
over	O
a	O
Heap	O
of	O
Rubbish	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
fling	O
the	O
Hat	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ailce	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
laced	O
Pinners	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Katherine	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	O
Gurney	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Ailce	O
Young	O
being	O
a	O
poor	O
Woman	O
,	O
that	O
cry	O
'd	O
Rags	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
having	O
some	O
old	O
Rags	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
her	O
in	O
,	O
designing	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
Mary	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
Sister	I-pers
,	O
and	O
bade	O
her	O
come	O
in	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
Deponent	O
having	O
Occasion	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
bade	O
her	O
keep	O
down	O
;	O
however	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Assurance	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Deponent	O
being	O
inform	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Stairs	O
were	O
wet	O
,	O
suspected	O
Mary	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Head-Cloaths	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Pan	O
of	O
Water	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
very	O
Stair-Case	O
on	O
which	O
Mary	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
stood	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
not	O
being	O
plain	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Alice	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Mary	O
Walker	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
15	O
Yards	O
of	O
Lace	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Hatch	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
Pretence	O
of	O
wanting	O
some	O
Edging	O
but	O
she	O
not	O
being	O
a	O
ready	O
Money	O
Customer	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
not	O
knowing	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
expect	O
Credit	O
,	O
yet	O
willing	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Dealer	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
Way	O
,	O
she	O
artificially	O
palm	O
'd	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Lace	O
upon	O
a	O
Card	O
,	O
but	O
conveying	O
it	O
into	O
her	O
Bosom	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
seen	O
by	O
a	O
Lad	O
next	O
Door	O
,	O
who	O
pursu	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Lace	O
in	O
her	O
Bosom	O
.	O
She	O
pretended	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
it	O
dropp	O
'd	O
into	O
her	O
Bosom	O
by	O
Accident	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
coming	O
back	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
apprehended	O
:	O
but	O
as	O
one	O
Part	O
of	O
her	O
Defence	O
was	O
impossible	O
,	O
the	O
Card	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
very	O
improbable	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
hurrying	O
on	O
a	O
contrary	O
Way	O
from	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Mug	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sturgis	I-pers
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sturgis	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
out	O
of	O
Business	O
,	O
he	O
invited	O
him	O
to	O
Dinner	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
readily	O
accepted	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
Dinner	O
,	O
was	O
as	O
ready	O
to	O
assist	O
in	O
serving	O
the	O
Customers	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
;	O
but	O
afterwards	O
a	O
Tankard	O
being	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
remembering	O
he	O
lost	O
a	O
Pint	O
Pot	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
assisted	O
him	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
both	O
the	O
Pint	O
Pot	O
and	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
obstinately	O
denied	O
for	O
some	O
Time	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
length	O
confess	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
Brooks	O
of	O
his	O
Acquaintance	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Tankard	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
in	O
the	O
Entry	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
Brooks	O
afterwards	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
Hole	O
in	O
the	O
Wall	O
below	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
going	O
down	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
in	O
the	O
Hole	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
the	O
Tankard	O
;	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
he	O
likewife	O
confess	O
'd	O
his	O
taking	O
the	O
Pint	O
Pot	O
,	O
and	O
directed	O
them	O
to	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Gibbs	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
sold	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
Mrs.	O
Gibbs	O
confirming	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
for	O
the	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Moor	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Holland	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
Chocolate	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Beedham	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
,	O
junior	O
,	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
reach	O
his	O
Hand	O
over	O
the	O
Grate	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
Chocolate	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
pursu	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
sling	O
the	O
Chocolate	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
got	O
away	O
himself	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
Deponent	O
was	O
too	O
nimble	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
Drunk	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
stand	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
sober	O
enough	O
to	O
run	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hoskins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Mug	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Launch	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
;	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
to	O
warm	O
Small	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Silver	O
Mug	O
as	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
carried	O
to	O
Pawn	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
finding	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Pawnbroker	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
at	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hammond	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Catherine	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Clutterbuck	I-pers
,	O
of	O
White-Chapel	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Dish	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Josiah	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Needham	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
but	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Butterfield	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
8	O
Books	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Manuscripts	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Writer	O
for	O
the	O
late	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	O
Gilbert	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
his	O
Lordship	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Clerk	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
whose	O
House	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Books	O
and	O
the	O
Manuscripts	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
left	O
as	O
a	O
Legacy	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
by	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	O
Gilbert	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
promise	O
not	O
to	O
publish	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
a	O
Key	O
made	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
Manuscripts	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
them	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
House	O
,	O
got	O
Persons	O
to	O
transcribe	O
them	O
for	O
his	O
own	O
private	O
Advantage	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
8	O
Books	O
he	O
pawn	O
'd	O
,	O
of	O
all	O
which	O
he	O
made	O
Confession	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Mathews	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
November	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
one	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Silver	O
hafted	O
Knives	O
,	O
one	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Silver	O
Hafted	O
Forks	O
,	O
two	O
Silver	O
Salvers	O
,	O
a	O
Pepper	O
Box	O
,	O
a	O
Milk	O
Pot	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Boat	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
pieces	O
of	O
Silver	O
Furniture	O
,	O
besides	O
a	O
Cloak	O
,	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Shagreen	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Christopher	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
as	O
his	O
Custom	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
carried	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
Street	O
Door	O
up	O
Stairs	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
left	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
Back	O
Door	O
with	O
his	O
Servants	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
he	O
was	O
inform	O
'd	O
by	O
his	O
Maid	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Street	O
Door	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
paine	O
of	O
Glass	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
surpris	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
any	O
Thing	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Goldsmiths-hall	O
,	O
and	O
caus	O
'd	O
his	O
Plate	O
to	O
be	O
advertis	O
'd	O
by	O
Description	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Advertisements	O
distributed	O
to	O
the	O
several	O
Silver-Smiths	O
and	O
Pawn-brokers	O
about	O
Town	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
Method	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
hear	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
disposing	O
of	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Plate	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
confess	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
one	O
Cockeril	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
;	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
then	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
who	O
he	O
knew	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
satisfied	O
with	O
his	O
Character	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
well	O
acquainted	O
with	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Coxiter	O
,	O
and	O
directed	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
went	O
and	O
enquir	O
'd	O
out	O
the	O
Habitation	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
there	O
with	O
a	O
Search	O
Warrant	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
several	O
of	O
his	O
Goods	O
which	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
Evening	O
following	O
,	O
a	O
Woman	O
who	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Wife	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
Kneeling	O
upon	O
her	O
Knees	O
,	O
deliver	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
almost	O
all	O
his	O
Plate	O
.	O
The	O
Servants	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
severally	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Doors	O
were	O
all	O
fast	O
when	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
November	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Maid-Servant	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
a	O
Paine	O
of	O
Glass	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
open	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Martin	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
some	O
Plate	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
Sale	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
finding	O
it	O
describ	O
'd	O
in	O
an	O
Advertisement	O
,	O
stopp	O
'd	O
both	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
brought	O
into	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
further	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
first	O
apprehended	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
Acquaintance	O
with	O
one	O
Nash	O
,	O
who	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Nash	O
being	O
very	O
familiar	O
with	O
one	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Maid	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
this	O
Information	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
took	O
a	O
Warrant	O
out	O
for	O
Nash	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Maid	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
indict	O
them	O
.	O
However	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Opinion	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
break	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
in	O
the	O
Night-Time	O
,	O
as	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
they	O
therefore	O
only	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Ayres	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
48	O
lb	O
.	O
and	O
90	O
Quires	O
of	O
printed	O
Paper	O
,	O
intitled	O
,	O
The	O
Historical	O
Register	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Nutt	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Nutt	I-pers
aforesaid	O
;	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hamnet	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
inform	O
'd	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
John	B-pers
Ayres	I-pers
stealing	O
his	O
Paper	O
,	O
he	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hamnet	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Cheesemonger	O
in	O
Black-fryars	B-place
;	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
35	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
at	O
a	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hamnet	I-pers
,	O
for	O
three	O
Half-pence	O
a	O
Pound	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
several	O
Questions	O
,	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
his	O
Answers	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
only	O
,	O
had	O
the	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
Books	O
call	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Historical	O
Register	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Quires	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
had	O
been	O
printed	O
about	O
four	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
sell	O
the	O
Books	O
in	O
Quantities	O
to	O
any	O
Person	O
,	O
the	O
Booksellers	O
seldom	O
sending	O
for	O
above	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
at	O
one	O
Time	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
Book	O
which	O
still	O
continues	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
which	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
reasonable	O
Demand	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Paper	O
stole	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Warehouse	O
by	O
Ayres	O
was	O
entire	O
Books	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
waste	O
Paper	O
,	O
neither	O
had	O
he	O
any	O
Right	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
said	O
Paper	O
as	O
waste	O
Paper	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
other	O
Pretence	O
whatsoever	O
.	O
Ayres	O
's	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
sign	O
'd	O
with	O
his	O
own	O
Hand	O
before	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Billers	I-pers
,	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
sold	O
the	O
Paper	O
to	O
Hemnet	O
for	O
Three	O
Half-pence	O
a	O
Pound	O
,	O
and	O
besides	O
this	O
Confession	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Betterson	O
,	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Nutt	O
,	O
prov	O
'd	O
Ayres	O
's	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
with	O
the	O
Paper	O
,	O
and	O
getting	O
off	O
before	O
he	O
could	O
take	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
further	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
Paper	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hamnet	I-pers
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
then	O
Hamnet	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
for	O
three	O
Half-pence	O
a	O
Pound	O
.	O
Ayres	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
Hamnet	O
persuaded	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
this	O
Paper	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
first	O
carried	O
waste	O
Paper	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
Copy	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
buy	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
carried	O
the	O
Paper	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
encourag	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
bring	O
more	O
;	O
but	O
Ayres	O
being	O
a	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
Indicted	O
,	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Hamnet	O
;	O
and	O
Hamnet	O
bringing	O
several	O
Tradesmen	O
into	O
Court	O
,	O
who	O
severally	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
bought	O
Paper	O
good	O
and	O
clean	O
for	O
three	O
Half-pence	O
a	O
pound	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
saying	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
bought	O
this	O
very	O
Historical	O
Register	O
in	O
Quires	O
for	O
that	O
Price	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
appearing	O
for	O
his	O
Character	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
Ayres	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Damms	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Neal	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White-Chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Nevel	I-pers
,	O
by	O
violently	O
striking	O
,	O
and	O
knocking	O
down	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Stephen	B-pers
Nevel	I-pers
,	O
and	O
thereby	O
giving	O
him	O
several	O
mortal	O
Bruises	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languish	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
27th	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
felonious	O
staying	O
the	O
said	O
Stephen	B-pers
Nevel	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
Brandy-Shop	O
Door	O
in	O
White-Chappel	B-place
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Brandy-Shop	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
came	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
strove	O
to	O
get	O
his	O
Hat	O
off	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
struck	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
fell	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
he	O
never	O
spoke	O
,	O
but	O
seem	O
'd	O
in	O
convulsive	O
Fits	O
,	O
from	O
that	O
Time	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
Night	O
following	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Holloway	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
likewise	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Brandy-Shop	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
following	O
,	O
would	O
have	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
turning	O
about	O
,	O
struck	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
fell	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
not	O
sensible	O
after	O
his	O
Fall	O
,	O
but	O
continu	O
'd	O
in	O
a	O
languishing	O
Condition	O
till	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
follwing	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Surgeon	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Wound	O
on	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
suppos	O
'd	O
to	O
come	O
by	O
his	O
Fall	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
an	O
Inch	O
long	O
to	O
the	O
Scull	O
,	O
which	O
Wound	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
poor	O
Widow	O
of	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
her	O
Husband	O
went	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
well	O
in	O
Health	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
brought	O
home	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
after	O
this	O
unhappy	O
Accident	O
happen	O
'd	O
,	O
from	O
which	O
Time	O
he	O
was	O
never	O
heard	O
to	O
speak	O
,	O
nor	O
take	O
any	O
Sustenance	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
continu	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Condition	O
till	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
Morning	O
following	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Malice	O
at	O
Heart	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
he	O
design	O
to	O
hurt	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
assaulted	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
before	O
he	O
struck	O
again	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Aldersgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Sugar	O
Dish	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Boat	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
Dozen	O
Spoons	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Quilter	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Raynor	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
those	O
Goods	O
to	O
Madam	O
Watts	O
,	O
a	O
Silver-Smith	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
sold	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
being	O
shew	O
'd	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Quilter	O
,	O
she	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
House	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Nutt	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Person	O
who	O
sold	O
Sausages	O
about	O
the	O
Streets	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
into	O
her	O
Mistress	O
's	O
Shop	O
(	O
she	O
being	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
)	O
and	O
begg	O
'd	O
some	O
small	O
Beer	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
to	O
draw	O
her	O
some	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
her	O
alone	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
missing	O
soon	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
plain	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bride	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Yards	O
of	O
Ribband	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Silk	O
Lace	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Worsley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Billingsgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pound	O
and	O
half	O
of	O
Cocoa	O
Nut	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Josiah	B-pers
Lambert	I-pers
;	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
appearing	O
plain	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Weaks	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Pewter	O
Porringers	O
and	O
two	O
pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Cutler	I-pers
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Rachel	B-pers
Cow	I-pers
,	O
of	B-place
St.	I-place
Bottolph	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Bed	O
Curtains	O
,	O
two	O
Blankets	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
;	O
which	O
being	O
very	O
plainly	O
proved	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Matth.ew	O
Handsir	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Macknig	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
Nov	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
suspicious	O
Person	O
together	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
caught	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
and	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
either	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
or	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
believing	O
otherwise	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
Ten	O
pence	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kinnerstone	I-pers
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Shelton	I-pers
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Shelton	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
lost	O
a	O
Shirt	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Kinnerstone	O
's	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
with	O
another	O
Shirt	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Peter	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Sheet	O
of	O
her	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
suspecting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
charg	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
make	O
this	O
appear	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquicted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Newington	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
5	O
Cocks	O
,	O
6	O
Hens	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Bed	O
,	O
Boulster	O
,	O
Pillow	O
,	O
Pillow-Case	O
,	O
a	O
Quilt	O
,	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Blankets	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Cock	O
's	O
being	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Meads	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
with	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
his	O
Door	O
,	O
leaving	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
return	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
charg	O
'd	O
them	O
with	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
at	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Wolley	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
Pawnbroker	O
,	O
who	O
inform	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Meads	I-pers
,	O
who	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
Sister	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
great	O
Distress	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
Occasion	O
to	O
borrow	O
some	O
Money	O
on	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Man	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
(	O
like	O
his	O
First-Father	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
fell	O
into	O
Sin	O
)	O
that	O
his	O
Wife	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
pawn	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Wife	O
said	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
found	O
them	O
upon	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
Husband	O
;	O
but	O
their	O
Excuses	O
being	O
of	O
no	O
Effect	O
,	O
without	O
Proof	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
Thomas	O
Meads	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
but	O
the	O
Wife	O
being	O
under	O
the	O
Power	O
and	O
Direction	O
of	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Michael	B-pers
Conally	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Elias	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Elias	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
11	O
or	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
his	O
Doors	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
next	O
Morning	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
been	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
he	O
suspected	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
caused	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
apprehended	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
then	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wadmore	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
him	O
confess	O
his	O
taking	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
he	O
then	O
work	O
'd	O
at	O
,	O
at	O
Hamersmith	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
it	O
out	O
from	O
under	O
the	O
moulding	O
Board	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Smith	O
,	O
saying	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
,	O
Erra	O
,	O
dear	O
Joy	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
betray	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
Shillings	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lacey	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
an	O
Ell	O
of	O
India	O
Dimitty	O
,	O
four	O
Napkins	O
,	O
two	O
Hoods	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
lost	O
an	O
Ell	O
of	O
India	O
Dimitty	O
,	O
three	O
Ells	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
two	O
Aprons	O
,	O
a	O
Table-Cloth	O
,	O
four	O
Napkins	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
musling	O
Hoods	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
her	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
away	O
,	O
she	O
missing	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
took	O
a	O
search	O
Warrant	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Remnant	O
of	O
Dimitty	O
in	O
her	O
Custody	O
.	O
The	O
Piece	O
of	O
India	O
Dimitty	O
was	O
brought	O
into	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
it	O
was	O
hers	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
one	O
Richard	B-pers
Wittacre	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
found	O
the	O
same	O
Piece	O
of	O
Dimitty	O
in	O
Custody	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
They	O
saw	O
the	O
Dimitty	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Holland	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
,	O
after	O
she	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Service	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
then	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
given	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
in	O
Opposition	O
to	O
the	O
Evidence	O
given	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
produc	O
'd	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
of	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
an	O
extraordinary	O
Character	O
,	O
in	O
particular	O
,	O
the	O
Lady	O
whom	O
she	O
now	O
serves	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
intrusted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
Diamonds	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
2000	O
l.	O
and	O
she	O
never	O
knew	O
her	O
to	O
wrong	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
a	O
Farthing	O
;	O
and	O
what	O
turn	O
'd	O
more	O
still	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Advantage	O
,	O
and	O
quite	O
clear	O
'd	O
her	O
from	O
the	O
Imputation	O
of	O
the	O
Crime	O
she	O
stood	O
indicted	O
for	O
,	O
was	O
,	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
Court	O
holding	O
the	O
Piece	O
of	O
India	O
Dimitty	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Custody	O
as	O
aforemention	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Piece	O
of	O
Dimety	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
brought	O
to	O
match	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Piece	O
,	O
perceived	O
them	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Width	O
,	O
but	O
differed	O
near	O
2	O
Inches	O
,	O
for	O
tho	O
'	O
the	O
Piece	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
brought	O
was	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Piece	O
found	O
in	O
Custody	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
work	O
'd	O
with	O
Silk	O
in	O
Flowers	O
,	O
yet	O
the	O
Piece	O
so	O
work	O
'd	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
Custody	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
widest	O
,	O
and	O
consequently	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Piece	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Vincint	I-pers
,	O
Sen.	O
of	O
Hammersmith	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Cocks	O
and	O
12	O
Hens	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Windham	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
William	B-pers
Ellard	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Son	O
's	O
House	O
at	O
the	O
King's-Head	O
at	O
Hammersmith	B-place
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
in	O
Company	O
,	O
intie	O
'd	O
him	O
and	O
his	O
Brother	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
them	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Lady	O
Windham	O
's	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
their	O
Bodies	O
he	O
would	O
kill	O
them	O
:	O
upon	O
which	O
this	O
Deponent	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
himself	O
and	O
his	O
Brother	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Lady	O
Windham	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
hoisted	O
his	O
Brother	O
over	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Brother	O
flung	O
over	O
3	O
Fowls	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
not	O
being	O
satisfied	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
got	O
upon	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
up	O
a	O
Brick	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
his	O
Body	O
he	O
would	O
kill	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
fling	O
them	O
all	O
over	O
;	O
that	O
his	O
Brother	O
then	O
flung	O
over	O
about	O
10	O
or	O
11	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pulling	O
off	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
wrapp	O
'd	O
them	O
all	O
up	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
his	O
Son	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
,	O
this	O
Deponent	O
and	O
his	O
Brother	O
,	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
eating	O
of	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Ellard	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
likewise	O
drinking	O
with	O
his	O
Brother	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
his	O
Son	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
persuaded	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
threatned	O
to	O
kill	O
them	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Lady	O
Windham	O
's	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
then	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
flung	O
him	O
over	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
which	O
so	O
hurt	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
speak	O
for	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
that	O
then	O
recovering	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
put	O
me	O
over	O
for	O
?	O
To	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
answered	O
,	O
for	O
Fowls	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
flung	O
over	O
three	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
his	O
Body	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
kill	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
fling	O
over	O
all	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
standing	O
upon	O
the	O
Wall	O
and	O
holding	O
a	O
Brick	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
had	O
flung	O
over	O
all	O
the	O
Fowls	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
false	O
which	O
they	O
had	O
accused	O
him	O
of	O
and	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
against	O
him	O
were	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
Villains	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
industrieas	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
brought	O
up	O
a	O
great	O
Family	O
without	O
any	O
Charge	O
to	O
the	O
Parish	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Long	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
harm	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
never	O
did	O
him	O
any	O
Wrong	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
ever	O
he	O
heard	O
any	O
good	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Indeed	O
he	O
never	O
heard	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
good	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
nor	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
harm	O
;	O
after	O
this	O
Chip	O
in	O
Pottage	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Savoury	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
never	O
did	O
him	O
any	O
harm	O
neither	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
he	O
ever	O
hear	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
him	O
very	O
extraordinary	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Webster	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Fisherman	O
,	O
likewise	O
appeared	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
most	O
he	O
could	O
say	O
for	O
him	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
never	O
stole	O
any	O
of	O
his	O
Fish	O
.	O
Several	O
others	O
were	O
called	O
in	O
his	O
Behalf	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
indulg	O
'd	O
to	O
say	O
what	O
they	O
could	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
their	O
Depositions	O
were	O
all	O
put	O
together	O
,	O
he	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
a	O
disorderly	O
Life	O
and	O
Conversation	O
;	O
and	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
appear	O
in	O
a	O
true	O
Light	O
,	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
of	O
Hammersmith	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
for	O
these	O
8	O
Years	O
last	O
past	O
,	O
there	O
has	O
been	O
30	O
or	O
40	O
Complaints	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
keeps	O
a	O
Nursery	O
to	O
breed	O
up	O
lewd	O
young	O
Fellows	O
to	O
rob	O
Hen-roosts	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
dextrous	O
proficient	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bone	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
set	O
with	O
Diamonds	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
set	O
with	O
Emeralds	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Rathbone	I-pers
,	O
Doctor	O
of	O
Physick	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Dr.	O
John	B-pers
Rathbone	I-pers
.	O
Dr.	O
Rathbone	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
November	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
his	O
Man	O
for	O
Water	O
to	O
wash	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
his	O
Rings	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Man	O
not	O
bringing	O
the	O
Water	O
immediately	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Room	O
to	O
give	O
some	O
Directions	O
to	O
his	O
Gardener	O
,	O
leaving	O
his	O
Rings	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
Minutes	O
,	O
his	O
Rings	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
from	O
the	O
Table	O
on	O
which	O
he	O
left	O
them	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Tretter	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
heard	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
Parlour	O
,	O
(	O
she	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
)	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
her	O
Master	O
's	O
Footman	O
,	O
to	O
run	O
up	O
Stairs	O
and	O
see	O
who	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
fear	O
'd	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Thief	O
there	O
,	O
who	O
would	O
steal	O
her	O
Master	O
's	O
Sword	O
,	O
that	O
whilst	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
these	O
Fears	O
,	O
she	O
heard	O
somebody	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Parlour	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
after	O
him	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
run	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
the	O
Man	O
who	O
run	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
going	O
up	O
Stairs	O
and	O
find-his	O
Master	O
's	O
Rings	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
ran	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
who	O
he	O
heard	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
as	O
he	O
went	O
,	O
if	O
any	O
one	O
pass	O
'd	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
upon	O
the	O
run	O
that	O
he	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
got	O
over	O
a	O
Wall	O
.	O
that	O
he	O
pursued	O
him	O
to	O
Tottenham-Court	O
Road	O
,	O
crying	O
,	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
apprehended	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Parlour	O
Door	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
confess	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Rings	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
stood	O
indicted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Haws	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
hearing	O
a	O
cry	O
of	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
,	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
turn	O
'd	O
back	O
and	O
talk	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
then	O
a	O
Plaisterer	O
's	O
Hammer	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
this	O
Deponent	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
what	O
the	O
Matter	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
why	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
answered	O
,	O
They	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
two	O
Rings	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
;	O
this	O
Deponent	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
he	O
would	O
surrender	O
and	O
clear	O
himself	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
clear	O
of	O
what	O
they	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
only	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
one	O
Mr.	O
May	O
,	O
a	O
Plaisterer	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
Tale	O
this	O
Deponent	O
left	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
pursued	O
by	O
the	O
others	O
who	O
were	O
behind	O
.	O
He	O
made	O
this	O
a	O
Part	O
of	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
likewise	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
Bailiffs	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
Information	O
from	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Acquaintance	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
danger	O
of	O
being	O
arrested	O
:	O
Being	O
ask	O
'd	O
why	O
he	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Haws	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
who	O
were	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
him	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
two	O
Rings	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
overheard	O
his	O
Pursuers	O
say	O
he	O
had	O
stolen	O
two	O
Rings	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Benson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
told	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
that	O
Morning	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
himself	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
laid	O
in	O
a	O
Goal	O
for	O
16	O
Pounds	O
which	O
he	O
owed	O
to	O
her	O
Master	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
resolved	O
to	O
arrest	O
him	O
.	O
Several	O
others	O
appeared	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
an	O
extraordinary	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Plaisterer	O
,	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
his	O
Masters	O
in	O
that	O
Business	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
behaved	O
himself	O
very	O
honestly	O
for	O
several	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
acquitted	O
himself	O
in	O
Noblemen	O
's	O
Houses	O
with	O
Reputation	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
twenty	O
nine	O
Pounds	O
Weight	O
of	O
Indigo	O
,	O
value	O
32	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Deacon	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
weekly	O
Servant	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Warehouse	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
neither	O
did	O
he	O
miss	O
any	O
of	O
his	O
Indigo	O
;	O
but	O
finding	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Hands	O
of	O
one	O
Charles	B-pers
Stamper	I-pers
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
George	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
he	O
caused	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
apprehended	O
:	O
He	O
likewise	O
said	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
a	O
clandestine	O
Manner	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
Confession	O
not	O
being	O
clearly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Stamper	I-pers
,	O
who	O
gave	O
this	O
Information	O
,	O
not	O
appearing	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Acton	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cock	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
Hens	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
First	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Lock	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Barnet	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Cock	O
and	O
Hens	O
were	O
his	O
Mistress	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
Roost	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
Day	O
following	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Watchman	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
Sack	O
upon	O
his	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
something	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
thought	O
fit	O
to	O
examine	O
him	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
Fowls	O
there	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
this	O
Deponent	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
wanted	O
such	O
a	O
Chap	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
Custody	O
.	O
The	O
Fowls	O
were	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Lock	I-pers
Jun	O
.	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
Mother	O
's	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
as	O
aforementioned	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Uxbridge	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
back	O
,	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
with	O
a	O
Sack	O
upon	O
his	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
his	O
asking	O
the	O
Man	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
flung	O
the	O
Sack	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
very	O
innocently	O
,	O
and	O
only	O
for	O
thus	O
finding	O
the	O
Sack	O
of	O
Fowls	O
,	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
Custody	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
its	O
much	O
more	O
common	O
for	O
Felons	O
,	O
to	O
invent	O
an	O
Excuse	O
,	O
than	O
to	O
clear	O
themselves	O
by	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
,	O
these	O
idle	O
Tales	O
are	O
of	O
little	O
Effect	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Mayson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Billinsgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
25	O
Pounds	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Butling	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Paul	B-pers
Chamberlain	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
's	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bed-Ticking	O
,	O
a	O
Flock-Boulster	O
,	O
two	O
Blankets	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Sheets	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Flock	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Person	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
Lodgings	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
lived	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
some	O
Time	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
t'other	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
look	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
afterwards	O
they	O
finding	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
broad	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
caused	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
apprehended	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
having	O
no	O
real	O
Foundation	O
for	O
charging	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Emans	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Clarkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
20	O
Streaks	O
of	O
Iron	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
Coach-Wheels	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Iron	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Cornelius	B-pers
Spooner	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
lost	O
a	O
considerable	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Iron	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
have	O
stolen	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
enquiring	O
amongst	O
those	O
who	O
buy	O
old	O
Iron	O
,	O
found	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Streaks	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Peter's-Street	O
,	O
mark	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Letter	O
R	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
he	O
always	O
mark	O
'd	O
his	O
Iron	O
,	O
to	O
distinguish	O
it	O
from	O
other	O
People	O
's	O
;	O
some	O
other	O
Pieces	O
he	O
found	O
at	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Wilkinson	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
deals	O
in	O
that	O
Commodity	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Pieces	O
at	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Long-Lane	O
,	O
all	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
stole	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
first	O
taken	O
into	O
Custody	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Saunders	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
stole	O
20	O
Streaks	O
of	O
Iron	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
besides	O
a	O
Cradle	O
Iron	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
very	O
falsly	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
never	O
wrong	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
but	O
of	O
two	O
Streaks	O
of	O
Iron	O
in	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Paul	B-pers
Kerney	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
forging	O
,	O
counterfeiting	O
,	O
and	O
publishing	O
a	O
false	O
Bill	O
of	O
Lading	O
,	O
subscribed	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Ship	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Sea-Horse	O
,	O
purporting	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Ship	O
,	O
1050	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
in	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Eight	O
;	O
by	O
which	O
counterfeit	O
Bill	O
of	O
Lading	O
,	O
he	O
defrauded	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
200	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
borrowing	O
the	O
said	O
Sum	O
of	O
Money	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Credit	O
of	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
forged	O
counterfeit	O
and	O
false	O
Bill	O
of	O
Lading	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
Council	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
opened	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
the	O
Heinousness	O
of	O
the	O
Crime	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Methods	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
taken	O
to	O
abuse	O
the	O
Credulity	O
and	O
good	O
Nature	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
,	O
pretending	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Spanish	O
Merchant	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
great	O
Effects	O
abroad	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
in	O
Reality	O
he	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
than	O
an	O
idle	O
Person	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
hapned	O
to	O
lodge	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
lend	O
him	O
Money	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
readily	O
do	O
,	O
upon	O
good	O
Security	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
then	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
this	O
Bill	O
of	O
Lading	O
,	O
and	O
insinuated	O
himself	O
so	O
far	O
into	O
his	O
Affections	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
this	O
Gold	O
was	O
insur	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
freely	O
lend	O
him	O
the	O
200	O
l.	O
he	O
desired	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
Kerney	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
it	O
was	O
but	O
a	O
counterfeit	O
Bill	O
of	O
Lading	O
,	O
had	O
his	O
pretended	O
Effects	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Sea-Horse	O
,	O
insur	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
the	O
Policy	O
,	O
who	O
immediately	O
lent	O
him	O
the	O
200	O
Pounds	O
,	O
upon	O
a	O
promissary	O
Note	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Obligation	O
of	O
the	O
Bill	O
of	O
Lading	O
;	O
but	O
Kerney	O
trifling	O
in	O
his	O
Promises	O
and	O
Accounts	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
gave	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
,	O
occasion	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
look	O
narrowly	O
into	O
the	O
Affair	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
all	O
a	O
Cheat	O
and	O
Delusion	O
,	O
and	O
charging	O
Kerney	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
left	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
absconded	O
;	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
being	O
industrious	O
in	O
his	O
Inquiries	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
heard	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Tunbridge	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
Pleasure	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
their	O
in	O
Pursuit	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Beggars	O
Opera	O
.	O
The	O
sham	O
Bill	O
of	O
Lading	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
dated	O
from	O
Calis	O
,	O
and	O
sign	O
'd	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
Commander	I-pers
,	O
with	O
promise	O
to	O
deliver	O
Paul	B-pers
Kerney	I-pers
,	O
as	O
his	O
own	O
proper	O
Right	O
,	O
1050	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
so	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
Ship	O
Sea-Horse	O
,	O
then	O
mooring	O
at	O
Calis	O
,	O
should	O
arrive	O
in	O
the	O
Port	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
he	O
paying	O
the	O
Freight	O
.	O
Several	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Captain	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
's	O
Hand-Writing	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
this	O
pretended	O
Bill	O
of	O
Lading	O
,	O
was	O
not	O
of	O
his	O
drawing	O
up	O
,	O
it	O
not	O
having	O
any	O
Resemblance	O
with	O
his	O
Writing	O
.	O
It	O
further	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Disgrace	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
That	O
not	O
contented	O
with	O
imposing	O
on	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
,	O
in	O
deluding	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
200	O
l.	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Assurance	O
to	O
ask	O
for	O
a	O
hundred	O
Pounds	O
more	O
,	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
lent	O
him	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
this	O
hundred	O
Pounds	O
was	O
not	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
a	O
tedious	O
Tale	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
very	O
little	O
Effect	O
;	O
for	O
he	O
could	O
neither	O
alledge	O
one	O
Truth	O
in	O
his	O
Vindication	O
,	O
nor	O
shew	O
a	O
single	O
Circumstance	O
which	O
might	O
serve	O
to	O
mitigate	O
his	O
Crime	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Barrow	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Catherine	B-pers
Scriven	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Chamber-pot	O
and	O
a	O
pewter	O
Bason	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Cowthorn	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
200	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
Iron	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Lester	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Cryer	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
returning	O
from	O
Transportation	O
before	O
the	O
Term	O
of	O
7	O
Years	O
was	O
expired	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
his	O
Sentence	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Farmer	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Mary	B-pers
Marks	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
one	O
Guinea	O
and	O
24	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
appearing	O
plain	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
George	B-pers
Gutridge	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
appearing	O
plain	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cap	O
and	O
Clout	O
a	O
Shirt	O
and	O
a	O
Shift	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Morphew	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susanna	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
a	O
Blanket	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Getheril	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Hales	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
Counterfeiting	O
and	O
Forging	O
,	O
a	O
certain	O
Writing	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
defraud	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
other	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Subjects	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
which	O
Note	O
he	O
knowing	O
to	O
be	O
false	O
and	O
Counterfeit	O
,	O
did	O
publish	O
as	O
a	O
true	O
Note	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
said	O
7th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Copy	O
of	O
the	O
Note	O
was	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Aug.	O
27	O
,	O
1728	O
.	O
I	O
promise	O
to	O
pay	O
to	O
George	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
or	O
Order	O
,	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
Six	O
Thousand	O
four	O
hundred	O
Pounds	O
upon	O
Demand	O
,	O
the	O
like	O
Value	O
received	O
;	O
for	O
myself	O
and	O
Partners	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
.	O
After	O
the	O
Council	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
had	O
opened	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
the	O
heinousness	O
of	O
the	O
Crime	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Reasons	O
they	O
had	O
to	O
believe	O
by	O
their	O
Instructions	O
,	O
that	O
William	B-pers
Hales	I-pers
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
Counterfeiting	O
,	O
Forging	O
,	O
and	O
Publishing	O
the	O
abovementioned	O
Writing	O
,	O
they	O
proceeded	O
to	O
examine	O
the	O
following	O
Witnesses	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Philip	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
for	O
some	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
about	O
a	O
Year	O
and	O
a	O
Half	O
ago	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
(	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Gibson	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
Member	O
of	O
Parliament	O
)	O
and	O
desired	O
he	O
would	O
get	O
him	O
two	O
Letters	O
Frank	O
'd	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
who	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
Frank	O
his	O
Letters	O
was	O
gone	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
gave	O
this	O
Deponent	O
two	O
Sheets	O
of	O
large	O
Paper	O
,	O
folded	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
large	O
Size	O
for	O
Letters	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
they	O
might	O
be	O
directed	O
to	O
Robert	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
at	O
Bristol	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
accordingly	O
done	O
by	O
Mr	O
Gibson	O
,	O
who	O
,	O
as	O
his	O
Manner	O
was	O
,	O
wrote	O
the	O
Directions	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
under	O
the	O
Directions	O
he	O
wrote	O
Free	O
Tho	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Counterfeit	O
Note	O
of	O
6400	O
l.	O
Sign	O
'd	O
Tho	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
,	O
being	O
shew	O
'd	O
to	O
this	O
Deponent	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
Opinion	O
that	O
the	O
Contrivance	O
was	O
manag	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
those	O
Letters	O
Mr.	O
Gibson	O
Frank	O
'd	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
;	O
he	O
likewise	O
discovered	O
that	O
the	O
Word	O
for	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Note	O
for	O
myself	O
and	O
Partners	O
.	O
was	O
partly	O
eras	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
between	O
the	O
f	O
and	O
r	O
an	O
o	O
was	O
crowded	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
ee	O
's	O
being	O
rubb	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
Word	O
Free	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
wrote	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gibson	O
,	O
was	O
made	O
for	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
w	O
as	O
immediately	O
added	O
,	O
myself	O
and	O
Partners	O
,	O
he	O
likewise	O
observ	O
'd	O
(	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
observ	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
)	O
that	O
the	O
Letter	O
o	O
,	O
crowded	O
between	O
the	O
F	O
and	O
r	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Words	O
myself	O
and	O
Partners	O
,	O
were	O
of	O
different	O
Ink	O
from	O
the	O
Name	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
;	O
and	O
tho	O
'	O
it	O
faintly	O
imitated	O
Mr.	O
Gibson	O
's	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
different	O
from	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
the	O
Note	O
,	O
yet	O
he	O
who	O
was	O
well	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Gibson	O
's	O
Hand	O
,	O
could	O
plainly	O
discover	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Counterfeit	O
,	O
and	O
only	O
the	O
ff	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Gibson	O
's	O
Way	O
of	O
writing	O
when	O
he	O
wrote	O
Free	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Name	O
Tho	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Gibson	O
's	O
own	O
writing	O
,	O
he	O
further	O
took	O
Notice	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Stile	O
and	O
Manner	O
of	O
this	O
Note	O
differ	O
'd	O
not	O
a	O
little	O
from	O
the	O
Manner	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Gibson	O
's	O
writing	O
a	O
Promissory	O
Note	O
,	O
for	O
as	O
in	O
this	O
it	O
was	O
myself	O
and	O
Partners	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Gibson	O
always	O
writes	O
,	O
for	O
myself	O
and	O
Co.	O
for	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Gibson	O
never	O
uses	O
the	O
Phrase	O
for	O
Value	O
received	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
wrote	O
in	O
this	O
counterfeit	O
Writing	O
:	O
Other	O
Remarks	O
were	O
made	O
,	O
that	O
over	O
the	O
m	O
for	O
my	O
,	O
there	O
appeared	O
the	O
Bottom	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
ee	O
's	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
but	O
a	O
bungling	O
Figure	O
in	O
the	O
Counterfeit	O
Note	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
observ	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
who	O
gave	O
his	O
Notes	O
in	O
exchange	O
for	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
of	O
his	O
receiving	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Piece	O
of	O
Paper	O
on	O
which	O
this	O
Note	O
was	O
drawn	O
,	O
appeared	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
cut	O
or	O
torn	O
to	O
serve	O
the	O
Design	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
seem	O
'd	O
ridiculous	O
,	O
to	O
think	O
Mr.	O
Gibson	O
should	O
draw	O
a	O
Note	O
of	O
such	O
Consequence	O
upon	O
such	O
a	O
diminutive	O
scrap	O
of	O
Paper	O
;	O
besides	O
,	O
the	O
Note	O
seemed	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
folded	O
as	O
a	O
Letter	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
of	O
Bristol	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
never	O
received	O
a	O
Letter	O
either	O
Frank	O
'd	O
or	O
otherwise	O
,	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
Person	O
in	O
Bristol	O
but	O
himself	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
and	O
Title	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Thomas	B-pers
Romsey	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
for	O
above	O
a	O
Year	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
particular	O
,	O
from	O
last	O
June	O
to	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
last	O
September	O
,	O
when	O
being	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
in	O
Duke-street	O
,	O
Westminster	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
on	O
a	O
light	O
Coat	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
red	O
Waistcoat	O
and	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
broad	O
open	O
laced	O
Hat	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
bade	O
him	O
put	O
himself	O
in	O
a	O
different	O
Dress	O
,	O
naming	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
plain	O
Cloth	O
,	O
which	O
this	O
Deponent	O
had	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
because	O
he	O
had	O
never	O
a	O
Hat	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
edg	O
'd	O
with	O
Silver	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
bade	O
him	O
put	O
on	O
a	O
plain	O
Hat	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
thus	O
dress	O
'd	O
himself	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Way	O
brought	O
him	O
a	O
Pocket-Book	O
,	O
or	O
Case	O
for	O
Notes	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
he	O
proceeded	O
further	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
look	O
still	O
more	O
like	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
Business	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Middle-Row	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
him	O
a	O
dark	O
Wig	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
to	O
put	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
bade	O
him	O
put	O
his	O
light	O
Wig	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
this	O
done	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
together	O
to	O
John	O
's	O
Coffee-House	O
in	O
Sheer-Lane	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
long	O
before	O
a	O
Porter	O
came	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
address	O
'd	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
want	O
Mr.	O
Romsey	O
,	O
the	O
Porter	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
delivering	O
a	O
Letter	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Romsey	O
,	O
this	O
Deponent	O
,	O
and	O
bade	O
him	O
open	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
counterfeit	O
Note	O
(	O
for	O
it	O
being	O
shew	O
'd	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Romsey	O
,	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
very	O
same	O
)	O
in	O
los	O
'd	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
the	O
Letter	O
was	O
only	O
wrote	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Lady	O
Harriot	O
Elliot	O
4300	O
l.	O
and	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Hind	I-pers
Cotton	I-pers
2100	O
l.	O
under	O
which	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
bade	O
him	O
write	O
,	O
to	O
James	B-pers
Moreton	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
or	O
Bearer	O
70	O
l.	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
gave	O
him	O
three	O
Bank	O
Notes	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
40	O
l.	O
and	O
two	O
of	O
25	O
l.	O
each	O
,	O
which	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Counterfeit	O
Note	O
of	O
6400	O
l.	O
he	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
New	O
Pocket-Case	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Names	O
aforementioned	O
tore	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Letter	O
,	O
and	O
bade	O
him	O
go	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Snow	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
Banker	O
(	O
whose	O
House	O
he	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
in	O
View	O
)	O
and	O
desire	O
they	O
would	O
change	O
those	O
Notes	O
for	O
Notes	O
of	O
their	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
them	O
payable	O
to	O
the	O
Persons	O
to	O
whom	O
the	O
other	O
Paper	O
directed	O
,	O
in	O
such	O
Sums	O
as	O
their	O
mentioned	O
:	O
With	O
these	O
Notes	O
and	O
Directions	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Snow	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
first	O
shew	O
'd	O
the	O
Bank	O
Notes	O
,	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Poultock	O
readily	O
chang	O
'd	O
as	O
desired	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
the	O
6400	O
l.	O
Note	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
Mr.	O
Poultock	O
to	O
exchange	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
refus	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
all	O
Mr.	O
Gibson	O
's	O
Hand-Writing	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
meddle	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
went	O
again	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
who	O
stood	O
at	O
some	O
Distance	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Success	O
he	O
had	O
met	O
with	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
again	O
to	O
John	O
's	O
Coffee-House	O
,	O
in	O
Sheer-Lane	O
,	O
where	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
write	O
on	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Paper	O
,	O
to	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Grovesnor	I-pers
,	O
4300	O
l.	O
and	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	O
Hind	O
Cotton	O
,	O
2100	O
l.	O
from	O
whence	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
went	O
to	O
shew	O
him	O
Mr.	O
Hoare	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
he	O
should	O
get	O
the	O
Notes	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Hoare	O
and	O
Comp	O
.	O
payable	O
to	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Grovesnor	I-pers
and	O
Sir	O
John	O
Hind	O
Cotton	O
.	O
He	O
likewise	O
gave	O
him	O
another	O
Note	O
,	O
of	O
about	O
seventy	O
Pounds	O
,	O
to	O
exchange	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
should	O
ask	O
his	O
Name	O
,	O
to	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
Fowler	O
;	O
at	O
this	O
Place	O
he	O
got	O
the	O
Notes	O
chang	O
'd	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Notes	O
of	O
Hoare	O
and	O
Comp	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
waiting	O
at	O
a	O
Fruit-Stall	O
,	O
hard	O
by	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
directly	O
to	O
the	O
Change	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
Janeway	O
's	O
Coffee-House	O
,	O
where	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
bade	O
him	O
write	O
1100	O
l.	O
and	O
1200	O
l.	O
payable	O
to	O
Samuel	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
or	O
Bearer	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
him	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Woodward	O
's	O
,	O
to	O
change	O
the	O
Notes	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
before	O
taken	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Hoare	O
's	O
,	O
for	O
Notes	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Woodward	O
's	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
paid	O
to	O
Samuel	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
with	O
Directions	O
as	O
before	O
,	O
to	O
call	O
himself	O
Thomas	O
Fowler	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
ask	O
'd	O
after	O
Mr.	O
Palmer	O
,	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
Mansfields-Street	O
,	O
Goodmans-Fields	O
;	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Woodward	O
's	O
Door	O
being	O
shut	O
up	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
sent	O
him	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bracey	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
got	O
the	O
Notes	O
payable	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Palmer	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Lien	O
,	O
gave	O
the	O
other	O
Notes	O
he	O
had	O
before	O
received	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Hoare	O
's	O
.	O
This	O
being	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
late	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
together	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
Mr.	O
Romsey	O
lay	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
bid	O
him	O
be	O
ready	O
on	O
Monday	O
Morning	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Dress	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
accordingly	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
again	O
to	O
Jansway	O
's	O
Coffee-House	O
,	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
sent	O
him	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Hankey	O
's	O
and	O
exchang	O
'd	O
Notes	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Halsey	O
's	O
,	O
to	O
turn	O
these	O
several	O
Notes	O
into	O
South-Sea	O
and	O
India-Bonds	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
afterwards	O
converted	O
into	O
Bank	O
Notes	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Produce	O
of	O
the	O
6400	O
l.	O
had	O
been	O
wound	O
about	O
into	O
several	O
Intricacies	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
had	O
all	O
this	O
while	O
an	O
other	O
Emissary	O
at	O
Work	O
,	O
getting	O
off	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Bank	O
Notes	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
better	O
Success	O
than	O
Mr.	O
Romsey	O
;	O
for	O
he	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Bank	O
,	O
with	O
two	O
Notes	O
of	O
200	O
l.	O
each	O
,	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Affair	O
being	O
found	O
out	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gibson	O
's	O
Cashier	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
vile	O
Imposition	O
,	O
and	O
trac	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
several	O
Places	O
where	O
the	O
Affair	O
had	O
been	O
transacted	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
Romsey	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Bank	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
Custody	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
,	O
who	O
waited	O
for	O
him	O
at	O
Robi	O
's	O
Coffee-House	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Jury	O
,	O
was	O
taken	O
soon	O
after	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Poultock	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Richard	B-pers
Hoar	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Turner	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Hankey	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Cole	O
,	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Halsey	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
George	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
all	O
confirm	O
'd	O
Romsey	O
's	O
Evidence	O
,	O
of	O
his	O
exchanging	O
Notes	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
depos	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
Robert	O
Hall	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
Mr.	O
Hale	O
's	O
Taylor	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Order	O
and	O
Direction	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
,	O
had	O
taken	O
Notes	O
and	O
Money	O
for	O
him	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Bracey	O
's	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Bank	O
,	O
and	O
receiv	O
'd	O
Money	O
for	O
the	O
Bank	O
Notes	O
he	O
receiv	O
'd	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Bracey	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
gave	O
him	O
Orders	O
,	O
if	O
any	O
one	O
should	O
ask	O
his	O
Name	O
,	O
to	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
John	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
Hay-Market	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
other	O
Place	O
he	O
could	O
remember	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Maddox	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
Instructions	O
to	O
stop	O
any	O
Person	O
who	O
should	O
bring	O
Notes	O
to	O
the	O
Bank	O
,	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
Number	O
,	O
which	O
Notes	O
were	O
stopp	O
'd	O
upon	O
Romsey	O
,	O
who	O
sent	O
a	O
Letter	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
,	O
at	O
Robin	O
's	O
Coffee-House	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
found	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Bank	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
6400	O
l.	O
Note	O
came	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
with	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
Notes	O
found	O
upon	O
Romsey	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
Notes	O
found	O
upon	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
whole	O
Sum	O
of	O
6400	O
l.	O
the	O
Note	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
of	O
one	O
Samuel	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
confess	O
'd	O
this	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Bellamy	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
.	O
The	O
Council	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
insist	O
upon	O
its	O
not	O
being	O
a	O
counterfeit	O
Note	O
,	O
only	O
said	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Bankrupt	O
those	O
last	O
twenty	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
obtain	O
his	O
Certificate	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
transact	O
his	O
Affairs	O
under	O
fictitious	O
Names	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Names	O
of	O
other	O
People	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Security	O
of	O
his	O
Effects	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
should	O
endeavour	O
to	O
prove	O
,	O
He	O
had	O
dealt	O
very	O
largely	O
,	O
in	O
particular	O
with	O
one	O
Samuel	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
of	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
6400	O
l.	O
Note	O
,	O
sign	O
'd	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Granper	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
knew	O
one	O
Samuel	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
employ	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
East-India	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
abroad	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
now	O
nor	O
that	O
he	O
ever	O
had	O
any	O
Dealings	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
.	O
He	O
likewise	O
call	O
'd	O
another	O
Witness	O
to	O
his	O
Character	O
,	O
but	O
neither	O
of	O
these	O
Witnesses	O
speaking	O
to	O
the	O
Purpose	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
call	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
procuring	O
and	O
obtaining	O
the	O
Notes	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Hoare	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Hoare	I-pers
,	O
by	O
false	O
Tokens	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
great	O
Damage	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Benjamin	O
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Hoare	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
same	O
Witnesses	O
being	O
call	O
'd	O
,	O
as	O
were	O
examined	O
before	O
,	O
the	O
Fact	O
appear	O
'd	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
Judgement	O
is	O
respited	O
till	O
next	O
Sessions	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
will	O
be	O
tried	O
upon	O
other	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Judith	B-pers
Holloway	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Broad-Street	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
Shillings	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Staples	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Staples	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Staples	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Helen	I-place
's	I-place
Meeting-House	I-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
press	O
'd	O
very	O
hard	O
against	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
immediately	O
put	O
her	O
Hand	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Hand	O
there	O
;	O
that	O
her	O
Snuff-Box	O
was	O
then	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
she	O
was	O
certain	O
it	O
was	O
there	O
but	O
just	O
before	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Staples	I-pers
,	O
Jun	O
.	O
Sister-in-Law	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
press	O
'd	O
very	O
hard	O
against	O
her	O
Sister	O
,	O
and	O
self	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
her	O
Sister	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
is	O
the	O
Woman	O
who	O
did	O
it	O
,	O
(	O
meaning	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
)	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
Man	O
behind	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Staples	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
behind	O
her	O
Sister	O
when	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
is	O
the	O
Woman	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
very	O
Instant	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
fling	O
down	O
something	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
stooping	O
down	O
,	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
her	O
Sister	O
's	O
Snuff-Box	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Witeman	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
heard	O
Madam	O
Staples	O
say	O
,	O
her	O
Pocket	O
was	O
pick	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Moment	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drop	O
a	O
silver	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
dropp	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
same	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
