TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
:	O
AND	O
On	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
16th	O
,	O
17th	O
,	O
18th	O
,	O
and	O
19th	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
and	O
Thursday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
21st	O
and	O
24th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
1729	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Second	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
Six	O
Pence	O
.	O
)	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
ROBERT	B-pers
BAYLIS	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Raymond	I-pers
,	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
of	O
the	O
King's-Bench	O
,	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Hale	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Worshipful	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Denton	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
Raby	O
,	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
;	O
with	O
others	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
;	O
Together	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Garret	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bodwell	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
C	I-pers
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Boheme	I-pers
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Atwood	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Levet	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Briscoe	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Seagrave	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hare	I-pers
,	O
Ebenezer	B-pers
Brathwait	I-pers
,	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Low	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rex	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Shelton	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
Theophilus	B-pers
Lightfoot	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
,	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Phipps	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Witcher	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Akers	I-pers
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Dent	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Katherine	I-place
's	I-place
Creed-Church	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
9	O
Yards	O
of	O
Diaper	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
Day	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
which	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Black-Fryers	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linen	O
Sheet	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Briton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Silver	O
Plate	O
Wire	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Panton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
an	O
Apprentice	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Silver-Spinner	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
this	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Hester	B-pers
Batt	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Alban	I-place
's	I-place
Woodstreet	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
Hundred	O
Leaden	O
Weight	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Web	I-pers
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Prosser	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Allhallow	B-place
's	I-place
London-Wall	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
of	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Lucy	B-pers
Waring	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Whiston	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
His	O
Mistress	O
was	O
a	O
Baker	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
at	O
Work	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
at	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
past	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
somebody	O
jump	O
off	O
from	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Shop-Floor	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
ran	O
up	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
Assistance	O
,	O
which	O
coming	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
secur	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
found	O
that	O
the	O
Shutters	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
had	O
been	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
a	O
very	O
large	O
and	O
strong	O
Shoemaker	O
's	O
Awl	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
Penknife	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
feign	O
'd	O
himself	O
drunk	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Wicks	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
shut	O
up	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
fasten	O
'd	O
the	O
Shutters	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
hearing	O
an	O
Out-cry	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
Whiston	O
standing	O
over	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
drunk	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Shutters	O
of	O
the	O
Shop-Window	O
broke	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
suppos	O
'd	O
to	O
get	O
in	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
large	O
Awl	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Penknife	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
carrying	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-House	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Watchman	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lie	O
upon	O
a	O
Bench	O
at	O
the	O
next	O
Door	O
about	O
One	O
a-Clock	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
seiz	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
how	O
he	O
got	O
in	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Samson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Mars	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Bovington	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Joseph	B-pers
Darvel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Undershaft	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Pair	O
of	O
Cotton	O
Sleeves	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
:	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
all	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Skinner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Billingsgate	I-place
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
30	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Spanish	O
Wool	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
her	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Cowel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bartholomew	I-place
the	I-place
Less	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Walton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
April	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
apprehended	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
presently	O
after	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Featherstone	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Bride	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
tame	O
Deer	O
,	O
Value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposd	O
,	O
He	O
living	O
at	O
Hornchurch	B-place
,	O
in	O
Essex	B-place
,	O
lost	O
his	O
Deer	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Blood	O
in	O
his	O
Ground	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
he	O
imagin	O
d	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
kill	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
Notice	O
to	O
the	O
Persons	O
in	O
London	O
who	O
bought	O
such	O
Meat	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
Intelligence	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
sell	O
into	O
Fleetstreet	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Indictment	O
being	O
laid	O
for	O
Deer	O
,	O
which	O
tho	O
'	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
when	O
alive	O
in	O
Essex	O
,	O
yet	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
Deer	O
,	O
but	O
Venison	O
,	O
when	O
in	O
London	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
to	O
be	O
indicted	O
for	O
it	O
in	O
Essex	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Allhallow	B-place
's	I-place
Barkin	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Ambrose	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
16	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Trimlet	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
House	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Possession	O
of	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Ambrose	O
,	O
was	O
under	O
his	O
Care	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
did	O
several	O
Houses	O
,	O
lying	O
sometimes	O
in	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
somes	O
in	O
another	O
;	O
that	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
aforesaid	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Window-Shutter	O
below	O
Stairs	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Plates	O
taken	O
off	O
the	O
Shelf	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
one	O
upon	O
another	O
on	O
the	O
Dresser	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
hid	O
under	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
without	O
his	O
Shoes	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
before	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
not	O
that	O
his	O
Landlord	O
was	O
gone	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
Window	O
open	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
in	O
to	O
lodge	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
no	O
Intent	O
to	O
steal	O
:	O
His	O
Landlady	O
confirm	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
about	O
a	O
Month	O
before	O
lodg	O
'd	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
believe	O
,	O
knew	O
not	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
Several	O
Persons	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Hull	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Chiswick	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
several	O
Books	O
,	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Standish	O
,	O
and	O
Tinder-Box	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
stolen	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Summer-House	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
sell	O
a	O
Book	O
call	O
'd	O
Wood	O
's	O
Instructor	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Hull	I-pers
,	O
pleaded	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	O
,	O
produc	O
'd	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Persons	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
Woman	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
Edward	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
,	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
Concern	O
in	O
the	O
Affair	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
an	O
Acquaintance	O
with	O
Mary	B-pers
Hull	I-pers
when	O
she	O
offer	O
'd	O
the	O
Book	O
to	O
Sale	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cowsel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
Bottles	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
6	O
Bottles	O
of	O
Cyder	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Dyke	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Rummet	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Tanner	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Durant	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
.	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
Yards	O
of	O
Sattin	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
l.	O
and	O
30	O
Yards	O
of	O
Brussels	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
36	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Ridley	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Sarah	O
Rummet	O
,	O
was	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
having	O
taken	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
two	O
Mornings	O
sooner	O
than	O
usual	O
,	O
was	O
suspected	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Tapper	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
Hannover-Square	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Weather	O
Sheep	O
,	O
value	O
22	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Stephenson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
lost	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Sheep	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Ground	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
feeding	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ashley	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Tapper	O
,	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
inform	O
'd	O
that	O
a	O
Sheep	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
Notice	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
and	O
searching	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Pluck	O
hanging	O
up	O
,	O
the	O
Carcass	O
of	O
the	O
Sheep	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
cover	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Bed-cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Entrails	O
in	O
the	O
Skin	O
lying	O
wrapp	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Bed-Curtains	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Sheep	O
by	O
the	O
Mark	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Harwood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
8	O
Yards	O
of	O
Lindsey-Woolsey	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Katherine	B-pers
Gondevin	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Hammerson	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Godwin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
97	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Walnut-tree	O
Wood	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
April	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Hammerson	O
,	O
offer	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
Sale	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Godwin	O
had	O
been	O
Journeyman	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
,	O
who	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
carried	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Goods	O
.	O
Hammerson	O
pleaded	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
their	O
being	O
stolen	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
only	O
employ	O
'd	O
by	O
William	B-pers
Godwin	I-pers
to	O
got	O
him	O
a	O
Chapman	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
instead	O
of	O
Money	O
for	O
Work	O
done	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
,	O
each	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Field	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Jackets	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Possonby	I-pers
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
under	O
Pretence	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
discover	O
d	O
,	O
was	O
presently	O
pusued	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
nothing	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
trifling	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samuel	B-pers
Salmon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
43	O
Washballs	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
about	O
Ten	O
a-Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
seen	O
by	O
some	O
Neighbours	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
was	O
pursued	O
,	O
and	O
stopp	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
dropp	O
'd	O
down	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Tims	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bow	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Boots	O
and	O
Spurs	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
lost	O
the	O
Boots	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
his	O
having	O
offer	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
Sale	O
;	O
but	O
pleaded	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
an	O
empty	O
House	O
among	O
some	O
Rubbish	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Hill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
250	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
coming	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
Course	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	O
Beckford	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Beckford	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Packer	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Sugar	O
was	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Hogshead	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Beckford	O
's	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
broken	O
open	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Pemberton	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
employ	O
'd	O
as	O
a	O
Watchman	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
a-Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
with	O
a	O
Bag	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
;	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
?	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
What	O
was	O
that	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
carry	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-House	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Way	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Bag	O
of	O
Sugar	O
he	O
had	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
17	O
d.	O
halfpenny	O
,	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
get	O
away	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
calling	O
out	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
and	O
secur	O
'd	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
likewise	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
a	O
Coach	O
standing	O
over-against	O
the	O
Monument	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
running	O
away	O
,	O
the	O
Coachman	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
He	O
believ	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
Thieves	O
in	O
his	O
Coach	O
;	O
and	O
thereupon	O
the	O
Coach	O
being	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
therein	O
3	O
large	O
Bags	O
of	O
Sugar	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
examining	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
encouraging	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
being	O
made	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Beckford	O
's	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
others	O
were	O
concern	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
but	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
before	O
sold	O
about	O
250	O
lb	O
.	O
to	O
one	O
in	O
Bird-Cage-Alley	O
in	O
Southwark	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
search	O
'd	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
such	O
a	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Sugar	O
that	O
answer	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Sample	O
;	O
however	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jacob	B-pers
Stock	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Billingsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Barrel	O
of	O
Anchovies	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Forster	I-pers
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Allen	B-pers
Sawyer	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Billingsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
20	O
lb	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
positive	O
Proof	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Persons	O
appearing	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
an	O
honest	O
Character	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Lambert	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Alpress	I-pers
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Alpress	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
about	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
a-Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
drinking	O
with	O
Company	O
till	O
late	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
having	O
a	O
Mind	O
to	O
play	O
a	O
Game	O
at	O
Cards	O
,	O
there	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Dispute	O
about	O
rubbing	O
out	O
a	O
Chalk	O
,	O
whereupon	O
they	O
resolv	O
'd	O
to	O
fight	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
Company	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
to	O
fight	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Battle	O
,	O
except	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
staid	O
below	O
Stairs	O
with	O
the	O
Tankard	O
;	O
that	O
before	O
they	O
went	O
up	O
they	O
lock	O
'd	O
the	O
outward	O
Doors	O
,	O
that	O
nobody	O
would	O
either	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
or	O
come	O
in	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Fight	O
was	O
over	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
Dispute	O
about	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
paying	O
his	O
Share	O
of	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
about	O
1	O
or	O
2	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
,	O
she	O
chose	O
rather	O
to	O
lose	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Part	O
than	O
have	O
any	O
farther	O
Disturbance	O
,	O
wherefore	O
she	O
let	O
him	O
and	O
his	O
Friend	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
;	O
that	O
his	O
Friend	O
never	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
left	O
,	O
but	O
put	O
on	O
his	O
Cloaths	O
in	O
the	O
Entry	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
that	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Acquaintance	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Company	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
3	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Tankard	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Tankard	O
could	O
be	O
found	O
;	O
this	O
Evidence	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
3	O
Persons	O
who	O
thus	O
staid	O
to	O
drink	O
:	O
But	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
Evidence	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
take	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Crick	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
appear	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
Spoon	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
lent	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Husband	O
,	O
(	O
since	O
deceas	O
'd	O
)	O
and	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Martin	O
had	O
taken	O
her	O
up	O
for	O
it	O
while	O
her	O
Husband	O
was	O
alive	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
with	O
his	O
Approbation	O
:	O
This	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
well	O
confirm	O
'd	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
wooden	O
Box	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
for	O
a	O
Pennyworth	O
of	O
Sugar-Candy	O
,	O
and	O
throwing	O
his	O
Money	O
so	O
that	O
it	O
fell	O
down	O
behind	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
was	O
stooping	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
catch	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
Money-Box	O
,	O
the	O
Servant	O
hearing	O
it	O
rattle	O
,	O
presently	O
made	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
running	O
round	O
a	O
Hogshead	O
,	O
dropp	O
'd	O
the	O
Box	O
and	O
got	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
presently	O
pursued	O
and	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Raven	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Tanner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hammer	O
,	O
Pincers	O
,	O
Rasp	O
,	O
Old	O
Shoes	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Bent	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
a	O
Cobler	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Things	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Stall	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
pawn	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Geneva	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samuel	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Linnen	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear'd-by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
while	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Room	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
seen	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
out	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
was	O
pursued	O
and	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Josiah	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
34	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Beef	O
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Hugh	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Beef	O
was	O
hanging	O
at	O
his	O
Stall	O
in	O
Leadenhall-Market	B-place
;	O
that	O
it	O
being	O
missing	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
inform	O
'd	O
a	O
Person	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
carry	O
such	O
a	O
Piece	O
to	O
the	O
Hole	O
in	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
;	O
where	O
he	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
both	O
Beef	O
and	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
pretended	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
some	O
Persons	O
he	O
met	O
in	O
Wapping	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
not	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
nor	O
believ	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Butcher	O
being	O
positive	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
Beef	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Burgess	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
81	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Linnen	O
Rags	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
;	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
Mr.	O
Parker	O
's	O
,	O
nor	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
steal	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
divers	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Aram	I-pers
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
February	O
:	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
liv	O
'd	O
as	O
Man	O
and	O
Wife	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
fallen	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
parted	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
return	O
'd	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
thereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
GERARD	B-pers
Vandike	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
Hanover-Square	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
on	O
or	O
near	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
Randal	B-pers
Goslin	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Pen	I-pers
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
having	O
been	O
to	O
carry	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Pipes	O
for	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
receiv	O
'd	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
that	O
coming	O
along	O
Chelsea	B-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
struck	O
the	O
Basket	O
off	O
from	O
his	O
Head	O
;	O
he	O
asking	O
what	O
that	O
was	O
for	O
?	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
fell	O
a	O
fighting	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
thrown	O
down	O
,	O
his	O
Money	O
fell	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
Lappet	O
of	O
his	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
snatch	O
'd	O
it	O
up	O
:	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
Money	O
falling	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
taking	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
up	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
another	O
Evidence	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
that	O
were	O
by	O
,	O
who	O
saw	O
them	O
quarrelling	O
,	O
and	O
ha	O
ing	O
and	O
pulling	O
,	O
and	O
fighting	O
one	O
with	O
another	O
for	O
the	O
space	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
soundly	O
beaten	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
several	O
others	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Goat-Alehouse	O
,	O
not	O
far	O
off	O
,	O
to	O
wash	O
,	O
clean	O
,	O
and	O
refresh	O
himself	O
,	O
staying	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Hours	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
got	O
a	O
Constable	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
he	O
lost	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
more	O
than	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
done	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Guinea	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
just	O
before	O
the	O
Fray	O
began	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
Alehouse-Man	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
just	O
before	O
been	O
drinking	O
,	O
to	O
depose	O
it	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
on	O
both	O
Sides	O
,	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
rather	O
an	O
accidental	O
Quarrel	O
and	O
Fray	O
than	O
a	O
Robbery	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Wormington	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Shoes	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Ferrin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
How	I-pers
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Cane	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
several	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Sigley	I-pers
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Lodging	O
by	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
by	O
his	O
Direction	O
or	O
Consent	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
s	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
and	O
robbing	O
Philip	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
39	O
Yards	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Graves	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
As	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Bell-Court	B-place
,	I-place
near	O
Brooks-Market	B-place
,	O
and	O
having	O
the	O
Goods	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
pull	O
'd	O
the	O
Holland	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
came	O
immediately	O
to	O
his	O
Assistance	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Miles	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
hearing	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
immediately	O
pursued	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
dropp	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
hid	O
himself	O
in	O
a	O
Corner	O
of	O
the	O
Alley	O
,	O
where	O
Mary	B-pers
Miles	I-pers
inform	O
'd	O
him	O
she	O
saw	O
him	O
run	O
to	O
hide	O
himself	O
:	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
indeed	O
was	O
positive	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
seem	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
an	O
Accomplice	O
,	O
who	O
got	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
old	O
,	O
and	O
Lamp-Light	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Disorder	O
he	O
must	O
of	O
Necessity	O
be	O
in	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
possible	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
mistaken	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
only	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Arthur	B-pers
Banks	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Carcass	O
of	O
a	O
Lamb	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Lamb	O
hung	O
at	O
his	O
Stall	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Lever	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
throw	O
it	O
upon	O
his	O
Shoulders	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Munday	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drop	O
the	O
Lamb	O
from	O
off	O
his	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
presently	O
seiz	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
reason	O
he	O
ran	O
,	O
was	O
because	O
he	O
thought	O
he	O
saw	O
some	O
Bailiffs	O
:	O
This	O
Excuse	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Lewis	B-pers
Hewit	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Thatcher	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gallon	O
Pewter	O
Pot	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
London	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Stephenson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cock	O
and	O
2	O
Hens	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
which	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Saw	O
and	O
and	O
Ax	O
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
&	O
c.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Custody	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Pemberton	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Pendry	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Pendron	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
Baglin	I-pers
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
Francis	B-pers
Tidcomb	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
14	O
Guineas	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Pemberton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
her	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
her	O
going	O
,	O
she	O
miss	O
'd	O
her	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
inform	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Days	O
before	O
enquir	O
'd	O
where	O
the	O
Bristol	O
Waggon	O
stood	O
,	O
she	O
sent	O
after	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Barns	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Watchman	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
under	O
her	O
Arm	O
,	O
at	O
about	O
2	O
a-Clock	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
for	O
a	O
Midwife	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Haynes	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Bristol	O
Waggon	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
Francis	B-pers
Tidcomb	I-pers
with	O
her	O
,	O
who	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
having	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
given	O
him	O
to	O
keep	O
for	O
Pemberton	O
,	O
but	O
knew	O
not	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
stolen	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
Purse	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
Money	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
sweeping	O
the	O
Shop	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
that	O
Francis	B-pers
Tidcomb	I-pers
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
or	O
knew	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
stolen	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Stranger	O
to	O
her	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
going	O
to	O
Marlborough	O
to	O
see	O
his	O
Friends	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Cecil	B-pers
Holms	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	O
Holms	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
having	O
sent	O
the	O
Trunk	O
to	O
a	O
Friend	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
in	O
her	O
Name	O
,	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Daniel	B-pers
Beard	I-pers
and	O
Abraham	B-pers
Calloway	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bow	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
stealing	O
Iron	O
Pins	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
,	O
and	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Hucks	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
latter	O
for	O
receiving	O
them	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
against	O
Beard	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
but	O
Calloway	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Daniel	O
Beard	O
was	O
indicted	O
again	O
for	O
stealing	O
Iron	O
Dogs	O
of	O
a	O
Dray	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Potter	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Ashby	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wallis	I-pers
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Cary	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
taking	O
Money	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wheatly	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
April	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Fountain-Tavern	B-place
in	O
Drury-Lane	B-place
the	O
Time	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
drank	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Guinea	O
to	O
lie	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
sent	O
down	O
a	O
23	O
s.	O
Piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
d.	O
sent	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
Change	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
afterwards	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
his	O
Money	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Cane	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Kensington	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Robert	B-pers
Daniel	I-pers
,	O
junior	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
28	O
s.	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Daniel	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
having	O
a	O
Fair	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
Kensington	O
at	O
12	O
a-Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
refus	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Coach-Box	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
would	O
bilk	O
him	O
of	O
his	O
Fair	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
stand	O
by	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
Kensington	O
,	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
paid	O
him	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Drink	O
;	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
back	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
him	O
get	O
into	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
needs	O
get	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
Box	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
coming	O
back	O
,	O
about	O
9	O
a-Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Horses	O
Reins	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
Money	O
he	O
wanted	O
,	O
and	O
Money	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
,	O
and	O
threatned	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
him	O
what	O
Money	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
drew	O
a	O
Knife	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
thereupon	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
put	O
the	O
Point	O
of	O
the	O
Knife	O
in	O
his	O
Mouth	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
Money	O
over	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
That	O
if	O
ever	O
he	O
betray	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
live	O
longer	O
than	O
any	O
of	O
his	O
Gang	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
thinking	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Floyd	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
's	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
10	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Wheat-Flower	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Oatmeal	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
finding	O
herself	O
declining	O
,	O
upon	O
casting	O
up	O
her	O
Accounts	O
,	O
and	O
admiring	O
how	O
it	O
should	O
come	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
,	O
suspected	O
Dishonesty	O
in	O
some	O
of	O
her	O
Servants	O
;	O
therefore	O
examining	O
her	O
Servants	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
inform	O
'd	O
by	O
her	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
enticed	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
carry	O
away	O
his	O
Mistress	O
's	O
Flower	O
and	O
Meal	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
many	O
Times	O
,	O
and	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
carry	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Cakehouse	O
,	O
and	O
Treat	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
engag	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
with	O
bitter	O
Wishes	O
on	O
himself	O
if	O
he	O
ever	O
discover	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
divers	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Mumford	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Prosecutor	O
liv	O
'd	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
was	O
between	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Felony	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Forgeham	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
George	I-place
the	I-place
Martyr	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Quilt	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Carey	I-pers
;	O
but	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
in	O
charging	O
William	B-pers
Cornish	I-pers
with	O
committing	O
Sodomy	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d	O
of	O
him	O
for	O
concealing	O
the	O
said	O
Crime	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cornish	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
being	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Jame	I-place
's	I-place
Park	I-place
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
near	O
9	O
a-Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
sat	O
down	O
on	O
a	O
Bench	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Servant	O
?	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
his	O
Father	O
,	O
an	O
Upholster	O
in	O
Gerard-Street	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
show	O
9	O
Inches	O
;	O
asking	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
?	O
Upon	O
this	O
,	O
he	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
collar	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
If	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
swear	O
Sodomy	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
so	O
much	O
Money	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
One	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
much	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
One	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
Account	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
wanted	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
Walk	O
in	O
the	O
Park	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
Guineas	O
a-Night	O
of	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
because	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
expos	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
follow	O
him	O
wherever	O
he	O
went	O
;	O
that	O
at	O
length	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Friend	O
and	O
borrow	O
'd	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
;	O
and	O
3	O
Days	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
borrow	O
3	O
Guineas	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
Note	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
Half	O
Guinea	O
into	O
the	O
Sum	O
;	O
upon	O
this	O
,	O
he	O
procur	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
apprehended	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Court	O
order	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
stand	O
on	O
the	O
Pillory	O
at	O
Charing-Cross	O
,	O
to	O
suffer	O
3	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
pay	O
a	O
Fine	O
of	O
10	O
l	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Draper	I-pers
,	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Oakly	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Stocker	I-pers
;	O
which	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Simkins	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Coffee	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
against	O
Jones	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
and	O
acquitted	O
Simkins	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Major	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Reed	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Oliver	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Armstead	I-pers
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
Sarah	B-pers
Major	I-pers
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
taken	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Reed	I-pers
to	O
sell	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
Husband	O
's	O
she	O
being	O
newly	O
married	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
against	O
Sarah	B-pers
Major	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d	O
but	O
acquitted	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Reed	I-pers
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Simkin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
14	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Messerwy	I-pers
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
It	O
was	O
Lump-Sugar	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
about	O
Ten	O
a-Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
dropp	O
'd	O
the	O
Sugar	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
the	O
Sugar	O
was	O
thrown	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
fallen	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
o'th	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
But	O
this	O
Plea	O
neither	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
nor	O
appearing	O
probable	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Atwood	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Elsley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Magnes	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
4	O
Cocks	O
,	O
and	O
37	O
Hens	O
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Darvil	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Peter	I-place
's	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
Pound	O
of	O
Sealing-Wax	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Grosvenor	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
she	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Ralph	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Tate	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
half-Hundred	O
Weight	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Merchant	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Gile	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Wyat	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Hogs	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
,	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Maidman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Hundred	O
Weight	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Ship	O
Wiltshire	O
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Ship	O
came	O
from	O
St.	O
Christopher	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
at	O
Ratcliff-Cross	B-place
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
keeping	O
a	O
Victualling-House	O
there	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Royal-Oak	O
,	O
came	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
said	O
Ship	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Men	O
to	O
have	O
Provisions	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
brought	O
with	O
him	O
an	O
Iron	O
Hammer	O
in	O
his	O
Boat	O
;	O
that	O
by	O
the	O
Connivance	O
of	O
the	O
Officers	O
he	O
open	O
'd	O
3	O
Hogsheads	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
2	O
Hundred	O
Weight	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
headed	O
them	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
the	O
Sugar	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
his	O
Boat	O
,	O
carry	O
'd	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
for	O
2	O
d.	O
per	O
Pound	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
If	O
they	O
would	O
get	O
Sugar	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
it	O
off	O
their	O
Hands	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Hundred	O
Weight	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Lighter	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Ship	O
Wiltshire	O
.	O
-	B-pers
Pearse	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
As	O
the	O
Lighter	O
was	O
going	O
from	O
the	O
said	O
Ship	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
on	O
board	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Boat	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
Leave	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
little	O
Sugar	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
open	O
'd	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Hogsheads	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
that	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
his	O
Boat	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Lamp	O
,	O
brought	O
this	O
Evidence	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Merchants	O
Watchman	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
divers	O
Persons	O
to	O
his	O
Character	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Facts	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Cluff	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
her	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
Right	O
Thigh	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Breadth	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
Depth	O
of	O
five	O
Inches	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
April	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
w	O
as	O
indicted	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
Stabbing	O
;	O
and	O
likewise	O
the	O
3d	O
Time	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	O
Green	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Diana	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Green	B-place
Lattica	I-place
in	O
Holborn	B-place
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
her	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
the	O
Deceased	O
Mary	O
Green	O
;	O
that	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
or	O
ten	O
Minutes	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
carry	O
'd	O
out	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Drink	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
walking	O
about	O
the	O
Taphouse	O
with	O
the	O
Child	O
in	O
her	O
Arms	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
Mary	O
Green	O
go	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
bring	O
up	O
2	O
Pints	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
one	O
for	O
a	O
Customer	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
for	O
herself	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
carried	O
into	O
a	O
Box	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
Dinner	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
Minutes	O
before	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
done	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
come	O
in	O
,	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
to	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
4	O
Minutes	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
Madam	O
Pray	O
come	O
here	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Floor	O
,	O
sitting	O
on	O
her	O
Backside	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
holding	O
her	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
Shoulders	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Blood	O
running	O
from	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
Quantity	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
James	O
,	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
done	O
?	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
Madam	O
,	O
nothing	O
:	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
her	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
herself	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
saw	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
:	O
That	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
did	O
neither	O
speak	O
nor	O
move	O
,	O
and	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
dead	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
affrighted	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
for	O
an	O
Apothecary	O
.	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
his	O
Servant	O
about	O
2	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
a	O
just	O
and	O
honest	O
Servant	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
as	O
his	O
Wife	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
carried	O
out	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
drew	O
2	O
Pints	O
of	O
Drink	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
or	O
Box	O
where	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
the	O
Door	O
with	O
an	O
uncommon	O
Violence	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
call	O
'd	O
his	O
Wife	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
himself	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
sitting	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
supported	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
near	O
while	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
an	O
inclos	O
'd	O
one	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Ceiling	O
to	O
about	O
3	O
Foot	O
,	O
yet	O
he	O
heard	O
no	O
Noise	O
,	O
nor	O
a	O
Word	O
spoke	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
no	O
Knife	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
also	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
9	O
or	O
10	O
a-Clock	O
that	O
Forenoon	O
,	O
a	O
Man	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
who	O
he	O
heard	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Sweetheart	O
of	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
sat	O
down	O
,	O
drank	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
smoak	O
'd	O
a	O
Pipe	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
being	O
washing	O
some	O
Rooms	O
,	O
came	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
and	O
drank	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
trundled	O
her	O
Mop	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up-Stairs	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
she	O
sat	O
down	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
the	O
Man	O
did	O
kiss	O
her	O
,	O
or	O
whisper	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
sat	O
directly	O
over-against	O
the	O
Bar	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
an	O
Alteration	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Countenance	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
look	O
'd	O
ruffled	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
any	O
Courtship	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
between	O
them	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Saunders	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
dining	O
that	O
Day	O
at	O
Mr	O
.	O
Pain	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drew	O
him	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
spoke	O
for	O
a	O
Tankard	O
to	O
be	O
carry	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
;	O
that	O
while	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
two	O
more	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
drew	O
two	O
Pints	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
one	O
for	O
the	O
Men	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
the	O
other	O
into	O
the	O
Box	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
Dinner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
saw	O
no	O
Knife	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
the	O
Drink	O
;	O
that	O
soon	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Box	O
to	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
3	O
Minutes	O
,	O
or	O
thereabouts	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Madam	O
,	O
pray	O
come	O
here	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
what	O
is	O
done	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
,	O
calling	O
Mr	O
.	O
Pain	O
,	O
saying	O
there	O
was	O
Murder	O
committed	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
and	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Posture	O
before	O
related	O
;	O
that	O
Mr	O
.	O
Pain	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Villain	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
He	O
believ	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
should	O
give	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
it	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
clear	O
'd	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
He	O
was	O
as	O
innocent	O
as	O
the	O
Child	O
at	O
his	O
Mistress	O
's	O
Breast	O
:	O
His	O
Master	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
how	O
it	O
came	O
;	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
draw	O
the	O
2	O
Pints	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
she	O
carried	O
a	O
Knife	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
her	O
leaning	O
upon	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
James	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
dead	O
Woman	O
:	O
That	O
seeing	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Blood	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
how	O
it	O
came	O
?	O
but	O
she	O
made	O
him	O
no	O
Answer	O
,	O
but	O
tumbled	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Chair	O
;	O
that	O
thereupon	O
a	O
Candle	O
was	O
lighted	O
,	O
and	O
Mr	O
.	O
Pain	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
himself	O
,	O
some	O
Stairs	O
,	O
but	O
saw	O
not	O
a	O
Drop	O
of	O
Blood	O
;	O
and	O
added	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
when	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
draw	O
the	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
saw	O
no	O
Knife	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Cox	O
,	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
about	O
2	O
a-Clock	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
immediately	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
lying	O
on	O
her	O
Back	O
and	O
a	O
vast	O
Effusion	O
of	O
Blood	O
,	O
but	O
her	O
Lips	O
chang	O
'd	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
searching	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Wound	O
in	O
the	O
upper	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Thigh	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
had	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Femoral	O
Artery	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
Knife	O
among	O
the	O
other	O
Knives	O
,	O
which	O
Knife	O
had	O
a	O
little	O
Blood	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
compar	O
'd	O
the	O
Knife	O
with	O
the	O
Cuts	O
in	O
her	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
the	O
Wound	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
answer	O
'd	O
exactly	O
to	O
all	O
;	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
broad-pointed	O
Knife	O
,	O
yet	O
had	O
gone	O
through	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
a	O
quilted	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Stuff-petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
course	O
strong	O
Shift	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
it	O
must	O
go	O
with	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
Force	O
to	O
do	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
to	O
penetrate	O
as	O
it	O
did	O
5	O
Inches	O
into	O
the	O
Thigh	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Wound	O
went	O
obliquely	O
upwards	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
he	O
thought	O
,	O
was	O
scarce	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
by	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Posture	O
she	O
was	O
suppos	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Knife	O
also	O
lay	O
about	O
4	O
Foot	O
from	O
where	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
sitting	O
,	O
as	O
was	O
said	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
of	O
Opinion	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
Wound	O
given	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
hardly	O
place	O
it	O
there	O
;	O
that	O
such	O
a	O
Wound	O
in	O
that	O
Part	O
was	O
so	O
immediately	O
mortal	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Person	O
could	O
not	O
live	O
above	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Minutes	O
;	O
that	O
under	O
her	O
Chin	O
,	O
and	O
under	O
her	O
Left	O
Ear	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
her	O
Elbows	O
,	O
there	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
some	O
confinement	O
or	O
Violence	O
used	O
,	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
cause	O
the	O
Blood	O
to	O
stagnate	O
,	O
and	O
prevent	O
its	O
circulating	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Groves	O
,	O
that	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
Wash	O
for	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Pain	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
about	O
six	O
Weeks	O
before	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
complain	O
'd	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
beating	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
bear	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
show	O
'd	O
her	O
her	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
Bump	O
upon	O
it	O
as	O
big	O
as	O
an	O
Egg	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
got	O
some	O
Rum	O
and	O
bath	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
thrown	O
a	O
Candlestick	O
at	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
hit	O
her	O
:	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
heard	O
them	O
quarrel	O
several	O
times	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
once	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
If	O
you	O
do	O
me	O
a	O
Mischief	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
live	O
to	O
see	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
those	O
that	O
will	O
live	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
hang	O
'd	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Baldwin	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
being	O
at	O
Mr	O
.	O
Pain	O
's	O
about	O
9	O
a-Clock	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Discourse	O
passing	O
among	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
of	O
the	O
Deceas	O
d	O
,	O
She	O
knows	O
what	O
's	O
what	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
she	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
a	O
Bastard	O
;	O
that	O
soon	O
after	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
Tea	O
or	O
Sugar	O
for	O
her	O
Mistress	O
,	O
and	O
Mr	O
.	O
Pain	O
being	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
always	O
out	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
most	O
wanted	O
;	O
that	O
thereupon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
struck	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Backside	O
with	O
the	O
Poker	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
Sawcy	O
Slut	O
must	O
my	O
Master	O
give	O
you	O
an	O
Account	O
?	O
and	O
he	O
thought	O
he	O
look	O
'd	O
maliciously	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Maid	O
push	O
'd	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
strike	O
me	O
for	O
?	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
thought	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
ill-natur	O
'd	O
Fellow	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Duncarton	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
about	O
7	O
Weeks	O
since	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
beat	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Back-Kitchin	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
afterwards	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
Will	O
my	O
Mistress	O
suffer	O
this	O
?	O
She	O
asking	O
her	O
why	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
beat	O
her	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
Because	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
some	O
Sticks	O
to	O
light	O
her	O
Fire	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
laid	O
by	O
to	O
light	O
his	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Mother	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
Easter-Tuesday	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
Mother	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
wild	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
not	O
kept	O
my	O
Places	O
,	O
but	O
now	O
I	O
am	O
used	O
so	O
barbarously	O
by	O
my	O
Fellow-Servant	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
bear	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
should	O
not	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
come	O
and	O
give	O
her	O
Mistress	O
Warning	O
;	O
she	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
bear	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
she	O
could	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
was	O
bare	O
of	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
her	O
Mother	O
was	O
poor	O
,	O
and	O
incapable	O
to	O
get	O
them	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
tho	O
'	O
they	O
had	O
had	O
high	O
Words	O
,	O
yet	O
they	O
never	O
had	O
had	O
Blows	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
,	O
that	O
Day	O
they	O
were	O
very	O
loving	O
together	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
touch	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Poker	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
came	O
,	O
with	O
whom	O
she	O
drank	O
,	O
he	O
only	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
more	O
Drink	O
than	O
would	O
do	O
her	O
good	O
;	O
that	O
at	O
Dinner-time	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
ended	O
his	O
Dinner	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
to	O
draw	O
Drink	O
:	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
went	O
to	O
draw	O
two	O
Pints	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
a	O
Knife	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
with	O
that	O
?	O
she	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
What	O
is	O
that	O
to	O
you	O
James	O
?	O
That	O
afterwards	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
carry	O
'd	O
out	O
Drink	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
again	O
into	O
the	O
Box	O
to	O
Dinner	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
her	O
sitting	O
,	O
leaning	O
her	O
Head	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
James	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Dead	O
Woman	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
Dear	O
Mary	O
,	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
Matter	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
and	O
immediately	O
,	O
without	O
making	O
any	O
Answer	O
,	O
she	O
fell	O
down	O
dead	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
his	O
Mistress	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
a	O
Minute	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
seem	O
to	O
be	O
any	O
ways	O
out	O
of	O
Temper	O
that	O
Day	O
.	O
On	O
a	O
full	O
Hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Drinkwater	I-pers
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hoy	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1300	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Ship	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Burwell	O
,	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Tostick	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
Agreement	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Ship	O
Burwell	O
,	O
Constantine	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
Master	O
,	O
from	O
Virginia	O
,	O
among	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
the	O
1st	O
and	O
2d	O
Mate	O
,	O
the	O
Boatswain	O
,	O
Gunner	O
,	O
and	O
Captain	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
to	O
stock	O
,	O
i.e	O
.	O
to	O
take	O
Tobacco	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Merchants	O
Hogsheads	O
,	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
share	O
the	O
Money	O
among	O
them	O
,	O
it	O
having	O
been	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
an	O
old	O
Custom	O
so	O
to	O
do	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
opened	O
the	O
Heads	O
of	O
those	O
Hogsheads	O
that	O
were	O
easiest	O
to	O
come	O
at	O
,	O
took	O
out	O
30	O
or	O
40	O
lb	O
.	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Hogshead	O
,	O
headed	O
them	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
carry	O
'd	O
it	O
on	O
shore	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
shar	O
'd	O
the	O
Money	O
equally	O
among	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
this	O
Evidence	O
went	O
on	O
shore	O
,	O
sold	O
the	O
Tobacco	O
for	O
6	O
d.	O
per	O
Pound	O
,	O
receiv	O
'd	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
rest	O
aboard	O
,	O
every	O
Man	O
his	O
Share	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Hoy	O
also	O
did	O
receive	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
the	O
other	O
Men	O
their	O
Shares	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hodges	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
boarded	O
on	O
the	O
Ship	O
Burwell	O
in	O
July	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
came	O
afterwards	O
to	O
Limehouse	B-place
;	O
that	O
they	O
said	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Custom	O
on	O
board	O
that	O
Ship	O
to	O
stock	O
for	O
the	O
good	O
of	O
the	O
Officers	O
;	O
that	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Drinkwater	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
with	O
Tostick	O
;	O
that	O
afterwards	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
work	O
'd	O
hard	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Tobacco	O
was	O
handed	O
from	O
the	O
Skuttle	O
to	O
the	O
Forecastle	O
,	O
and	O
thence	O
into	O
Boats	O
;	O
that	O
Drinkwater	O
and	O
others	O
handed	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Hold	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
on	O
shore	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
6	O
d.	O
per	O
Pound	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
him	O
,	O
this	O
Evidence	O
,	O
his	O
Share	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Persons	O
theirs	O
;	O
that	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hoy	I-pers
also	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
made	O
up	O
a	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
work	O
'd	O
hard	O
;	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
a	O
Boat	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
6	O
d.	O
per	O
Pound	O
,	O
gave	O
the	O
5	O
Officers	O
and	O
6	O
of	O
the	O
Ship	O
's	O
Crew	O
,	O
each	O
Man	O
his	O
Share	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Persons	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
They	O
had	O
known	O
them	O
many	O
Years	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
born	O
an	O
honest	O
Character	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
.	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
ShowGlass	O
,	O
containing	O
21	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
13	O
Stone	O
Rings	O
,	O
8	O
Snuff-Boxes	O
,	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
's	O
Instrument	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
Gold	O
and	O
Silver	O
Coins	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
York	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Show-Glass	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
his	O
Shop-Window	O
about	O
4	O
a-Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
;	O
that	O
missing	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
stept	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
inquiring	O
of	O
his	O
next	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
inform	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
tall	O
,	O
ancient	O
Gentlewoman	O
in	O
a	O
short	O
black	O
Cloak	O
and	O
a	O
Velvet	O
Hood	O
,	O
was	O
looking	O
into	O
it	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
before	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
immediately	O
got	O
several	O
Persons	O
to	O
pursue	O
,	O
running	O
one	O
one	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
another	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
apprehended	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
with	O
the	O
Show-Glass	O
in	O
her	O
Lap	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
opening	O
one	O
Door	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
jump	O
'd	O
out	O
:	O
that	O
,	O
however	O
,	O
he	O
seiz	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
her	O
Pockets	O
stuff	O
'd	O
full	O
the	O
Things	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Glasses	O
were	O
broke	O
all	O
to	O
Pieces	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Hands	O
were	O
very	O
bloody	O
,	O
being	O
cut	O
by	O
breaking	O
the	O
Glass	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
several	O
Rings	O
on	O
her	O
Fingers	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Seager	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
induc	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
commit	O
the	O
Fact	O
?	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
Necessity	O
,	O
she	O
having	O
a	O
Husband	O
and	O
10	O
Children	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
;	O
but	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Persons	O
of	O
Credit	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
her	O
Character	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Person	O
that	O
had	O
liv	O
'd	O
well	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Husband	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
handsomly	O
maintain	O
'd	O
by	O
her	O
Relations	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
lay	O
under	O
no	O
Necessity	O
to	O
commit	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
that	O
instead	O
of	O
10	O
Children	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
but	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
provided	O
for	O
by	O
the	O
Rev	O
.	O
Dr.	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
supposing	O
her	O
not	O
compos	O
mentis	O
when	O
she	O
committed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Barber	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Ruffet	B-pers
,	O
and	O
Martha	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Pugh	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
taking	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Jonas	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
at	O
the	O
Rose	B-place
and	I-place
Fountain	I-place
in	O
Drury-Lane	B-place
,	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
two	O
others	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Damn	O
you	O
Jack	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
give	O
us	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
or	O
we	O
'll	O
give	O
you	O
one	O
:	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
them	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
them	O
a	O
Bottle	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
forc	O
'd	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
Room	O
up	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
up	O
two	O
Pints	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
Table-Bed	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
they	O
threw	O
him	O
down	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Barber	I-pers
held	O
him	O
by	O
one	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
by	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
Buckles	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
from	O
off	O
his	O
Neck	O
,	O
his	O
Buttons	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
which	O
she	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Barber	I-pers
,	O
did	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Days	O
after	O
restore	O
him	O
again	O
;	O
Mary	B-pers
Barber	I-pers
took	O
the	O
Buttons	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shirt	O
,	O
and	O
Pugh	O
's	O
Hand	O
was	O
at	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
that	O
having	O
detain	O
'd	O
him	O
till	O
about	O
One	O
a-Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
afraid	O
if	O
he	O
made	O
any	O
Noise	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
murder	O
'd	O
by	O
their	O
Bullies	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Room	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
being	O
backwards	O
,	O
stay	O
'd	O
quietly	O
till	O
Morning	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
knocking	O
,	O
they	O
at	O
last	O
let	O
him	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
demanding	O
his	O
Things	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Barber	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Mistress	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
She	O
would	O
endeavour	O
to	O
help	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
Buckles	O
and	O
Buttons	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
believ	O
'd	O
the	O
2	O
Bitches	O
had	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
endeavour	O
to	O
help	O
him	O
to	O
that	O
again	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
afterwards	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
return	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
Buckles	O
,	O
Gloves	O
,	O
and	O
Rule	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
that	O
not	O
being	O
produc	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
procur	O
'd	O
a	O
Warant	O
to	O
apprehend	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
procured	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
arrested	O
for	O
5	O
l.	O
for	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Bryan	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
having	O
been	O
drinking	O
with	O
2	O
Women	O
,	O
about	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
a-Clock	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
Bed	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
forward	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Lock	O
upon	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
Mistress	O
,	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
pay	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
her	O
Mistress	O
,	O
who	O
lay	O
below	O
Stairs	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
treat	O
her	O
with	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
White	O
or	O
Red	O
,	O
she	O
chose	O
White	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
drank	O
together	O
very	O
friendly	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
wanted	O
his	O
Buckles	O
and	O
Buttons	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
pay	O
her	O
Mistress	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Shilling	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
spent	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
6	O
d.	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
but	O
3	O
s.	O
Frogdon	B-pers
Poplish	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
arrested	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
on	O
Easter-Monday	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Suit	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Ruffet	O
,	O
for	O
4	O
l.	O
19	O
s.	O
That	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
swear	O
a	O
Robbery	O
against	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
pay	O
her	O
before	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
send	O
her	O
to	O
Newgate	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
for	O
assaulting	O
and	O
violently	O
taking	O
the	O
Things	O
before-mention	O
'd	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
first	O
Indictment	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
both	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
praying	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
the	O
Indictments	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
granted	O
them	O
one	O
upon	O
the	O
last	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Harwood	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Badger	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Radford	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
her	O
Male	O
Bastard-Infant	O
,	O
by	O
throwing	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
suffocated	O
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hanby	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
view	O
'd	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
did	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
its	O
full	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
be	O
Born	O
alive	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
upon	O
making	O
Trial	O
of	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
the	O
Lungs	O
put	O
into	O
Water	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
buoyant	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
sink	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
observe	O
any	O
visible	O
Marks	O
of	O
Violence	O
on	O
the	O
Child	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Cummins	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
the	O
Fact	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
Lodging	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
3	O
d.	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
having	O
no	O
other	O
Conveniency	O
,	O
she	O
lay	O
with	O
another	O
Lodger	O
;	O
that	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
she	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
some	O
Drops	O
of	O
Blood	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
Lodgers	O
,	O
enquir	O
'd	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
had	O
been	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
whose	O
Nose	O
had	O
bled	O
?	O
they	O
all	O
saying	O
no	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
and	O
near	O
the	O
little	O
Vault	O
saw	O
a	O
great	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Blood	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
down	O
the	O
Hole	O
,	O
saw	O
a	O
Child	O
;	O
that	O
going	O
up	O
and	O
taxing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
having	O
murder	O
'd	O
her	O
Child	O
,	O
she	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
for	O
a	O
Midwife	O
,	O
fastening	O
the	O
Doors	O
after	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
home	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
having	O
got	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
got	O
into	O
another	O
House	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Marclew	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Bed	O
with	O
her	O
that	O
Night	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
up	O
about	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
a-Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
grip	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Pot	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Place	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
went	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
there	O
about	O
3	O
quarters	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
heard	O
neither	O
Sigh	O
nor	O
Groan	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
,	O
made	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
nor	O
were	O
there	O
any	O
Signs	O
upon	O
the	O
Stairs	O
;	O
that	O
about	O
8	O
or	O
9	O
a-Clock	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
eating	O
a	O
Pennyworth	O
of	O
Milk	O
,	O
when	O
Mrs.	O
Cummins	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
found	O
.	O
Katherine	B-pers
Wall	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Child	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Vault	O
,	O
and	O
wash	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
on	O
each	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Ear	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
black	O
Spot	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
believe	O
they	O
might	O
be	O
caus	O
'd	O
by	O
her	O
helping	O
herself	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Eastwood	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Midwife	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
4	O
Days	O
after	O
,	O
she	O
examining	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
found	O
she	O
had	O
Milk	O
in	O
her	O
Breasts	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Plaisters	O
were	O
over	O
them	O
to	O
dry	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
she	O
was	O
so	O
near	O
her	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
at	O
the	O
necessary	O
House	O
,	O
was	O
taken	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
swoon	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
not	O
sensible	O
of	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
dropping	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
never	O
laid	O
her	O
Finger	O
upon	O
it	O
to	O
hurt	O
it	O
,	O
nor	O
could	O
remember	O
how	O
she	O
got	O
up	O
Stairs	O
again	O
.	O
Damaris	B-pers
Lamb	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
,	O
desiring	O
her	O
to	O
help	O
her	O
to	O
a	O
Lodging	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
sent	O
her	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Cummins	O
,	O
and	O
perceiving	O
her	O
Condition	O
,	O
gave	O
her	O
some	O
odd	O
Things	O
,	O
as	O
Cotton	O
for	O
Sleeves	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
also	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
divers	O
other	O
Things	O
at	O
her	O
Father's-in-Law	O
at	O
the	O
Kings-Arms	O
in	O
Lawrence	O
Lane	O
in	O
New	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
.	O
Upon	O
a	O
full	O
Hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Boyce	I-pers
and	O
Anthony	B-pers
Godfrey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Shelly	I-pers
,	O
Bart	O
.	O
one	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
a	O
Chain	O
and	O
Seal	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Sir	O
John	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
having	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Commons	O
the	O
Day	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
7	O
a-Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
before	O
he	O
had	O
Din	O
'd	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
order	O
'd	O
his	O
Coachman	O
to	O
drive	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Coffee-house	O
at	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
,	O
whither	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
usual	O
Custom	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
an	O
Evening	O
;	O
but	O
finding	O
himself	O
,	O
while	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
somewhat	O
uneasy	O
in	O
his	O
Stomach	O
,	O
he	O
thought	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
of	O
Use	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
walk	O
in	O
the	O
Park	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
a	O
little	O
Air	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
order	O
'd	O
his	O
Coachman	O
to	O
set	O
him	O
down	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
walking	O
,	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
a-Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
felt	O
an	O
Uneasiness	O
in	O
his	O
Foot	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
before	O
had	O
the	O
Gout	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
sat	O
down	O
on	O
a	O
Bench	O
not	O
far	O
from	O
the	O
Ld	O
.	O
Chetwind	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
to	O
case	O
his	O
Foot	O
by	O
loosening	O
his	O
Shoe	O
;	O
sitting	O
there	O
about	O
3	O
Minutes	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
he	O
was	O
stooping	O
,	O
he	O
felt	O
a	O
Hand	O
about	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Watch	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
immediately	O
started	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
close	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
collar	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
Centinel	O
for	O
Assistance	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
to	O
Anthony	B-pers
Godfrey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
drawing	O
out	O
his	O
Bayonet	O
,	O
threatned	O
to	O
stick	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Heart	O
if	O
he	O
made	O
any	O
Noise	O
,	O
or	O
talk	O
'd	O
any	O
more	O
of	O
being	O
robb	O
'd	O
;	O
that	O
Godfrey	O
,	O
who	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Companion	O
,	O
(	O
he	O
seeing	O
them	O
walking	O
together	O
before	O
he	O
sat	O
down	O
)	O
came	O
immediately	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bid	O
him	O
assist	O
him	O
to	O
secure	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
He	O
had	O
attempted	O
to	O
commit	O
Sodomy	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Centinel	O
coming	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Persons	O
,	O
he	O
charg	O
'd	O
them	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
also	O
charg	O
'd	O
the	O
Centinel	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
went	O
together	O
to	O
the	O
Guard-House	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Best	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Buckingham-House	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
Sir	O
John	O
sitting	O
on	O
the	O
Bench	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
catch	O
'd	O
hold	O
of	O
Boyce	O
by	O
the	O
Collar	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
if	O
not	O
of	O
his	O
Money	O
;	O
that	O
,	O
upon	O
thus	O
,	O
Boyce	O
drew	O
his	O
Bayonet	O
,	O
and	O
threatned	O
to	O
stab	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
being	O
robb	O
'd	O
and	O
that	O
upon	O
the	O
coming	O
up	O
of	O
Godfrey	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
Sir	O
John	O
had	O
handled	O
his	O
Privy-Parts	O
for	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
made	O
before	O
John	B-pers
Slater	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
wherein	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
what	O
he	O
took	O
from	O
Sir	O
John	O
,	O
to	O
Anthony	B-pers
Godfrey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
did	O
never	O
receive	O
any	O
Money	O
,	O
or	O
Part	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Slater	O
also	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Boyce	O
,	O
did	O
confess	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
Sir	O
John	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Accusation	O
was	O
false	O
.	O
Isaac	O
-	O
,	O
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Boyce	O
,	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
Sir	O
John	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Sir	O
John	O
did	O
not	O
do	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
accus	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
;	O
begg	O
'd	O
Sir	O
John	O
's	O
Pardon	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
the	O
justice	O
in	O
another	O
Room	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
fram	O
'd	O
this	O
Accusation	O
to	O
bring	O
himself	O
off	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
both	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
Boyce	O
pleaded	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
sitting	O
on	O
the	O
Bench	O
in	O
the	O
Park	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
buckling	O
on	O
his	O
Spatterdashes	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Sir	O
John	O
came	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
by	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
sat	O
together	O
a	O
considerable	O
Time	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Sir	O
John	O
attempted	O
Sodomitical	O
Practices	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
But	O
these	O
Allegations	O
having	O
been	O
sufficiently	O
contradicted	O
before	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Allegations	O
of	O
several	O
Evidences	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
Boyce	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Proof	O
against	O
Godfrey	O
not	O
being	O
so	O
satisfactory	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Jepthah	B-pers
Big	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
on	O
a	O
Statue	O
made	O
in	O
the	O
9th	O
Year	O
of	O
King	O
George	O
the	O
First	O
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
sending	O
2	O
Letters	O
without	O
Names	O
,	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Newnham	I-pers
,	O
senior	O
,	O
demanding	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
85	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
2d	O
,	O
100	O
Guineas	O
,	O
containing	O
divers	O
Menaces	O
,	O
and	O
threatning	O
the	O
Life	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Newnham	I-pers
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
if	O
the	O
said	O
Sums	O
of	O
Money	O
were	O
not	O
punctually	O
sent	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Directions	O
contain	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Letter	O
.	O
The	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
having	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Cause	O
,	O
supported	O
the	O
Charge	O
by	O
the	O
following	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Salter	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
Squirrel-Alley	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
drink	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
together	O
to	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Ship	O
,	O
a	O
House	O
where	O
he	O
,	O
this	O
Evidence	O
,	O
us	O
'd	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
some	O
other	O
House	O
,	O
saying	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
particular	O
Affair	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
him	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Sieve	O
in	O
the	O
little	O
Minories	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
then	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
Peter	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
something	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
every	O
body	O
know	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
want	O
10	O
or	O
15	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
get	O
me	O
60	O
or	O
more	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
what	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
him	O
to	O
do	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
his	O
Brother	O
was	O
Coachman	O
to	O
a	O
fearful	O
Old	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
send	O
him	O
a	O
Letter	O
to	O
send	O
him	O
a	O
Parcel	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
him	O
,	O
this	O
Evidence	O
,	O
fix	O
upon	O
a	O
House	O
where	O
the	O
Parcel	O
may	O
be	O
sent	O
,	O
and	O
received	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
not	O
suspected	O
;	O
asking	O
him	O
,	O
Is	O
there	O
not	O
a	O
House	O
at	O
Billingsgate	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
use	O
,	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
of	O
Mutton	O
?	O
will	O
they	O
have	O
any	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
you	O
?	O
to	O
which	O
this	O
Evidence	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
this	O
Evidence	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
of	O
Mutton	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
the	O
Parcel	O
was	O
come	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
sit	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
for	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
a	O
Porter	O
came	O
for	O
a	O
Parcel	O
directed	O
for	O
John	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
if	O
he	O
suspected	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
immediately	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Krag's-Head	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
King's-Head-Court	O
,	O
on	O
Fishstreet-Hill	O
:	O
That	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
of	O
Mutton	O
,	O
a	O
Porter	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Paper	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
the	O
Landlord	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Here	O
is	O
a	O
Note	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Landlord	O
's	O
Son	O
came	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
his	O
Father	O
a	O
Jog	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
in	O
another	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
gave	O
the	O
Porter	O
the	O
Parcel	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
this	O
Evidence	O
,	O
seeing	O
this	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
King's-Head-Alebouse	O
,	O
and	O
acquainted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
thence	O
into	O
Moorfields	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
vex	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
disappointed	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
gotten	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
design	O
'd	O
to	O
have	O
given	O
this	O
Evidence	O
5	O
Guineas	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Three	O
Tuns	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
2	O
penny	O
worth	O
of	O
Bacon	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
was	O
disappointed	O
in	O
his	O
Design	O
now	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
write	O
him	O
another	O
Letter	O
that	O
should	O
make	O
him	O
tremble	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
2d	O
Parcel	O
should	O
be	O
directed	O
to	O
be	O
left	O
at	O
the	O
Black-Boy	O
in	O
Goodman's-Fields	O
,	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
as	O
before	O
;	O
for	O
there	O
the	O
Man	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
had	O
no	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
him	O
:	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sent	O
for	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
Day	O
of	O
April	O
to	O
the	O
Ship	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
,	O
sending	O
his	O
Name	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
something	O
for	O
Breakfast	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
had	O
2	O
Sheep	O
's	O
Tongues	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
have	O
me	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Black-Boy	O
in	O
Goodman's-Fields	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
the	O
Parcel	O
were	O
come	O
thither	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
You	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
but	O
to	O
sit	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
observe	O
whether	O
there	O
be	O
a	O
Trap	O
laid	O
to	O
catch	O
me	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Black-Boy	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
read	O
the	O
News-Paper	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
said	O
,	O
nobody	O
would	O
ever	O
appear	O
since	O
it	O
was	O
advertiz	O
'd	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
left	O
this	O
Evidence	O
at	O
the	O
Black-Boy	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
meet	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Rose	O
at	O
Algate	O
;	O
that	O
a	O
Porter	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Whitaker	O
at	O
the	O
Black-Boy	O
took	O
the	O
Note	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
rather	O
the	O
Person	O
had	O
come	O
for	O
it	O
himself	O
,	O
however	O
you	O
shall	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Man	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
Porter	O
the	O
Parcel	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
and	O
deliver	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Person	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
after	O
the	O
Porter	O
,	O
but	O
on	O
a	O
different	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
stay	O
'd	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Rose	O
at	O
Aldgate	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Trap	O
laid	O
to	O
catch	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
Brother	O
,	O
who	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Newnham	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
hard-by	O
his	O
Brother	O
's	O
,	O
they	O
din	O
'd	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Brother	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
stay	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
on	O
an	O
Errand	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
back	O
quickly	O
;	O
that	O
accordingly	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
reply	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
design	O
'd	O
to	O
come	O
away	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
You	O
have	O
complain	O
'd	O
your	O
Master	O
was	O
cross	O
and	O
peevish	O
;	O
ay	O
,	O
replies	O
the	O
Brother	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Cause	O
is	O
known	O
now	O
,	O
a	O
vile	O
Rogue	O
has	O
sent	O
him	O
a	O
Letter	O
to	O
send	O
him	O
a	O
great	O
Sum	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
threatening	O
his	O
Life	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
ay	O
,	O
a	O
vile	O
Rogue	O
indeed	O
;	O
says	O
the	O
Brother	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
an	O
Advertisement	O
of	O
it	O
:	O
That	O
afterwards	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Sieve	O
in	O
the	O
Little	O
Minories	O
,	O
and	O
read	O
the	O
Advertisement	O
;	O
that	O
from	O
thence	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
White-Swan	O
in	O
Goodman	O
's	O
Fields	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
endeavour	O
to	O
know	O
when	O
the	O
Old	O
Man	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
send	O
him	O
another	O
Letter	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
this	O
Evidence	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
you	O
will	O
meddle	O
with	O
such	O
Affairs	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
very	O
dangerous	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
You	O
need	O
not	O
fear	O
,	O
nothing	O
can	O
hurt	O
you	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
Life	O
is	O
in	O
your	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
ever	O
you	O
discover	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
share	O
the	O
same	O
Fate	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Long	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Newnham	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
a	O
Letter	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
Penny-Post	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
March	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
read	O
Part	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
read	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
same	O
Evening	O
a	O
Parcel	O
was	O
made	O
up	O
of	O
about	O
2	O
lb	O
.	O
Weight	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
Money	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
brown	O
Paper	O
,	O
directed	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
and	O
he	O
carried	O
it	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Ward	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
of	O
Mutton	O
;	O
and	O
also	O
,	O
that	O
another	O
Letter	O
came	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Hand	O
,	O
dated	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Parcel	O
was	O
made	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
directed	O
for	O
John	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
and	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Black-Boy	O
in	O
Goodman's-Fields	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Ward	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Parcel	O
was	O
left	O
with	O
him	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Long	O
,	O
directed	O
for	O
John	B-pers
