TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
At	O
the	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
And	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
;	O
For	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
26th	O
,	O
27th	O
,	O
and	O
28th	O
,	O
of	O
February	O
;	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
Monday	O
and	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
1st	O
,	O
3d	O
,	O
and	O
5th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
1728-9	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Second	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
'S	O
Reign	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
Six	O
Pence	O
.	O
)	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
ROBERT	B-pers
BAYLIS	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Cummins	I-pers
;	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Price	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Probyn	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
Raby	O
,	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
;	O
with	O
other	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
aforesaid	O
;	O
Together	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Seagood	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Alloway	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Gimber	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Tucker	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Gore	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Mayo	I-pers
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Baily	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Humphreys	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Chandler	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Coggin	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Goddard	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Rice	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Wyatt	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barnett	I-pers
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Bostock	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
several	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Christian	B-pers
Colebrank	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
Christian	B-pers
Colebrank	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
January	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
pay	O
130	O
l.	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Martin	O
,	O
but	O
remembring	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
occasion	O
for	O
some	O
Money	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
from	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Martin	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Compter	O
by	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
presently	O
he	O
saw	O
it	O
move	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
behind	O
him	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
snatch	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
pursued	O
him	O
and	O
never	O
lost	O
Sight	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
Bag	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Allen	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Bag	O
and	O
Money	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
which	O
Bag	O
and	O
Money	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
Mr.	O
Colebrank	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
carried	O
before	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
bewitch	O
'd	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
run	O
after	O
him	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
Money	O
into	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
a	O
worse	O
Excuse	O
than	O
t'other	O
,	O
and	O
neither	O
of	O
them	O
appearing	O
reasonable	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
of	O
small	O
Value	O
,	O
and	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Masters	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rudge	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Katherine	I-place
Cree-Church	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
4	O
Bodices	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
one	O
Gun	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
by	O
the	O
Directions	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
,	O
to	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
five	O
Years	O
since	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
received	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
that	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
since	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
Person	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
surrender	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
by	O
her	O
Directions	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
not	O
all	O
appearing	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Rice	B-pers
Beven	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
Crooked-Lane	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
60	O
Razors	O
,	O
283	O
Penknives	O
,	O
95	O
Ivory	O
Combs	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Willson	I-pers
;	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
one	O
Price	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
who	O
has	O
escaped	O
out	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
of	O
a	O
considerable	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Hard	O
Ware	O
,	O
and	O
Price	O
taking	O
a	O
Lodging	O
at	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Carter	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
bringing	O
Goods	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
suspected	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
likewise	O
bringing	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
like	O
Sort	O
to	O
Price	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Carter	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
by	O
the	O
Mark	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
going	O
to	O
Bevels	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
found	O
a	O
considerable	O
Quantity	O
of	O
his	O
Goods	O
there	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
of	O
Price	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Cellar	O
Window	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
single	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Willson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cag	O
of	O
strong	O
Waters	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Tower	B-place
Ward	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
42	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
Bees	O
Wax	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
single	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Bostock	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
not	O
having	O
the	O
Fear	O
of	O
God	O
before	O
her	O
Eyes	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
led	O
by	O
the	O
Malice	O
and	O
Instigation	O
of	O
the	O
Devil	O
,	O
did	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
February	O
Inst	O
.	O
kill	O
and	O
murder	O
her	O
Infant	O
male	O
Bastard	O
Child	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
was	O
then	O
privately	O
deliver	O
'd	O
.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
lodg	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Burgess	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
then	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
deliver	O
'd	O
of	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
seeing	O
her	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Necessary	O
House	O
with	O
a	O
Mop	O
and	O
other	O
Tokens	O
,	O
suspected	O
her	O
to	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
8	O
at	O
Night	O
she	O
inform	O
'd	O
her	O
Husband	O
and	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
of	O
her	O
Suspicions	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Bingley	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Child	O
in	O
the	O
Necessary	O
House	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
with	O
a	O
Stick	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Bingley	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Child	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Necessary	O
House	O
and	O
wash	O
'd	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
Pail	O
of	O
Water	O
,	O
when	O
there	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
any	O
Marks	O
of	O
Cruelty	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Burgess	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
her	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
heard	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
tax	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
before	O
this	O
Accident	O
happen	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
bid	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
mend	O
a	O
Sheet	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
so	O
employed	O
,	O
she	O
herself	O
fell	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
awaked	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
trundling	O
a	O
Mop	O
near	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
her	O
in	O
she	O
sent	O
her	O
of	O
an	O
Errand	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
found	O
something	O
that	O
gave	O
her	O
no	O
little	O
uneasiness	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Reason	O
to	O
believe	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
deliver	O
'd	O
of	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
she	O
return	O
'd	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
confess	O
it	O
;	O
however	O
,	O
she	O
proceeded	O
so	O
far	O
in	O
her	O
Searches	O
as	O
was	O
a	O
sufficient	O
demonstration	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
deny	O
it	O
no	O
longer	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
really	O
been	O
deliver	O
'd	O
of	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
's	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
soon	O
after	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
her	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
gone	O
her	O
full	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
had	O
no	O
Marks	O
or	O
Bruises	O
as	O
if	O
any	O
Violence	O
had	O
been	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Midwife	O
likewise	O
confirm	O
'd	O
this	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
all	O
agreed	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
came	O
from	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
help	O
its	O
falling	O
down	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Midwife	O
said	O
was	O
possible	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
brought	O
in	O
their	O
Verdict	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Kelly	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Owen	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Nisbitt	B-pers
,	O
of	O
Thomas-street	B-place
,	O
Drury-Lane	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
not	O
having	O
the	O
Fear	O
of	O
God	O
before	O
his	O
Eyes	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
led	O
by	O
the	O
Malice	O
and	O
Instigation	O
of	O
the	O
Devil	O
,	O
did	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
kill	O
and	O
murder	O
Robert	B-pers
Nisbitt	I-pers
,	O
with	O
a	O
Razor	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
in	O
the	O
Throat	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Length	O
of	O
10	O
Inches	O
and	O
Depth	O
of	O
4	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Murder	O
,	O
to	O
both	O
which	O
Indictments	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
before	O
the	O
Accident	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
House	O
to	O
heat	O
a	O
Glew	O
Pot	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
not	O
seeing	O
the	O
Deceas'd	O
's	O
Door	O
open	O
as	O
usual	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
Key	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
Lock	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
that	O
finding	O
the	O
Door	O
not	O
open	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
Deceas'd	O
's	O
Son	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Grandson	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
together	O
listed	O
up	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
loose	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
let	O
in	O
the	O
Deceas'd	O
's	O
Grandson	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
found	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Blood	O
on	O
the	O
Floor	O
near	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
something	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
in	O
a	O
Lump	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Nisbitt	I-pers
,	O
Grandson	O
of	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Deceas'd	O
's	O
Room	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
Morning	O
about	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
him	O
lying	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
his	O
Head	O
covered	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Breast	O
naked	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
perceived	O
he	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Blood	O
by	O
the	O
Bedside	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
it	O
had	O
ran	O
off	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
told	O
his	O
Father	O
without	O
making	O
any	O
further	O
Discovery	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Wood	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Son	O
of	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
sent	O
for	O
her	O
to	O
provide	O
a	O
Coffin	O
for	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
fear	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
murder	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Deceas'd	O
's	O
Room	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
his	O
Head	O
covered	O
,	O
his	O
Hands	O
a-cross	O
upon	O
his	O
Belly	O
,	O
his	O
Head	O
leaning	O
backwards	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Throat	O
cut	O
in	O
a	O
barbarous	O
Manner	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Blanket	O
stuffed	O
into	O
the	O
Wound	O
,	O
that	O
presently	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
a	O
Father	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
hold	O
of	O
a	O
Coat	O
and	O
3	O
Ells	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
fear	O
'd	O
it	O
was	O
well	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
dutiful	O
Son	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
know	O
the	O
Deceas'd	O
's	O
Room	O
and	O
Circumstances	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Money	O
in	O
that	O
Trunk	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
empty	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Pockets	O
were	O
turn	O
'd	O
inside	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Watch	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
this	O
was	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Archer	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
lives	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
Room	O
to	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
Morning	O
(	O
being	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
the	O
Murder	O
was	O
discover	O
'd	O
)	O
about	O
3	O
o'Clock	O
she	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Door	O
lock	O
and	O
unlock	O
twice	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
Morning	O
about	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Watchman	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
a	O
publick	O
House	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
Barnes	O
?	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
answered	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
to	O
think	O
,	O
why	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Nisbit	O
is	O
dead	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
first	O
found	O
out	O
about	O
Ten	O
o'Clock	O
that	O
Morning	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Circumstances	O
mentioned	O
by	O
the	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
how	O
he	O
heard	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
so	O
soon	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
Agnes	B-pers
Daniel	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
keeps	O
a	O
Cook	O
's	O
Shop	O
near	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
lived	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
about	O
a	O
Quarter	O
after	O
9	O
that	O
Morning	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
murdered	O
(	O
tho	O
'	O
a	O
considerable	O
Time	O
before	O
it	O
was	O
known	O
to	O
any	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
ruin	O
'd	O
and	O
undone	O
for	O
ever	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Nisbit	O
is	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
fear	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
murder	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
and	O
learn	O
how	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
half	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
he	O
return	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Nisbitt	O
was	O
murdered	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
all	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
his	O
Watch	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
his	O
best	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
opened	O
his	O
Trunk	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
two	O
Iron	O
Bolts	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
all	O
the	O
Money	O
away	O
and	O
every	O
Thing	O
else	O
but	O
a	O
Stock	O
and	O
Turnover	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Razor	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
it	O
was	O
said	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
shave	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
fear	O
'd	O
they	O
would	O
take	O
him	O
up	O
upon	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
was	O
told	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
Ten	O
o'Clock	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
Morning	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
some	O
Time	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
idle	O
Fellow	O
,	O
going	O
about	O
to	O
Alehouses	O
with	O
two	O
Jows	O
Harps	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
play	O
upon	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
a	O
grave	O
,	O
sober	O
,	O
good	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
true	O
Servant	O
of	O
God	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
at	O
Christmas	O
last	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
Dine	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
there	O
and	O
seeing	O
Mr.	O
Nisbitt	O
,	O
ran	O
out	O
again	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Nisbitt	O
seeing	O
him	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
well	O
run	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
lent	O
him	O
Money	O
to	O
buy	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
been	O
kind	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
made	O
a	O
grateful	O
Return	O
;	O
these	O
Things	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
came	O
fresh	O
into	O
her	O
Memory	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
some	O
Fear	O
he	O
was	O
guilty	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
Morning	O
about	O
two	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
mention	O
Mr.	O
Nisbitt	O
's	O
Death	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Shalley	O
the	O
Constable	O
at	O
the	O
Deceas'd	O
's	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Razor	O
with	O
which	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
murder	O
'd	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Shelley	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
about	O
12	O
,	O
or	O
betwixt	O
that	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Murder	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Sheath	O
of	O
the	O
Razor	O
upon	O
the	O
Bolster	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
,	O
he	O
,	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Watchman	O
,	O
look	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
Instrument	O
,	O
and	O
Thompson	O
found	O
the	O
Razor	O
behind	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
all	O
bloody	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
shew	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
farther	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
Morning	O
,	O
i.e	O
.	O
the	O
Morning	O
the	O
Trial	O
was	O
heard	O
,	O
one	O
Isaac	B-pers
Dale	I-pers
had	O
informed	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Presence	O
of	O
Agnes	B-pers
Daniel	I-pers
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
offered	O
two	O
Razors	O
to	O
pawn	O
or	O
sell	O
at	O
a	O
Gin	O
Shop	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
before	O
the	O
Murder	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
described	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Razors	O
,	O
which	O
exactly	O
answer	O
'd	O
the	O
Description	O
of	O
this	O
Razor	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Shelley	O
produc	O
'd	O
it	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
tied	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
towards	O
the	O
Blade	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Thread	O
,	O
the	O
Handle	O
of	O
it	O
crooked	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Rivet	O
broke	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Description	O
he	O
gave	O
without	O
seeing	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
having	O
it	O
describ	O
'd	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Dale	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
a	O
Gin	O
Shop	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
drinking	O
about	O
eight	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
begg	O
'd	O
they	O
would	O
lend	O
him	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Gin	O
on	O
2	O
Razors	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Mind	O
to	O
buy	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
remember	O
'd	O
very	O
well	O
the	O
Handle	O
was	O
tied	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
next	O
the	O
Blade	O
with	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Thread	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Handle	O
was	O
crack	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
at	O
one	O
End	O
the	O
River	O
,	O
or	O
piece	O
of	O
Pewter	O
which	O
covers	O
the	O
Rivet	O
,	O
was	O
broke	O
off	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
,	O
the	O
Razor	O
being	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
behind	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
positive	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
very	O
same	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
offer	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Gin	O
Shop	O
as	O
aforementioned	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Edwards	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
Deceas'd	O
's	O
Door	O
was	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
after	O
the	O
Murder	O
was	O
discover	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
lay	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
Yard	O
from	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
thrust	O
under	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
likewise	O
observed	O
by	O
others	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Key	O
with	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Spencer	O
opened	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
another	O
though	O
it	O
opened	O
that	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
but	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Friend	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
lent	O
him	O
Money	O
to	O
buy	O
Cloaths	O
and	O
3	O
Ells	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
pawn	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
lent	O
him	O
Money	O
to	O
fetch	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
pawn	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
give	O
no	O
satisfactory	O
Account	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Razor	O
,	O
nor	O
could	O
he	O
deny	O
being	O
with	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
Morning	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
confess	O
he	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Nisbitt	O
was	O
dead	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Journeyman	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
so	O
a	O
Year	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
Work	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
,	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
and	O
Wednesday	O
aforemention	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
sometimes	O
work	O
,	O
he	O
sometimes	O
very	O
idle	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
an	O
excellent	O
Hand	O
at	O
playing	O
upon	O
2	O
Jews	O
Harps	O
at	O
once	O
,	O
which	O
involv	O
'd	O
him	O
in	O
bad	O
Company	O
and	O
exposed	O
him	O
to	O
keep	O
ill	O
Hours	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
this	O
Murder	O
was	O
discovered	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Wedding	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
till	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
further	O
,	O
told	O
a	O
long	O
Tale	O
,	O
or	O
compound	O
of	O
Mirth	O
and	O
Madness	O
,	O
as	O
their	O
throwing	O
the	O
Stocking	O
,	O
drinking	O
,	O
dancing	O
,	O
and	O
playing	O
upon	O
the	O
Jews	O
Harps	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
for	O
3	O
d.	O
and	O
he	O
lent	O
him	O
Money	O
to	O
fetch	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
drunk	O
and	O
carried	O
the	O
Bridegroom	O
's	O
Wig	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
next	O
Morning	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
Morning	O
about	O
9	O
or	O
10	O
o	O
'	O
Clock	O
he	O
came	O
with	O
a	O
Concern	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
best	O
Friend	O
Mr.	O
Nisbitt	O
,	O
for	O
his	O
Throat	O
was	O
cut	O
.	O
He	O
call	O
'd	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
could	O
say	O
any	O
Thing	O
material	O
,	O
one	O
indeed	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
heat	O
pretended	O
to	O
invalidate	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Watchman	O
,	O
on	O
his	O
saying	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
h	O
im	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Nisbitt	O
's	O
Death	O
at	O
Two	O
o'Clock	O
on	O
the	O
Morning	O
before	O
the	O
Murder	O
or	O
his	O
Death	O
was	O
found	O
out	O
or	O
discovered	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
William	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
say	O
,	O
said	O
this	O
Deponent	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
spoke	O
a	O
silly	O
Word	O
,	O
which	O
would	O
bring	O
him	O
into	O
Trouble	O
at	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
heard	O
Peter	O
the	O
Irishman	O
say	O
,	O
(	O
that	O
was	O
a	O
Nick-name	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
by	O
)	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Nisbitt	O
was	O
dead	O
at	O
Two	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
told	O
it	O
to	O
others	O
:	O
But	O
this	O
was	O
so	O
far	O
from	O
taking	O
off	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
Barnes	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
rather	O
confirm	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
every	O
Circumstance	O
being	O
considered	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
several	O
Incidents	O
compar	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Dawkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Buck	O
Skins	O
Dress	O
'd	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
,	O
which	O
appearing	O
very	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bateman	I-pers
Long	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Tipler	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cotton	O
Apron	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Pinner	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
3d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cotton	O
Gown	O
and	O
a	O
Camblet	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
several	O
Caps	O
,	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Mercer	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
third	O
Time	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Inkley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
's	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Moidore	O
,	O
and	O
10	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Brin	I-pers
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Mother	O
of	O
Pearl	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
Shop	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
designing	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
Money	O
for	O
one	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
length	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
soon	O
after	O
taken	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Box	O
was	O
convey	O
'd	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
,	O
single	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Snell	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Deal	O
Board	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Soams	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Thornton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sheet	O
,	O
a	O
Bolster	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Iron	O
Pot	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Hooper	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
single	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Edmonds	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Harrow	B-place
on	I-place
the	I-place
Hill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Black	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Miles	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
Horse	O
was	O
in	O
keeping	O
at	O
one	O
Daniel	B-pers
Fenning	I-pers
's	O
,	O
who	O
sent	O
him	O
Word	O
the	O
Horse	O
was	O
stolen	O
away	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
advertised	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Horse	O
at	O
Justice	O
Gifford	O
's	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Fenning	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Horse	O
was	O
stolen	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Yard	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
say	O
nothing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
some	O
old	O
Iron	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
in	O
Rosemary-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
Sale	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
then	O
was	O
upon	O
a	O
Black	O
Gelding	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
some	O
Time	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
he	O
agreed	O
about	O
the	O
Price	O
of	O
the	O
Iron	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
suspecting	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
order	O
'd	O
his	O
Men	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
Paddington	O
,	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
(	O
as	O
he	O
pretended	O
)	O
the	O
Iron	O
was	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
employed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Man	O
got	O
up	O
behind	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
together	O
towards	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Master	O
's	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
still	O
being	O
dissatisfied	O
,	O
went	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
in	O
Holborn	O
they	O
got	O
off	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
then	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
enquired	O
why	O
they	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
who	O
answered	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
buy	O
some	O
Bran	O
for	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
told	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
the	O
Iron	O
was	O
stolen	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
answered	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
steal	O
the	O
Iron	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
stolen	O
the	O
Horse	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Servant	O
of	O
this	O
Deponent	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
this	O
Confession	O
.	O
He	O
made	O
a	O
very	O
idle	O
Defence	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
the	O
Horse	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
Care	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
Design	O
to	O
steal	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Constable	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunston	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Lombard	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
the	O
Bodies	O
of	O
two	O
Shifts	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
intire	O
Shift	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Lombard	I-pers
,	O
but	O
only	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
single	O
Felony	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Cotton	O
Cloth	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Linnen	O
Cloth	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Garrat	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
5	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Rum	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Garrat	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
single	O
Felony	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
3	O
Cotton	O
Shirts	O
,	O
7	O
Linnen	O
Shirts	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Benjamin	O
Green	O
,	O
and	O
only	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
single	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Pool	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sign	O
Plate	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Tomkins	I-pers
,	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
an	O
extraordinary	O
Character	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Glare	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
2	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Castain	B-pers
Standorph	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Sale	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Tollard	B-pers
,	O
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Wise	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bride	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
String	O
and	O
a	O
Seal	O
,	O
value	O
41	O
Shillings	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
Fleet-street	B-place
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
pick	O
'd	O
him	O
up	O
and	O
persuaded	O
him	O
to	O
their	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
carried	O
him	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
drank	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Rasberry	O
Brandy	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
they	O
made	O
him	O
pay	O
6	O
d.	O
that	O
afterwards	O
they	O
sate	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
's	O
Feet	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Breeches	O
were	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Watch	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Fob	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
Noise	O
and	O
the	O
Watch	O
were	O
call	O
'd	O
,	O
who	O
carried	O
him	O
and	O
his	O
Mistress	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
searched	O
the	O
Room	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Watch	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Garret	O
,	O
but	O
tho	O
'	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
lewd	O
Persons	O
,	O
(	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
much	O
better	O
)	O
yet	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
any	O
appearance	O
of	O
a	O
Robbery	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
in	O
an	O
indecent	O
Posture	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
on	O
which	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Fenn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Coleman-street	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
several	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Widdow	B-pers
Halten	I-pers
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Swash	I-pers
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Parks	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Swan	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
near	O
Chancery-Lane	B-place
in	O
Fleet-street	B-place
,	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
nothing	O
?	O
that	O
he	O
felt	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
charg	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
immediately	O
,	O
who	O
pull	O
'd	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
then	O
ran	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Hercules	O
Pillars	O
,	O
and	O
People	O
following	O
them	O
found	O
several	O
other	O
Things	O
in	O
the	O
Entry	O
,	O
which	O
it	O
was	O
suppos	O
'd	O
he	O
dropp	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
finding	O
him	O
obstinate	O
and	O
very	O
mischievous	O
,	O
tied	O
his	O
Hands	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
threatned	O
them	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
murder	O
them	O
all	O
as	O
freely	O
as	O
so	O
many	O
Dogs	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
put	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
to	O
carry	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
he	O
swore	O
,	O
if	O
his	O
Gang	O
in	O
Southwark	O
knew	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
used	O
so	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
kill	O
every	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
hang	O
'd	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
likewise	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
several	O
others	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
used	O
such	O
Expressions	O
,	O
and	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
dangerous	O
Fellow	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Crompton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Aldgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Books	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Franshaw	I-pers
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
appearing	O
their	O
Recognizance	O
was	O
estreated	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Copper	O
Coffee	O
Pot	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Shift	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Susanna	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
but	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
not	O
appearing	O
their	O
Recognizance	O
was	O
estreated	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Kelley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
8	O
Planes	O
,	O
7	O
Chissels	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Gouges	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Newell	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Katherine	B-pers
Twitt	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
Brass	O
Cocks	O
and	O
2	O
Brass	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wall	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Patience	B-pers
Westall	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
,	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
freely	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
home	O
about	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
and	O
slipp	O
'd	O
his	O
Ring	O
off	O
his	O
Finger	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
search	O
her	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
apprehended	O
her	O
immediately	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Dunn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Woollen	O
Coat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Moate	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Paul	B-pers
Anthony	I-pers
Shoot	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Crawley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
52	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Phelps	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Lythe	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
Hanover	I-place
Square	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Geldings	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
23rd	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Sentamore	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Groom	O
of	O
his	O
Stables	O
,	O
and	O
Word	O
being	O
brought	O
that	O
his	O
Horses	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
surprised	O
that	O
the	O
Door	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
apprehended	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
carrying	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Blagney	O
,	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
agreed	O
with	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Barrington	I-pers
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Horses	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Barrington	O
was	O
gone	O
off	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
bring	O
him	O
half	O
the	O
Money	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
should	O
sell	O
them	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Maccabine	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
tax	O
'd	O
with	O
stealing	O
the	O
Horses	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
what	O
would	O
be	O
the	O
Consequence	O
if	O
he	O
should	O
confess	O
,	O
that	O
afterwards	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
into	O
Justice	O
Blagney	O
's	O
Entry	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
agreed	O
with	O
Barrington	O
to	O
go	O
halves	O
in	O
the	O
Money	O
for	O
which	O
the	O
Horses	O
should	O
be	O
sold	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
Keys	O
of	O
the	O
Stables	O
to	O
Barrington	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Horses	O
away	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
likewise	O
confirmed	O
by	O
two	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Kelley	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Handcock	I-pers
.	O
He	O
made	O
a	O
trifling	O
Defence	O
very	O
little	O
to	O
the	O
Purpose	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bowls	I-pers
.	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
40	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Beef	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
considerable	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Sewet	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Staples	I-pers
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
with	O
them	O
was	O
admitted	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
his	O
Deposition	O
and	O
other	O
Proofs	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Briggs	I-pers
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Timothy	B-pers
Cotton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Marple	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
's	I-place
Hanover	I-place
Square	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Stout	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
2	O
pounds	O
of	O
Butter	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Capt	B-pers
.	I-pers
Trever	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
a	O
Stock	O
and	O
Buckle	O
,	O
5	O
Shillings	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
John	B-pers
Stout	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
at	O
about	O
Three	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Kensington	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Park	B-place
Corner	I-place
near	O
Buckingham	B-place
House	I-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
another	O
Person	O
,	O
one	O
Rowden	O
,	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
damn	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
bidding	O
him	O
deliver	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
unbuttoning	O
his	O
Cloaths	O
they	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pockets	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
then	O
tied	O
his	O
Hands	O
and	O
slung	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
Ditch	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
got	O
loose	O
,	O
and	O
pursued	O
them	O
till	O
Cotton	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
Knife	O
,	O
Buckle	O
and	O
Stock	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Kelly	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
hearing	O
the	O
Cry	O
of	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Cotton	O
,	O
running	O
,	O
he	O
stopp	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
Mr.	O
Stout	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
a	O
Garter	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
tied	O
his	O
Hands	O
,	O
and	O
Cotton	O
having	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Stockings	O
untied	O
,	O
they	O
compar	O
'd	O
the	O
Garter	O
with	O
his	O
other	O
Garter	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
exact	O
Fellows	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Piece	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
Magestrate	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
Cotton	O
pulling	O
out	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
a	O
Stock	O
and	O
Buckle	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
which	O
Stout	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
searching	O
further	O
,	O
found	O
a	O
Pistol	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
assisted	O
in	O
apprehending	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
Circumstances	O
of	O
the	O
Garters	O
,	O
Stock	O
,	O
Buckle	O
,	O
and	O
Pistol	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
likewise	O
further	O
proved	O
by	O
the	O
Depositions	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
who	O
further	O
added	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
William	B-pers
Marple	I-pers
,	O
and	O
one	O
Rowden	O
,	O
were	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Key	I-pers
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
by	O
the	O
Directions	O
of	O
Cotton	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
others	O
apprehended	O
William	B-pers
Marple	I-pers
,	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
and	O
said	O
you	O
are	O
my	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Marple	O
answered	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
begg	O
'd	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
use	O
him	O
ill	O
before	O
his	O
Mother	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
search	O
'd	O
his	O
Pockets	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
were	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
a	O
Vizard	O
Mask	O
,	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Natural	O
Wig	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
others	O
had	O
been	O
ruled	O
by	O
him	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
taken	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
blinded	O
the	O
Person	O
they	O
robb	O
'd	O
and	O
a	O
Person	O
saying	O
,	O
a	O
Man	O
was	O
a	O
Fool	O
to	O
be	O
robb	O
'd	O
by	O
such	O
Boys	O
,	O
Marple	O
said	O
,	O
had	O
he	O
seen	O
them	O
a	O
Day	O
or	O
two	O
ago	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
called	O
them	O
Men	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
made	O
six	O
Men	O
ride	O
from	O
a	O
Coach	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gough	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
like	O
Effect	O
,	O
confirming	O
every	O
Circumstance	O
with	O
the	O
former	O
Deponents	O
,	O
adding	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
William	B-pers
Marple	I-pers
was	O
before	O
Justice	O
Slaughter	O
,	O
he	O
seem	O
'd	O
inclined	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Confession	O
if	O
he	O
could-be	O
admitted	O
as	O
an	O
Evidence	O
;	O
but	O
finding	O
that	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
obtain	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
take	O
two	O
Lives	O
away	O
and	O
be	O
of	O
no	O
Service	O
to	O
himself	O
:	O
However	O
,	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
Rowden	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
Man	O
who	O
assaulted	O
Mr.	O
Stout	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
himself	O
ran	O
up	O
a	O
dirty	O
Lane	O
,	O
thinking	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
pursued	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
follow	O
him	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Place	O
.	O
Captain	O
Slaughter	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
several	O
Things	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
Cotton	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
searched	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
Stout	O
depos	O
'd	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
two	O
others	O
,	O
that	O
afterwards	O
Marple	O
was	O
brought	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
some	O
Body	O
had	O
squeak	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
should	O
now	O
be	O
Cast	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
off	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
blinded	O
Stout	O
with	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
turn	O
'd	O
him	O
2	O
or	O
three	O
Times	O
round	O
,	O
but	O
Rowden	O
would	O
not	O
consent	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
ran	O
up	O
a	O
dirty	O
Lane	O
after	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
slung	O
Stout	O
's	O
Hat	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
Park	O
Wall	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
refused	O
to	O
Sign	O
his	O
Confession	O
without	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Promise	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
that	O
at	O
another	O
Examination	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
make	O
himself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
one	O
Shaddo	O
and	O
Rowden	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
thus	O
plain	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
very	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Isabel	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Feather	O
Pillow	O
,	O
a	O
Sheet	O
and	O
a	O
Curtain	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Wynn	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
single	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Haws	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
20	O
Pence	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Banbary	B-pers
Bevis	I-pers
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Barlow	I-pers
and	O
Lucy	B-pers
Faulkner	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
10	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Moreton	I-pers
,	O
but	O
he	O
not	O
appearing	O
his	O
Recognizance	O
was	O
estreated	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Dutmash	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Salt	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Prayer-Book	O
,	O
some	O
Pewter	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Potter	I-pers
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Cutting	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Potter	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
February	O
about	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
found	O
his	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
presently	O
that	O
all	O
his	O
Servant	O
's	O
Cloaths	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
her	O
Shoes	O
,	O
an	O
old	O
pair	O
being	O
left	O
in	O
their	O
Room	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
his	O
Servant	O
formerly	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
suspected	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
Lodgings	O
in	O
Barnaby-street	O
,	O
Southwark	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
found	O
her	O
with	O
his	O
Servant	O
's	O
Shoes	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
charging	O
her	O
with	O
robbing	O
him	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
carrying	O
him	O
up	O
Stairs	O
she	O
gave	O
him	O
all	O
his	O
Goods	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
got	O
into	O
his	O
House	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
conceal	O
'd	O
in	O
a	O
Place	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Cole-hole	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
lays	O
his	O
Twopenny	O
Drink	O
(	O
being	O
a	O
Victualler	O
)	O
.	O
This	O
Confession	O
she	O
likewise	O
made	O
before	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
and	O
sign	O
'd	O
it	O
with	O
her	O
own	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Gardener	I-pers
proved	O
the	O
Confession	O
which	O
he	O
heard	O
her	O
make	O
and	O
saw	O
her	O
sign	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Oldfield	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bride	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l	O
a	O
Seal	O
and	O
String	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Weston	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Joseph	O
Weston	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
persuaded	O
him	O
down	O
Castle-Court	B-place
,	O
and	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
of	O
a	O
Watch	O
and	O
Seal	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
of	O
her	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
heard	O
of	O
his	O
Watch	O
some	O
Days	O
after	O
from	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
offer	O
'd	O
a	O
Guinea	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
help	O
him	O
to	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
into	O
her	O
House	O
and	O
enquired	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
immediately	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
directed	O
there	O
to	O
find	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
give	O
a	O
Guinea	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
have	O
his	O
Watch	O
again	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
about	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Pocket	O
and	O
shew	O
'd	O
it	O
her	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
it	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
and	O
would	O
keep	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
sold	O
the	O
Watch	O
after	O
this	O
for	O
50	O
Shillings	O
to	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Hildridge	I-pers
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Assiduity	O
of	O
this	O
Deponent	O
,	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
found	O
afterwards	O
at	O
Mr	O
.	O
Snow	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
Pawnbroker	O
.	O
The	O
Servant	O
of	O
Snow	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
in	O
Pawn	O
of	O
Hildridge	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
produced	O
,	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Watch	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Watch	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
shew	O
'd	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Adams	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
Favour	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
she	O
mentioned	O
as	O
if	O
it	O
were	O
no	O
Crime	O
)	O
and	O
he	O
prosecuted	O
her	O
because	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
admit	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Familiarity	O
again	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Boucher	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Graden	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
marrying	O
Richard	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
her	O
former	O
Husband	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
Graden	I-pers
,	O
being	O
alive	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
made	O
it	O
appear	O
that	O
John	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
Graden	I-pers
had	O
another	O
Wife	O
living	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
was	O
ignorant	O
of	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
true	O
,	O
and	O
procured	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
the	O
Register	O
she	O
thought	O
herself	O
clear	O
of	O
the	O
Matrimonial	O
Obligation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
100	O
weight	O
of	O
Fat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Featherstone	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
buying	O
and	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
but	O
Cook	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Baker	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Nuttal	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
800	O
Weight	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
;	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Porter	O
employed	O
to	O
Land	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
stole	O
the	O
Tobacco	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
but	O
on	O
another	O
Indictment	O
for	O
stealing	O
800	O
weight	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
from	O
another	O
Ship	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Oram	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
400	O
weight	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
on	O
Board	O
the	O
Ship	B-place
London	I-place
Hope	I-place
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Munkford	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Gowns	O
,	O
2	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Boden	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Everitt	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Whitechapel	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Barrel	O
of	O
Figs	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Roger	B-pers
Wallron	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samuel	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
600	O
weight	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Ship	O
Philip	B-place
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
200	O
weight	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Ship	O
Hopewell	B-place
,	O
he	O
being	O
employed	O
by	O
the	O
Merchants	O
to	O
work	O
as	O
a	O
Cooper	O
on	O
Board	O
,	O
and	O
fit	O
the	O
Hogsheads	O
to	O
be	O
brought	O
on	O
Shore	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
on	O
each	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Lighterman	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
150	O
weight	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
50	O
weight	O
,	O
and	O
200	O
weight	O
,	O
from	O
several	O
Ships	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
try	O
'd	O
on	O
3	O
several	O
Indictments	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
on	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
300	O
weight	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Lighterman	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
200	O
weight	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
and	O
70	O
weight	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
on	O
two	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Swart	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hether	I-pers
,	O
by	O
flinging	O
Salt	O
in	O
her	O
Eyes	O
,	O
which	O
so	O
grieved	O
and	O
distampered	O
the	O
said	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hether	I-pers
,	O
that	O
she	O
languished	O
from	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
to	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Month	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
with	O
Malice	O
aforethought	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Evan	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
several	O
Sums	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Jacob	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
Mary	B-pers
Dew	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Mackmasters	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Majesty	B-pers
Bess	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bride	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
considerable	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Money	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Stanton	I-pers
(	O
which	O
may	O
learn	O
him	O
a	O
little	O
Wit	O
)	O
the	O
chief	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
was	O
Sarah	O
,	O
the	O
Widow	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
Peter	B-pers
Levee	I-pers
,	O
who	O
died	O
suddenly	O
of	O
a	O
Suffocation	O
in	O
the	O
Road	O
to	O
Paddington	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
chief	O
Witnesses	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
were	O
such	O
as	O
Date	O
their	O
Widowhood	O
from	O
Execution	O
Day	O
,	O
in	O
particular	O
,	O
the	O
Widow	O
of	O
the	O
famous	O
Thomas	B-pers
Neaves	I-pers
;	O
notwithstanding	O
they	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
Persons	O
of	O
infamous	O
Characters	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Mackmasters	I-pers
was	O
acquitted	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Stokes	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Rings	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Male	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
old	O
Iron	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
born	O
Blind	O
and	O
am	O
so	O
still	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
buy	O
the	O
Iron	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
buy	O
it	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Neal	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
buy	O
the	O
Iron	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
Deaf	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
hear	O
the	O
Bargain	O
,	O
an	O
Ear	O
for	O
an	O
Eye	O
exchanged	O
betwixt	O
these	O
Deponents	O
,	O
would	O
have	O
confirmed	O
the	O
Matter	O
more	O
substantially	O
;	O
however	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
both	O
for	O
and	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
so	O
ready	O
at	O
Swearing	O
he	O
was	O
set	O
aside	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
9	O
Bottles	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Note	O
,	O
This	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
Tidewaiter	O
,	O
or	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
they	O
Deal	O
by	O
Wholesale	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Curtis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Looking-Glass	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Humphrey	B-pers
Moorsides	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Table-cloth	O
and	O
two	O
Aprons	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Allison	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Coats	O
,	O
two	O
Waistcoats	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Samuel	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Edgings	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
200	O
weight	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
but	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Trotter	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
and	O
a	O
considerable	O
Quantity	O
of	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Giles	B-pers
Rawlings	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
great	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
in	O
three	O
several	O
Indictments	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
of	O
each	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Dimsdale	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cheese	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Woodman	I-pers
,	O
which	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
long	O
'd	O
for	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Shirt	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Jarvis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Saw	O
and	O
an	O
Ax	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Doddington	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Durham	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Ewe	O
Sheep	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Owner	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jones	B-pers
Sherley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Planes	O
and	O
a	O
Saw	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jonas	B-pers
Verner	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Andersby	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Fork	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
Hounourable	O
James	B-pers
,	O
Earl	B-pers
Abercol	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Aprons	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Marriot	I-pers
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Nodder	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
and	O
acquitte	O
d.	O
William	B-pers
Cryer	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
returning	O
from	O
Transportation	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mash	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
Shirts	O
and	O
two	O
Aprons	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Pennings	I-pers
and	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
buying	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
315	O
weight	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
knowing	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
Pair	O
of	O
Scissars	O
,	O
some	O
Razors	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Friend	I-pers
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
ripping	O
off	O
22	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Liddal	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Turton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
wilful	O
and	O
corrupt	O
Perjury	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Marsden	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
counterfeiting	O
and	O
forging	O
a	O
Note	O
of	O
5	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
on	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Gladman	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Holdford	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cheese	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Less	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Oliver	B-pers
Varmun	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Keys	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Chad	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Cotton	O
Ribbs	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Stockford	I-pers
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Valantine	B-pers
Coltis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
James	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
not	O
certain	O
when	O
he	O
apprehended	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
stole	O
the	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
indicted	O
him	O
on	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
ordered	O
him	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
his	O
Indictment	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Edmonds	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Pladwell	I-pers
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Roger	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
20	O
Moidores	O
and	O
30	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hale	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Overbury	I-pers
,	O
but	O
by	O
some	O
Management	O
or	O
other	O
no	O
Prosecutor	O
appeared	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cummins	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
dead	O
Lamb	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Odle	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Wynn	I-pers
,	O
with	O
Intent	O
to	O
commit	O
the	O
heinous	O
Sin	O
of	O
Sodomy	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Roger	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
was	O
again	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
20	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Sudor	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Sudor	I-pers
;	O
but	O
the	O
chief	O
Evidence	O
who	O
should	O
have	O
appeared	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
gone	O
or	O
sent	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
a	O
Year	O
since	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
good	O
Fortune	O
,	O
once	O
more	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Mace	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Dawling	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hackney	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Humphry	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
4	O
Moidores	O
,	O
a	O
Broad	O
Piece	O
,	O
14	O
Guineas	O
,	O
9	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Humphrey	O
Wood	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
three	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
after	O
breaking	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
came	O
forcibly	O
into	O
his	O
Bed-Chamber	O
,	O
with	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
a	O
Lighted	O
Candle	O
in	O
his	O
left	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
drawn	O
Sword	O
in	O
his	O
Right	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
for	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
Money	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
then	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
Cook	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
him	O
?	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
answered	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
Cook	O
said	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
if	O
I	O
thought	O
you	O
did	O
I	O
'd	O
kill	O
you	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
then	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
found	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
out	O
a	O
Pane	O
of	O
Glass	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
Casement	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
they	O
entered	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
fast	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
on	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
they	O
came	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
1	O
or	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
when	O
he	O
heard	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
being	O
remarkable	O
Persons	O
and	O
all	O
in	O
Soldiers	O
Waistcoats	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
leaving	O
the	O
Town	O
he	O
pursued	O
'em	O
to	O
Wolverhampton	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
saw	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Monday	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
Persons	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
drawn	O
up	O
in	O
Ranks	O
,	O
(	O
being	O
listed	O
for	O
Soldiers	O
)	O
when	O
he	O
caused	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
apprehended	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Wood	O
,	O
and	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Son-in-Law	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
Persons	O
who	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
House	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
tied	O
them	O
all	O
with	O
Cords	O
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Monday	O
,	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
latter	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Evidence	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
,	O
only	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
produce	O
no	O
Witnesses	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
,	O
or	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
for	O
their	O
Character	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
all	O
three	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Geahogan	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Katherine	B-pers
Geahogan	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Gorgon	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Fryer	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bride	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
in	O
counterfeiting	O
and	O
making	O
13	O
pieces	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
Shillings	O
,	O
of	O
Copper	O
,	O
Tin	O
,	O
Brass	O
,	O
Pewter	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
mix	O
'd	O
Metals	O
,	O
bearing	O
the	O
Stamp	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
after	O
the	O
Likeness	O
and	O
Similitude	O
of	O
the	O
current	O
Coin	O
of	O
Great	O
Britain	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
making	O
6	O
other	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
Six-pences	O
,	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
and	O
knowing	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
be	O
false	O
,	O
base	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
counterfeit	O
,	O
putting	O
off	O
the	O
said	O
Money	O
for	O
the	O
current	O
Coin	O
of	O
Great	O
Britain	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
(	O
being	O
admitted	O
an	O
Evidence	O
)	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
in	O
November	O
last	O
he	O
first	O
became	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Blake	O
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Geahogan	I-pers
,	O
and	O
one	O
Ferris	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Temple	B-place
Muse	I-place
in	O
White	B-place
Fryers	I-place
,	O
where	O
Blake	O
kept	O
a	O
Fencing	O
School	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
that	O
Time	O
Geahogan	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
counterfeit	O
Sixpence	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
put	O
it	O
off	O
for	O
2	O
Quarts	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
they	O
all	O
commended	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
discover	O
'd	O
and	O
brought	O
back	O
by	O
the	O
Servant	O
;	O
that	O
after	O
this	O
Blake	O
advis	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
to	O
steal	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Plate	O
,	O
saving	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
convert	O
it	O
into	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
Half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
he	O
would	O
learn	O
him	O
to	O
make	O
Money	O
of	O
hard	O
Pewter	O
,	O
Brass	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Materials	O
,	O
with	O
Glass	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
ring	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
with	O
Blake	O
and	O
Ferris	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
Henry	O
Geahogan	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
Katherine	B-pers
Geahogan	I-pers
,	O
his	O
Mother	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
out	O
a	O
Gallipot	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
hard	O
Mettal	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
melting	O
Ladle	O
,	O
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Geahogan	I-pers
held	O
it	O
whilst	O
his	O
Mother	O
blow	O
'd	O
the	O
Fire	O
;	O
that	O
it	O
soon	O
melted	O
,	O
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Geahogan	I-pers
poured	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
Mould	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
Shilling	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
12	O
more	O
,	O
bearing	O
the	O
Impression	O
of	O
King	O
William	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
in	O
like	O
Manner	O
they	O
made	O
fix	O
Sixpences	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Sort	O
of	O
Mettal	O
,	O
that	O
Blake	O
made	O
Notches	O
with	O
a	O
File	O
on	O
the	O
Edges	O
,	O
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Geahogan	I-pers
was	O
the	O
Finisher	O
;	O
that	O
soon	O
after	O
,	O
Blake	O
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Geahogan	I-pers
,	O
Ferris	O
,	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
that	O
goes	O
for	O
Blake	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
went	O
together	O
to	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Bignel	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
Pawnbroker	O
,	O
where	O
Blake	O
pawn	O
'd	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
his	O
Cloaths	O
for	O
five	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
good	O
Shilling	O
from	O
the	O
five	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
a	O
counterfeit	O
Shilling	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
4	O
,	O
went	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
Pawnbroker	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
a	O
bad	O
Shilling	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
changed	O
,	O
upon	O
his	O
swearing	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
Ferris	O
chang	O
'd	O
another	O
bad	O
Shilling	O
that	O
Morning	O
at	O
a	O
Brandy	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
bid	O
him	O
change	O
another	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
in	O
Church-Lane	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Landlady	O
perceived	O
it	O
was	O
bad	O
and	O
refused	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
Blake	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
and	O
made	O
7	O
Half	O
Crowns	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Mettal	O
as	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Sixpences	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
next	O
Money	O
they	O
made	O
was	O
agreed	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
this	O
Deponent	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
consented	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
liking	O
the	O
Course	O
of	O
Life	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
Information	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
discovering	O
the	O
whole	O
Villany	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
them	O
taken	O
into	O
Custody	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Sharpless	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
by	O
Steward	O
's	O
Information	O
to	O
his	O
Room	O
,	O
with	O
others	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Henry	B-pers
Geahogan	I-pers
there	O
sitting	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
16	O
counterfeit	O
Sixpences	O
upon	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
unfinished	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
found	O
a	O
Tub	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
Moulds	O
,	O
Files	O
,	O
Crucibles	O
,	O
a	O
Ladle	O
,	O
several	O
Sorts	O
of	O
Metal	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Materials	O
for	O
their	O
Purpose	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
then	O
Geahogan	O
seem	O
'd	O
in	O
great	O
Surprize	O
,	O
insomuch	O
that	O
the	O
Sweat	O
ran	O
down	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
Blake	O
's	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
by	O
a	O
Charcoal	O
Fire	O
made	O
in	O
a	O
Chavendish	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
put	O
a	O
Pan	O
of	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Bacon	O
in	O
a	O
Pan	O
,	O
but	O
neither	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
warm	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
him	O
believe	O
they	O
were	O
put	O
on	O
upon	O
the	O
Surprize	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
put	O
in	O
upon	O
his	O
coming	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
however	O
,	O
nothing	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Room	O
but	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Vitorel	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Jacock	O
confirm	O
'd	O
every	O
Part	O
of	O
this	O
Evidence	O
,	O
adding	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
to	O
Geahogan	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
Steward	O
,	O
I	O
little	O
thought	O
you	O
would	O
have	O
took	O
my	O
Life	O
away	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
assisted	O
in	O
taking	O
Blake	O
and	O
said	O
as	O
was	O
mentioned	O
before	O
on	O
that	O
Occasion	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Sharpless	O
,	O
who	O
likewise	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Lodgings	O
of	O
Katherine	B-pers
Geahogan	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
there	O
a	O
Paper	O
of	O
mix	O
'd	O
Metal	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
a	O
File	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Edges	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
appearance	O
of	O
the	O
Metal	O
.	O
Most	O
of	O
the	O
Circumstances	O
were	O
likewise	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
Mr.	O
King	O
,	O
who	O
assisted	O
in	O
taking	O
them	O
.	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Cope	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
kept	O
the	O
Temple	O
Muse	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
White	O
Fryers	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
bad	O
6	O
d.	O
was	O
brought	O
by	O
Steward	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Servant	O
Maid	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
carried	O
it	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
Geahogan	O
gave	O
her	O
another	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Bignel	O
the	O
Pawnbroker	O
produced	O
the	O
bad	O
Shilling	O
she	O
had	O
of	O
Blake	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
swore	O
by	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
some	O
Imprecations	O
because	O
she	O
scrupled	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
she	O
heard	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
say	O
,	O
we	O
have	O
put	O
the	O
Bite	O
upon	O
the	O
Mort	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Ferry	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Blake	O
paid	O
her	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
a	O
Shilling	O
and	O
a	O
Sixpence	O
and	O
returned	O
them	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Little	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
bad	O
Sixpence	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Geahogan	I-pers
,	O
or	O
at	O
least	O
he	O
offered	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
another	O
Time	O
he	O
offered	O
him	O
a	O
bad	O
Shilling	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
broke	O
and	O
flung	O
away	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Pinkney	O
,	O
Deputy	O
Warden	O
of	O
the	O
Mint	O
,	O
examined	O
the	O
Moulds	O
and	O
other	O
Tools	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
his	O
Opinion	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
for	O
counterfeiting	O
Money	O
.	O
Blake	O
made	O
a	O
long	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
prove	O
he	O
was	O
innocent	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Whole	O
was	O
a	O
Contrivance	O
of	O
Steward	O
's	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
Malice	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Geahogan	I-pers
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
Steward	O
had	O
contrived	O
all	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Hand	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Katherine	B-pers
Geahogan	I-pers
,	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
proved	O
her	O
Son	O
Henry	O
a	O
most	O
accomplish	O
'd	O
Villain	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Deposition	O
of	O
Rachael	B-pers
Abbot	I-pers
,	O
who	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
beat	O
his	O
Mother	O
in	O
a	O
most	O
barbarous	O
Manner	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
End	O
was	O
,	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
Steward	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
Katherine	B-pers
Geahogan	I-pers
at	O
the	O
Time	O
he	O
said	O
she	O
assisted	O
in	O
making	O
Money	O
,	O
for	O
said	O
they	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
intercede	O
with	O
the	O
Mother	O
for	O
the	O
Son	O
's	O
enlargement	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Discourse	O
,	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
Mother	O
,	O
or	O
had	O
ever	O
seen	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
Jan.	O
but	O
Steward	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
assisted	O
in	O
making	O
Money	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
February	O
:	O
Several	O
gave	O
her	O
an	O
extraordinary	O
Character	O
,	O
for	O
an	O
industrious	O
sober	O
Person	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bowen	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Bag	O
,	O
48	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
7	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Fardell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	B-pers
Fardell	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
he	O
put	O
the	O
Money	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
in	O
his	O
Till	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
leaving	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
his	O
Errand	O
Boy	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Waring	I-pers
,	O
only	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
return	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
the	O
Till	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
advertised	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
News	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
apprehended	O
at	O
Oxford	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
himself	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
the	O
Mayor	O
,	O
and	O
recovered	O
the	O
best	O
Part	O
of	O
his	O
Money	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
then	O
and	O
there	O
confessed	O
his	O
taking	O
the	O
Whole	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Waring	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
his	O
Master	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
the	O
Till	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
must	O
go	O
down	O
to	O
Breakfast	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
ready	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
first	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
back	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
return	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
his	O
Master	O
return	O
'd	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
discovered	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Keeper	O
of	O
Oxford	O
Goal	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
opened	O
the	O
Till	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Bag	O
of	O
Money	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Sparrow	I-pers
,	O
and	O
George	B-pers
Galey	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
George	B-pers
Canfield	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
one	O
Guinea	O
in	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Silver	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Groom	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Willsden	I-place
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
a	O
Whip	O
,	O
one	O
Shilling	O
and	O
three	O
Pence	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Groom	I-pers
,	O
and	O
20	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stansby	I-pers
.	O
George	B-pers
Canfield	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
George	B-pers
Galey	I-pers
attack	O
'd	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
whilst	O
Sparrow	O
and	O
another	O
robb	O
'd	O
his	O
Friend	O
John	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
,	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
Galey	O
said	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
would	O
shoot	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
his	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
from	O
him	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Foreman	I-pers
being	O
admitted	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
disappointed	O
in	O
receiving	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
his	O
Complaint	O
to	O
Galey	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
Money	O
owing	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
receive	O
it	O
he	O
would	O
lend	O
it	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
consented	O
to	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
a	O
Day	O
or	O
two	O
after	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
Galey	O
brought	O
Sparrow	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
all	O
mounted	O
and	O
rode	O
towards	O
Edger	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Bushey	O
Heath	O
Galey	O
discover	O
'd	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
true	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
drive	O
the	O
Road	O
before	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Pistol	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
,	O
not	O
suspecting	O
their	O
Purpose	O
before	O
,	O
knowing	O
Galey	O
lived	O
by	O
selling	O
Brandy	O
about	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
yet	O
seeing	O
him	O
resolute	O
,	O
and	O
fearing	O
they	O
would	O
use	O
him	O
ill	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
should	O
refuse	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Pistol	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
with	O
the	O
atmost	O
reluctance	O
,	O
that	O
presently	O
they	O
met	O
3	O
Men	O
on	O
Horseback	O
whom	O
they	O
resolved	O
to	O
attack	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
prevailed	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
decline	O
it	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
equal	O
in	O
Number	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
hazardous	O
;	O
that	O
afterwards	O
they	O
met	O
a	O
single	O
Person	O
,	O
and	O
Galey	O
clapp	O
'd	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
his	O
Breast	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
led	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
Sparrow	O
guarding	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Pistol	O
;	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
Dusky	O
he	O
got	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
Spurs	O
to	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
pursued	O
and	O
overtook	O
him	O
,	O
Galey	O
clapp	O
'd	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
his	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Rogue	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
Mind	O
to	O
leave	O
him	O
dead	O
on	O
the	O
Spot	O
;	O
that	O
to	O
save	O
his	O
Life	O
he	O
protested	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Design	O
to	O
leave	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
Sight	O
of	O
them	O
by	O
Accident	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
hazy	O
;	O
that	O
Galey	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
'd	O
forgive	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
'd	O
rob	O
the	O
first	O
Man	O
they	O
met	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
they	O
met	O
the	O
two	O
Prosecutors	O
,	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
two	O
Indictments	O
;	O
that	O
after	O
they	O
robb	O
'd	O
two	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Boy	O
,	O
suppos	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
his	O
Grace	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Chandois	O
,	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
ride	O
off	O
,	O
which	O
Galey	O
perceiving	O
,	O
hid	O
him	O
follow	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Boy	O
gave	O
him	O
18	O
Pence	O
,	O
but	O
Galey	O
made	O
him	O
search	O
the	O
Boy	O
for	O
more	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
a	O
half	O
Guinea	O
;	O
that	O
after	O
this	O
Day	O
's	O
Exploits	O
Galey	O
and	O
Sparrow	O
insisted	O
upon	O
his	O
going	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Practice	O
being	O
contrary	O
to	O
his	O
Inclinations	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
Information	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
them	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
assisting	O
in	O
apprehending	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
in	O
Galey	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
two	O
Brace	O
of	O
Pistols	O
,	O
loaded	O
with	O
Powder	O
and	O
Ball	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Groom	I-pers
swore	O
positively	O
to	O
their	O
Persons	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
by	O
them	O
and	O
the	O
several	O
Persons	O
concerned	O
in	O
taking	O
them	O
confirmed	O
the	O
Deposition	O
of	O
Foreman	O
,	O
in	O
that	O
Part	O
of	O
their	O
being	O
apprehended	O
by	O
his	O
Information	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Pistols	O
being	O
found	O
loaded	O
at	O
Galey	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Depositions	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Robberies	O
were	O
committed	O
about	O
3	O
Miles	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
from	O
London	O
,	O
half	O
a	O
Mile	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
Killbourn	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Mile	O
or	O
more	O
on	O
this	O
side	O
the	O
five	O
Mile	O
Stone	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Essington	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
Wandsworth	B-place
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
Merchant	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
and	O
brought	O
to	O
Trial	O
,	O
pursuant	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
Prayer	O
,	O
for	O
concealing	O
2	O
Books	O
of	O
Accompts	O
from	O
the	O
Commissioners	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
declared	O
a	O
Bankrupt	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Avery	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Broadstreet	O
,	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
prove	O
him	O
a	O
Trader	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
James	O
Duke	O
Crisp	O
,	O
of	O
Wandsworth	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Avery	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
bought	O
and	O
sold	O
Goods	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Essington	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
produce	O
no	O
Evidence	O
of	O
his	O
having	O
any	O
such	O
Orders	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Essington	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
upon	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Rolsey	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
whither	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
bought	O
some	O
Brandy	O
,	O
he	O
declar	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Bill	O
of	O
Parcels	O
and	O
Receipt	O
were	O
both	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Avery	O
's	O
own	O
Name	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Essington	O
's	O
being	O
any	O
way	O
concern	O
'd	O
.	O
Crisp	O
spoke	O
to	O
his	O
Trading	O
in	O
general	O
,	O
but	O
supported	O
by	O
no	O
other	O
Evidence	O
but	O
his	O
own	O
.	O
The	O
Commission	O
itself	O
was	O
produced	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
Mr	O
.	O
Crisp	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
1727	O
,	O
denied	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Essington	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
own	O
Order	O
,	O
to	O
one	O
Devon	O
at	O
the	O
Copper	O
Office	O
in	O
Bush-Lane	O
,	O
but	O
Devon	O
,	O
on	O
his	O
Examination	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
certain	O
to	O
the	O
Day	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
Trading	O
and	O
Act	O
of	O
Bankruptcy	O
rest	O
'd	O
wholly	O
on	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Avery	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Crisp	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Essington	O
resting	O
it	O
there	O
,	O
desired	O
they	O
would	O
proceed	O
to	O
the	O
Concealments	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Crisp	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
a	O
Book	O
of	O
13	O
Inches	O
long	O
and	O
4	O
wide	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Essington	O
made	O
Entries	O
of	O
all	O
his	O
Promissary	O
and	O
Negotiable	O
Notes	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
Avery	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
Jan.	O
1727	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
that	O
Book	O
was	O
not	O
amongst	O
his	O
Books	O
and	O
Papers	O
delivered	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Commissioners	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
Cross-examined	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
name	O
one	O
single	O
Item	O
in	O
the	O
pretended	O
Book	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Avery	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
a	O
Marble	O
colour	O
'd	O
Quarto	O
writing	O
Book	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
believed	O
Mr.	O
Essington	O
had	O
made	O
Entries	O
of	O
their	O
Accompts	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
check	O
'd	O
his	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Avery	O
's	O
Accompts	O
thereby	O
at	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-Yard	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
,	O
upon	O
a	O
Cross-examination	O
could	O
not	O
name	O
one	O
single	O
Article	O
therein	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
formely	O
a	O
Coachman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Essington	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
had	O
seen	O
Mr.	O
Essington	O
make	O
several	O
Entries	O
in	O
a	O
Book	O
or	O
Books	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
Contents	O
.	O
Several	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
,	O
but	O
theirs	O
was	O
all	O
hearsay	O
,	O
and	O
nothing	O
of	O
their	O
own	O
Knowledge	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Essington	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
had	O
obtained	O
an	O
Order	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
for	O
Liberty	O
to	O
inspect	O
his	O
Books	O
and	O
Papers	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
detain	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
Extremity	O
,	O
on	O
Pretence	O
they	O
were	O
too	O
numerous	O
to	O
be	O
brought	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
the	O
Trial	O
came	O
on	O
they	O
brought	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
Sack	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Essington	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
denied	O
ever	O
having	O
a	O
Book	O
13	O
Inches	O
long	O
and	O
4	O
wide	O
,	O
but	O
admitted	O
he	O
had	O
such	O
a	O
Marble	O
colour	O
'd	O
Book	O
as	O
describ	O
'd	O
by	O
David	B-pers
Avery	I-pers
,	O
and	O
very	O
plainly	O
proved	O
the	O
Delivery	O
thereof	O
by	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
assisted	O
in	O
making	O
out	O
his	O
Accompts	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Depositions	O
before	O
the	O
Commissioners	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
several	O
Letters	O
to	O
support	O
the	O
Charges	O
in	O
his	O
Accompts	O
against	O
Crisp	O
and	O
Avery	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
to	O
produce	O
the	O
Papers	O
deliver	O
'd	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
not	O
doing	O
,	O
he	O
proved	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Goostree	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Thornley	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Horan	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
given	O
Notice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hurdman	O
Attorney	O
to	O
the	O
Commission	O
,	O
to	O
produce	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
themselves	O
had	O
examined	O
all	O
the	O
Papers	O
he	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Marble	O
colour	O
'd	O
Book	O
Mark	O
'd	O
K	O
Numb	O
.	O
7.	O
in	O
the	O
Examination	O
before	O
the	O
Commissioners	O
,	O
and	O
28	O
material	O
Letters	O
under	O
Crisp	O
's	O
own	O
Hand	O
,	O
to	O
support	O
the	O
said	O
Accompts	O
,	O
were	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
amongst	O
them	O
,	O
though	O
Letter	O
K	O
,	O
Numb	O
8	O
,	O
and	O
9	O
,	O
were	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
acting	O
Commissioners	O
being	O
present	O
,	O
gave	O
the	O
Court	O
a	O
full	O
Account	O
of	O
what	O
passed	O
before	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
being	O
examined	O
to	O
the	O
threatning	O
Expressions	O
Crisp	O
had	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
,	O
if	O
Mr.	O
Essington	O
would	O
not	O
screen	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
very	O
great	O
Character	O
given	O
him	O
by	O
a	O
great	O
Number	O
of	O
Persons	O
of	O
Honour	O
and	O
Distinction	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
short	O
Time	O
,	O
after	O
a	O
Trial	O
of	O
7	O
Hours	O
,	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Not	O
guilty	O
,	O
which	O
gave	O
a	O
general	O
Satisfaction	O
,	O
it	O
appearing	O
a	O
scandalous	O
and	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
carried	O
on	O
by	O
the	O
Debtors	O
to	O
his	O
Estate	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
,	O
Hanah	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Hozel	B-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Geabogan	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Gorgan	B-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Ferris	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
in	O
counterfeiting	O
the	O
current	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
in	O
particular	O
7	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
bearing	O
the	O
Similitude	O
of	O
Half	O
Crowns	O
,	O
and	O
Six	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Money	O
call	O
'd	O
Sixpences	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
putting	O
off	O
the	O
said	O
Money	O
for	O
good	O
Coin	O
,	O
knowing	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
be	O
false	O
and	O
counterfeit	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
,	O
was	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Robert	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Geahogan	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Katherine	B-pers
Geahogan	I-pers
,	O
(	O
who	O
before	O
was	O
an	O
Evidence	O
in	O
this	O
Prosecution	O
)	O
the	O
former	O
Part	O
of	O
his	O
Evidence	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
former	O
Trial	O
,	O
of	O
his	O
becoming	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Blake	O
,	O
Geahogan	O
,	O
and	O
Ferris	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
Fact	O
for	O
which	O
they	O
stood	O
indicted	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
Two	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
Blake	O
,	O
Ferris	O
,	O
Geahogan	O
,	O
and	O
himself	O
,	O
jointly	O
agreed	O
to	O
make	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
all	O
assisted	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
Geahogan	O
made	O
the	O
Moulds	O
,	O
and	O
Ferris	O
struck	O
in	O
the	O
Nails	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
straitned	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
Blake	O
's	O
Wife	O
held	O
the	O
Tobacco-pipe	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
mix	O
'd	O
,	O
base	O
Metal	O
was	O
melted	O
,	O
that	O
Blake	O
and	O
himself	O
by	O
Turns	O
blow	O
'd	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
that	O
Ferris	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
a	O
good	O
Half	O
Crown	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
Moulds	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
fill	O
'd	O
with	O
Whiting	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
made	O
the	O
Impression	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
then	O
they	O
cast	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
Half	O
Crowns	O
of	O
mix	O
'd	O
Metal	O
,	O
when	O
Ferris	O
took	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
advised	O
them	O
to	O
carry	O
only	O
one	O
bad	O
piece	O
of	O
Money	O
about	O
them	O
at	O
a	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
good	O
Piece	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
any	O
Trouble	O
should	O
come	O
upon	O
them	O
he	O
would	O
bring	O
them	O
off	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
Attorney	O
and	O
understood	O
the	O
Law	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
after	O
this	O
they	O
made	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
Sixpences	O
he	O
likewise	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
Blake	O
put	O
off	O
some	O
counterfeit	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
Ferris	O
put	O
off	O
two	O
.	O
And	O
to	O
confirm	O
the	O
Particulars	O
,	O
he	O
produced	O
the	O
same	O
Witnesses	O
as	O
were	O
call	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
former	O
Trial	O
.	O
Ferris	O
brought	O
two	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
severally	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
February	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
them	O
at	O
Westminster	O
from	O
Two	O
till	O
Four	O
,	O
and	O
produced	O
a	O
Note	O
which	O
he	O
wrote	O
that	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
dated	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
was	O
not	O
believed	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
who	O
brought	O
him	O
,	O
Geahogan	O
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
,	O
in	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
Blake	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Humble	I-pers
,	O
formerly	O
convicted	O
.	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
ended	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
follows	O
:	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
16.	O
Peter	B-pers
Kelly	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Edmonds	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Lythe	I-pers
,	O
Timothy	B-pers
Cotton	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Marple	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Dudmash	I-pers
,	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Oldfield	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Mase	I-pers
,	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Dauling	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Geahogan	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bowen	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Sparrow	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Galey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Fernis	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
1.	O
Mary	B-pers
Humble	I-pers
,	O
formerly	O
convicted	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
1.	O
John	B-pers
Kelly	I-pers
.	O
Transportation	O
48.	O
Henry	B-pers
Bostock	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Masters	I-pers
Rice	B-pers
Revan	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Daukins	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Tipler	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Snell	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Thornton	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Constable	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Glare	I-pers
,	O
Martha	B-pers
Fenn	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Parks	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Inkley	I-pers
,	O
Katherine	B-pers
Twitt	I-pers
,	O
Patience	B-pers
Westall	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Dunn	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Meake	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Crawley	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bowles	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Nuttal	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Munkford	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Everit	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
,	O
Evan	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Dew	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Stokes	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Curtis	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Trotter	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Dimsdale	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
