TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
:	O
AND	O
On	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
21st	O
,	O
22d	O
,	O
23d	O
,	O
and	O
24th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
1729	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Second	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
Six	O
Pence	O
.	O
)	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
ROBERT	B-pers
BAYLIS	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Worshipful	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Page	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
Raby	O
,	O
Deputy-Recorder	O
;	O
with	O
others	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
;	O
Together	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Phil	B-pers
Crushard	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Fillebrown	I-pers
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Sejourney	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Greg	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
.	O
Dan	B-pers
Town	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Clayton	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Hoar	I-pers
.	O
Martin	B-pers
Wardel	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Pitt	I-pers
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Price	I-pers
.	O
James	B-pers
King	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
King	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stanley	I-pers
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Kentish	I-pers
John	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
.	O
Christ	B-pers
Thornton	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Ansun	I-pers
.	O
Arthur	B-pers
Rawlinson	I-pers
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Sanders	I-pers
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Holms	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Lever	I-pers
,	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samuel	B-pers
Eggletton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Half-Crown	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Wounlaten	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
May	O
;	O
which	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Peter	B-pers
Crompton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Thomas	B-pers
Coxon	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
:	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Masham	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Linnen	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Desborough	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Littler	I-pers
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Hannah	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
marrying	O
Henry	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
,	O
her	O
first	O
Husband	O
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Millard	I-pers
,	O
beng	O
living	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
first	O
Marriage	O
being	O
not	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
they	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cock	O
and	O
Hens	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Freelove	I-pers
,	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Tweed	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Mare	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Smorthwait	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
a	O
Snuff	O
Box	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
not	O
amounting	O
to	O
a	O
full	O
Proof	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
Mordecai	B-pers
Jonas	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Delaval	I-pers
the	O
22d	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
,	O
Tea	O
,	O
Coffee	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Hands	O
of	O
several	O
Persons	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
disposed	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Comkins	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Nore	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary-White-Chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
Value	O
50	O
s.	O
a	O
Snuff-Box	O
and	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Downing	I-pers
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
Deficiency	O
in	O
the	O
Evidence	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Katherine	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Jonas	B-pers
Grey	I-pers
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Blakesly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Leicester	I-pers
the	O
14th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
the	O
20th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Moor	I-pers
the	O
30th	O
of	O
April	O
;	O
but	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Judith	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Estrick	I-pers
the	O
31st	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Body	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Girling	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Black	I-pers
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Which	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Gallon	O
Pot	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Edmunds	I-pers
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Jones	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
Hanover-Square	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Livery-Coat	O
and	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Coach-House	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Lord	I-pers
Viscount	I-pers
Tracy	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Bridget	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
30	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Sail-Cloth	O
Yarn	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Radbourn	I-pers
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
his	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hilton	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hilton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
whereas	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Girling	I-pers
had	O
stolen	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Black	I-pers
,	O
she	O
did	O
receive	O
them	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
pawned	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
being	O
made	O
to	O
appear	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
King	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Janeway	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealling	O
two	O
Moidores	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
Guineas	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
having	O
receiv	O
'd	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
something	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
there	O
claim	O
'd	O
some	O
Acquaintance	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
mentioned	O
a	O
particular	O
Place	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
Left	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sat	O
on	O
his	O
Left	O
Hand	O
;	O
that	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
drank	O
some	O
Time	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sure	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
taxing	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
a	O
Guinea	O
was	O
drop	O
'd	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
taking	O
a	O
Candle	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
saying	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Shilling	O
,	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Bed	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
she	O
were	O
Acquaintance	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
her	O
gone	O
to	O
Smithfield	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
,	O
her	O
Shoes	O
being	O
bad	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
Money	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
his	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
Whether	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
some	O
familiar	O
Conversation	O
,	O
between	O
them	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
drinking	O
?	O
He	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
She	O
laid	O
her	O
Leg	O
over	O
his	O
Thigh	O
for	O
about	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
;	O
but	O
though	O
he	O
was	O
inclined	O
to	O
Drinking	O
,	O
yet	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
such	O
Conversation	O
with	O
her	O
as	O
was	O
suspected	O
;	O
for	O
being	O
Old	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Call	O
that	O
Way	O
.	O
There	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Scales	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
Value	O
50	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
having	O
been	O
drinking	O
at	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
Home	O
about	O
11	O
a-Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
sat	O
down	O
on	O
his	O
own	O
Bench	O
and	O
fell	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
waked	O
his	O
Watch	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
having	O
Notice	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
by	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
at	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
on	O
Tower-Hill	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
thither	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
You	O
old	O
Rogue	O
,	O
your	O
come	O
about	O
your	O
Watch	O
,	O
I	O
warrant	O
you	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
shewing	O
him	O
her	O
Shoes	O
and	O
Stockings	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
bought	O
them	O
with	O
his	O
Money	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
were	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
take	O
the	O
Watch	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Pocket	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
sleeping	O
upon	O
a	O
Bench	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
pawned	O
to	O
a	O
Broker	O
in	O
Houndsditch	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
and	O
informed	O
a	O
Constable	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
Broker	O
depos	O
'd	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
pawn	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Name	O
for	O
20	O
s.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
Intimacy	O
between	O
her	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
used	O
to	O
be	O
with	O
him	O
constantly	O
a	O
Nights	O
,	O
being	O
let	O
in	O
privately	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
promised	O
her	O
Money	O
to	O
buy	O
her	O
Clothes	O
;	O
and	O
not	O
having	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Watch	O
to	O
pawn	O
for	O
20	O
s.	O
But	O
this	O
being	O
contrary	O
to	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
denying	O
that	O
he	O
ever	O
saw	O
her	O
before	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
of	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susanna	B-pers
Tindal	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Lucy	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Brailey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Kensington	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Plough-Irons	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Oakly	I-pers
;	O
and	O
also	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
for	O
stealing	O
Plough-Irons	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Rolph	I-pers
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
;	O
and	O
both	O
Facts	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
each	O
Indictment	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Isabel	B-pers
Manning	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
16	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
owning	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
swearing	O
positively	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Thorp	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Thompson	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Knipe	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Body	O
appearing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Franklin	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
marrying	O
with	O
Joseph	B-pers
Parry	I-pers
,	O
her	O
first	O
Husband	O
,	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Hooker	I-pers
,	O
being	O
alive	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
first	O
Marriage	O
not	O
being	O
clearly	O
prov	O
'd	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Nicholas	I-pers
Philippon	I-pers
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
she	O
stole	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Turton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
did	O
pawn	O
the	O
Goods	O
without	O
the	O
Knowledge	O
and	O
Consent	O
of	O
her	O
Landlady	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Nodder	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Budget	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
in	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
:	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
any	O
Evidence	O
to	O
confirm	O
that	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Accomplice	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Lewis	B-pers
Duroy	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Lombard	I-pers
;	O
but	O
no	O
Body	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Susannah	B-pers
Pidgeon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Turn-Over	O
,	O
Value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Snow-Hill	B-place
,	O
Susannah	B-pers
Pidgeon	I-pers
snatch	O
'd	O
his	O
Turn-Over	O
from	O
his	O
Neck	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
catching	O
hold	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Wheeler	O
,	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
having	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
given	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
desiring	O
the	O
Favour	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
for	O
Wheeler	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
defrauding	O
several	O
Persons	O
of	O
several	O
Sums	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
disposing	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
Use	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
intrusted	O
to	O
receive	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
not	O
paying	O
it	O
according	O
to	O
Order	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
rather	O
be	O
prosecuted	O
by	O
Action	O
than	O
Indictment	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Hardy	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Black-Friars	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Holton	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night-Time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Saw	O
and	O
other	O
Tools	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
Journey-Man	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
owing	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
Money	O
he	O
stopt	O
the	O
Tools	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
indeed	O
break	O
open	O
the	O
Cellar-Window	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
the	O
Tools	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
none	O
but	O
his	O
own	O
Tools	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
the	O
House	O
tho	O
'	O
it	O
was	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
yet	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
with	O
a	O
felonious	O
Intent	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Gregory	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
of	O
Bohee-Tea	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Journey-Man	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
steal	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Gregg	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
Finch	O
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
steal	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
several	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
missing	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
fetcht	O
away	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Godfrey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Warming	O
Pan	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Blackbourn	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
rather	O
the	O
Effect	O
of	O
Drunkenness	O
,	O
than	O
a	O
felonious	O
Intent	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Ray	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
75	O
Silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Gee	I-pers
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
under	O
a	O
Pretence	O
to	O
buy	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
there	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
missed	O
them	O
immediately	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
pursue	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
overtake	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pass	O
by	O
his	O
Shop	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
he	O
apprehended	O
him	O
.	O
Two	O
other	O
Evidences	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
see	O
two	O
Men	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
a	O
Bundle	O
under	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
did	O
believe	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Person	O
.	O
But	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
swear	O
positively	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
being	O
satisfied	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
steal	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
nor	O
was	O
an	O
Accomplice	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
committing	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Barbara	B-pers
May	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
taking	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Hutchinson	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
a	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
Half	O
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
a	O
Shop	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
a-Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
that	O
having	O
drank	O
three	O
Quarterns	O
of	O
Liquor	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
to	O
lodge	O
there	O
that	O
Night	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Landlady	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
spare	O
Bed	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
might	O
lye	O
on	O
the	O
Couch	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
fell	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
awaked	O
his	O
Money	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
turned	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
Street	O
.	O
The	O
Landlady	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Roll	O
and	O
Cheese	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
eat	O
and	O
drank	O
familiarly	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
her	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
him	O
Husband	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
offering	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
his	O
Watch	O
and	O
Money	O
to	O
keep	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
had	O
you	O
not	O
as	O
good	O
give	O
it	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
give	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
)	O
and	O
she	O
saw	O
her	O
put	O
the	O
Watch	O
into	O
her	O
Bosom	O
.	O
That	O
afterwards	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
Lane	O
by	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
Breeches	O
down	O
full	O
of	O
Nastiness	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
the	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
and	O
Half	O
Guinea	O
,	O
bidding	O
her	O
keep	O
it	O
till	O
her	O
Husband	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
kept	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
with	O
a	O
Warrant	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Constable	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
after	O
hearing	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
wilful	O
Perjury	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Marriot	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
Outwich	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night-Time	O
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
steal	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
about	O
three	O
a-Clock	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
out	O
till	O
about	O
two	O
a-Clock	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
;	O
that	O
being	O
let	O
in	O
by	O
his	O
Mother	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
strong	O
Smell	O
of	O
Turpentine	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Cellar	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
apprehending	O
some	O
Vessel	O
of	O
Turpentine	O
or	O
Varnish	O
might	O
be	O
running	O
out	O
or	O
broken	O
,	O
took	O
a	O
Candle	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
a	O
Ladder	O
that	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
and	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
running	O
up	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
imitating	O
the	O
Barking	O
of	O
a	O
Dog	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Cellar-Door	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Street	O
being	O
open	O
,	O
(	O
as	O
he	O
suppos	O
'd	O
opened	O
before	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
he	O
ran	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
struck	O
up	O
his	O
Heels	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
got	O
clear	O
of	O
him	O
again	O
and	O
run	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
still	O
pursued	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
never	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Sight	O
before	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
the	O
Watch	O
;	O
that	O
being	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-House	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Chissel	O
,	O
a	O
Gimlet	O
,	O
a	O
String	O
of	O
Pick-Lock	O
Keys	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Bag	O
with	O
a	O
Tinder-Box	O
.	O
Flint	O
,	O
Steel	O
,	O
and	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Wax-Candle	O
in	O
his	O
Breeches	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Mother	O
,	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
first	O
Part	O
of	O
her	O
Son	O
's	O
Evidence	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
her	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
up	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Cellar	O
on	O
her	O
Son	O
's	O
going	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
positive	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
very	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
Enquiry	O
was	O
inform	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Cellar-Door	O
was	O
before	O
that	O
Time	O
fast	O
bolted	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
fast	O
bolted	O
with	O
two	O
Bolts	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gainsborough	O
the	O
Constable	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Chissel	O
,	O
Gimlet	O
,	O
Pick-Lock-Keys	O
,	O
Tinder-Box	O
,	O
and	O
Wax-Candles	O
,	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
some	O
in	O
one	O
Pocket	O
some	O
in	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Bag	O
,	O
with	O
Tinder-Box	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
his	O
Breeches	O
.	O
By	O
other	O
Evidence	O
it	O
did	O
appear	O
that	O
the	O
Shutter	O
of	O
the	O
Shop-Window	O
was	O
bored	O
and	O
broken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
supposed	O
that	O
Way	O
to	O
get	O
in	O
;	O
that	O
a	O
Desk	O
had	O
been	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Mark	O
of	O
a	O
Chissel	O
answering	O
to	O
that	O
taken	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
was	O
seen	O
on	O
the	O
Shutter	O
,	O
Desk	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
that	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
secured	O
,	O
in	O
bringing	O
him	O
back	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
run	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
a	O
Dark	O
Lanthorn	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Sort	O
of	O
Wax-Candle	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
another	O
Bunch	O
of	O
larger	O
Pick-Lock-Keys	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
pleaded	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Night	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
a	O
Friend	O
of	O
his	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
in	O
Wapping	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
drank	O
a	O
Bowl	O
of	O
Punch	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
Club	O
of	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
drank	O
a	O
Bowl	O
of	O
Punch	O
of	O
18	O
s.	O
At	O
their	O
Return	O
,	O
as	O
passing	O
by	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Friend	O
being	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
his	O
Return	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
Two	O
a-Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
Cornhill	O
,	O
entring	O
Leaden-Hall-Street	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
pressing	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
seeming	O
to	O
yield	O
,	O
did	O
turn	O
down	O
towards	O
Bishopsgate-Street	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
being	O
talking	O
together	O
for	O
the	O
Space	O
of	O
two	O
Minutes	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
Outcry	O
of	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Man	O
came	O
running	O
by	O
and	O
drop	O
'd	O
some	O
Things	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
the	O
Things	O
mentioned	O
as	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
stoop	O
'd	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
ran	O
in	O
Pursuit	O
of	O
the	O
Persons	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
To	O
prove	O
this	O
,	O
he	O
called	O
John	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Brewer	O
's	O
Clerk	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
six	O
Years	O
,	O
had	O
sometimes	O
deposited	O
40	O
or	O
50	O
l.	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
had	O
it	O
honestly	O
return	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
the	O
Night	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
pleaded	O
;	O
that	O
afterwards	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
would	O
see	O
him	O
Part	O
of	O
his	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
in	O
Discourse	O
,	O
would	O
still	O
go	O
a	O
little	O
further	O
,	O
'till	O
at	O
last	O
they	O
came	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
St.	O
Ann	O
's	O
Church	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
parted	O
,	O
being	O
then	O
about	O
One	O
a-Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Belson	I-pers
also	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
on	O
Thursday	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
was	O
met	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
upper	O
End	O
of	O
Cornhill	O
,	O
about	O
Two	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
would	O
have	O
her	O
drink	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Wine	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
spoke	O
six	O
Words	O
,	O
before	O
a	O
Man	O
came	O
running	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
dropp	O
'd	O
some	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pick	O
'd	O
them	O
up	O
.	O
Being	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
the	O
knew	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
She	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
:	O
But	O
afterwards	O
being	O
inform	O
'd	O
of	O
an	O
Advertisement	O
in	O
a	O
News-Paper	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
was	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
thus	O
met	O
,	O
would	O
be	O
so	O
kind	O
to	O
appear	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
of	O
great	O
Service	O
to	O
one	O
who	O
was	O
now	O
under	O
Trouble	O
in	O
Newgate	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
go	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
there	O
knew	O
him	O
by	O
his	O
Voice	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
by	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
singled	O
him	O
out	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
there	O
were	O
about	O
fifty	O
Persons	O
present	O
.	O
Being	O
ask	O
'd	O
how	O
she	O
could	O
know	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Dark	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
what	O
Light	O
,	O
She	O
own	O
'd	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Light	O
but	O
that	O
of	O
the	O
Sky	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
know	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
stood	O
Face	O
to	O
Face	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
some	O
Persons	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
to	O
hear	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
made	O
some	O
Improvement	O
of	O
some	O
Expressions	O
said	O
to	O
be	O
dropt	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
no	O
Purpose	O
.	O
He	O
likewise	O
called	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
him	O
for	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
bore	O
an	O
honest	O
Character	O
among	O
his	O
Neighbours	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
so	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Rickets	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
her	O
Male	O
Bastard	O
Infant	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
by	O
throwing	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Miles	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
see	O
a	O
New-born	O
Infant	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Vault	O
by	O
some	O
Hand	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
by	O
whose	O
Hand	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
believed	O
it	O
had	O
lain	O
there	O
three	O
Weeks	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
confess	O
that	O
her	O
Master	O
was	O
the	O
Father	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
it	O
dropt	O
from	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
Vault	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
also	O
owned	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
with	O
her	O
own	O
Hand	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
no	O
Marks	O
of	O
Violence	O
on	O
it	O
but	O
one	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
supposed	O
might	O
be	O
caused	O
by	O
poking	O
in	O
the	O
Vault	O
in	O
having	O
been	O
stopt	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Midwife	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
afterward	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Round	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
Beadle	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
inquiring	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
own	O
,	O
but	O
for	O
some	O
Time	O
deny	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
Child	O
;	O
but	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
Miscarriage	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Lord	O
Bruce	O
's	O
Family	O
some	O
Months	O
before	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
being	O
examined	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Child	O
not	O
long	O
before	O
that	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
length	O
owned	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
behind	O
a	O
Washing-Tub	O
in	O
the	O
Back-Kitchin	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
could	O
find	O
no	O
Child	O
there	O
;	O
that	O
afterward	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
buried	O
under	O
a	O
Bench	O
that	O
the	O
Washing-Tub	O
stood	O
upon	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
a	O
Grave-Digger	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
dig	O
up	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
washing	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
believe	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
its	O
full	O
Time	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
Marks	O
of	O
Hurt	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
seemed	O
they	O
might	O
be	O
occasioned	O
by	O
what	O
had	O
been	O
depos	O
'd	O
by	O
poking	O
in	O
the	O
Vault	O
,	O
to	O
remove	O
some	O
Stoppage	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
taking	O
up	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Grave-Digger	O
.	O
Other	O
Evidences	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
made	O
some	O
Provision	O
of	O
Linen	O
for	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Things	O
were	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
depos	O
'd	O
on	O
Oath	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
fetch	O
'd	O
them	O
by	O
her	O
Direction	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
not	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
so	O
near	O
her	O
Time	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
dropp	O
'd	O
from	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
Vault	O
,	O
when	O
uncapable	O
to	O
help	O
it	O
.	O
Upon	O
a	O
full	O
Hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hickterhall	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Hannah	B-pers
Merrit	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Bridges	B-pers
Wats	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night-Time	O
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
and	O
fifty	O
two	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
latter	O
for	O
receiving	O
them	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Window	O
seemed	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
forced	O
with	O
a	O
Crow	O
;	O
that	O
Hannah	B-pers
Merrit	I-pers
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
received	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
either	O
sold	O
or	O
pawned	O
them	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Ann	B-pers
Merrit	I-pers
brought	O
the	O
Tankard	O
and	O
Plates	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
whereas	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Hat	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
Hickterbal	O
's	O
Hat	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
making	O
it	O
out	O
that	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
broken	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
And	O
Hannah	B-pers
Merrit	I-pers
having	O
inform	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
voluntarily	O
of	O
her	O
having	O
received	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hickterhall	I-pers
,	O
Humphrey	B-pers
Belmosset	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Sarah	O
,	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
Humphrey	B-pers
Belmosset	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Hannah	B-pers
Merrit	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Shadwel	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
about	O
11	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
rising	O
about	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
a	O
Chair-Woman	O
came	O
about	O
that	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
his	O
House	O
had	O
been	O
broken	O
open	O
;	O
several	O
Goods	O
were	O
missing	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
with	O
Sarah	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
and	O
not	O
liking	O
their	O
Ways	O
,	O
she	O
gave	O
Information	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
lost	O
.	O
Other	O
Evidences	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
Hickterhall	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Waistcoat	O
on	O
his	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Maclues	O
Stockings	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Things	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
Hannah	B-pers
Merrit	I-pers
's	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Felony	O
was	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
Hickterhall	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Burglary	O
not	O
being	O
proved	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
only	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
all	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Parry	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
thirty	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Henly	I-pers
,	O
Baronet	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Sir	O
Robert	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
to	O
London	O
he	O
wanted	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
Captain	O
Broderick	O
offered	O
to	O
lend	O
him	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
lost	O
Money	O
at	O
several	O
Times	O
,	O
he	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
be	O
satisfied	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
63	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
Half	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
told	O
them	O
three	O
Times	O
over	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
Times	O
more	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
;	O
and	O
getting	O
up	O
in	O
his	O
Night-Gown	O
and	O
Slippers	O
,	O
(	O
as	O
his	O
usual	O
Custom	O
was	O
,	O
)	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Anti-Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
fetch	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
counting	O
the	O
Money	O
found	O
one	O
Guinea	O
wanting	O
;	O
that	O
upon	O
charging	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
confess	O
it	O
,	O
told	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
laid	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
urged	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
after	O
that	O
been	O
employ	O
'd	O
in	O
Sir	O
Robert	O
's	O
Service	O
,	O
and	O
entrusted	O
to	O
carry	O
Plate	O
from	O
London	O
to	O
Richmond	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Suit	O
depending	O
between	O
Sir	O
Robert	O
and	O
another	O
Person	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Subpoena	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Evidence	O
in	O
the	O
Court	O
at	O
Westminster	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
Habeas	O
Corpus	O
ad	O
testisicandum	O
for	O
him	O
for	O
that	O
Purpose	O
.	O
Upon	O
a	O
full	O
Hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Boyle	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
twenty	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
Value	O
Forty	O
Shillings	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Down	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Sixth	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
twenty	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Silver	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
;	O
which	O
Fact	O
being	O
also	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Godfrey	B-pers
Buckley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
Elizabeth	O
Parsons	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Joseph	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Knap	I-pers
,	O
did	O
break	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Mary	B-pers
Paget	I-pers
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
divers	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Silver	O
,	O
Plate	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
Godfrey	B-pers
Buckley	I-pers
as	O
an	O
Accessary	O
before	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
in	O
inticing	O
,	O
procuring	O
,	O
aiding	O
and	O
abetting	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
dwelt	O
in	O
Mrs.	O
Paget	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
committed	O
to	O
the	O
Care	O
of	O
his	O
Wife	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
that	O
Night	O
lye	O
at	O
Home	O
,	O
some	O
Company	O
being	O
there	O
that	O
Night	O
;	O
but	O
lying	O
hard	O
by	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
called	O
up	O
by	O
a	O
Washerwoman	O
so	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
Break	O
of	O
Day	O
or	O
not	O
;	O
but	O
about	O
Three	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
being	O
inform	O
'd	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Paget	O
's	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
immediately	O
and	O
found	O
all	O
the	O
Doors	O
open	O
;	O
and	O
did	O
fear	O
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Paget	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
had	O
been	O
murthered	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
called	O
out	O
aloud	O
to	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
Are	O
you	O
alive	O
?	O
that	O
she	O
answering	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
found	O
several	O
Doors	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
Cabinets	O
,	O
Buroes	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
divers	O
Goods	O
missing	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
Night-Time	O
she	O
heard	O
a	O
great	O
Knocking	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Noises	O
,	O
as	O
of	O
something	O
falling	O
,	O
drawing	O
out	O
of	O
Drawers	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
a	O
Man	O
cough	O
in	O
the	O
Dining-Room	O
;	O
but	O
was	O
afraid	O
to	O
take	O
any	O
Notice	O
,	O
or	O
call	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
House	O
being	O
a	O
Lone	O
-	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
into	O
the	O
Park	O
backwards	O
,	O
and	O
inclosed	O
with	O
a	O
Wall	O
and	O
Court-Yard	O
forwards	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
expect	O
to	O
be	O
heard	O
.	O
She	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
three	O
Nights	O
before	O
she	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Gate	O
,	O
was	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
three	O
Men	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
away	O
at	O
her	O
coming	O
out	O
,	O
locking	O
the	O
Gate	O
after	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Men	O
,	O
(	O
whom	O
she	O
verily	O
believes	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
)	O
came	O
back	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
Whether	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Paget	O
did	O
not	O
live	O
there	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Knap	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
George	B-pers
Buckley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
,	O
inticed	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
to	O
Westminster	O
;	O
that	O
going	O
along	O
they	O
saw	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
Booty	O
,	O
he	O
bidding	O
him	O
,	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
,	O
)	O
go	O
knock	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
Kemp	O
riffle	O
his	O
Pockets	O
.	O
That	O
afterwards	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
this	O
Evidence	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Place	O
and	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
Man	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Paget	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
saying	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
mind	O
your	O
Business	O
,	O
and	O
Godfrey	O
did	O
speak	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Philips	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
before	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
was	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Nights	O
before	O
the	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
That	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Nights	O
after	O
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Kemp	B-pers
,	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Paget	O
's	O
House	O
about	O
Twelve	O
a-Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
hoisted	O
him	O
,	O
this	O
Evidence	O
,	O
over	O
the	O
Wall	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
Gate	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
standing	O
on	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Parson	I-pers
's	O
Knees	O
,	O
got	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
cursing	O
him	O
for	O
not	O
opening	O
it	O
,	O
did	O
with	O
an	O
Iron	O
Chissel	O
so	O
wrench	O
the	O
Staple	O
back	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Lock	O
flew	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Mary	O
Parsons	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
Kemp	O
took	O
down	O
the	O
Glass	O
,	O
bored	O
the	O
Shutters	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
took	O
down	O
an	O
Iron	O
Bar	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
all	O
went	O
in	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
Kemp	O
taking	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Pistols	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
all	O
about	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
open	O
Cabinets	O
or	O
Buroes	O
,	O
took	O
Plate	O
and	O
many	O
other	O
Things	O
;	O
that	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
took	O
two	O
Pistols	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Chamber	O
where	O
the	O
Gentlewomen	O
lay	O
,	O
told	O
him	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
Booty	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
in	O
and	O
Cut	O
their	O
Throats	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
White-Handled	O
Penknife	O
for	O
that	O
Purpose	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
a	O
Penny	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
about	O
Two	O
Hours	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
carried	O
to	O
Buckley	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
Parsons	O
she	O
sold	O
some	O
and	O
pawned	O
others	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
,	O
this	O
Evidence	O
,	O
afterwards	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
Eighty	O
Miles	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
uneasy	O
in	O
his	O
Mind	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
rest	O
,	O
continually	O
dreaming	O
of	O
clambering	O
over	O
Walls	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
like	O
;	O
that	O
thereupon	O
he	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
discovered	O
the	O
Matter	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wyburn	O
's	O
Servant	O
the	O
Pawn-Broker	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
had	O
pawned	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Knap	I-pers
having	O
given	O
Notice	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
Orders	O
from	O
Justice	O
Robe	O
to	O
stop	O
Parsons	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
also	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
John	B-pers
Knap	I-pers
made	O
himself	O
a	O
voluntary	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Upon	O
a	O
full	O
Hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Kemp	O
,	O
passing	O
for	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
,	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
as	O
not	O
being	O
accountable	O
,	O
as	O
acting	O
under	O
the	O
Direction	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Company	O
of	O
her	O
Husband	O
Joseph	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
;	O
and	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
any	O
Evidence	O
to	O
corroborate	O
that	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Knap	I-pers
,	O
Godfrey	B-pers
Buckley	I-pers
was	O
likewise	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Huggins	I-pers
,	O
late	O
Warden	O
of	O
the	O
Fleet	O
,	O
was	O
also	O
Try	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Arne	I-pers
:	O
The	O
Prosecution	O
was	O
carried	O
on	O
by	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Attorney-General	O
and	O
Council	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
many	O
Witnesses	O
both	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
a	O
long	O
Trial	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
in	O
their	O
Verdict	O
,	O
Special	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bambridge	I-pers
,	O
late	O
Warden	O
of	O
the	O
Fleet-Prison	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
at	O
the	O
Sessions-House	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
,	O
and	O
Try	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Castel	I-pers
,	O
and	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Cluff	I-pers
,	O
try	O
'd	O
and	O
acquitted	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Green	I-pers
.	O
against	O
whom	O
William	O
Green	O
,	O
Brother	O
and	O
Heir	O
to	O
Mary	O
Green	O
,	O
did	O
,	O
after	O
his	O
being	O
acquitted	O
,	O
bring	O
an	O
Appeal	O
,	O
and	O
appear	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
mov	O
'd	O
the	O
Court	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
try	O
'd	O
this	O
Sessions	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
not	O
having	O
taken	O
Care	O
to	O
bring	O
a	O
Venire	O
facias	O
in	O
Time	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
done	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
usual	O
Course	O
of	O
Law	O
,	O
his	O
Trial	O
is	O
deferr	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Stock	I-pers
,	O
former	O
Convicts	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
ended	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
follows	O
:	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
4.	O
William	B-pers
Tweed	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Marriot	I-pers
,	O
Mordecai	B-pers
Jonas	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Boyle	I-pers
.	O
For	O
Transportation	O
11.	O
Mary	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Compton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hickterhal	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Girling	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Jones	O
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Scales	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Brayley	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
Katherine	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
7.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Eggleston	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
Susanna	B-pers
Tindal	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Walker	O
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Masham	I-pers
,	O
Jacob	B-pers
Stock	I-pers
,	O
former	O
Convicts	O
.	O
BOOKS	O
Printed	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
Sold	O
by	O
E.	O
Symon	O
,	O
over	O
against	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
Cornhill	O
.	O
I	O
.	O
THE	O
Works	O
of	O
JOHN	B-pers
LOCKE	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
In	O
Three	O
Volumes	O
.	O
With	O
Alphabetical	O
Tables	O
.	O
Vol	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
The	O
Third	O
Edition	O
.	O
II	O
.	O
ANNALS	O
of	O
the	O
Reformation	O
,	O
and	O
Establishment	O
of	O
Religion	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Church	O
of	O
England	O
.	O
Containing	O
Accounts	O
of	O
the	O
Government	O
and	O
Inspection	O
of	O
the	O
Bishops	O
in	O
their	O
respective	O
Diocesses	O
;	O
as	O
Matters	O
,	O
requiring	O
their	O
Care	O
,	O
sell	O
out	O
each	O
Year	O
:	O
Ecclesiastical	O
Commissions	O
.	O
The	O
busy	O
Actings	O
of	O
Papists	O
and	O
Puritans	O
:	O
The	O
Difficulties	O
and	O
Dangers	O
the	O
State	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
the	O
Church	O
met	O
with	O
from	O
Time	O
to	O
Time	O
:	O
Occasioned	O
chiefly	O
from	O
the	O
Endeavours	O
to	O
overthrow	O
both	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Power	O
and	O
Practices	O
of	O
such	O
as	O
favoured	O
Mary	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
of	O
Scots	O
:	O
Of	O
whom	O
many	O
special	O
Transactions	O
;	O
and	O
chiefly	O
of	O
her	O
Sentence	O
and	O
Death	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Consequences	O
thereof	O
,	O
are	O
shewn	O
:	O
And	O
the	O
Spanish	O
Invasion	O
in	O
1588	O
.	O
Both	O
serving	O
to	O
enlighten	O
those	O
Two	O
Great	O
Crises	O
of	O
Queen	O
Elizabeth	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Together	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Political	O
Affairs	O
of	O
Note	O
interspersed	O
.	O
This	O
History	O
is	O
also	O
improved	O
by	O
Notices	O
given	O
concerning	O
the	O
State	O
and	O
Events	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
of	O
Ireland	O
;	O
Occurrences	O
and	O
Differences	O
that	O
fell	O
out	O
in	O
our	O
Universities	O
;	O
Remarks	O
of	O
many	O
Persons	O
of	O
Rank	O
and	O
Quality	O
in	O
Church	O
and	O
State	O
:	O
Books	O
of	O
Learning	O
and	O
Note	O
,	O
Libels	O
,	O
Pamphlets	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
published	O
yearly	O
.	O
All	O
commencing	O
from	O
the	O
Year	O
of	O
our	O
Lord	O
,	O
MDLXXXI	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
continued	O
for	O
divers	O
Years	O
.	O
Collected	O
diligently	O
and	O
faithfully	O
from	O
Records	O
,	O
Papers	O
of	O
State	O
,	O
Original	O
Letters	O
of	O
Privy	O
Counsellors	O
,	O
Ambassadors	O
,	O
Bishops	O
,	O
Learned	O
Men	O
in	O
the	O
Universities	O
,	O
as	O
elsewhere	O
:	O
And	O
from	O
other	O
choice	O
MSS	O
.	O
reserved	O
in	O
our	O
publick	O
Libraries	O
,	O
or	O
more	O
private	O
Archives	O
.	O
Together	O
with	O
an	O
Appendix	O
:	O
Containing	O
many	O
choice	O
Records	O
,	O
and	O
Papers	O
of	O
Value	O
;	O
Transcribed	O
from	O
Originals	O
:	O
Referred	O
to	O
in	O
the	O
Work	O
;	O
in	O
Order	O
to	O
the	O
Vindication	O
,	O
Proof	O
,	O
and	O
Illustration	O
of	O
the	O
foregoing	O
History	O
.	O
By	O
JOHN	B-pers
STRYPE	I-pers
,	O
M.	O
A.	O
Vol	O
.	O
III	O
.	O
Memento	O
dierum	O
antiquorum	O
.	O
Cogita	O
Generationes	O
singulas	O
;	O
Interroga	O
Patrem	O
tuum	O
,	O
&	O
annuntiabit	O
tibi	O
;	O
Majores	O
tuos	O
,	O
&	O
dicent	O
tibi	O
.	O
Deutr	O
.	O
xxxii	O
.	O
7	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
First	O
and	O
Second	O
Volumes	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
at	O
the	O
Place	O
above-mention	O
'd	O
.	O
III	O
.	O
Dictionarium	O
Rusticum	O
,	O
Urbanicum	O
&	O
Botanicum	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
a	O
Dictionary	O
of	O
Husbandry	O
,	O
Gardening	O
,	O
Trade	O
,	O
Commerce	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
Country-Affairs	O
.	O
Containing	O
more	O
particularly	O
,	O
1	O
.	O
The	O
whole	O
Art	O
of	O
Gardening	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Sowing	O
,	O
Setting	O
,	O
Grasting	O
,	O
Inoculating	O
,	O
Transplanting	O
,	O
Salleting	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
with	O
the	O
Names	O
,	O
Descriptions	O
,	O
Virtues	O
,	O
and	O
Uses	O
of	O
most	O
sorts	O
of	O
Plants	O
,	O
Flowers	O
and	O
Fruits	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
The	O
raising	O
,	O
and	O
ordering	O
of	O
all	O
manner	O
of	O
Forest	O
and	O
Fruit-Trees	O
,	O
both	O
Standards	O
and	O
Dwarfs	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
Agriculture	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
Art	O
of	O
Husbandry	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
various	O
Parts	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
with	O
the	O
modern	O
Improvements	O
made	O
therein	O
.	O
4	O
.	O
The	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Recreation	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
Arts	O
of	O
riding	O
the	O
manag	O
'd	O
House	O
,	O
Hunting	O
,	O
Ferreting	O
,	O
Hawking	O
,	O
Fowling	O
,	O
Cock	O
fighting	O
,	O
Fishing	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
including	O
not	O
only	O
an	O
accurate	O
Description	O
of	O
the	O
several	O
Animals	O
,	O
but	O
even	O
of	O
the	O
Tackle	O
,	O
Nets	O
,	O
Gins	O
,	O
and	O
Traps	O
,	O
different	O
Instruments	O
used	O
in	O
those	O
Sports	O
.	O
5	O
.	O
The	O
Farrier	O
's	O
Art	O
,	O
with	O
those	O
of	O
Horsemanship	O
and	O
Manage	O
.	O
Also	O
a	O
particular	O
Account	O
of	O
every	O
Disease	O
incident	O
to	O
a	O
Horse	O
,	O
with	O
its	O
Causes	O
,	O
Symptoms	O
,	O
Effects	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
a	O
View	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
proper	O
and	O
approved	O
Remedies	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
The	O
breeding	O
,	O
feeding	O
,	O
and	O
managing	O
of	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
Cattle	O
;	O
as	O
also	O
of	O
Bees	O
,	O
Silkworms	O
,	O
Poultry	O
,	O
and	O
Singing-Birds	O
;	O
with	O
all	O
their	O
respective	O
Diseases	O
and	O
Cures	O
.	O
7	O
.	O
The	O
preparing	O
of	O
many	O
sorts	O
of	O
English	O
Liquors	O
,	O
common	O
Eatables	O
and	O
Drinkables	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
several	O
Parts	O
of	O
Country	O
Housewisry	O
.	O
8	O
.	O
The	O
digging	O
,	O
refining	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
of	O
Metals	O
and	O
Minerals	O
;	O
with	O
Salt	O
and	O
Sugar-Works	O
,	O
the	O
Art	O
of	O
making	O
of	O
Bricks	O
,	O
Bird-lime	O
,	O
Gun-powder	O
,	O
Shot	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
9	O
.	O
Terms	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
in	O
Merchandizing	O
,	O
Traffick	O
,	O
and	O
Trade	O
;	O
with	O
Handicraft	O
Terms	O
and	O
Instruments	O
,	O
Country	O
Words	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
10	O
.	O
An	O
Account	O
of	O
Coins	O
,	O
Weights	O
and	O
Measures	O
,	O
domestick	O
and	O
foreign	O
,	O
with	O
their	O
respective	O
Values	O
and	O
Capacities	O
.	O
11	O
.	O
The	O
Productions	O
,	O
Manufactures	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Counties	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
and	O
even	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
remarkable	O
of	O
Foreign	O
Countries	O
.	O
12	O
.	O
A	O
Collection	O
of	O
the	O
principal	O
Statute	O
Laws	O
,	O
relating	O
to	O
Tenures	O
and	O
Country	O
Affairs	O
,	O
especially	O
those	O
of	O
the	O
Forests	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Functions	O
of	O
Field	O
and	O
Forest-Officers	O
;	O
also	O
the	O
ancient	O
Customs	O
,	O
a	O
nd	O
natural	O
Rarities	O
of	O
Great-Britain	O
.	O
Illustrated	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
Number	O
of	O
Cutts	O
.	O
Vol	O
.	O
I	O
.	O
The	O
3d	O
Edition	O
revised	O
,	O
corrected	O
and	O
Improved	O
;	O
with	O
the	O
Addition	O
of	O
above	O
300	O
Articles	O
.	O
IV	O
.	O
The	O
Physical	O
Dictionary	O
.	O
Wherein	O
the	O
Terms	O
of	O
Anatomy	O
,	O
the	O
Names	O
and	O
Causes	O
of	O
Diseases	O
,	O
Chirurgical	O
Instruments	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
Use	O
,	O
are	O
accurately	O
described	O
.	O
As	O
also	O
the	O
Names	O
and	O
Virtues	O
of	O
Medicinal	O
Plants	O
,	O
Minerals	O
,	O
Stones	O
,	O
Gums	O
,	O
Salts	O
,	O
Earths	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Method	O
of	O
chusing	O
the	O
best	O
Drugs	O
:	O
The	O
Terms	O
of	O
Chymistry	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
Apothecary	O
's	O
Art	O
:	O
The	O
various	O
Forms	O
of	O
Medicines	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
ways	O
of	O
compounding	O
them	O
.	O
By	O
Stephen	B-pers
Blancard	I-pers
,	O
M.	O
D.	O
Professor	O
of	O
Physick	O
at	O
Middleburg	O
in	O
Zealand	O
.	O
The	O
seventh	O
Edition	O
:	O
With	O
the	O
Addition	O
of	O
many	O
Thousand	O
Terms	O
of	O
Art	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
Explanation	O
,	O
(	O
from	O
the	O
last	O
and	O
best	O
Edition	O
of	O
Castellus	O
's	O
Lexicon	O
Medicum	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Authors	O
)	O
more	O
than	O
in	O
any	O
former	O
Impression	O
.	O
Also	O
a	O
Catalogue	O
of	O
the	O
Characters	O
us	O
'd	O
in	O
Physick	O
,	O
both	O
in	O
Latin	O
and	O
English	O
,	O
curiously	O
Engrav	O
'd	O
on	O
Copper	O
.	O
V.	O
The	O
Experienc	O
'd	O
Farrier	O
,	O
or	O
Farring	O
compleated	O
.	O
Containing	O
every	O
thing	O
that	O
belongs	O
to	O
a	O
compleat	O
Horseman	O
,	O
Groom	O
,	O
Farrier	O
or	O
Horseleach	O
.	O
With	O
the	O
Office	O
of	O
the	O
Breeder	O
,	O
Keeper	O
,	O
Rider	O
,	O
Feeder	O
,	O
Buyer	O
and	O
Farrier	O
:	O
Shewing	O
the	O
Marks	O
of	O
Beauty	O
,	O
Goodness	O
,	O
Faults	O
and	O
Impersections	O
of	O
Horses	O
;	O
with	O
the	O
best	O
Method	O
of	O
buying	O
,	O
dieting	O
,	O
shooing	O
,	O
and	O
otherwise	O
managing	O
of	O
Horses	O
for	O
all	O
Uses	O
.	O
Also	O
plain	O
Directions	O
in	O
the	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
all	O
Distempers	O
and	O
Accidents	O
incident	O
to	O
Horses	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
With	O
the	O
best	O
Receipts	O
and	O
Methods	O
used	O
in	O
their	O
Cure	O
,	O
never	O
published	O
before	O
.	O
In	O
2	O
Parts	O
,	O
Physical	O
and	O
Chyrurgical	O
.	O
By	O
E.R	O
.	O
Gent	O
.	O
The	O
4th	O
Edition	O
.	O
VI	O
.	O
A	O
Description	O
of	O
the	O
English	O
Province	O
of	O
Carolana	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Spaniards	O
call	O
'd	O
Florida	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
French	O
La	O
Louisiane	O
.	O
As	O
also	O
of	O
the	O
great	O
and	O
famous	O
River	O
Meschasebe	O
,	O
or	O
Missisippi	O
,	O
the	O
five	O
vast	O
Navigable	O
Lakes	O
of	O
fresh	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Parts	O
adjacent	O
.	O
Together	O
with	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Commodities	O
of	O
the	O
Growth	O
and	O
Production	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Province	O
.	O
And	O
a	O
Preface	O
containing	O
some	O
Considerations	O
on	O
the	O
Consequences	O
of	O
the	O
French	O
making	O
Settlements	O
there	O
.	O
By	O
Daniel	B-pers
Coxe	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Non	O
minor	O
est	O
Virtus	O
quam	O
quarere	O
parti	O
tueri	O
.	O
VII	O
.	O
A	O
Dissertation	O
on	O
the	O
high	O
Operation	O
for	O
the	O
Stone	O
,	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Morand	O
,	O
Surgeon	O
to	O
the	O
Royal	O
Hospital	O
of	O
Invalids	O
,	O
Member	O
of	O
the	O
Royal	O
Academy	O
at	O
Paris	O
,	O
and	O
F.	O
R.	O
S.	O
Translated	O
from	O
the	O
French	O
by	O
JOHN	B-pers
DOUGLAS	I-pers
,	O
Surgeon	B-pers
,	O
F.	B-pers
R.	I-pers
S	I-pers
.	I-pers
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
an	O
Appendix	O
containing	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
sixty	O
odd	O
Patients	O
cut	O
after	O
this	O
Method	O
,	O
by	O
various	O
Hands	O
:	O
With	O
some	O
general	O
Inferences	O
from	O
the	O
Whole	O
.	O
As	O
also	O
a	O
short	O
Syllabus	O
of	O
the	O
Chirurgical	O
Operations	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
Anatomia	O
Chirurgis	O
Situ	O
Summe	O
Necessaria	O
.	O
Fusca	O
repurgatur	O
fugiehant	O
Nubile	O
Coelo	O
.	O
Ovid	O
.	O
VIII	O
.	O
The	O
military	O
Memoirs	O
of	O
Captain	O
George	B-pers
Carleton	I-pers
.	O
From	O
the	O
Dutch	O
War	O
,	O
1672.	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
serv	O
'd	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Conclusion	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
at	O
Utrecht	O
,	O
1713	O
.	O
Illustrating	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
remarkable	O
Transactions	O
,	O
both	O
by	O
Sea	O
and	O
Land	O
,	O
during	O
the	O
Reigns	O
of	O
King	O
Charles	O
and	O
King	O
James	O
the	O
II	O
.	O
hitherto	O
unobserv	O
'd	O
by	O
all	O
the	O
Writers	O
of	O
those	O
Times	O
.	O
Together	O
with	O
an	O
exact	O
Series	O
of	O
the	O
War	O
in	O
Spain	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
particular	O
Description	O
of	O
the	O
several	O
Places	O
of	O
the	O
Author	O
's	O
Residence	O
in	O
many	O
Cities	O
,	O
Towns	O
,	O
and	O
Countries	O
;	O
their	O
Customs	O
,	O
Manners	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Also	O
Observations	O
on	O
the	O
Genius	O
of	O
the	O
Spaniards	O
(	O
among	O
whom	O
he	O
continued	O
some	O
Years	O
a	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
their	O
Monasteries	O
and	O
Nunneries	O
(	O
especially	O
that	O
fine	O
one	O
at	O
Montserat	O
)	O
and	O
on	O
their	O
publick	O
Diversions	O
;	O
more	O
particularly	O
their	O
famous	O
Bull-Feasts	O
.	O
IX	O
.	O
Miscellaneous	O
Essays	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
Of	O
Company	O
and	O
Conversation	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
Of	O
Solitariness	O
and	O
Retirement	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
Of	O
Nobility	O
.	O
4.	O
of	O
Contentment	O
.	O
5	O
.	O
Of	O
Women	O
.	O
6.	O
of	O
the	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
God	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
Atheism	O
.	O
7	O
.	O
Of	O
Religion	O
.	O
8	O
.	O
Of	O
Kings	O
,	O
Princes	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Education	O
of	O
a	O
Prince	O
.	O
9	O
.	O
Of	O
Greatness	O
of	O
Mind	O
.	O
10	O
.	O
Of	O
the	O
Education	O
of	O
Children	O
.	O
11	O
.	O
Of	O
Law	O
.	O
12	O
.	O
Of	O
Man	O
.	O
13	O
.	O
Of	O
Old	O
Age	O
.	O
With	O
the	O
Life	O
and	O
Conversion	O
of	O
St.	O
Mary	O
Magdalen	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Reflections	O
upon	O
the	O
Conversion	O
of	O
the	O
good	O
Thief	O
;	O
also	O
,	O
the	O
Life	O
and	O
Conversion	O
of	O
St.	O
Paul	O
.	O
By	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Bulstrode	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Envoy	O
at	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
Brussels	O
,	O
from	O
King	O
Charles	B-pers
II	I-pers
.	O
and	O
King	O
James	B-pers
II	I-pers
.	O
Published	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Preface	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
Son	O
Whitlocke	O
Bulstrode	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
the	O
2d	O
Edition	O
.	O
X	O
.	O
The	O
English	O
Tutor	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
plain	O
Pathway	O
to	O
the	O
English	O
Tongue	O
.	O
Being	O
a	O
most	O
plain	O
and	O
familiar	O
Method	O
for	O
the	O
teaching	O
of	O
Children	O
to	O
spell	O
and	O
read	O
English	O
exactly	O
.	O
With	O
Examples	O
of	O
most	O
Words	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
to	O
six	O
Syllables	O
;	O
both	O
in	O
whole	O
Words	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
divided	O
.	O
With	O
Rules	O
how	O
to	O
Spell	O
them	O
,	O
by	O
Way	O
of	O
Question	O
and	O
Answer	O
.	O
Together	O
with	O
Sacred	O
Hymns	O
and	O
Proverbs	O
,	O
prepar	O
'd	O
and	O
methodiz	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
Use	O
and	O
Benefit	O
of	O
English	O
Schools	O
.	O
XI	O
.	O
The	O
Expediency	O
of	O
a	O
Divine	O
Revelation	O
represented	O
.	O
A	O
Sermon	O
preach	O
'd	O
before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
Aldermen	O
,	O
and	O
Citizens	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Cathedral	O
Church	O
of	O
St.	O
Paul	O
,	O
on	O
Sunday	O
February	O
16	O
,	O
1728-9	O
.	O
By	O
John	B-pers
Conybeare	I-pers
,	O
D.D	O
.	O
Fellow	O
of	O
Exeter	O
College	O
in	O
Oxford	O
.	O
Publish	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Request	O
of	O
the	O
Lord-Mayor	O
.	O
XII	O
.	O
Self-Communion	O
recommended	O
and	O
prescrib	O
'd	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
Sermon	O
preach	O
'd	O
before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord-Mayor	O
,	O
Aldermen	O
,	O
and	O
Citizens	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Cathedral	O
Church	O
of	O
St.	O
Paul	O
,	O
on	O
Sunday	O
December	O
1	O
,	O
1728	O
.	O
By	O
Richard	B-pers
Meadowcourt	I-pers
,	O
M.A	O
.	O
Fellow	O
of	O
Merton	O
College	O
,	O
in	O
Oxford	O
,	O
and	O
Chaplain	O
to	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
William	B-pers
Earl	I-pers
Cowper	I-pers
.	O
Publish	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Request	O
of	O
the	O
Lord-Mayor	O
.	O
XIII	O
.	O
The	O
Present	O
State	O
of	O
Great	O
Britain	O
,	O
and	O
Ireland	O
,	O
in	O
Three	O
Parts	O
.	O
The	O
I	O
.	O
Of	O
South	O
,	O
the	O
IId	O
.	O
of	O
North	O
Britain	O
.	O
III	O
.	O
Of	O
Ireland	O
.	O
Containing	O
an	O
Accurate	O
and	O
Impartial	O
Account	O
of	O
these	O
famous	O
Islands	O
:	O
Of	O
their	O
several	O
Counties	O
and	O
Inhabitants	O
;	O
the	O
Advantages	O
and	O
Disadvantages	O
of	O
Both	O
,	O
in	O
Respect	O
to	O
Foreign	O
Countries	O
;	O
and	O
their	O
Curiosities	O
of	O
Nature	O
and	O
Art	O
.	O
Of	O
the	O
vast	O
,	O
populous	O
,	O
and	O
opulent	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Metropolis	O
of	O
England	O
;	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
celebrated	O
Universities	O
,	O
Oxford	O
and	O
Cambridge	O
.	O
Of	O
the	O
Britons	O
Original	O
,	O
Language	O
,	O
Temper	O
,	O
Genius	O
,	O
Religion	O
,	O
Morals	O
,	O
Trade	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Their	O
Nobility	O
,	O
Gentry	O
,	O
Clergy	O
,	O
and	O
Commonalty	O
.	O
Their	O
Laws	O
and	O
Government	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
succinct	O
History	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
English	O
Monarchs	O
to	O
this	O
Time	O
.	O
With	O
Lists	O
of	O
the	O
present	O
Officers	O
in	O
Church	O
and	O
State	O
;	O
and	O
of	O
both	O
Houses	O
of	O
Parliament	O
:	O
Also	O
the	O
present	O
State	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Dominions	O
in	O
Germany	O
.	O
The	O
Sixth	O
Edition	O
Corrected	O
.	O
Price	O
Six	O
Shillings	O
.	O
XIV	O
.	O
The	O
Adventures	O
of	O
Telemachus	O
,	O
the	O
Son	O
of	O
Ulysses	O
.	O
In	O
Twenty-four	O
Books	O
.	O
With	O
the	O
Adventures	O
of	O
Aristonous	O
.	O
Written	O
by	O
the	O
Archbishop	O
of	O
Cambray	O
.	O
Done	O
into	O
English	O
from	O
the	O
last	O
Paris	O
(	O
which	O
is	O
the	O
only	O
Genuine	O
)	O
Edition	O
.	O
By	O
Mr.	O
Is	O
.	O
Littlebury	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
A.	O
Boyer	O
.	O
Adorn	O
'd	O
with	O
Twentyfour	O
Plates	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Map	O
of	O
Telemachus	O
's	O
Travels	O
.	O
All	O
curiously	O
Engraven	O
by	O
very	O
good	O
Hands	O
.	O
The	O
Twelfth	O
Edition	O
.	O
Vol	O
.	O
I.	O
XV	O
.	O
The	O
CLUB	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
A	O
Grey-Cap	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
Green-Head	O
;	O
in	O
a	O
Dialogue	O
between	O
Father	O
and	O
Son	O
.	O
In	O
vino	O
veritas	O
.	O
The	O
Fourth	O
Edition	O
,	O
with	O
Additions	O
.	O
XVI	O
.	O
The	O
Dealer	O
in	O
Stock	O
's	O
Assistant	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
A	O
Calculation	O
of	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
any	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Stock	O
from	O
10000	O
l.	O
to	O
1	O
l.	O
at	O
the	O
Rate	O
of	O
1-16th	O
of	O
a	O
Pound	O
per	O
Cent	O
.	O
to	O
200	O
l.	O
per	O
Cent	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Ease	O
of	O
the	O
Proprietors	O
of	O
the	O
several	O
transferrable	O
Stocks	O
in	O
buying	O
,	O
selling	O
,	O
and	O
casting	O
up	O
Dividends	O
.	O
By	O
G.	O
Clerke	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
South-Sea-House	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Sold	O
by	O
J.	O
Roberts	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Oxford-Arms	O
in	O
Warwick-Lane	O
.	O
