TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
ON	O
Friday	O
the	O
4th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
5th	O
,	O
Monday	O
the	O
7th	O
,	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
and	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
December	O
1730	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Fourth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
First	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
HUMPHREY	B-pers
PARSONS	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1730	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
I.	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
YEAR	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
T.	O
PAYNE	O
,	O
in	O
Pater-noster-Row	O
.	O
M.DCC.XXXI	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
Six	O
Pence	O
.	O
)	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
AND	O
ON	O
The	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
,	O
Monday	O
,	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
and	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
4th	O
,	O
5th	O
,	O
7th	O
,	O
8th	O
,	O
and	O
9th	O
of	O
December	O
1730	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Fourth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
HUMPHREY	B-pers
PARSONS	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Page	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Commins	I-pers
;	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
Raby	O
,	O
Deputy-Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Freebody	I-pers
,	O
Paul	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Champion	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Peers	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Busby	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Sherley	I-pers
,	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Basnet	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Pilkington	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Clutterbuck	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Whitehorn	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Harwood	I-pers
,	O
Alexander	B-pers
Horrock	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Woolley	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Beak	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Crouch	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Pugh	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Leaden	O
Pipe	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
against	O
Thomas	O
Hudson	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
as	O
to	O
Elizabeth	O
Pugh	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
marrying	O
Mary	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
,	O
his	O
former	O
Wife	O
Mary	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
being	O
Alive	O
.	O
Both	O
the	O
Marriages	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Tonson	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Shilback	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Ridinghood	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Kirkpatrick	I-pers
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
was	O
going	O
Home	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
of	O
Things	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
Women	O
were	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
Sword	B-place
and	I-place
Buckler	I-place
Court	I-place
,	O
who	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
make	O
them	O
drink	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
refusing	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
treat	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
thereupon	O
he	O
going	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
there	O
fell	O
asleep	O
,	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
Ridinghood	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Bundle	O
,	O
and	O
flunk	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Husband	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
might	O
have	O
the	O
Goods	O
again	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
being	O
eating	O
some	O
Oysters	O
upon	O
Ludgate	O
Hill	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
picking	O
up	O
Women	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
tumbling	O
in	O
the	O
Dirt	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
and	O
Black	O
Nell	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Drink	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
and	O
drank	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Pints	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
fancy	O
to	O
lie	O
with	O
Black	O
Nell	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
go	O
Home	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
reckoning	O
being	O
to	O
be	O
paid	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
the	O
Bundle	O
?	O
And	O
it	O
was	O
opened	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
Ridinghood	O
and	O
some	O
Children	O
's	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
they	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
If	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
Wife	O
?	O
that	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
one	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
Dead	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
Black	O
Nell	O
the	O
Things	O
to	O
pawn	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
Money	O
to	O
go	O
Home	O
to	O
lie	O
with	O
her	O
all	O
Night	O
.	O
After	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Pearse	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Catherine's-Creed	I-place
Church	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
and	O
Pillowbier	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Malachi	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Saracen's-Head	B-place
Inn	I-place
,	I-place
near	O
Aldgate	B-place
,	O
to	O
Lodge	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
away	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
the	O
Sheets	O
were	O
missing	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Proof	O
of	O
his	O
taking	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bartholomew	I-place
the	I-place
Great	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
5	O
Linen	O
Mobs	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Linen	O
lying	O
on	O
a	O
Dresser	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
taking	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
5	O
hundred	O
Weight	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Israel	B-pers
Wilks	I-pers
,	O
jun	O
.	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appearing	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Lead	O
was	O
taken	O
off	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Compting-House	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
fix	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Freehold	O
,	O
the	O
Indictment	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
laid	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
a	O
Felony	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
upon	O
this	O
Indictment	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
inform	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
Indict	O
him	O
again	O
for	O
taking	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
Freehold	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Danbury	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hammersmith	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
five	O
Window	O
Curtains	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
prove	O
,	O
that	O
though	O
she	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
it	O
with	O
a	O
felonious	O
Intent	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Cornick	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
together	O
with	O
Edward	B-pers
Welsh	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Dickson	I-pers
,	O
did	O
feloniously	O
steal	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Alice	B-pers
Kilham	I-pers
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
Oct	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Kilham	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
lost	O
from	O
the	O
Golden	B-place
Hind	I-place
in	O
Redcross-street	B-place
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Bordwell	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
two	O
other	O
Men	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
Mistress	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Tankard	O
of	O
Beer	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
drew	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
deliver	O
'd	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Hand	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
going	O
up	O
Stairs	O
with	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
hearing	O
a	O
Noise	O
below	O
,	O
ran	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Men	O
and	O
Tankard	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Mistress	O
's	O
Son	O
and	O
others	O
ran	O
after	O
them	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Kilham	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
drew	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Company	O
a	O
second	O
Tankard	O
,	O
and	O
deliver	O
'd	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Hand	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
commending	O
the	O
Beer	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
going	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
to	O
draw	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
while	O
they	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
not	O
staying	O
to	O
pay	O
tho	O
Reckoning	O
.	O
Tho	B-pers
Ansel	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
hearing	O
a	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
running	O
,	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Man	O
striking	O
up	O
his	O
Heels	O
,	O
he	O
apprehended	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Tankard	O
was	O
not	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Companions	O
having	O
ran	O
a	O
contrary	O
way	O
,	O
got	O
clear	O
off	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
very	O
plain	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
others	O
were	O
all	O
of	O
a	O
Gang	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
all	O
away	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
was	O
equally	O
Guilty	O
with	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
actually	O
had	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Thimble	O
,	O
and	O
18	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Chiddick	I-pers
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Chiddick	I-pers
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Chiddick	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
her	O
Shop-Door	O
in	O
Hounsditch	B-place
to	O
see	O
a	O
Funeral	O
pass	O
by	O
,	O
between	O
Ten	O
and	O
Eleven	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
stood	O
by	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
cut	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
her	O
Money	O
,	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
missing	O
her	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
her	O
Pocket	O
cut	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
immediately	O
pursued	O
,	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
all	O
wrap	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Linen	O
Bag	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
hers	O
.	O
The	O
finding	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Money	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Darby	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Beadle	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Watchman	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
value	O
it	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
were	O
not	O
tuck	O
'd	O
up	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
only	O
going	O
over	O
the	O
Herring	O
Pond	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Denston	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
in	O
unlawfully	O
and	O
unjustly	O
ripping	O
off	O
120	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Freehold	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Campion	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Hannah	B-pers
Ayres	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Seymour	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
a	O
Chain	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Bryan	I-pers
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
latter	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
said	O
Watch	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
near	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
Chick-Lane	B-place
,	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
Women	O
standing	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Ayres	O
,	O
who	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
something	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
refusing	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
they	O
dragged	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
little	O
Alley	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
Women	O
,	O
being	O
one	O
on	O
each	O
Side	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Ayres	O
said	O
,	O
lets	O
feel	O
what	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
her	O
Hand	O
to	O
his	O
Fob	O
,	O
pulled	O
out	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
off	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
stopping	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
got	O
away	O
from	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
pursued	O
her	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Chick-Lane	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
shut	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
got	O
the	O
Watch	O
and	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
her	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
knew	O
where	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
should	O
never	O
have	O
it	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Ayres	I-pers
pleaded	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
but	O
having	O
been	O
for	O
a	O
Midwife	O
,	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
with	O
two	O
Women	O
,	O
and	O
halting	O
,	O
and	O
asking	O
,	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
doing	O
with	O
the	O
Man	O
?	O
They	O
swore	O
at	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
damn	O
'd	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
Bitch	O
,	O
what	O
was	O
that	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
following	O
her	O
,	O
charg	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
his	O
Watch	O
;	O
she	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
before	O
lost	O
3	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Silk	O
on	O
Ludgate-Hill	O
.	O
After	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
both	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gladmore	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bow	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
Carcass	O
of	O
a	O
Sheep	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Street	I-pers
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Kellet	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
hired	O
to	O
carry	O
five	O
Sheep	O
to	O
Newgate-Market	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
having	O
taken	O
three	O
of	O
the	O
Sheep	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Basket	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
two	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
found	O
but	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
pursuing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Sheep	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
seeing	O
a	O
Man	O
carrying	O
away	O
Sheep	O
,	O
thought	O
he	O
might	O
carry	O
away	O
a	O
Sheep	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
another	O
Man	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Martha	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
Hanover-Square	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Betilly	I-pers
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Stephen	B-pers
Gay	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Kensington	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Bag	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
a	O
Moidore	O
,	O
11	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
35	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bonny	I-pers
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
having	O
gone	O
with	O
his	O
Ware	O
to	O
Covent-Garden-Market	O
,	O
about	O
Three	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
had	O
News	O
brought	O
him	O
about	O
Eight	O
that	O
his	O
House	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
went	O
Home	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
Pane	O
of	O
Glass	O
had	O
been	O
broken	O
,	O
and	O
though	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
nothing	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
yet	O
found	O
Bonny	O
's	O
Box	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
)	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
gone	O
;	O
and	O
suspecting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
employ	O
'd	O
by	O
him	O
as	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
had	O
lain	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
it	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
he	O
caused	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
apprehended	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bonny	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
His	O
Chest	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
was	O
stolen	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
being	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Aldar	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
suspected	O
,	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Aldar	O
,	O
his	O
Landlord	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
that	O
Morning	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
to	O
the	O
Vault	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
going	O
to	O
look	O
in	O
the	O
Vault	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Cieling	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
where	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Hole	O
broke	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Bag	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
Ring	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Mr.	O
Aldar	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
hearing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
who	O
lay	O
over	O
his	O
Head	O
walk	O
about	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
down	O
Stairs	O
about	O
Two	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
wondered	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
thinking	O
no	O
harm	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
Sleep	O
again	O
;	O
but	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
began	O
to	O
be	O
suspicious	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
with	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
search	O
in	O
the	O
Vault	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Money	O
as	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
had	O
depos	O
'd	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Bag	O
,	O
a	O
Ring	O
,	O
a	O
Moidore	O
,	O
10	O
Guineas	O
,	O
6	O
Crown	O
Pieces	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
Crowns	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
to	O
the	O
Bag	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Ring	O
and	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
clearly	O
prov	O
'd	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
having	O
stolen	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Peter	I-place
's	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Spurs	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Fag	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
also	O
another	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Spurs	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Chymist	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Spurs	O
were	O
in	O
his	O
Possession	O
,	O
and	O
stolen	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Room	O
.	O
Joh	B-pers
Tripplet	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Spurs	O
upon	O
his	O
Boots	O
,	O
and	O
chang	O
'd	O
them	O
away	O
for	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Buckles	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
another	O
Pair	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
offering	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
Father	O
's	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
suspecting	O
him	O
,	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
c	O
onfess	O
'd	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Chymist	I-pers
swore	O
to	O
the	O
Spurs	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Katharine	B-pers
Wilcox	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Catherine	I-place
's	I-place
Creed-Church	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Kirkham	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
at	O
Christ-Church	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Water	O
,	O
coming	O
Home	O
had	O
the	O
Misfortune	O
to	O
fall	O
into	O
the	O
Water	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
to	O
an	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Landlord	O
lent	O
him	O
dry	O
Clothes	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
drank	O
hot	O
Liquors	O
to	O
prevent	O
his	O
taking	O
Cold	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
drank	O
more	O
than	O
he	O
usually	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
on	O
this	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Water	O
to	O
the	O
Old	O
Swan	O
,	O
drank	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Pints	O
with	O
two	O
Friends	O
,	O
from	O
whom	O
he	O
parted	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
making	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
his	O
way	O
Home	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
two	O
Women	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
make	O
them	O
drink	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Business	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
presently	O
after	O
he	O
met	O
two	O
Women	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
same	O
Women	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
That	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Women	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
became	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
clapped	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Gold	O
,	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
Robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
search	O
'd	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
desiring	O
that	O
he	O
himself	O
might	O
be	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
consented	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Watchman	O
search	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
only	O
18	O
d.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Gold	O
;	O
that	O
afterwards	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
put	O
her	O
Hand	O
in	O
his	O
Coat	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
half	O
Guinea	O
was	O
still	O
missing	O
.	O
-	O
Frisby	O
and	O
-	O
Carter	O
,	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Rimes	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
searching	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
no	O
Gold	O
about	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
finding	O
the	O
Guinea	O
,	O
afterwards	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
she	O
put	O
it	O
there	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
Persons	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
;	O
where	O
upon	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Durant	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dionis	I-place
Back-Church	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
taking	O
Money	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Stock	I-pers
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
December	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
selling	O
his	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Fowl	B-place
Market	I-place
of	I-place
Leaden-Hall	I-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Person	O
justled	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
kneeling	O
down	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
other	O
push	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
had	O
almost	O
thrown	O
him	O
down	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
felt	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Hand	O
at	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
recover	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
clap	O
'd	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
apprehended	O
would	O
have	O
made	O
the	O
Matter	O
up	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
to	O
an	O
Inn	O
in	O
White-Chappel	O
,	O
where	O
his	O
House	O
stood	O
,	O
for	O
Money	O
,	O
offering	O
his	O
Horse	O
to	O
the	O
Innkeeper	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
refus	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
sending	O
for	O
Money	O
to	O
make	O
up	O
the	O
Matter	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
other	O
Evidences	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Ray	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
5	O
Silver	O
Watches	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Paul	B-pers
Beauvau	I-pers
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
And	O
John	B-pers
Winslow	I-pers
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Watches	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
lost	O
his	O
Watches	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
at	O
what	O
time	O
,	O
nor	O
how	O
they	O
were	O
stolen	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Ray	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Winslow	I-pers
's	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Favour	O
to	O
ask	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
must	O
not	O
divulge	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
a	O
young	O
Woman	O
,	O
that	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
long	O
about	O
the	O
Town	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
pick	O
'd	O
up	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
but	O
knew	O
not	O
how	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
agreed	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
promising	O
him	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
her	O
bring	O
the	O
Woman	O
to	O
him	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
that	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
tell	O
him	O
the	O
Truth	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
stolen	O
it	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
then	O
they	O
knew	O
better	O
what	O
to	O
do	O
between	O
themselves	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
she	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
pulled	O
out	O
another	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
make	O
a	O
present	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
pawning	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
Winslow	O
gave	O
a	O
Penny	O
to	O
have	O
his	O
Wig	O
powder	O
'd	O
,	O
put	O
on	O
a	O
clean	O
Shirt	O
,	O
and	O
borrow	O
'd	O
a	O
Footman	O
's	O
Shoes	O
and	O
Buckles	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
pawn	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Watches	O
being	O
advertis	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
other	O
Evidences	O
,	O
that	O
Charles	B-pers
Ray	I-pers
was	O
a	O
Barber	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
to	O
trim	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
going	O
to	O
him	O
on	O
that	O
Account	O
,	O
found	O
opportunity	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Watches	O
;	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
Watches	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
by	O
the	O
Direction	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Ray	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Charles	B-pers
Ray	I-pers
could	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Winslow	I-pers
deny	O
'd	O
his	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
the	O
Watch	O
being	O
stolen	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
several	O
Persons	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anthony	B-pers
Wrigglesworth	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
23	O
Guineas	O
,	O
3	O
Moidores	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Susannah	B-pers
Carlton	I-pers
,	O
then	O
Widow	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Deer	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Combs	I-pers
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Deer	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Dwelling	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
her	O
Husband	O
and	O
she	O
coming	O
to	O
Town	O
,	O
took	O
Lodgings	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Combs	I-pers
,	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
falling	O
Sick	O
of	O
the	O
Small	O
Pox	O
,	O
died	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
remov	O
'd	O
her	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
being	O
also	O
very	O
ill	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
her	O
Nurse	O
to	O
get	O
her	O
things	O
brought	O
over	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
the	O
Chest	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Wriggles-worth	O
having	O
taken	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
Custody	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
own	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
out	O
29	O
l.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Chest	O
.	O
That	O
when	O
she	O
demanded	O
her	O
Money	O
to	O
pay	O
her	O
Nurse	O
and	O
Apothecary	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
pay	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
pay	O
the	O
Apothecary	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
the	O
Nurse	O
upwards	O
of	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
herself	O
two	O
Moidores	O
and	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
but	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
because	O
(	O
as	O
she	O
supposes	O
)	O
she	O
being	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
he	O
expected	O
she	O
would	O
die	O
:	O
And	O
she	O
depos	O
'd	O
she	O
never	O
committed	O
the	O
Money	O
to	O
his	O
keeping	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
other	O
Evidences	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Acknowledgment	O
of	O
his	O
having	O
taken	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Chest	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
when	O
it	O
came	O
to	O
a	O
Trial	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
it	O
appear	O
what	O
Right	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
detain	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Felony	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gage	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
,	I-place
Hackney	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Cocks	O
,	O
and	O
six	O
Hens	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Lever	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Velvet	O
Cap	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Henry	I-pers
Beauly	I-pers
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Holden	I-pers
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Beauly	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Cap	O
was	O
stolen	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop-Window	O
.	O
Other	O
Evidences	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
seeing	O
him	O
steal	O
some	O
other	O
Things	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
,	O
they	O
apprehended	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Cap	O
and	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Facts	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
upon	O
each	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Hollywell	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Huggins	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
an	O
Assault	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
commit	O
the	O
detestable	O
Crime	O
of	O
Buggery	O
upon	O
the	O
latter	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
for	O
consenting	O
and	O
submitting	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Rowden	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
for	O
many	O
Years	O
his	O
Business	O
to	O
show	O
the	O
upper	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Cathedral	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
;	O
that	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
betwixt	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Dinner	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
heard	O
the	O
old	O
Man	O
's	O
Door	O
shut	O
,	O
he	O
afterwards	O
heard	O
some	O
Persons	O
that	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
coming	O
up	O
softly	O
,	O
he	O
hearken	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
heard	O
no	O
Voices	O
,	O
that	O
suspecting	O
something	O
more	O
than	O
usual	O
,	O
he	O
look	O
'd	O
through	O
the	O
Light	O
of	O
the	O
Newel	O
Stairs	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
about	O
30	O
or	O
40	O
Steps	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
discover	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
very	O
indecent	O
Postures	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
made	O
haste	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
following	O
Posture	O
;	O
Huggins	O
's	O
Breeches	O
were	O
down	O
,	O
he	O
stooping	O
very	O
low	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
his	O
Shirt	O
was	O
turn	O
'd	O
up	O
on	O
his	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Back-side	O
was	O
bare	O
;	O
Hollywell	O
was	O
standing	O
close	O
by	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
fore	O
Parts	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
's	O
Posteriors	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Body	O
in	O
Motion	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
fore	O
Parts	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
then	O
see	O
,	O
his	O
Back	O
being	O
towards	O
him	O
,	O
this	O
Evidence	O
:	O
That	O
having	O
thus	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
Huggins	O
was	O
busy	O
'd	O
in	O
putting	O
up	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
Hollywell	O
struggled	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
have	O
got	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
have	O
gone	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
tore	O
his	O
Turnover	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
having	O
disengag	O
'd	O
himself	O
,	O
Hollywell	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
Church	O
Door	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
out	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
Lock	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
the	O
Key	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
Lock	O
'd	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
Side-Isle	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
Clerk	O
of	O
the	O
Works	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
acquaint	O
the	O
Dean	O
with	O
the	O
Matter	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
Hollywell	O
was	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
he	O
left	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
found	O
for	O
a	O
considerable	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
was	O
found	O
hidden	O
in	O
a	O
Gallery	O
adjoining	O
to	O
the	O
Organ-Loft	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
Hollywell	O
's	O
Shirt	O
was	O
examin	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
appear	O
'd	O
plain	O
Tokens	O
of	O
Emission	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Huggins	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
of	O
his	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
an	O
industrious	O
Man	O
in	O
his	O
Calling	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
that	O
of	O
a	O
Waterman	O
)	O
of	O
a	O
loving	O
Husband	O
to	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
tender	O
Father	O
to	O
his	O
Children	O
,	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
in	O
his	O
Dealings	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
a	O
religious	O
Man	O
that	O
kept	O
to	O
his	O
Church	O
constantly	O
on	O
Sundays	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
Men	O
they	O
should	O
have	O
suspected	O
as	O
to	O
such	O
Practices	O
,	O
and	O
should	O
more	O
readily	O
have	O
credited	O
his	O
Familiarity	O
with	O
Women	O
,	O
he	O
commonly	O
associating	O
himself	O
with	O
Women	O
more	O
than	O
Men	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
Character	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
against	O
positive	O
and	O
credible	O
Evidence	O
;	O
and	O
Hollywell	O
not	O
calling	O
one	O
single	O
Evidence	O
to	O
his	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Hollywell	O
:	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Alexander	B-pers
Reytown	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
,	I-place
Hanover	I-place
Squ	I-place
are	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
,	O
ravishing	O
,	O
and	O
carnally	O
knowing	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Sanderson	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
contrary	O
to	O
the	O
Will	O
and	O
Consent	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Elizabeth	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Sanderson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
being	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Druit	O
,	O
a	O
Baker	O
,	O
in	O
Shepherd's-Street	B-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Lodging	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
Abroad	O
that	O
Day	O
,	O
came	O
Home	O
about	O
Twelve	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
or	O
near	O
One	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
in	O
Bed	O
with	O
her	O
young	O
Mistress	O
,	O
and	O
fast	O
asleep	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
him	O
knock	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
let	O
in	O
by	O
her	O
old	O
Mistress	O
,	O
who	O
lay	O
below	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Captain	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
Chamber-Door	O
for	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
getting	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
slipping	O
on	O
her	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
carried	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
set	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Room	O
,	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
bid	O
her	O
shut	O
the	O
Window-Shutters	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
unbuckle	O
his	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
off	O
his	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
took	O
her	O
in	O
his	O
Arms	O
and	O
threw	O
her	O
into	O
a	O
two-arm	O
'd	O
Chair	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
Hands	O
up	O
her	O
Coats	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
strugling	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
deal	O
with	O
her	O
there	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
laid	O
her	O
cross	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
having	O
put	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
Breath	O
,	O
and	O
stopp	O
'd	O
her	O
Mouth	O
with	O
his	O
Sleeve	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
Fingers	O
into	O
her	O
Body	O
.	O
She	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
to	O
her	O
more	O
?	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
She	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
within	O
her	O
Body	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
,	O
but	O
how	O
long	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
Being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
what	O
part	O
of	O
him	O
was	O
within	O
her	O
Body	O
?	O
she	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
P	O
-	O
tle	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
felt	O
something	O
come	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
Moisture	O
.	O
Being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
If	O
she	O
made	O
any	O
Resistance	O
,	O
or	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
for	O
help	O
?	O
she	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
She	O
did	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
she	O
could	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
stopp	O
'd	O
her	O
Breath	O
with	O
his	O
Sleeve	O
,	O
and	O
hurt	O
her	O
Eye	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
and	O
almost	O
put	O
her	O
Eye	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
his	O
Surgeon	O
to	O
cure	O
her	O
Eye	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
bled	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
plaister	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
thus	O
abus	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
her	O
a	O
Guinea	O
to	O
say	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
gotten	O
her	O
with	O
Child	O
he	O
would	O
keep	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
thrust	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
into	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
following	O
Evidences	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Druit	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
She	O
let	O
the	O
Captain	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Maid	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
heard	O
her	O
carry	O
him	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
go	O
into	O
he	O
Room	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
shut	O
her	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
heard	O
no	O
Noise	O
,	O
neither	O
struggling	O
,	O
nor	O
calling	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
must	O
have	O
done	O
if	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
any	O
,	O
her	O
Door	O
being	O
open	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
hear	O
her	O
complain	O
of	O
any	O
ill	O
Usage	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
nor	O
for	O
some	O
considerable	O
time	O
after	O
.	O
The	O
like	O
was	O
depos	O
'd	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Druit	O
himself	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Sophia	O
Druit	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
she	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
Chamber	O
over	O
the	O
Captain	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
up	O
again	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
never	O
heard	O
her	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
she	O
make	O
complaint	O
to	O
her	O
of	O
the	O
Captain	O
having	O
used	O
her	O
ill	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
other	O
Evidences	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
complained	O
not	O
of	O
any	O
such	O
Injury	O
till	O
a	O
considerable	O
time	O
after	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
Captain	O
had	O
offered	O
any	O
such	O
Injury	O
?	O
She	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
No	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
afterwards	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
her	O
30	O
Guineas	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
work	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
lead	O
him	O
a	O
dance	O
;	O
after	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Conspiracy	O
,	O
with	O
design	O
to	O
charge	O
John	B-pers
Battle	I-pers
with	O
the	O
Crime	O
of	O
Sodomy	O
,	O
unless	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
them	O
ten	O
Guineas	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Battle	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
November	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
the	B-place
Castle	I-place
in	O
Mark-Lane	B-place
,	O
and	O
Jones	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
his	O
Apprentice	O
offering	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
show	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
Jones	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
himself	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Castle	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
called	O
out	O
from	O
his	O
Company	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
his	O
Business	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
then	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Bridewell	O
Boy	O
?	O
that	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
knows	O
you	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
hard	O
by	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
have	O
him	O
call	O
'd	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
going	O
into	O
a	O
Room	O
,	O
in	O
came	O
Lewis	O
,	O
leaning	O
upon	O
a	O
Broomstick	O
;	O
that	O
Jones	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
Fistula	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
Friend	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
came	O
by	O
Buggery	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
says	O
you	O
have	O
been	O
concern	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
would	O
have	O
10	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
must	O
have	O
6	O
Guineas	O
now	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
had	O
not	O
so	O
much	O
Money	O
,	O
that	O
Jones	O
reply	O
'd	O
then	O
,	O
He	O
must	O
borrow	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
put	O
them	O
off	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
Jones	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
give	O
Lewis	O
something	O
to	O
bear	O
his	O
Expences	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
himself	O
should	O
not	O
come	O
,	O
being	O
obliged	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Woolwich	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Globe	O
Tavern	O
at	O
Stocks-Market	O
,	O
(	O
being	O
in	O
much	O
Confusion	O
of	O
Mind	O
to	O
have	O
such	O
a	O
Crime	O
charg	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
willing	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
should	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
Ears	O
of	O
his	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
to	O
blast	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
they	O
threatening	O
otherwise	O
to	O
expose	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Attorney	O
being	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
)	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
found	O
both	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
them	O
five	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
more	O
,	O
having	O
forgot	O
that	O
Jones	O
said	O
be	O
must	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
10	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
would	O
cure	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
should	O
hear	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
being	O
unwilling	O
to	O
be	O
expos	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
be	O
further	O
troubled	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
Home	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
four	O
Guineas	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Receipt	O
,	O
and	O
Jones	O
wrote	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
Lewis	O
signed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
Jones	O
witnessed	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
November	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
Monday	O
the	O
9th	O
,	O
Jones	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
needs	O
drink	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Wine	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
being	O
at	O
the	O
Tavern	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
Lewis	O
had	O
been	O
Gaming	O
,	O
and	O
lost	O
all	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Mother	O
was	O
a	O
turbulent	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
come	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
and	O
make	O
a	O
Riot	O
,	O
unless	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
20	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
away	O
to	O
Holland	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
trouble	O
him	O
more	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
he	O
appointed	O
to	O
meet	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
Sun	O
Tavern	O
by	O
the	O
Monument	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
Jones	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
asking	O
for	O
Lewis	O
,	O
Jones	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
such	O
a	O
shabby	O
Dog	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
asham	O
'd	O
to	O
bring	O
him	O
thither	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Bell	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Nicholas-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
Jones	O
fetch	O
'd	O
Lewis	O
,	O
that	O
then	O
they	O
propos	O
'd	O
to	O
have	O
20	O
Guineas	O
as	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
Lewis	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
Holland	O
,	O
and	O
trouble	O
him	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
Jones	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
put	O
him	O
on	O
Board	O
of	O
Ship	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
him	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
he	O
making	O
some	O
Hesitation	O
,	O
Jones	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
his	O
Mother	O
would	O
come	O
and	O
be	O
very	O
riotous	O
,	O
and	O
Lewis	O
could	O
be	O
a	O
Witness	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
told	O
them	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
so	O
much	O
Money	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
must	O
stay	O
while	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Jones	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Friend	O
that	O
should	O
write	O
a	O
general	O
Release	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
he	O
promised	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Money	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Morning	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
acquainted	O
his	O
Attorney	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
for	O
apprehending	O
them	O
of	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Brocas	I-pers
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Tavern	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
appointed	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
both	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
Lewis	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
If	O
he	O
had	O
brought	O
the	O
Money	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Friend	O
below	O
that	O
would	O
lend	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
stepping	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
Constable	O
and	O
Attorney	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Constable	O
being	O
charg	O
'd	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
Jones	O
said	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Battle	O
,	O
Lord	O
,	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
done	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
you	O
would	O
have	O
serv	O
'd	O
me	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
fell	O
a	O
trembling	O
,	O
and	O
begging	O
,	O
and	O
praying	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
carried	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
might	O
not	O
be	O
prosecuted	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
or	O
give	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
owned	O
that	O
they	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
harm	O
by	O
him	O
(	O
Mr.	O
Battle	O
)	O
begged	O
the	O
Attorney	O
to	O
intercede	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
begg	O
'd	O
and	O
pray	O
'd	O
for	O
Mercy	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Brocas	I-pers
own	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
him	O
(	O
Mr.	O
Battle	O
)	O
before	O
in	O
their	O
Lives	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
it	O
to	O
get	O
Money	O
.	O
This	O
Confession	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Harrison	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Constable	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Ealing	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
being	O
an	O
ill-disposed	O
Person	O
,	O
and	O
greedy	O
of	O
wicked	O
Lucre	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
first	O
Day	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1723	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
November	O
1730	O
,	O
the	O
Laws	O
and	O
Statutes	O
of	O
this	O
Realm	O
not	O
esteeming	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
knowingly	O
,	O
unlawfully	O
,	O
wickedly	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
send	O
a	O
Letter	O
,	O
without	O
a	O
Name	O
,	O
to	O
Edward	B-pers
Leicester	I-pers
,	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Leicester	I-pers
,	O
demanding	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
5	O
l.	O
to	O
the	O
evil	O
Example	O
of	O
others	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
the	O
Peace	O
of	O
our	O
Sovereign	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
and	O
contrary	O
to	O
the	O
Statutes	O
in	O
that	O
Case	O
made	O
and	O
provided	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
for	O
sending	O
a	O
Letter	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stump	I-pers
,	O
demanding	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
two	O
Guineas	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
for	O
sending	O
a	O
Letter	O
to	O
James	B-pers
Barret	I-pers
,	O
demanding	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
50	O
l.	O
the	O
said	O
28th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Licester	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
finding	O
a	O
Letter	O
at	O
his	O
Door	O
about	O
Eight	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
Letter	O
being	O
as	O
follows	O
,	O
To	O
James	B-pers
Leicester	I-pers
,	O
Malster	O
,	O
at	O
Brandford	O
,	O
You	O
miserly	O
Son	O
of	O
a	O
Bitch	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
you	O
get	O
this	O
,	O
lay	O
5	O
l.	O
at	O
the	O
Back-door	O
of	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Anchor	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
Care	O
to	O
set	O
no	O
Watch	O
;	O
if	O
you	O
comply	O
we	O
will	O
give	O
no	O
further	O
Trouble	O
,	O
if	O
not	O
,	O
by	O
God	O
,	O
we	O
will	O
destroy	O
you	O
.	O
Upon	O
reading	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
shew	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
that	O
suspecting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
seen	O
lurking	O
about	O
the	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
a	O
Letter	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
some	O
Similitude	O
in	O
the	O
Hands	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
this	O
was	O
a	O
Letter	O
of	O
his	O
Wife	O
's	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
owned	O
himself	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Irish	O
Roman	B-pers
Catholick	I-pers
,	O
was	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
as	O
a	O
Stroller	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
seen	O
in	O
the	O
Town	O
about	O
Nine	O
o'Clock	O
that	O
Morning	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stump	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
found	O
his	O
Letter	O
just	O
within	O
his	O
Door	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
suppos	O
'd	O
,	O
thrust	O
in	O
between	O
a	O
Vacancy	O
of	O
the	O
upper	O
and	O
under-part	O
of	O
his	O
Shop-door	O
.	O
The	O
Substance	O
of	O
the	O
Letter	O
is	O
as	O
follows	O
:	O
You	O
are	O
hereby	O
order	O
'd	O
to	O
leave	O
two	O
Guineas	O
under	O
the	O
right	O
Post	O
of	O
-	O
If	O
not	O
,	O
by	O
God	O
,	O
we	O
will	O
destroy	O
your	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
your	O
Family	O
;	O
if	O
you	O
wait	O
twelve	O
Months	O
you	O
shall	O
not	O
take	O
us	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Barret	I-pers
's	O
Letter	O
was	O
thus	O
:	O
I	O
desire	O
you	O
will	O
to	O
morrow	O
Morning	O
put	O
50	O
l.	O
at	O
the	O
Back-door	O
of	O
your	O
Meeting-House	O
,	O
otherwise	O
we	O
will	O
destroy	O
you	O
and	O
your	O
Family	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
by	O
God	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
Persons	O
who	O
have	O
these	O
Notes	O
sent	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
do	O
not	O
comply	O
,	O
we	O
will	O
lay	O
the	O
Town	O
in	O
Ashes	O
.	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
Proof	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
seen	O
lurking	O
about	O
the	O
Town	O
that	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
giving	O
any	O
good	O
Account	O
of	O
himself	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
ask	O
'd	O
several	O
Questions	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
as	O
follows	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
at	O
Chelsea	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
liv	O
'd	O
there	O
13	O
Months	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
France	O
;	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
way	O
of	O
living	O
,	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
none	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
uncapable	O
of	O
working	O
,	O
by	O
Reason	O
of	O
a	O
Swelling	O
in	O
his	O
Neck	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
supported	O
by	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
(	O
who	O
,	O
as	O
Justice	O
Venner	O
,	O
who	O
examin	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
no	O
otherwise	O
his	O
Wife	O
than	O
before	O
God	O
,	O
)	O
that	O
he	O
set	O
out	O
from	O
Chelsea	O
on	O
Saturday	O
about	O
One	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
designing	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
,	O
a	O
Romish	O
Priest	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Lord	O
Shrewsbury	O
's	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
dirty	O
,	O
lay	O
at	O
Hammersmith	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
likewise	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
upon	O
Examination	O
,	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
formerly	O
kill	O
'd	O
a	O
Man	O
at	O
Lisle	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
went	O
to	O
France	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
true	O
Name	O
was	O
not	O
Russel	O
,	O
but	O
Kelly	O
.	O
He	O
deny	O
'd	O
his	O
having	O
any	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
the	O
Letters	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Roger	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Mordecai	B-pers
Pitts	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
High-way	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
and	O
Danger	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
a	O
Periwig	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
Value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
Mordecai	B-pers
Pitts	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Muggleston	O
came	O
to	O
ask	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
a	O
Judge	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
King's-Head	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Chancery-Lane	B-place
,	O
and	O
waited	O
there	O
till	O
they	O
were	O
inform	O
'd	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
Raymond	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
spoke	O
with	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
having	O
gone	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
his	O
Left-hand	O
catch	O
'd	O
off	O
his	O
Wig	O
and	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
his	O
Right	O
,	O
threw	O
a	O
handful	O
of	O
Snuff	O
in	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
ran	O
cross	O
the	O
way	O
with	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
himself	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
beaten	O
and	O
abus	O
'd	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Pool	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
is	O
Yeoman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Pitts	O
,	O
a	O
Serjeant	O
of	O
the	O
Poultry-Compter	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
Raymond	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
to	O
Chancery-Lane	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
King's-Head	O
Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
inform	O
'd	O
his	O
Lordship	O
was	O
ready	O
,	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
his	O
Chambers	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
near	O
Chancery-Lane	O
,	O
they	O
saw	O
four	O
Men	O
with	O
Clubs	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
his	O
Left-hand	O
catch	O
'd	O
off	O
Mr.	O
Pitt	O
's	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
his	O
Right	O
threw	O
Snuff	O
in	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Pulford	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
walking	O
along	O
about	O
Six	O
o-Clock	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
an	O
out-cry	O
of	O
stop	O
Street-Robbers	O
,	O
he	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
running	O
,	O
stopp	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
for	O
God-sake	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
stop	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
soon	O
after	O
Mr.	O
Pitts	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
desir	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
might	O
be	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
If	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
the	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
make	O
a	O
Demand	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
following	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
Riot	O
and	O
Tumult	O
,	O
and	O
clashing	O
of	O
Sticks	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
cry	O
out	O
Murther	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Boy	O
going	O
out	O
kick	O
'd	O
a	O
Wig	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
scuffle	O
began	O
at	O
the	O
King's-Head	O
Back-Door	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
some	O
Body	O
say	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
's	O
gone	O
,	O
he	O
's	O
gone	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
carried	O
the	O
Wig	O
to	O
the	O
King's-Head	O
Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Officer	O
that	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
Partner	O
's	O
Wig	O
,	O
give	O
it	O
me	O
.	O
It	O
appearing	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
to	O
be	O
rather	O
a	O
Riot	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
an	O
Escape	O
than	O
a	O
Robbery	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Frances	B-pers
Clinch	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Stephen	I-place
's	I-place
Wallbrook	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
one	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
13	O
s.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Proof	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
George	B-pers
William	I-pers
Monguibert	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
forging	O
a	O
promissory	O
Note	O
for	O
60	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Sparks	I-pers
,	O
payable	O
to	O
himself	O
or	O
Order	O
,	O
for	O
Value	O
receiv	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
for	O
tearing	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Note	O
never	O
having	O
been	O
executed	O
,	O
nor	O
the	O
Forgery	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Isaacson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Arthur	B-pers
Moor	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
And	O
Jane	B-pers
Molloon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
White-Chapel	B-place
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
them	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
against	O
the	O
two	O
former	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Burglary	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
only	O
,	O
each	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
being	O
made	O
out	O
that	O
the	O
latter	O
knew	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Daniel	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
the	I-place
Evangelist	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Churchill	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
;	O
which	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
94	O
Guineas	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Earle	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
November	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Magdelen	B-pers
Bucknel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Chandler	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Alhallow	B-place
's	I-place
the	I-place
Great	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Hammond	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
;	O
which	O
Fact	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bigrave	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Kilpatrick	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
latter	O
for	O
receiving	O
them	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Rowe	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Nevil	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Macartney	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Westmore	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Wagstaff	I-pers
:	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Sansum	I-pers
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
North	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Mawson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Body	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Strange	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
December	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Maudlin	B-pers
Aubour	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
70	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Borroughs	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Proof	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lambert	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Conner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Ashley	I-pers
,	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Wyatt	I-pers
and	O
Daniel	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Forster	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
latter	O
for	O
receiving	O
them	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
;	O
to	O
this	O
Indictment	O
the	O
former	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Proof	O
against	O
the	O
latter	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
latter	O
for	O
receiving	O
them	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
against	O
Wyat	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
against	O
the	O
latter	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Benson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
sufficient	O
Proof	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
and	O
Honour	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Faber	I-pers
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
latter	O
an	O
Accessory	O
after	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
latter	O
deluded	O
her	O
to	O
do	O
the	O
Fact	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
Money	O
to	O
tell	O
her	O
Fortune	O
,	O
promising	O
her	O
great	O
Things	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Alice	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Rag	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Hornby	I-pers
,	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
;	O
both	O
which	O
Facts	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
upon	O
each	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	O
de	O
la	O
Port	O
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
near	O
Leicester-House	B-place
,	O
and	O
going	O
pretty	O
fast	O
,	O
because	O
it	O
Rain	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
catch	O
'd	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Coat	O
as	O
he	O
pass	O
'd	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
refusing	O
,	O
she	O
clap	O
'd	O
her	O
Hand	O
to	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
out	O
a	O
Crown-piece	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Crown	O
to	O
oblige	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
though	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
have	O
it	O
done	O
in	O
a	O
beastly	O
manner	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
demanded	O
the	O
Crown	O
again	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
Six-pence	O
was	O
enough	O
for	O
such	O
an	O
ugly	O
Bitch	O
as	O
she	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
Plea	O
not	O
availing	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Mansel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bone	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Hartshorn	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hilliard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Curtis	I-pers
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
;	O
which	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
,	O
and	O
also	O
two	O
Bank	O
Notes	O
,	O
for	O
200	O
l.	O
each	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
a	O
young	O
Girl	O
about	O
10	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
)	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
Mother	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Cellar	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
abroad	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
stopp	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
going	O
to	O
pawn	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
Bank	O
Notes	O
,	O
upon	O
Examination	O
,	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
burnt	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
answering	O
to	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Notes	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
that	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Butcher	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Caine	I-pers
,	O
in	O
an	O
open	O
Place	O
near	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buttons	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Matth.ew	O
Goodwin	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Tar-pawlin	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Mecchum	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
5	O
Cheeses	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hooker	I-pers
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
November	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Christopher	B-pers
Husband	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White-Chapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
taking	O
a	O
Wire-show-Grate	O
from	O
the	O
Shop-window	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Marshal	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
apprehended	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
carrying	O
away	O
the	O
Grate	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Tomlin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Fuller	I-pers
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
against	O
Anderson	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
not	O
proved	O
against	O
Tomlin	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Isaiah	B-pers
Marshal	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Christ-Church	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Shoes	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ingleberd	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Cuppleditch	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dummer	I-pers
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Alice	B-pers
Grace	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hollyman	I-pers
;	O
but	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Proof	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Feuterel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Pancras	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Fowls	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hillary	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Batt	I-pers
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Show-Glass	O
with	O
Cutlery-Ware	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Patrick	B-pers
Forster	I-pers
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Paul	I-pers
and	O
Christopher	B-pers
Husband	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White-Chapel	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Show-Grate	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Riding	I-pers
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
proved	O
upon	O
Husband	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
but	O
Paul	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Rawbone	B-pers
William	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
,	I-place
Hanover-Square	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Cocks	O
and	O
Hens	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Lachston	I-pers
;	O
but	O
no	O
Body	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Peck	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
England	I-pers
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samuel	B-pers
Dexter	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Thorp	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Smart	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Gabriel	B-pers
Verdiere	I-pers
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Proof	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
wilful	O
and	O
corrupt	O
Perjury	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Body	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Sullivan	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Stanley	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Wall	B-pers
,	O
and	O
Isabella	B-pers
Gwyn	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Eaton	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
2	O
Guineas	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
about	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Crown	B-place
Tavern	I-place
in	O
Sherard-street	B-place
,	O
by	O
Golden-Square	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchin	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
several	O
Pints	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
at	O
the	O
most	O
;	O
that	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
counted	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
laying	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
put	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
two	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Silver	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
being	O
present	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
sometimes	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
another	O
,	O
alternately	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
stirr	O
'd	O
from	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
he	O
sat	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
they	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
14	O
Pints	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
is	O
certain	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
above	O
six	O
at	O
the	O
most	O
,	O
that	O
feeling	O
for	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
his	O
Guineas	O
were	O
missing	O
;	O
that	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
contending	O
about	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
a	O
Guinea	O
was	O
thrown	O
under	O
the	O
Table	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Neal	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
passing	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
House	O
,	O
heard	O
a	O
Bell-Harp	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
in	O
,	O
espy	O
'd	O
his	O
Friend	O
sitting	O
,	O
and	O
knowing	O
that	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
carry	O
Money	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
thinking	O
him	O
in	O
danger	O
of	O
loosing	O
it	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
p	O
ersuade	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
;	O
that	O
feeling	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
for	O
Money	O
to	O
pay	O
his	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
two	O
Guineas	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
)	O
had	O
sunk	O
the	O
Guineas	O
to	O
bilk	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
at	O
length	O
a	O
Guinea	O
thrown	O
under	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
believes	O
,	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Eaton	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
heard	O
fall	O
under	O
or	O
near	O
Sullivan	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
took	O
up	O
and	O
gave	O
to	O
Eaton	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
here	O
's	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
Madam	O
,	O
take	O
your	O
Reckoning	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
,	O
according	O
as	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
was	O
14	O
Shillings	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
but	O
5	O
Shillings	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
swear	O
positively	O
which	O
of	O
them	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Mines	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Minshum	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Mitchel	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
four	O
Pence	O
Half-penny	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
set	O
upon	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
Bloomsbury-Square	B-place
,	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
five	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
Company	O
;	O
that	O
Mines	O
held	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
Saunders	O
riffl	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
to	O
White	O
he	O
could	O
say	O
nothing	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
making	O
Complaint	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
where	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
told	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Persons	O
who	O
had	O
Robb	O
'd	O
him	O
would	O
be	O
there	O
by	O
and	O
bye	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
sold	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
drink	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
in	O
Gin	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
coming	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
shuffled	O
him	O
and	O
got	O
away	O
.	O
Rowland	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
committed	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
that	O
Minshum	O
held	O
the	O
Pistol	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
that	O
Saunders	O
riffled	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
having	O
sold	O
the	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Brandy-shop	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
taxed	O
them	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Caleb	B-pers
Jencock	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
having	O
taken	O
Minshum	O
,	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
Robb	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
John	O
Debel	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
taxing	O
Rowland	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
with	O
having	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
this	O
Robbery	O
,	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
himself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
Notice	O
to	O
apprehend	O
Saunders	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Minshum	O
own	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Pistol	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
was	O
that	O
which	O
he	O
presented	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Breast	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
having	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
all	O
three	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Tylor	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Constance	B-pers
Buckle	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Richard	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
Street	O
about	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Hat	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
Rowland	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
himself	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
having	O
been	O
drinking	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Griffith	O
's	O
Shop	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
they	O
all	O
came	O
out	O
together	O
with	O
a	O
design	O
to	O
get	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
and	O
met	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
that	O
Saunders	O
hit	O
him	O
a	O
knock	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
Hat	O
did	O
not	O
fall	O
off	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
Tyler	O
hit	O
him	O
another	O
and	O
it	O
fell	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
Constance	B-pers
Buckle	I-pers
took	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
her	O
Coats	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
next	O
Morning	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Sharples	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Debel	I-pers
apprehended	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Tyler	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
that	O
Night	O
with	O
Rowland	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
and	O
that	O
Constance	B-pers
Buckle	I-pers
own	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
them	O
when	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Debel	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Rowland	B-pers
James	I-pers
bid	O
him	O
apprehend	O
Saunders	O
for	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
all	O
three	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
[	O
Buckle	O
:	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Brabent	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Richard	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
15	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Turn-stile	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
pass	O
'd	O
by	O
him	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
Brabent	O
stood	O
still	O
and	O
stared	O
him	O
full	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Coal-Yard	O
,	O
near	O
Drury-Lane	B-place
,	O
Brabent	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
struck	O
him	O
first	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
him	O
real	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
his	O
Cane	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
;	O
he	O
making	O
some	O
Resistance	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
struck	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
fell	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
stunned	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
to	O
himself	O
found	O
his	O
Wig	O
lying	O
under	O
him	O
,	O
his	O
Breeches	O
unbuttoned	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Money	O
which	O
was	O
15	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Fob	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Debel	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
having	O
a	O
Warrant	O
against	O
James	O
Hall	O
for	O
another	O
Robbery	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
Brabent	O
did	O
this	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
himself	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Hat	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
Brabent	O
had	O
sunk	O
the	O
Money	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Hall	O
wanted	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
an	O
Evidence	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Tyrrell	I-pers
,	O
that	O
Hall	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
impeach	O
several	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
be	O
made	O
an	O
Evidence	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
likewise	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
Edward	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
;	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
both	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Sherlock	I-pers
,	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
November	O
assault	O
James	B-pers
Ramsey	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
put	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
1	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
Holbourn	O
between	O
2	O
and	O
3	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Dean-street	B-place
,	O
he	O
saw	O
Hall	O
standing	O
near	O
the	O
Channel	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
stood	O
near	O
the	O
Houses	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
them	O
so	O
plainly	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
look	O
'd	O
at	O
them	O
for	O
two	O
Minutes	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
came	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Cuts	O
on	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
his	O
Breeches	O
unbuttoned	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Money	O
gone	O
.	O
That	O
taking	O
Notice	O
that	O
a	O
Man	O
and	O
Woman	O
look	O
'd	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
that	O
House	O
and	O
enquir	O
'd	O
if	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
remember	O
a	O
Man	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
thereabouts	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
up	O
and	O
kept	O
3	O
Days	O
and	O
4	O
Nights	O
,	O
and	O
discharg	O
'd	O
,	O
they	O
not	O
knowing	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
at	O
a	O
Brandy-shop	O
near	O
that	O
place	O
.	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Goodale	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
passing	O
to	O
and	O
fro	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
about	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
knock	O
down	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
William	B-pers
Sherlock	I-pers
was	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
living	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
a	O
Brandy-shop	O
that	O
they	O
used	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
again	O
apprehended	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Days	O
after	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Debel	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
him	O
three	O
Days	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
finding	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
discharg	O
'd	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
coming	O
afterwards	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
describing	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
apprehended	O
him	O
again	O
at	O
the	O
Brandy-shop	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
own	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
but	O
deny	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
.	O
This	O
Fact	O
also	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
and	O
Peter	B-pers
Norman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Samuel	B-pers
Addison	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
Fields	O
between	O
White-Chappel	B-place
and	O
Ratcliff	B-place
Highway	I-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
Field	O
beyond	O
the	O
Night-Field	O
,	O
three	O
Men	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
first	O
presented	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
his	O
right	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
second	O
a	O
Bayonet	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
turn	O
'd	O
his	O
Apron	O
aside	O
,	O
took	O
his	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
sixteen	O
Pence	O
,	O
or	O
sixteen	O
Pence	O
Farthing	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
offer	O
him	O
any	O
personal	O
Abuse	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
pull	O
'd	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
from	O
off	O
his	O
Neck	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
positively	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
believe	O
Holland	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
presented	O
the	O
Pistol	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Asey	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
himself	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
going	O
over	O
Stepney	B-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
and	O
meeting	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
Holland	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
and	O
himself	O
with	O
a	O
Bayonet	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Norman	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
ten	O
Pence	O
Farthing	O
,	O
and	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
Pocket	O
six	O
Pence	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
off	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
being	O
a	O
good	O
one	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
took	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
eight	O
Pence	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
Holland	O
eight	O
Pence	O
,	O
and	O
Norman	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
odd	O
Farthing	O
they	O
threw	O
away	O
.	O
Norman	O
call	O
'd	O
some	O
Evidences	O
to	O
his	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
prove	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Sick	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
when	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
not	O
making	O
it	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Matthias	B-pers
Pepin	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Richard	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
a	O
Cornelian	O
Seal	O
set	O
in	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Richard	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Spectacles	O
and	O
Case	O
of	O
Joanna	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
Capt	O
.	O
Griffith	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
,	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
going	O
home	O
to	O
Mile-End	B-place
,	O
beyond	O
the	O
Turnpike	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
Stones	O
throw	O
,	O
was	O
attack	O
'd	O
by	O
several	O
Men	O
,	O
that	O
Hall	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
presenting	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
your	O
Money	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
your	O
Money	O
!	O
Friend	O
do	O
you	O
always	O
say	O
so	O
when	O
you	O
are	O
drunk	O
?	O
That	O
thereupon	O
Smith	O
said	O
,	O
shoot	O
him	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
use	O
him	O
as	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
;	O
and	O
Hall	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
we	O
will	O
use	O
you	O
like	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
riffling	O
him	O
of	O
his	O
Watch	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
leave	O
him	O
some	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
thinks	O
was	O
Pepin	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
leave	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
some	O
Silver	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
great	O
Number	O
of	O
Sheep	O
coming	O
through	O
the	O
Turn-pike	O
,	O
they	O
having	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
made	O
off	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
White-Chapel	O
,	O
and	O
acquainted	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Barton	I-pers
went	O
in	O
Quest	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
outer	O
Case	O
of	O
his	O
Watch	O
near	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
afterwards	O
found	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
;	O
that	O
Hall	O
was	O
taken	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
an	O
Evidence	O
.	O
-	O
Hall	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
himself	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
committed	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
that	O
tho	O
'	O
Holland	O
was	O
not	O
indeed	O
present	O
,	O
yet	O
he	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
to	O
look	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
be	O
ready	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
their	O
Assistance	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
should	O
want	O
any	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
parted	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
Holland	O
had	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
3	O
d.	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
himself	O
5	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
and	O
that	O
Pepin	O
had	O
the	O
like	O
part	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Barton	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
at	O
Justice	O
Philips	O
's	O
upon	O
another	O
Account	O
,	O
was	O
told	O
by	O
Harry	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
discover	O
'd	O
who	O
the	O
Fellows	O
were	O
that	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
Captain	O
Griffith	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
inform	O
'd	O
Captain	O
Griffith	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
him	O
apprehended	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
Captain	O
Griffith	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
inform	O
him	O
the	O
Night	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
an	O
Headborough	O
,	O
search	O
'd	O
several	O
suspected	O
Houses	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
apprehend	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
;	O
after	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
Pepin	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Barnet	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
's	I-place
White-Chapel	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
James	B-pers
Ivory	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
Field	O
,	O
or	O
open	O
Place	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Bag	O
,	O
Value	O
1	O
d.	O
an	O
Iron	O
Tobacco	O
Stopper	O
,	O
and	O
17	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
White-Chapel-Fields	B-place
,	O
at	O
the	O
back-side	O
of	O
the	O
Mount	O
,	O
about	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
two	O
Men	O
in	O
Soldiers	O
Clothes	O
with	O
Cutlasses	O
,	O
he	O
passed	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
bid	O
him	O
good	O
Night	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
saw	O
two	O
others	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
first	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
must	O
have	O
his	O
Money	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
poor	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
hoped	O
they	O
were	O
but	O
in	O
jest	O
;	O
they	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
earnest	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Man	O
in	O
Soldiers	O
Clothes	O
stood	O
by	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
riffled	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
If	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Fob	O
?	O
That	O
when	O
they	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Soldier	O
said	O
,	O
go	O
about	O
your	O
Business	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Asey	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
with	O
him	O
that	O
Night	O
at	O
a	O
Brandy-shop	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
agreed	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
a	O
Robbing	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
together	O
into	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
broke	O
open	O
a	O
Shed	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
nothing	O
there	O
but	O
an	O
old	O
Broom	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
old	O
Tinder-Box	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
pull	O
'd	O
the	O
Stick	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Broom	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
staid	O
till	O
about	O
Ten	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
with	O
a	O
Basket	O
,	O
that	O
Holland	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
and	O
Barnet	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
17	O
Pence	O
three	O
Farthings	O
as	O
he	O
pretended	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
them	O
3	O
d.	O
a-piece	O
,	O
and	O
spent	O
Four-pence	O
Half-penny	O
,	O
but	O
sunk	O
the	O
Money	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Bag	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
see	O
something	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
like	O
a	O
Purse	O
or	O
Bag	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
Barnet	O
had	O
bought	O
him	O
new	O
Shoes	O
,	O
Stockings	O
and	O
Shirt	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
rallied	O
him	O
for	O
cheating	O
them	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
last	O
Night	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
Farthing	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
thereupon	O
Holland	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
keep	O
the	O
Pistol	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Falkener	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
Barnet	O
,	O
Asey	O
and	O
Holland	O
were	O
at	O
Shelton	O
's	O
drinking	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
talking	O
about	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
but	O
3	O
d.	O
Half-penny	O
a-piece	O
,	O
and	O
Holland	O
said	O
he	O
saw	O
Barnet	O
take	O
something	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
that	O
look	O
'd	O
