TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
ON	O
Friday	O
the	O
15th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
16th	O
,	O
Monday	O
the	O
18th	O
,	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
19th	O
,	O
and	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
1731	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Fourth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Second	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
HUMPHREY	B-pers
PARSONS	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1731	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
II	O
.	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
YEAR	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
T.	O
PAYNE	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
,	O
in	O
Pater-noster-Row	O
.	O
1731	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
Six	O
Pence	O
.	O
)	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
AND	O
ON	O
The	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
,	O
Monday	O
,	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
and	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
15th	O
,	O
16th	O
,	O
18th	O
,	O
19th	O
,	O
and	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
1731	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Fourth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
HUMPHREY	B-pers
PARSONS	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Rt	O
.	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
;	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Probyn	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
Raby	O
,	O
Deputy-Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Purchass	I-pers
,	O
Edmund	B-pers
Homer	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Chamberlain	I-pers
,	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lander	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Mosden	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Picket	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Holliday	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Playstead	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Prater	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Gilmore	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Fortescue	I-pers
,	O
Stephen	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Fairchild	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Blackwell	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Pinnot	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Wren	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Power	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Belson	I-pers
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Hammock	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
Queen	I-place
Hithe	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
28	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Malt	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
28	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Malt	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Edward	B-pers
Day	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
having	O
told	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
with	O
a	O
Skiff	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Lighter	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
3	O
Quarters	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Malt	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
come	O
twice	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
each	O
time	O
3	O
Quarters	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Malt	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
paid	O
him	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
two	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
the	O
second	O
1	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
and	O
paid	O
for	O
the	O
Malt	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
Malt	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
4	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dashwood	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Boots	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
Murrey	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Roger	B-pers
Manley	I-pers
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
as	O
a	O
Groom	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Dashwood	O
's	O
Stables	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
taken	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39s	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Ashurst	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Ogilvy	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Christopher	B-pers
Laughlin	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
drinking	O
till	O
about	O
3	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
to	O
his	O
Lodging	O
;	O
and	O
was	O
met	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
who	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
beat	O
him	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
and	O
running	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
he	O
lodg	O
'd	O
,	O
got	O
in	O
and	O
shut	O
the	O
Door	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
other	O
Evidences	O
,	O
That	O
both	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
Prisoners	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
one	O
and	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
pretended	O
not	O
to	O
know	O
one	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
at	O
first	O
only	O
insisted	O
upon	O
Satisfaction	O
for	O
a	O
Shirt	O
that	O
was	O
torn	O
in	O
the	O
Fighting	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
between	O
them	O
at	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
not	O
charging	O
them	O
with	O
Robbing	O
him	O
of	O
5	O
s.	O
till	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
lay	O
several	O
Nights	O
after	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
both	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Carrol	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Welsh	I-pers
,	O
Patrick	B-pers
Gill	I-pers
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Roe	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
Jan.	O
Katharine	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Gill	O
had	O
brought	O
her	O
a	O
Letter	O
two	O
Days	O
before	O
,	O
for	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
certain	O
Place	O
to	O
fetch	O
some	O
Materials	O
for	O
Apparel	O
,	O
that	O
were	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
in	O
haste	O
(	O
she	O
being	O
a	O
Mantua-maker	O
)	O
but	O
she	O
not	O
knowing	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
own	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
carried	O
her	O
a	O
Letter	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
gone	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
committed	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
by	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Savil	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
notice	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
lurking	O
about	O
near	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
for	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Days	O
before	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Goddard	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
lodging	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
saw	O
Carrol	O
coming	O
down	O
Stairs	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
stopping	O
him	O
,	O
caus	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
apprehended	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Savil	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
other	O
three	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
apprehended	O
,	O
by	O
means	O
of	O
the	O
Impeachment	O
of	O
Carrol	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
Carrol	O
pleaded	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
by	O
the	O
Justice	O
admitted	O
as	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
which	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
;	O
but	O
at	O
finding	O
the	O
Bill	O
,	O
Carrol	O
being	O
put	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
was	O
oblig	O
'd	O
to	O
stand	O
the	O
Trial	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
own	O
Confession	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Goddard	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
but	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
against	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
three	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Malshaw	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Edmonton	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Riggot	I-pers
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
getting	O
up	O
betimes	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
divers	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
inform	O
'd	O
by	O
his	O
Boy	O
that	O
the	O
Maid	O
was	O
gone	O
away	O
,	O
arose	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
rode	O
towards	O
Shoreditch	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Road	O
overtook	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
carrying	O
her	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
,	O
she	O
delivered	O
to	O
him	O
all	O
the	O
Things	O
she	O
had	O
stolen	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Beby	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
,	O
sen.	O
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
,	O
jun	O
.	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
four	O
Yards	O
of	O
Broad-cloth	O
,	O
value	O
28	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lear	I-pers
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
being	O
Taylors	O
,	O
were	O
Journeymen	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
several	O
times	O
cut	O
off	O
three	O
Quarters	O
of	O
a	O
Yard	O
of	O
his	O
Cloth	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
Beby	O
and	O
Goodwin	O
,	O
sen.	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4s	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
;	O
but	O
Edward	O
Goodwin	O
,	O
jun	O
.	O
having	O
only	O
carried	O
away	O
three	O
Quarters	O
of	O
a	O
Yard	O
of	O
Cloth	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
given	O
him	O
by	O
his	O
Father	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Civility	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Bass	I-pers
,	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Hat	O
hung	O
up	O
at	O
his	O
Shop	O
Window	O
to	O
fell	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
inform	O
'd	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
pursued	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Hat	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Oxley	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Williams	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Leak	I-pers
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4s	O
.	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Tilbury	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White-Chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Money	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Ridley	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ridley	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
her	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
but	O
three	O
Days	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
gone	O
to	O
her	O
Shop	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
distant	O
from	O
her	O
Dwelling	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
for	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
her	O
Chamber	O
,	O
under	O
pretence	O
to	O
clean	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Draw	O
,	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Brand	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Stratford	I-place
le	I-place
Bow	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
40	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Middleditch	I-pers
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
Prisoner	O
were	O
Fellow-servants	O
to	O
Ambrose	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
he	O
restor	O
'd	O
39	O
Guineas	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Brass-Wire	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jeffery	B-pers
Gillingham	I-pers
,	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Journeyman	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Bellinger	I-pers
&	O
Francis	B-pers
Richmond	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Christ-Church	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Downs	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Silver	O
Tankards	O
,	O
value	O
10l	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Rim	O
of	O
a	O
Leather	O
Mug	O
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
House	O
had	O
been	O
broken	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Tankards	O
stolen	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
House	O
had	O
been	O
entred	O
at	O
a	O
Window	O
which	O
was	O
over	O
a	O
Slaughter-House	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Bellinger	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
having	O
lodged	O
there	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
,	O
knew	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
some	O
times	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
that	O
way	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
other	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
Bellinger	O
and	O
Richmond	O
had	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
carried	O
broken	O
Silver	O
to	O
one	O
James	O
Hall	O
,	O
a	O
Melter	O
,	O
to	O
melt	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
sat	O
by	O
him	O
while	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
Bellinger	O
gave	O
him	O
2	O
s.	O
for	O
his	O
Pains	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
broken	O
into	O
such	O
Pieces	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
discover	O
what	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Bellinger	O
pretended	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
it	O
wrapped	O
up	O
in	O
two	O
Parcels	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
kick	O
'd	O
it	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
Evidences	O
that	O
gave	O
Occasion	O
for	O
strong	O
Suspicion	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
swear	O
that	O
the	O
Masses	O
of	O
Silver	O
which	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
having	O
committed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
French	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Iron	O
Water-Cock	O
Keys	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Child	I-pers
,	O
Bart	O
.	O
Lord	O
Viscount	O
Castlemain	O
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Iron	O
was	O
stolen	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Lordship	O
's	O
Engine-House	O
in	O
the	O
Park	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Rayner	I-pers
,	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Seal	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
14	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
ten	O
Pounds	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ely	I-pers
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
John	O
Seal	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Money	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Trunk	O
in	O
his	O
Chamber	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
looking	O
for	O
his	O
Money	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
altho	O
'	O
he	O
found	O
his	O
Trunk	O
lock	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Key	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
Reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
in	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
coming	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
into	O
his	O
Room	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
being	O
House-Keeper	O
(	O
altho	O
'	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
lie	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
)	O
to	O
John	O
Seal	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
searching	O
Evans	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
not	O
far	O
,	O
a	O
Key	O
was	O
found	O
among	O
her	O
Keys	O
that	O
would	O
open	O
his	O
Trunk	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
also	O
proved	O
,	O
that	O
upon	O
searching	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Houses	O
,	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
nor	O
Rings	O
were	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Key	O
did	O
also	O
open	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
Drawers	O
:	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
other	O
Proof	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
calling	O
Persons	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
them	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Darrel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Israel	B-pers
Maurice	I-pers
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bever	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
King's-Arms	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Pallmal	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
up	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lying	O
upon	O
his	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Trunk	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
brought	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Chamber	O
into	O
his	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Things	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
lying	O
about	O
the	O
Room	O
;	O
that	O
upon	O
his	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
If	O
his	O
Lord	O
was	O
gone	O
?	O
That	O
he	O
suspecting	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Thief	O
,	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
struggling	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
got	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
ran	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
he	O
pursuing	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
getting	O
into	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
crying	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Black	O
Hoods	O
,	O
two	O
Mobs	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
-	O
Henry	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
hearing	O
an	O
out-cry	O
of	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
,	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
to	O
avoid	O
him	O
ran	O
among	O
some	O
Chairs	O
,	O
and	O
sell	O
over	O
the	O
Chair-Polls	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
seized	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
Drunk	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
nor	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
last	O
Evidence	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
If	O
he	O
was	O
Drunk	O
?	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
No	O
;	O
for	O
he	O
ran	O
more	O
like	O
a	O
Greyhound	O
than	O
a	O
drunken	O
Man	O
,	O
that	O
had	O
he	O
not	O
fell	O
(	O
though	O
himself	O
could	O
run	O
pretty	O
well	O
)	O
he	O
never	O
could	O
have	O
taken	O
him	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
running	O
Footman	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4s	O
.	O
10d	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Billing	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Stretton	I-pers
;	O
but	O
no	O
Body	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Appleton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Sunbury	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Leather	O
Surcingle	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
rubbing	O
Cloths	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Stable	O
of	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Frankland	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Table-Cloth	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Day	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Facts	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
upon	O
each	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gauthorn	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Highton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Pound	O
Weight	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
Pound	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Jecks	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
January	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Katharine	B-pers
Strange	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Picket	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
January	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Strutt	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Faith	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Books	O
in	O
Quires	O
,	O
the	O
History	O
of	O
Japan	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
and	O
the	O
Ancient	O
History	O
of	O
Britain	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
the	O
5th	O
April	O
1729	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
Reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
him	O
,	O
searched	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
(	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
married	O
Man	O
)	O
and	O
there	O
found	O
the	O
Books	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
;	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
defer	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
so	O
long	O
?	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
his	O
having	O
the	O
Books	O
;	O
but	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
were	O
made	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Waste	O
when	O
he	O
collated	O
the	O
Books	O
;	O
that	O
of	O
the	O
History	O
of	O
Japan	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Waste	O
that	O
came	O
from	O
Sir	O
Hans	B-pers
Sloan	I-pers
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
sole	O
Property	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Property	O
being	O
Mr.	O
Wotton	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
History	O
of	O
Britain	O
being	O
Mr.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
Woodman	O
's	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Indictment	O
being	O
laid	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Books	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
sole	O
Property	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Davis	O
,	O
whereas	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Joint	O
Property	O
of	O
other	O
Persons	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
her	O
female	O
Bastard-Child	O
.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Pedlar	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
suspected	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
complain	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Gripes	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
rose	O
again	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
about	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
thinking	O
she	O
look	O
'd	O
lesser	O
about	O
the	O
Waste	O
than	O
usual	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
into	O
the	O
Vault	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Child	O
;	O
that	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
that	O
she	O
discovered	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
not	O
taken	O
out	O
till	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
following	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
she	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
no	O
Marks	O
of	O
Violence	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Beadle	O
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Lilly	I-pers
,	O
that	O
caused	O
the	O
Child	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Lilly	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
came	O
and	O
acquainted	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Pace	I-pers
to	O
take	O
the	O
Child	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Vault	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
she	O
was	O
so	O
near	O
her	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
delivered	O
of	O
the	O
Child	O
at	O
the	O
Vault	O
by	O
surprize	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
Design	O
to	O
destroy	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
made	O
Provision	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
spoke	O
to	O
a	O
Midwife	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
Proof	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
following	O
Evidences	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
being	O
a	O
Midwife	O
,	O
did	O
view	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
but	O
saw	O
no	O
Marks	O
of	O
Violence	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
believe	O
that	O
it	O
came	O
two	O
Months	O
before	O
its	O
time	O
;	O
but	O
whether	O
born	O
Dead	O
or	O
Alive	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Midwife	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
She	O
likewise	O
viewed	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
no	O
Marks	O
of	O
Violence	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
believe	O
it	O
came	O
two	O
Months	O
before	O
its	O
time	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
added	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
several	O
times	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
believe	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
have	O
discovered	O
her	O
being	O
with	O
Child	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
bespeak	O
her	O
for	O
her	O
Midwife	O
;	O
the	O
Child-Bed	O
Linen	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Drawers	O
,	O
as	O
depos	O
'd	O
by	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
.	O
She	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Frances	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
January	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White-Chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
some	O
few	O
Days	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
two	O
Women	O
in	O
Rosemary-Lane	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Garnet	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Shadwel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Herring	I-pers
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
at	O
her	O
going	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
owning	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Abigal	B-pers
Gale	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Shadwel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Feather-Bed	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cave	I-pers
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
January	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Prosecutor	O
appearing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Earle	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
January	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Banks	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Hams	O
of	O
Bacon	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edmund	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4s	O
.	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Banks	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
at	O
Two	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Day-time	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
a	O
Pen-case	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Pool	I-pers
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Seal	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Arbuthnot	I-pers
.	O
He	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
promissory	O
Notes	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
45	O
s.	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
of	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Pool	I-pers
,	O
the	O
said	O
15th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
fourth	O
time	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Pool	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
Room	O
,	O
forc	O
'd	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
came	O
in	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
wanted	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
Money	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Pen-case	O
,	O
with	O
two	O
Notes	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
which	O
Notes	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Wife	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
burnt	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
her	O
Son	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Pool	I-pers
,	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
she	O
inform	O
'd	O
him	O
of	O
what	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
that	O
thereupon	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
that	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
apprehended	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Pool	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
apprehend	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
informed	O
by	O
his	O
Mother	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
taken	O
the	O
Things	O
and	O
Money	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sent	O
to	O
her	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Custody	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
Six-pence	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
his	O
Daughter	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Mother	O
's	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
to	O
convey	O
the	O
Pen-case	O
privately	O
into	O
some	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
to	O
pretend	O
to	O
find	O
it	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
produced	O
two	O
Notes	O
of	O
Pool	O
's	O
Hand	O
,	O
with	O
order	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
Pen-case	O
when	O
he	O
pleased	O
in	O
Satisfaction	O
or	O
Pledge	O
of	O
Money	O
he	O
lent	O
him	O
.	O
Pool	O
deny	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
said	O
Notes	O
to	O
Banks	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
forged	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
but	O
in	O
Contradiction	O
to	O
this	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
Mary	B-pers
Banks	I-pers
,	O
his	O
Daughter	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
did	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
write	O
all	O
or	O
part	O
of	O
those	O
Bills	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
also	O
desired	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
her	O
Father	O
,	O
to	O
sign	O
those	O
Bills	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
sign	O
them	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Name	O
was	O
written	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
himself	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
second	O
Indictment	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
agreed	O
to	O
take	O
3	O
s.	O
for	O
the	O
Seal	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
the	O
Instigation	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Pool	I-pers
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
third	O
and	O
fourth	O
Indictment	O
of	O
robbing	O
Pool	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Proof	O
but	O
that	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Pool	I-pers
himself	O
,	O
nor	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
any	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
but	O
seem	O
'd	O
rather	O
improbable	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
should	O
rob	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
go	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
borrow	O
Money	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
him	O
Notes	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
;	O
and	O
also	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
committed	O
by	O
the	O
Justice	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
,	O
no	O
mention	O
was	O
then	O
made	O
of	O
this	O
Robbery	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
nor	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
Guineas	O
till	O
afterwards	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
find	O
the	O
Bill	O
of	O
Indictment	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
After	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Loveday	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
Hanover-Square	I-place
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Gary	I-pers
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
was	O
Twelve-months	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
ten	O
Hats	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
latter	O
for	O
receiving	O
them	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
but	O
that	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rowley	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
(	O
as	O
he	O
said	O
)	O
an	O
Accomplice	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Gosteloe	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
the	I-place
Martyr	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Moses	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Rosamond	B-pers
Dorman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White-Chapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Mary	B-pers
Mac	I-pers
Daniel	I-pers
,	O
in	O
an	O
open	O
Place	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
near	O
Rag-Fair	O
,	O
in	O
an	O
Alley	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
met	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
her	O
Bitch	O
,	O
threatened	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
her	O
(	O
for	O
her	O
being	O
an	O
Evidence	O
that	O
her	O
Landlady	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Sawyer	O
,	O
Miscarried	O
,	O
she	O
having	O
been	O
arrested	O
on	O
that	O
account	O
)	O
fell	O
upon	O
her	O
violently	O
,	O
beat	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
bruis	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
her	O
Patten	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
felt	O
her	O
Hand	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
lost	O
the	O
Apron	O
and	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
beating	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
said	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
beating	O
her	O
,	O
Rose	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
Rob	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
first	O
assaulted	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
proceeded	O
from	O
Malice	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
William	B-pers
Fen	I-pers
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
Warrant	O
for	O
apprehending	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
been	O
employ	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Tip-Staff	O
to	O
set	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
meeting	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
fell	O
first	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
after	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brocket	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
the	I-place
Martyr	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
an	O
hundred	O
Weight	O
of	O
old	O
Iron	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ralph	B-pers
Greathead	I-pers
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
January	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Enfield	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
an	O
Iron	O
Lock	O
and	O
Bolt	O
of	O
a	O
Sluce	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Governour	B-pers
and	O
Company	B-pers
of	I-pers
the	I-pers
New	I-pers
River	I-pers
Water	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
seeing	O
two	O
Men	O
have	O
them	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Things	O
from	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
deliver	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Walk's-Man	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Surveyor	O
of	O
the	O
Works	O
met	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
having	O
taken	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
Sluce	O
.	O
He	O
like	O
wise	O
call	O
'd	O
some	O
Persons	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Winnard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Precinct	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Catharines	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cock	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Day	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
January	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
Bulk	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Fowl	O
was	O
stolen	O
.	O
Bennet	O
Hern	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
breaking	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Bulk	O
,	O
and	O
come	O
out	O
with	O
the	O
Cock	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
pursu	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
thrown	O
the	O
Cock	O
away	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Winn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Wigg	I-pers
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Journeyman	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
borrow	O
some	O
Money	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
an	O
idle	O
drunken	O
Fellow	O
,	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
lend	O
him	O
any	O
;	O
that	O
thereupon	O
he	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
immediately	O
followed	O
,	O
the	O
Shoes	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
took	O
down	O
the	O
Shoes	O
to	O
look	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
an	O
usual	O
thing	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
reel	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
came	O
and	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
stealing	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
O	I-pers
Neal	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Boots	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Millichamp	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
Jan	O
.	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
George	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
several	O
Fowls	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Reed	I-pers
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hewes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
28	O
Pound	O
of	O
Iron	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Kite	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Hackney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
18	O
Harrow	O
Tines	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
other	O
Iron	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
January	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Bagley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
from	O
Hannah	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
and	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Popplewel	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
was	O
twelve	O
Months	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Nodder	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
from	O
Anthony	B-pers
Rowse	I-pers
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4s	O
.	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Gale	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Rich	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bone	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joanna	B-pers
Worthington	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Body	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Street	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
marrying	O
Henry	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
her	O
first	O
Husband	O
Will	B-pers
Hind	I-pers
being	O
Alive	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Body	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Body	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ramsey	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Smith	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Whitehurst	I-pers
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Lockwood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Peter	I-place
's	I-place
Poor	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
8lb	O
.	O
of	O
Leaden	O
Pipe	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Myers	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Body	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bartlet	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
Hanover-Square	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
forging	O
and	O
uttering	O
a	O
promissory	O
Note	O
for	O
10	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
payable	O
to	O
himself	O
or	O
Order	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Mistake	O
in	O
the	O
drawing	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
quash	O
'd	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
be	O
rectified	O
the	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
Barbara	B-pers
Gun	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Mackey	I-pers
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
4s	O
.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Mackey	I-pers
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
furnish	O
'd	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
accordingly	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Black-Fryars	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
-	O
Loe	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Taylor	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Journeyman	O
;	O
that	O
having	O
taken	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Cloaths	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Thompson	O
's	O
to	O
alter	O
,	O
he	O
taking	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Breeches	O
by	O
the	O
Knees	O
,	O
a	O
Purse	O
sell	O
out	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
two	O
Queen	O
Ann	O
's	O
Guineas	O
,	O
three	O
other	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
half	O
Guineas	O
;	O
that	O
thereupon	O
he	O
designing	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
acquaint	O
Mr.	O
Thompson	O
,	O
had	O
put	O
the	O
Money	O
again	O
into	O
the	O
Purse	O
,	O
put	O
the	O
Purse	O
into	O
the	O
Fob	O
,	O
and	O
carrying	O
the	O
Clothes	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
Garret	O
,	O
was	O
giving	O
Orders	O
to	O
his	O
Journeyman	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
about	O
the	O
altering	O
the	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
laid	O
the	O
Breeches	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Purse	O
of	O
Guineas	O
folded	O
up	O
,	O
was	O
suddenly	O
call	O
'd	O
down	O
to	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
who	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Breeches	O
remov	O
'd	O
from	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
laid	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
lying	O
nearer	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
unfolded	O
;	O
and	O
examining	O
the	O
Purse	O
,	O
found	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
unty	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Queen	O
Ann	O
's	O
Guineas	O
gone	O
;	O
that	O
thereupon	O
he	O
taxed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Thompson	O
's	O
Christian	O
Name	O
was	O
Samuel	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
Richard	O
,	O
the	O
Indictment	O
was	O
quash	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
acquitted	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dun	I-pers
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
January	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
his	O
House	O
on	O
Charity	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
handy	O
,	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
to	O
work	O
at	O
mending	O
of	O
Linen	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
that	O
she	O
having	O
been	O
out	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
home	O
one	O
Night	O
till	O
it	O
was	O
late	O
,	O
was	O
let	O
in	O
by	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
sate	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
;	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
he	O
found	O
his	O
Fore-Windows	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
apprehended	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
as	O
Head-Dresses	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Linen	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
lock	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
,	O
a	O
Man	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
she	O
was	O
frightened	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Dark-Lanthorn	O
,	O
and	O
threatened	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
made	O
any	O
noise	O
he	O
would	O
cut	O
her	O
Throat	O
;	O
that	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
some	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Cupboard	O
,	O
and	O
bundled	O
up	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
he	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Fore-Windows	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
threatening	O
to	O
murder	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
do	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Man	O
and	O
she	O
sat	O
upon	O
a	O
Bench	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Things	O
that	O
were	O
found	O
,	O
telling	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
ungenerous	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
pretence	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Welsh	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
together	O
with	O
James	B-pers
Dickson	I-pers
,	O
did	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
feloniously	O
steal	O
a	O
Tankard	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Alice	B-pers
Kellum	I-pers
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Kellum	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
three	O
Men	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
having	O
drank	O
several	O
Tankards	O
of	O
drink	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Space	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
going	O
down	O
to	O
draw	O
some	O
drink	O
,	O
they	O
all	O
run	O
away	O
without	O
paying	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
immediately	O
pursued	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
running	O
divers	O
ways	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
pursue	O
but	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
Christopher	B-pers
Cornick	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
convicted	O
for	O
it	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
afterwards	O
being	O
informed	O
by	O
Thomas	O
Hall	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
thither	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
knew	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
in	O
Company	O
that	O
stole	O
the	O
Tankard	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4s	O
.	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Compton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
together	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Beck	I-pers
,	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Money-Box	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Sadler	I-pers
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
January	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Lewis	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
's	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
Simon	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Magnus	I-place
the	I-place
Martyr	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cheese	O
,	O
value	O
3s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Cock	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
January	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Cheese	O
was	O
stolen	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
pursued	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Cheese	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Neal	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
printed	O
Linen	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Moses	B-pers
Bradley	I-pers
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Bartholomew	I-place
the	I-place
Great	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joshua	B-pers
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lock	I-pers
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
January	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
another	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Tobacco	O
in	O
her	O
Apron	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Flemming	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Linen	O
Cloth	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Hammond	I-pers
,	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
Timothy	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
a	O
Woman	O
telling	O
him	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
going	O
along	O
Barbican	O
,	O
that	O
had	O
something	O
betwixt	O
her	O
Legs	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
scarce	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
gone	O
up	O
an	O
Alley	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
farther	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Alley	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
between	O
her	O
Legs	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
a	O
strange	O
Woman	O
gave	O
her	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Drams	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Cloth	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
her	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
her	O
Coats	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4s	O
.	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
John	B-pers
Haynes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Duke's-Place	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Grace	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Grace	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
18	O
Stock	O
Locks	O
,	O
value	O
20s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Bray	I-pers
,	O
and	O
62	O
Groce	O
of	O
Metal	O
Buttons	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Faggot	I-pers
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Body	O
appearing	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Lancaster	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Allhallows	B-place
Lombard-street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Riding-Coat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
January	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
Coneys	O
in	O
two	O
Hampers	O
on	O
a	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
leading	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
the	O
Coat	O
lay	O
between	O
the	O
Hampers	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
snatch	O
'd	O
off	O
the	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
running	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
stopped	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
clearly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Alexander	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Thomas	B-pers
Godbut	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Shoulder	O
of	O
Mutton	O
,	O
a	O
Remnant	O
of	O
Calimanco	O
,	O
some	O
Linen	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Arthur	B-pers
Garret	I-pers
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Godbut	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Lad	O
of	O
14	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
the	O
Things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
of	O
Mutton	O
on	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Goods	O
in	O
a	O
Bundle	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Little	O
Ambry	O
(	O
or	O
Almonry	O
)	O
a	O
Man	O
came	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
pushed	O
him	O
against	O
the	O
Steps	O
,	O
snatched	O
the	O
Things	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
some	O
Persons	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
he	O
ran	O
he	O
threw	O
away	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
of	O
Mutton	O
in	O
one	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Bundle	O
in	O
another	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
to	O
be	O
let	O
go	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
the	O
Boy	O
had	O
all	O
the	O
Things	O
again	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
hearing	O
an	O
out-cry	O
of	O
Murther	O
and	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
he	O
look	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
running	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ran	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
collar	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Bundle	O
lying	O
between	O
the	O
Man	O
and	O
the	O
Boy	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
desired	O
to	O
be	O
let	O
go	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
the	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
given	O
them	O
all	O
again	O
to	O
the	O
Boy	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Sims	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
about	O
6	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
on	O
Christmas-Day	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
Boy	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
Thieves	O
and	O
Murther	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
Harris	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
Constable	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
why	O
do	O
you	O
hold	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
Boy	O
has	O
got	O
all	O
his	O
Things	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Mutton	O
lying	O
in	O
one	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Bundle	O
in	O
another	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Clay	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
hearing	O
an	O
out	O
cry	O
of	O
Murther	O
,	O
and	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
the	O
Boy	O
and	O
Soldier	O
were	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
taxed	O
him	O
with	O
having	O
taken	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
assisted	O
John	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
in	O
carrying	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
But	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Anne	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Riding-Hood	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
Christmas-Day	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
Old	B-place
Palace-Yard	I-place
,	O
Westminster	B-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
clapt	O
his	O
Hand	O
cross	O
her	O
Eyes	O
,	O
she	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
ho	O
caught	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Throat	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
almost	O
strangled	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
violently	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
her	O
Riding-Hood	O
,	O
and	O
tore	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Arm	O
Holes	O
in	O
pulling	O
it	O
off	O
;	O
that	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
Church-Yard	O
,	O
and	O
meeting	O
two	O
Men	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
complaining	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
Robbed	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
met	O
a	O
Man	O
running	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
well	O
off	O
it	O
was	O
no	O
worse	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
she	O
went	O
Home	O
,	O
she	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
but	O
hearing	O
a	O
Man	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
a	O
Robbery	O
near	O
that	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Ridinghood	O
at	O
the	O
Constable	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
thither	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
her	O
Ridinghood	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Ridinghood	O
was	O
given	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
by	O
one	O
Clay	O
,	O
that	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
would	O
not	O
own	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
coming	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
shew	O
'd	O
her	O
the	O
Hood	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
Hood	O
was	O
hers	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Clay	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
he	O
perceiving	O
something	O
bulky	O
within	O
the	O
Breast	O
of	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
not	O
knowing	O
but	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
Arms	O
,	O
examined	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Ridinghood	O
or	O
Cloak	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
Wife	O
's	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
dropp	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
hearing	O
the	O
out-cry	O
ran	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Ridinghood	O
hang	O
between	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Legs	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
dropp	O
'd	O
down	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
the	O
Cloak	O
in	O
his	O
Bosom	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
dropp	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
fell	O
between	O
his	O
Legs	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Boy	O
that	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
just	O
behind	O
the	O
Boy	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Sims	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
following	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Cloak	O
drop	O
down	O
between	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Legs	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
stoop	O
'd	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Trumbold	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
an	O
ill	O
disposed	O
Person	O
,	O
and	O
greedy	O
of	O
wicked	O
Lucre	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
June	O
1723	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
November	O
1730	O
,	O
the	O
Laws	O
and	O
Statutes	O
of	O
this	O
Realm	O
not	O
esteeming	O
,	O
did	O
knowingly	O
,	O
wickedly	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
send	O
a	O
Letter	O
sign	O
'd	O
Armstrong	O
,	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Gaughton	I-pers
,	O
demanding	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
five	O
Guineas	O
,	O
otherwise	O
threatening	O
to	O
burn	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
to	O
the	O
evil	O
Example	O
of	O
others	O
,	O
and	O
contrary	O
to	O
the	O
Peace	O
of	O
our	O
Sovereign	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
and	O
contrary	O
to	O
the	O
Statute	O
in	O
that	O
Case	O
made	O
and	O
provided	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
he	O
keeping	O
a	O
Coffee-House	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
coming	O
down	O
about	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
that	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
returning	O
about	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
reading	O
a	O
Letter	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
Letter	O
for	O
you	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
it	O
does	O
belong	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
threatening	O
Letters	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
taking	O
the	O
Letter	O
,	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
going	O
for	O
Chips	O
to	O
light	O
a	O
Fire	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
advising	O
with	O
some	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
of	O
Opinion	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
by	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
Family	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
no	O
notice	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
set	O
him	O
to	O
write	O
out	O
a	O
Bill	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
carrying	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
Friends	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
of	O
Opinion	O
,	O
upon	O
comparing	O
the	O
Hands	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
or	O
at	O
least	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Similitude	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
went	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
caus	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
apprehended	O
.	O
The	O
Substance	O
of	O
the	O
Letter	O
was	O
as	O
follows	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Gaughton	O
,	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
this	O
Present	O
shall	O
enter	O
your	O
House	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
to	O
place	O
five	O
Guineas	O
in	O
a	O
Gutter	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
your	O
House	O
,	O
by	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
this	O
Night	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
have	O
your	O
House	O
burnt	O
by	O
this	O
Day	O
Seven-night	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
you	O
comply	O
,	O
no	O
harm	O
shall	O
be	O
done	O
;	O
Gaughton	O
comply	O
,	O
or	O
it	O
is	O
at	O
your	O
Peril	O
,	O
we	O
have	O
sworn	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Armstrong	O
.	O
He	O
added	O
,	O
That	O
there	O
were	O
afterwards	O
two	O
other	O
threatening	O
Letters	O
with	O
bits	O
of	O
Cork	O
in	O
them	O
,	O
conveyed	O
into	O
his	O
Yard	O
,	O
which	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
Hand	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
writing	O
or	O
placing	O
the	O
Letter	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
this	O
reason	O
for	O
not	O
shewing	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
immediately	O
after	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
;	O
That	O
he	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
for	O
Chips	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Letter	O
with	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Bread	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
about	O
an	O
Inch	O
long	O
,	O
and	O
throwing	O
away	O
the	O
Bread	O
,	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
without	O
looking	O
into	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
while	O
his	O
Master	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
,	O
little	O
Company	O
being	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
at	O
leisure	O
,	O
was	O
reading	O
the	O
News	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
some	O
threatening	O
Letters	O
,	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
the	O
Letter	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
reading	O
it	O
when	O
his	O
Master	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
farther	O
Proof	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
calling	O
several	O
Persons	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Character	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Corklin	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Cockland	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
as	O
before	O
,	O
for	O
sending	O
a	O
threatening	O
Letter	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Lamb	I-pers
,	O
demanding	O
of	O
her	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
two	O
Guineas	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
put	O
in	O
the	O
Spout	O
of	O
a	O
certain	O
Pump	O
,	O
threatening	O
otherwise	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
should	O
be	O
burnt	O
in	O
her	O
Bed	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
her	O
Lodger	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
coming	O
down	O
Stairs	O
stoop	O
'd	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
a	O
Letter	O
,	O
and	O
without	O
reading	O
the	O
Superscription	O
,	O
thrust	O
it	O
into	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
telling	O
her	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
writing	O
or	O
conveying	O
the	O
Letter	O
to	O
that	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Persons	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
Animosity	O
between	O
her	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
going	O
away	O
from	O
his	O
Lodging	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
lodg	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
she	O
likewise	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Persons	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
farther	O
Proof	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Goodday	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
14s	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
near	O
the	O
Two	B-place
Brewers	I-place
at	O
Clerkenwell-Green	B-place
,	O
and	O
took	O
14	O
s.	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
produc	O
'd	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
when	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
pretended	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
French-Horn	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
that	O
Night	O
;	O
also	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Moreland	O
,	O
who	O
also	O
pretended	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
a	O
Band	O
Box	O
,	O
with	O
Goods	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
3	O
l.	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Islington	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
both	O
very	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
at	O
Islington	O
,	O
to	O
inquire	O
if	O
the	O
Band-Box	O
had	O
been	O
left	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
also	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Persons	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
especially	O
his	O
Grace	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Leeds	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Eves	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Etty	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Stock	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Wastecoat	O
,	O
a	O
Woollen	O
Cap	O
,	O
18	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
met	O
by	O
four	O
Men	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Watch-House	O
,	O
at	O
Mile-End	B-place
,	O
about	O
7	O
o'Clock	O
the	O
Day	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
met	O
him	O
all	O
a	O
Breast	O
,	O
the	O
tallest	O
went	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
shortest	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
stand	O
and	O
deliver	O
;	O
that	O
another	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
strip	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
another	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
shoot	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
stript	O
off	O
his	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
turn	O
'd	O
him	O
round	O
to	O
the	O
light	O
(	O
the	O
Moon	O
shining	O
)	O
to	O
view	O
his	O
Shirt	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
torn	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
took	O
off	O
his	O
Garter	O
and	O
ty	O
'd	O
his	O
Hands	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
unty	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
on	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
then	O
ty	O
'd	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
about	O
his	O
Business	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
to	O
be	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
Men	O
by	O
their	O
Stature	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
their	O
Persons	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wills	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
himself	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
Robbing	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
executed	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
;	O
that	O
himself	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
pass	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
that	O
Smith	O
clap	O
'd	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
his	O
Breast	O
,	O
that	O
Joseph	B-pers
Eves	I-pers
clap	O
'd	O
another	O
Pistol	O
to	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
Side	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Etty	I-pers
took	O
of	O
his	O
Garter	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
him	O
to	O
see	O
his	O
Shirt	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
himself	O
took	O
the	O
Coat	O
from	O
Etty	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
Etty	O
ty	O
'd	O
his	O
Hands	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
both	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Wills	O
the	O
Evidence	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
to	O
contradict	O
them	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
Margaret	B-pers
Lyon	I-pers
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Wills	O
and	O
Etty	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Ship	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
Months	O
or	O
nine	O
Weeks	O
since	O
,	O
at	O
about	O
9	O
or	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Wills	O
went	O
out	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
Etty	O
stay	O
'd	O
with	O
two	O
Women	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
not	O
liking	O
their	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
Wills	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
not	O
returning	O
,	O
Etty	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
left	O
Word	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
she	O
should	O
tell	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
the	O
Key	O
he	O
knew	O
where	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Wills	O
and	O
Etty	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
three	O
times	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wills	I-pers
added	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
concern	O
'd	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
a	O
Robbing	O
,	O
he	O
resolv	O
'd	O
to	O
quit	O
himself	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
informed	O
Mary	B-pers
Tutton	I-pers
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
wanted	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
a	O
Robbing	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
Mary	B-pers
Tutton	I-pers
,	O
who	O
confirm	O
'd	O
it	O
:	O
He	O
added	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
all	O
met	O
him	O
in	O
Fetter-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
divulg	O
'd	O
their	O
Secrets	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
would	O
shoot	O
him	O
through	O
the	O
Head	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
upon	O
this	O
he	O
did	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
Robbed	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
Etty	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
leaving	O
Etty	O
there	O
,	O
as	O
Margaret	B-pers
Lyon	I-pers
had	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
himself	O
made	O
an	O
Evidence	O
;	O
and	O
returning	O
with	O
the	O
Constable	O
to	O
the	O
Ship	O
,	O
Etty	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
having	O
left	O
Word	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Lyon	O
as	O
before	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
Constable	O
to	O
where	O
Etty	O
lodg	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
Bed	O
with	O
Mary	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
,	O
and	O
directed	O
the	O
Constable	O
to	O
the	O
Two	O
Brewers	O
in	O
Parke's-Lane	O
,	O
where	O
Joseph	B-pers
Eves	I-pers
was	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
both	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Eves	I-pers
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
surrendered	O
himself	O
to	O
the	O
Officer	O
without	O
making	O
any	O
Resistance	O
.	O
They	O
call	O
'd	O
some	O
Evidences	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Wills	O
had	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
hang	O
Father	O
,	O
Mother	O
,	O
Brother	O
and	O
Sister	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
for	O
the	O
sake	O
of	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
both	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Persons	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
.	O
Etty	O
's	O
Evidences	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Bargeman	O
,	O
who	O
having	O
come	O
from	O
Reading	O
with	O
the	O
Barge	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
and	O
sprained	O
his	O
Ankle	O
thereby	O
,	O
prevented	O
his	O
going	O
down	O
with	O
the	O
Barge	O
again	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
many	O
Years	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
always	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
intrusted	O
with	O
receiving	O
and	O
paying	O
great	O
Sums	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
always	O
paid	O
what	O
he	O
receiv	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
up	O
his	O
Accounts	O
very	O
justly	O
.	O
This	O
Character	O
being	O
given	O
him	O
by	O
many	O
Persons	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
employ	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
that	O
affected	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wills	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
after	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
acquitted	O
both	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Tracey	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Tracey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Coster	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
5	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Human	O
Hair	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Malloon	I-pers
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
having	O
come	O
from	O
Ireland	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
a	O
Stranger	O
,	O
inquiring	O
for	O
a	O
Lodging	O
,	O
was	O
directed	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Tracey	O
's	O
,	O
that	O
desiring	O
to	O
have	O
his	O
Bag	O
of	O
Hair	O
laid	O
up	O
safe	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
Margaret	B-pers
Lacey	I-pers
's	O
Trunk	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
his	O
Hair	O
,	O
he	O
indeed	O
found	O
the	O
Trunk	O
lock	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
himself	O
had	O
kept	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
but	O
opening	O
it	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
back	O
had	O
been	O
opened	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
his	O
Hair	O
taken	O
out	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
the	O
Indictment	O
had	O
by	O
Mistake	O
been	O
drawn	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Mallard	O
,	O
instead	O
of	O
Malloon	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
quash	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
order	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
drawn	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
to	O
remain	O
in	O
Custody	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
find	O
sufficient	O
Bail	O
for	O
their	O
Appearance	O
the	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
Lee	B-pers
Elkington	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pancras	I-place
,	I-place
Soaper-Lane	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Mug	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
January	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Tankard	O
and	O
Mug	O
were	O
lost	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
how	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
miss	O
'd	O
at	O
two	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
the	O
one	O
being	O
seen	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
found	O
.	O
-	O
Elkington	O
,	O
Sister	O
to	O
Lee	O
Elkington	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Husband	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
on	O
Monday	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
knew	O
not	O
how	O
,	O
nor	O
which	O
way	O
it	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
7	O
Months	O
.	O
Moses	B-pers
Hastings	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
drank	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Tankard	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
set	O
in	O
the	O
Cup-board	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchin	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
up	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Mug	O
on	O
Monday	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
either	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
or	O
her	O
Husband	O
had	O
been	O
seen	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
at	O
any	O
thing	O
near	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Plate	O
was	O
missing	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Curtis	O
,	O
the	O
Pawn-Broker	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
him	O
the	O
Cup	O
and	O
Tankard	O
,	O
and	O
pawned	O
it	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Steward	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
Name	O
she	O
had	O
divers	O
times	O
pawned	O
Goods	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
often	O
redeem	O
'd	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
having	O
had	O
Dealings	O
with	O
her	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
found	O
any	O
dishonesty	O
by	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
lent	O
her	O
7	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
on	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
afterwards	O
having	O
an	O
Advertisement	O
brought	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
Notice	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Forth	O
,	O
and	O
acquainted	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
went	O
in	O
quest	O
of	O
Lee	O
Elkington	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Husband	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Lee	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
pawned	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
her	O
by	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
who	O
sent	O
her	O
to	O
pawn	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
not	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
told	O
her	O
it	O
was	O
lent	O
him	O
by	O
a	O
Friend	O
to	O
pawn	O
to	O
raise	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
gave	O
he	O
r	O
Husband	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
him	O
since	O
;	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
was	O
a	O
Journeyman	O
Hatter	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
bad	O
Husband	O
.	O
She	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
credible	O
Evidences	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
her	O
many	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
among	O
the	O
rest	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
himself	O
,	O
with	O
whom	O
she	O
had	O
sometimes	O
liv	O
'd	O
,	O
who	O
all	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
Characters	O
,	O
for	O
Honesty	O
and	O
Industry	O
;	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
something	O
to	O
have	O
her	O
Transported	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
heard	O
Hannah	B-pers
Elkington	I-pers
say	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
hang	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
if	O
they	O
could	O
;	O
the	O
Reason	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
up	O
a	O
Whore	O
,	O
with	O
whom	O
her	O
Husband	O
kept	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
her	O
sent	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
.	O
After	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Alhallows	B-place
Lombard	I-place
Street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
six	O
Pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
12	O
Pair	O
of	O
Thread	O
Stockings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Fog	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
a	O
Barber	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
out	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
at	O
the	O
Goat	O
and	O
Gate	O
in	O
Gracechurch-Street	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
lay	O
six	O
Pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Hose	O
,	O
and	O
twelve	O
Pair	O
of	O
Thread	O
Hose	O
at	O
the	O
Cellar	O
Window	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
to	O
pay	O
off	O
a	O
Note	O
of	O
Hand	O
for	O
30	O
s.	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
induced	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
,	O
for	O
his	O
Use	O
,	O
he	O
pretending	O
he	O
wanted	O
Money	O
to	O
pay	O
his	O
Rent	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
where	O
his	O
Master	O
and	O
Mistress	O
would	O
be	O
that	O
Evening	O
?	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
be	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
.	O
That	O
Shop	O
being	O
shut	O
,	O
he	O
laid	O
the	O
Stockings	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar-Window	O
,	O
as	O
directed	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
6	O
o'Clock	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
reaching	O
his	O
Hand	O
down	O
,	O
took	O
up	O
one	O
Bundle	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Tomlinson	O
's	O
Folks	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
other	O
Bundle	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
how	O
long	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
carried	O
on	O
this	O
Practice	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
since	O
July	O
last	O
was	O
twelve	O
Months	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
his	O
Master	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
Goods	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
of	O
him	O
from	O
time	O
to	O
time	O
,	O
value	O
30l	O
.	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
since	O
remembered	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
if	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
unwilling	O
to	O
furnish	O
him	O
with	O
what	O
he	O
spoke	O
for	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
threaten	O
him	O
to	O
inform	O
his	O
Master	O
of	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
before	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
being	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Tomlinson	O
,	O
who	O
liv	O
'd	O
over-against	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
did	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
two	O
Bundles	O
of	O
Stockings	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Cellar-Window	O
,	O
and	O
spoke	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
it	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Knowledge	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Budge	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
before	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Bell	O
,	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
desire	O
my	O
Life	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
have	O
your	O
Stockings	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
dozen	O
of	O
Hose	O
pawn	O
'd	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
's	O
in	O
Goodman's-Fields	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Grant	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Ticket-Porter	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
sent	O
him	O
several	O
times	O
with	O
Letters	O
to	O
Edward	B-pers
Fog	I-pers
,	O
and	O
also	O
had	O
sent	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
full	O
of	O
Stockings	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
home	O
to	O
his	O
Wife	O
.	O
Several	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Stockings	O
were	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
sworn	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
pawn	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
or	O
his	O
Wife	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
commanded	O
the	O
Pawn-Broker	O
,	O
to	O
let	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
see	O
his	O
Books	O
,	O
and	O
return	O
him	O
all	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Pippin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
divers	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Saffery	I-pers
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
Goods	O
were	O
stolen	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Possession	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Sparks	I-pers
;	O
they	O
were	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
swore	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
.	O
Anne	O
Sparks	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
her	O
by	O
both	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Hall	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
admitted	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
ought	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
try	O
'd	O
for	O
this	O
Fact	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
committed	O
before	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
put	O
this	O
Fact	O
into	O
his	O
Information	O
,	O
his	O
Plea	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Wig	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Boyle	I-pers
,	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
having	O
stripp	O
'd	O
himself	O
to	O
Fight	O
,	O
afterwards	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
Brandy-Shop	O
,	O
to	O
wash	O
and	O
dress	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
dressing	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
snatch	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
Clothes	O
,	O
handed	O
them	O
out	O
to	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
one	O
Patrick	B-pers
Gill	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Black	B-pers
Patty	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
indicted	O
for	O
another	O
Felony	O
,	O
own	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
himself	O
committed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
Thomas	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Coachman	O
,	O
was	O
standing	O
near	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Patrick	B-pers
Gill	I-pers
run	O
along	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
call	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
Fare	O
,	O
set	O
them	O
down	O
at	O
the	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
Gill	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
as	O
Gill	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
seeing	O
him	O
there	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
extraordinary	O
Evidence	O
,	O
not	O
seeming	O
probable	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Bowden	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stoke	B-place
Newington	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
14	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hills	I-pers
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
Prisoner	O
were	O
Chamber-Fellows	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Box	O
in	O
the	O
Chamber	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
to	O
his	O
Work	O
;	O
that	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
found	O
under	O
a	O
Bench	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sat	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
carried	O
into	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Howel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Can	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
January	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Drury-Lane	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
drink	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
and	O
drank	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Ale	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Gin	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
led	O
him	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
lay	O
down	O
with	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Candle	O
was	O
put	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
laid	O
her	O
Hand	O
upon	O
his	O
Thigh	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
free	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
gave	O
her	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
down	O
Stairs	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
asking	O
her	O
,	O
what	O
she	O
went	O
for	O
,	O
she	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
make	O
Water	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
ran	O
down	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
got	O
off	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
stolen	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
was	O
afterwards	O
produced	O
by	O
one	O
Hawkins	O
,	O
a	O
Serjeant	O
in	O
the	O
Guards	O
,	O
who	O
received	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Husband	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
she	O
had	O
carried	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Body	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
but	O
himself	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
Yes	O
;	O
his	O
Friend	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
sitting	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
never	O
come	O
nigh	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Purpose	O
as	O
the	O
foregoing	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Prosecutor	O
were	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
together	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Candle	O
being	O
out	O
,	O
what	O
they	O
did	O
there	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
sufficiently	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Lamb	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Niggy	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Carroty	B-pers
Peg	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Noel	B-pers
Lubert	I-pers
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Dunbar	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
a	O
Walloon	O
,	O
told	O
his	O
Story	O
in	O
scarce	O
intelligible	O
English	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Purpose	O
following	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
going	O
along	O
Windsor-Court	B-place
,	O
near	O
,	O
or	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	B-place
,	O
stopp	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
Carroty	O
Peg	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
drink	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
but	O
Six-Pence	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
rather	O
spend	O
it	O
,	O
than	O
have	O
his	O
Coat	O
tore	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
held	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Windsor-Court	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
willing	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
,	O
she	O
forc	O
'd	O
him	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Candle	O
was	O
brought	O
by	O
a	O
little	O
dirty	O
Creature	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
holding	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Coat	O
,	O
led	O
him	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
he	O
following	O
her	O
,	O
not	O
to	O
have	O
his	O
Coat	O
torn	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
opened	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
threw	O
him	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
fell	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
laid	O
her	O
Left-Hand	O
upon	O
his	O
Breast	O
,	O
that	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
need	O
not	O
be	O
so	O
merry	O
for	O
a	O
six-penny	O
Piece	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
tore	O
his	O
Fob	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
upon	O
his	O
Arms	O
,	O
and	O
Carroty	O
Peg	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
Carroty	O
Peg	O
got	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
putting	O
their	O
Hands	O
on	O
his	O
Mouth	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
hold	O
it	O
long	O
,	O
and	O
Carroty	O
Peg	O
gave	O
it	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
ran	O
down	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
Carroty	O
Peg	O
ran	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ran	O
down	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
follow	O
'd	O
them	O
where	O
they	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
shut	O
the	O
Door	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Gentlewoman	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
jump	O
'd	O
out	O
at	O
a	O
Window	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Chairman	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
caught	O
her	O
in	O
his	O
Arms	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
she	O
got	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
drank	O
with	O
her	O
since	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
charg	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
for	O
fear	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
had	O
heard	O
a	O
Man	O
had	O
had	O
his	O
Eyes	O
pick	O
'd	O
out	O
in	O
that	O
House	O
;	O
after	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
Hanover-Square	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
sending	O
threatening	O
Letters	O
,	O
one	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Clements	I-pers
,	O
demanding	O
15	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
others	O
to	O
Burrel	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
demanding	O
in	O
one	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
a	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
10	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
second	O
20	O
Guineas	O
;	O
John	O
Clements	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
Proof	O
of	O
that	O
Letter	O
being	O
made	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Burrel	O
Smith	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
Boy	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Letter	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Bakehouse	O
(	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Baker	O
)	O
but	O
he	O
not	O
bringing	O
his	O
Boy	O
,	O
this	O
likewise	O
caus	O
'd	O
a	O
Deficiency	O
in	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Letters	O
which	O
were	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
(	O
and	O
said	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
be	O
full	O
of	O
dreadful	O
Threatenings	O
,	O
profane	O
and	O
blasphemous	O
Expressions	O
,	O
and	O
direful	O
Imprecations	O
,	O
and	O
even	O
treasonable	O
ones	O
)	O
were	O
not	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
because	O
not	O
legally	O
proved	O
.	O
Burrel	O
Smith	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Letters	O
directing	O
Money	O
to	O
be	O
left	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
certain	O
Post	O
,	O
in	O
Turn-Stile-Alley	O
,	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
Drury-Lane	O
into	O
Catharine-Street	O
;	O
that	O
Money	O
was	O
deposited	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
set	O
Persons	O
to	O
watch	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
any	O
Body	O
came	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Adam	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
a	O
Bag	O
of	O
Cinders	O
was	O
first	O
lest	O
at	O
the	O
Post	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
some	O
Money	O
in	O
a	O
Bag	O
was	O
ty	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Post	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
Woman	O
and	O
a	O
Boy	O
about	O
twelve	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
pass	O
'd	O
by	O
,	O
he	O
leading	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
pass	O
'd	O
by	O
,	O
he	O
clapp	O
'd	O
his	O
Foot	O
upon	O
the	O
Bag	O
,	O
and	O
drew	O
it	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
from	O
the	O
Post	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Person	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
follow	O
them	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
where	O
they	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
them	O
turn	O
in	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
afterwards	O
appear	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
liv	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
lost	O
Sight	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
about	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
within	O
a	O
Yard	O
or	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
Post	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
about	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
any	O
Body	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
crept	O
to	O
the	O
Post	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
stood	O
looking	O
about	O
him	O
(	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
supposes	O
)	O
espying	O
him	O
,	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
the	O
same	O
way	O
he	O
went	O
;	O
that	O
thereupon	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
what	O
Business	O
he	O
