TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
13th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
14th	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
October	O
1731	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Fifth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Eighth	O
and	O
Last	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
HUMPHREY	O
PARSONS	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1731	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
VIII	O
.	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
YEAR	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
T.	O
PAYNE	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
,	O
in	O
Pater-noster-Row	O
.	O
1731	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
Six	O
Pence	O
.	O
)	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
,	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
AND	O
ON	O
The	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
;	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
13th	O
,	O
14th	O
,	O
and	O
15th	O
of	O
October	O
1731	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Fifth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
HUMPHREY	B-pers
PARSONS	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
Raymond	O
;	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Denton	O
;	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Recorder	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
Urlin	O
,	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hoggier	I-pers
,	O
Stephen	B-pers
Prue	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Yeoman	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Gery	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Clayton	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Brett	I-pers
,	O
Alexander	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sharp	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Pomeroy	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Alyffe	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
David	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Gass	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Henshaw	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Daniel	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Timbrel	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Banks	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary-Hill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Copper	O
Drinking-pot	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Coxhil	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
about	O
7	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
for	O
a	O
penny-worth	O
of	O
Ale	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
requiring	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
warm	O
'd	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Pot	O
being	O
afterwards	O
set	O
upon	O
the	O
Shelf	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
as	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
Notice	O
being	O
taken	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
something	O
conceal	O
'd	O
under	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
he	O
looking	O
for	O
the	O
Pot	O
,	O
found	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
pursu	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
running	O
away	O
,	O
got	O
off	O
:	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
again	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
House	O
upon	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
for	O
a	O
Penny-worth	O
of	O
Ale	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
notice	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
who	O
carried	O
away	O
the	O
Pot	O
;	O
that	O
thereupon	O
his	O
Master	O
apprehended	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
tax	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
stealing	O
the	O
Pot	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
but	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
buy	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Daughter	O
being	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
went	O
and	O
bought	O
a	O
large	O
new	O
Copper-Pot	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
satisfying	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
actually	O
did	O
take	O
the	O
Pot	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
C-	B-pers
K-	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bow	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
19	O
Yards	O
of	O
Linen	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Allen	B-pers
Brent	I-pers
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
Linen	O
hung	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop-window	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
notice	O
was	O
given	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
being	O
follow	O
'd	O
by	O
Joshua	B-pers
Snowden	I-pers
,	O
was	O
taken	O
near	O
Bow-Church	O
,	O
having	O
the	O
Linen	O
under	O
her	O
Apron	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
giving	O
Credit	O
to	O
this	O
Plea	O
of	O
hers	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Amy	B-pers
Dagg	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
Wood-street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
20	O
Yards	O
of	O
printed	O
Linen	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Jenks	I-pers
and	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Linen	O
had	O
been	O
stolen	O
from	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Green	I-pers
's	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
sent	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
be	O
glazed	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
a	O
loose	O
Character	O
,	O
was	O
suspected	O
to	O
have	O
stolen	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
apprehended	O
did	O
confess	O
the	O
stealing	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
directed	O
to	O
the	O
Pawn-Broker	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
pawned	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Stephen	I-place
's	I-place
Coleman-street	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Crimson-Bed-Damask	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Salisbury	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
an	O
Upholster	O
,	O
the	O
Piece	O
of	O
Damask	O
was	O
stolen	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
found	O
10	O
Yards	O
of	O
it	O
at	O
Mary	O
Holmes	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
Mantua-Maker	O
,	O
whither	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
into	O
a	O
Mantua-Gown	O
,	O
and	O
seven	O
Yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
more	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Damask	O
at	O
the	O
Pawn	O
Brokers	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
pawn	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
order	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
gave	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
10	O
Yards	O
of	O
the	O
Damask	O
before	O
mentioned	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
came	O
the	O
Eighth	O
of	O
September	O
(	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
it	O
was	O
stolen	O
)	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
cut	O
out	O
the	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
Damask	O
again	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
suspecting	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
have	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
and	O
Peter	B-pers
Beby	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
the	I-place
Evangelist	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland-Apron	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Windhurst	I-pers
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
latter	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
against	O
Eleanor	O
Brown	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
but	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
that	O
Peter	O
Beby	O
(	O
to	O
whom	O
they	O
were	O
pawn	O
'd	O
)	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
receiving	O
them	O
,	O
did	O
know	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Dorenny	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
some	O
Watch-maker	O
's	O
Tools	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Maiden	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anne	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sauce-Pan	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Elcock	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Salisbury	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Chamber-Pot	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cornwal	I-pers
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Pot	O
was	O
stolen	O
from	O
the	O
Castle	B-place
Tavern	I-place
in	O
Drury-Lane	B-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
apprehended	O
selling	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
clearly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Diploe	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Hind	I-pers
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
clearly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Esther	B-pers
Bazakerly	I-pers
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Felony	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Priestman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
the	I-place
Martyr	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Christopher	I-pers
,	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
employ	O
'd	O
to	O
assist	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
(	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Coachman	O
)	O
who	O
being	O
abroad	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
into	O
his	O
Room	O
and	O
stole	O
his	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
clearly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rayner	I-pers
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
4	O
Brass	O
Dog-Collars	O
,	O
a	O
Bell	O
,	O
some	O
Metal	O
Buckles	O
and	O
Buttons	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Moreton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
keeping	O
a	O
Stall	O
,	O
and	O
selling	O
Cutlery	O
Ware	O
in	O
Holbourn	B-place
,	O
found	O
his	O
Stall	O
broken	O
open	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
knew	O
not	O
who	O
had	O
stolen	O
them	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
saw	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
the	O
Round-House	O
.	O
Hugh	B-pers
Farnsworth	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
(	O
who	O
were	O
two	O
young	O
Boys	O
)	O
about	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
Brick-Kiln-Yard	O
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
ringing	O
a	O
Bell	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
If	O
he	O
would	O
sell	O
it	O
?	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
Yes	O
,	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
other	O
Things	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
shewing	O
him	O
a	O
Box	O
with	O
some	O
Buttons	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
examining	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
pretended	O
they	O
had	O
bought	O
them	O
for	O
6	O
d.	O
at	O
the	O
Pindar	O
of	O
Wakefield	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
suspecting	O
them	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
enquire	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
meeting	O
with	O
any	O
Confirmation	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
Custody	O
of	O
an	O
Officer	O
,	O
Smith	O
at	O
last	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
broken	O
open	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Stall	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
that	O
Thomas	O
Rayner	O
was	O
not	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
clearly	O
proved	O
against	O
Robert	O
Smith	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
but	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Thomas	O
Rayner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Butterfield	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Mould	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
27	O
Saws	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
2	O
of	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
's	O
,	O
5	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Keys	I-pers
,	O
4	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
's	O
,	O
6	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Raper	I-pers
's	O
,	O
6	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Sampson	I-pers
's	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Brody	I-pers
's	O
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
George	O
Butterfield	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
two	O
others	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
five	O
dozen	O
of	O
Pewter-Spoons	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Broadhurst	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
12	O
dozen	O
of	O
Spoons	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
found	O
but	O
5	O
dozen	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
found	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Rich	O
's	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Rich	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Spoons	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
by	O
Margaret	B-pers
Bedford	I-pers
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
goes	O
also	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
and	O
also	O
Hardis	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Spoons	O
to	O
pawn	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
that	O
deals	O
in	O
such	O
Ware	O
,	O
and	O
keeps	O
Fairs	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
produce	O
any	O
such	O
Person	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Young	I-pers
and	O
Timothy	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
76	O
Pound	O
of	O
Brass	O
Metal	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Hubbard	I-pers
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Achlan	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
Mother	O
having	O
had	O
Intelligence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Richard	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
her	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
had	O
given	O
Metal	O
to	O
his	O
Brother	O
Timothy	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
sent	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
her	O
again	O
(	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
found	O
out	O
to	O
have	O
done	O
the	O
like	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
forgiven	O
)	O
that	O
thereupon	O
he	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
keep	O
him	O
,	O
Richard	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
went	O
for	O
his	O
Brother	O
Timothy	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
found	O
in	O
Virginia-Street	O
,	O
who	O
being	O
taxed	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
Metal	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
selling	O
it	O
,	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
his	O
Brother	O
had	O
drawn	O
him	O
into	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Crime	O
;	O
and	O
Richard	O
,	O
likewise	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
several	O
times	O
given	O
him	O
Metal	O
of	O
his	O
Masters	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
likewise	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
had	O
several	O
times	O
bought	O
Parcels	O
of	O
Metal	O
of	O
Timothy	B-pers
Young	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Christopher	B-pers
Braner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Undershaft	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
20	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
standing	O
near	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Shop-Door	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Lime-street	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
Loaf	O
of	O
Sugar	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
Stall	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
pursuing	O
him	O
up	O
Lime-street	O
,	O
he	O
dropp	O
'd	O
the	O
Sugar	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
however	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
clearly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Kelly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Garnet	O
Stone-Ring	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Markham	I-pers
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
Anne	O
Markham	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
when	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Ring	O
being	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
she	O
swore	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
her	O
Ring	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Treasure	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
Mistress	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Ear-Ring	O
Drops	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
showing	O
her	O
several	O
,	O
she	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
her	O
slyly	O
to	O
convey	O
something	O
to	O
her	O
Bosom	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
missing	O
the	O
Ring	O
,	O
taxed	O
her	O
with	O
having	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
deny	O
'd	O
several	O
times	O
;	O
but	O
at	O
length	O
pulled	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Bosom	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Macklen	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Gold-Rings	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Prat	I-pers
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
frequently	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
to	O
sell	O
Oysters	O
,	O
took	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
Rings	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
owned	O
upon	O
her	O
being	O
apprehended	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Hosea	B-pers
May	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White-Church	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
five	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Barley	O
in	O
the	O
Straw	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Grub	I-pers
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
Barley	O
having	O
been	O
cut	O
,	O
and	O
lying	O
in	O
his	O
Field	O
in	O
the	O
Swarth	O
,	O
he	O
missing	O
Part	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
track	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
by	O
scatterings	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
considerable	O
quantity	O
of	O
Barley	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
verily	O
believe	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
then	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
Wife	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
it	O
by	O
Leasing	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
an	O
adjacent	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
,	O
or	O
near	O
half	O
a	O
Mile	O
off	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
,	O
an	O
opportunity	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
to	O
carry	O
great	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
Wood	O
not	O
far	O
off	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stole	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Barley	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
calling	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Welsden	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
five	O
Ewe-Sheep	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Lamb	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Sheep	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Possession	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
another	O
Man	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
produce	O
the	O
Person	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Wanklin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Leveret	I-pers
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Hasleden	I-pers
,	O
did	O
feloniously	O
steal	O
a	O
Cock	O
and	O
a	O
Hen	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lamb	I-pers
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Lamb	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
lost	O
her	O
Fowls	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
inform	O
'd	O
they	O
were	O
seen	O
in	O
Hasleden	O
's	O
Yard	O
by	O
Margaret	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Leveret	I-pers
,	O
being	O
at	O
play	O
at	O
Skettles	O
in	O
Hasleden	O
's	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Fowls	O
coming	O
in	O
,	O
they	O
drove	O
them	O
into	O
Hasleden	O
's	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
wrung	O
their	O
Necks	O
,	O
and	O
hung	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
what	O
became	O
of	O
them	O
afterwards	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
proof	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Neighbours	O
giving	O
him	O
an	O
honest	O
Character	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Eling	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Faulkner	I-pers
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
clearly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Abram	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
Bloomsbury	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Frances	B-pers
Westenham	I-pers
,	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
her	O
Lodger	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Thaffey	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Wood	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Kerby	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
and	O
Apron	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Alcroft	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Hutchinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Fanham	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
a	O
Coachman	O
had	O
put	O
his	O
Coat	O
into	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
and	O
go	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
apprehended	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
coming	O
to	O
pawn	O
some	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Cornelius	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Christ-Church	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
and	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Sumner	I-pers
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
clearly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susannah	B-pers
Carpenter	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Green	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Denton	B-pers
,	O
and	O
Christopher	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
Value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
three	O
Shifts	O
,	O
six	O
Mobs	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Durance	B-pers
Tyrach	I-pers
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
having	O
come	O
from	O
Hampstead	O
,	O
hired	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
carry	O
her	O
Box	O
of	O
Clothes	O
to	O
Tower-Hill	O
;	O
that	O
coming	O
into	O
Lombard-Street	B-place
,	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
drop	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Box	O
and	O
Clothes	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Miles	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
Value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hatton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
clearly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Richmond	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
four	O
linen	O
Clouts	O
,	O
a	O
Punch	O
Bowl	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Garden	O
Wall	O
,	O
went	O
into	O
an	O
Out-House	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
alarm	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
barking	O
of	O
a	O
Dog	O
,	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
in	O
his	O
Garden	O
,	O
and	O
pursuing	O
them	O
,	O
apprehended	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
an	O
adjacent	O
Field	O
;	O
but	O
his	O
Accomplice	O
made	O
his	O
Escape	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
clearly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Beaton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Velvet	O
Hat	O
,	O
Value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Gosten	I-pers
,	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
Dorcas	B-pers
Gosten	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Hat	O
hung	O
at	O
her	O
Shop-door	O
for	O
sale	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
afterwards	O
sold	O
to	O
Alice	B-pers
Stacey	I-pers
.	O
Alice	O
Stacey	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
bought	O
the	O
Hat	O
for	O
fourteen	O
pence	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Quilt	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
pawned	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Dorigny	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
4	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
a	O
Yard	O
of	O
Muslin	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
two	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
Guinea	O
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
stealing	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
by	O
his	O
own	O
Confession	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Stopforth	I-pers
,	O
who	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
New-Prison	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
a	O
single	O
Felony	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Proof	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
of	O
that	O
they	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Dowdy	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Body	O
appearing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Shene	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dionysius-Back-Church	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
put	O
a	O
pair	O
into	O
her	O
Coat	O
that	O
was	O
pinn	O
'd	O
up	O
.	O
That	O
being	O
tax	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Stockings	O
,	O
she	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
having	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Stockings	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Everett	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Ethelburgh	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
50	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Thread	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Journeyman	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
inform	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
seen	O
to	O
put	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Thread	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Thread	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
upon	O
Examination	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
own	O
'd	O
his	O
taking	O
the	O
Thread	O
from	O
his	O
Master	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
small	O
Parcel	O
that	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
being	O
a	O
full	O
proof	O
of	O
that	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
Shillings	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Jasper	B-pers
Cunst	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
walking	O
in	O
Fleet-street	B-place
,	O
a	O
Person	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
Nothing	O
;	O
that	O
feeling	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
said	O
Person	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
immediately	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Edgington	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
five	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
four-pence	O
half-penny	O
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
passing	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	B-place
,	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
o	O
'	O
clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Day	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
met	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
Edgington	O
coming	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
Blow	O
on	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
his	O
Nose	O
on	O
bleeding	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
Blood	O
ran	O
into	O
his	O
Mouth	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
.	O
That	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
Jones	O
took	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
Edgington	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
both	O
got	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
he	O
got	O
Edgington	O
apprehended	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
some	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
having	O
seen	O
him	O
at	O
his	O
Father	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
kept	O
a	O
Brandy	O
Shop	O
.	O
-	O
Allen	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
about	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
Watchman	O
,	O
all	O
dirty	O
and	O
bloody	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
he	O
told	O
two	O
Men	O
that	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
by	O
one	O
Shock	O
,	O
(	O
Edgington	O
,	O
)	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Pocket	O
had	O
been	O
pick	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
thereupon	O
he	O
went	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
and	O
made	O
Oath	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
describing	O
the	O
Persons	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
afterwards	O
apprehended	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
calling	O
some	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
home	O
to	O
their	O
Lodgings	O
at	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
nine	O
a	O
clock	O
,	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
believed	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
out	O
again	O
that	O
Night	O
;	O
the	O
Proof	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
resting	O
solely	O
on	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
might	O
possibly	O
be	O
mistaken	O
in	O
the	O
Fright	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Evidence	O
interfering	O
with	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
in	O
a	O
certain	O
Field	O
or	O
open	O
Place	O
near	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
Hat	O
,	O
Peruke	O
,	O
Sword	O
and	O
Neckcloth	O
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
playing	O
at	O
Whisk	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
much	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
home	O
two	O
Men	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
conduct	O
him	O
home	O
the	O
best	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
they	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Ducking-Pond	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
London-Spaw	B-place
,	O
and	O
they	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
change	O
Clothes	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
but	O
he	O
might	O
consent	O
to	O
,	O
being	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
and	O
supposing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Frolick	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
off	O
his	O
Coat	O
and	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
before	O
his	O
Face	O
to	O
blind	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
pull	O
off	O
his	O
Shirt	O
,	O
having	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
his	O
Stock	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
seeing	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
all	O
his	O
Clothes	O
from	O
him	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
no	O
other	O
,	O
having	O
taken	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
Wig	O
and	O
Sword	O
,	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Persons	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Assistance	O
.	O
That	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Whitmore	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
at	O
Saffron-Hill	O
,	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
I	O
beg	O
of	O
you	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
much	O
in	O
Liquor	O
.	O
And	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
we	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
clever	O
Girl	O
for	O
you	O
near	O
Hockley	O
in	O
the	O
Hole	O
.	O
And	O
he	O
dogg	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
they	O
would	O
do	O
with	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
he	O
suspecting	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Cross	O
's	O
Brew-house	O
,	O
and	O
turn	O
'd	O
towards	O
Black	O
Mary	O
's	O
Hole	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
towards	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Colchester	O
.	O
And	O
he	O
heard	O
them	O
coaxing	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
buss	O
you	O
.	O
That	O
thinking	O
they	O
were	O
Molleys	O
,	O
he	O
still	O
dogg	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
That	O
meeting	O
with	O
a	O
Watchman	O
,	O
he	O
inform	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
towards	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
beginning	O
to	O
cry	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
perceiving	O
the	O
Watchman	O
and	O
himself	O
coming	O
towards	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Clothes	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
near	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
which	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
had	O
the	O
Clothes	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
ran	O
up	O
the	O
Hill	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
clear	O
off	O
,	O
carrying	O
with	O
him	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Sword	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Betts	I-pers
the	O
Watchman	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
latter	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
him	O
put	O
out	O
his	O
Light	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
answer	O
that	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
putting	O
his	O
Lanthorn	O
under	O
his	O
Great	O
Coat	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Light	O
might	O
not	O
be	O
seen	O
,	O
made	O
towards	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
apprehended	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
has	O
been	O
before	O
deposed	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gill	O
the	O
Constable	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Gill	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
I	O
that	O
strip	O
'd	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
Michael	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
.	O
But	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
put	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
necessary	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
a	O
Robbery	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
owning	O
his	O
tacit	O
Consent	O
to	O
the	O
changing	O
Clothes	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Hampton	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Pegg	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Half	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
12	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
John	O
Pegg	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Hampton	O
Town	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
One	O
and	O
Two	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
take	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
swear	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
.	O
-	O
Flat	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stand	O
under	O
the	O
Pales	O
going	O
from	O
Hampton	B-place
Town	I-place
to	O
Hampton	B-place
Court	I-place
,	O
and	O
just	O
as	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
D-n	O
you	O
,	O
Stand	O
;	O
and	O
with	O
a	O
Stick	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
struck	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
avoided	O
the	O
Blow	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
no	O
Stick	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
defend	O
himself	O
,	O
ran	O
away	O
to	O
get	O
Assistance	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Lady	O
De	O
Lorrain	O
's	O
Footman	O
;	O
that	O
describing	O
the	O
Person	O
to	O
have	O
on	O
a	O
dark-colour	O
'd	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
black	O
Hair	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
young	O
Fellow	O
of	O
an	O
ill	O
Character	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
quest	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
about	O
12	O
o'clock	O
saw	O
him	O
leaning	O
over	O
his	O
Father	O
's	O
Pales	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
afraid	O
of	O
him	O
now	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
12	O
o'clock	O
the	O
last	O
Night	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
getting	O
into	O
his	O
Father	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Doors	O
were	O
shut	O
,	O
till	O
an	O
Officer	O
being	O
fetch	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
threatning	O
to	O
break	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
length	O
opened	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
apprehended	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Price	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
crying	O
out	O
Thieves	O
,	O
and	O
Murther	O
!	O
and	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Fellow-Servant	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
neither	O
Prosecutor	O
nor	O
Prisoner	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
very	O
dark	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Hat	O
,	O
but	O
hitting	O
it	O
with	O
his	O
Stick	O
,	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
also	O
a	O
great	O
Stick	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
at	O
Hampton-Court	O
,	O
calling	O
at	O
his	O
Window	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
they	O
were	O
afraid	O
he	O
was	O
murthered	O
,	O
he	O
answered	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
bruised	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
next	O
Evidence	O
was	O
positive	O
:	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
by	O
several	O
Evidences	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
dark	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
North	O
Light	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
,	O
altho	O
'	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
a	O
North	O
Light	O
,	O
yet	O
that	O
Place	O
was	O
so	O
shrouded	O
from	O
it	O
with	O
Trees	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
thought	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
know	O
a	O
Man	O
by	O
what	O
Light	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
to	O
prove	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
One	O
or	O
Two	O
o'clock	O
that	O
Morning	O
;	O
but	O
had	O
the	O
Misfortune	O
to	O
produce	O
no	O
Evidence	O
.	O
His	O
Father	O
appear	O
'd	O
;	O
but	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
at	O
10	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
his	O
Son	O
came	O
home	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
him	O
very	O
drunk	O
in	O
the	O
Barn	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
at	O
five	O
of	O
the	O
clock	O
.	O
He	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
his	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
(	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Carpenter	O
)	O
follow	O
'd	O
his	O
Business	O
regularly	O
,	O
liv	O
'd	O
civilly	O
,	O
was	O
very	O
obedient	O
and	O
dutiful	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
never	O
lien	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
House	O
but	O
one	O
Night	O
before	O
.	O
Several	O
of	O
his	O
Neighbours	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
had	O
never	O
heard	O
an	O
ill	O
Character	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
except	O
that	O
now	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
would	O
drink	O
a	O
little	O
too	O
much	O
.	O
After	O
a	O
full	O
Hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Stubbs	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Tenant	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Shift	O
,	O
a	O
Towel	O
,	O
some	O
Remnants	O
of	O
Plad	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
of	O
small	O
value	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Dame	O
Martha	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Lady	O
Johnson	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
her	O
Servant	O
for	O
about	O
nine	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
always	O
behav	O
'd	O
her	O
self	O
well	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
Mistrust	O
of	O
her	O
Dishonesty	O
,	O
having	O
all	O
along	O
entrusted	O
her	O
with	O
Things	O
of	O
value	O
;	O
but	O
having	O
occasion	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
left	O
her	O
in	O
her	O
Lodgings	O
in	O
German-street	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
her	O
Trunk	O
had	O
been	O
carried	O
out	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Knaves	O
Acre	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
inform	O
'd	O
it	O
was	O
carried	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
where	O
examining	O
that	O
Trunk	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Boxes	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
sworn	O
to	O
be	O
hers	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
Things	O
of	O
a	O
trifling	O
Consideration	O
.	O
Some	O
other	O
Evidences	O
were	O
call	O
'd	O
,	O
who	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
finding	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Trunk	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
were	O
her	O
own	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
brought	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Persons	O
to	O
her	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
who	O
had	O
often	O
heard	O
the	O
Character	O
her	O
Lady	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
her	O
self	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
last	O
of	O
her	O
coming	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
depos	O
'd	O
several	O
Things	O
which	O
made	O
it	O
probable	O
that	O
the	O
Difference	O
might	O
arise	O
between	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Prosecutor	O
upon	O
account	O
of	O
a	O
pressing	O
Demand	O
for	O
Wages	O
;	O
which	O
as	O
was	O
made	O
appear	O
,	O
did	O
amount	O
to	O
near	O
40	O
l.	O
several	O
other	O
Circumstances	O
were	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
made	O
it	O
seen	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
Foundation	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Trevor	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
Ludgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
a	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Ledbury	I-pers
,	O
and	O
also	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Ledbury	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
Drawer	O
at	O
the	O
Dog	B-place
Tavern	I-place
,	O
on	O
Ludgate-Hill	B-place
,	O
his	O
Fellow-Servant	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
come	O
from	O
the	O
Stairs	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
ran	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Door	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Clothes	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
gone	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
pursu	O
'd	O
,	O
was	O
taken	O
at	O
the	O
Wind-Mill	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
in	O
Newgate-Market	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
several	O
other	O
Evidences	O
,	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bullwant	I-pers
was	O
pretty	O
positive	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
near	O
the	O
Stairs	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
at	O
the	O
Tavern	O
Door	O
,	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
three	O
other	O
Persons	O
,	O
a	O
Person	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
Tavern	O
Door	O
without	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
earn	O
a	O
Shilling	O
?	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
would	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Bundle	O
,	O
bidding	O
him	O
carry	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Wind-Mill	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
himself	O
would	O
be	O
there	O
presently	O
;	O
to	O
confirm	O
this	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
three	O
Persons	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Bolk	I-pers
,	O
and	O
-	O
Steward	O
,	O
who	O
all	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
Swallow-street	O
,	O
near	O
Grosvenor-Square	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
together	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
Dog	O
Tavern	O
,	O
were	O
buying	O
some	O
Ginger-Bread	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
see	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
Entry	O
of	O
the	O
Dog	O
Tavern	O
,	O
without	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
who	O
did	O
offer	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
Shilling	O
,	O
to	O
carry	O
a	O
Bundle	O
to	O
the	O
Wind-Mill	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
and	O
left	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
likewise	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Persons	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Row	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Peter	I-place
's	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
17	O
Yards	O
of	O
Calicoe-wrapper	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Honourable	O
East-India	B-pers
Company	I-pers
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Workman	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
as	O
a	O
Labourer	O
in	O
the	O
Company	O
's	O
Warehouses	O
)	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
to	O
remove	O
Gunnies	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
walking	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Manner	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
apprehended	O
his	O
Breeches	O
were	O
stuffed	O
with	O
something	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
Token-House-Yard	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
but	O
instead	O
of	O
coming	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
putting	O
up	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
something	O
lie	O
white	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Piece	O
of	O
Calicoe-wrapper	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Favour	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
the	O
Commissioners	O
of	O
Warehouses	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
did	O
take	O
the	O
Wrapper	O
,	O
and	O
begg	O
'd	O
forgiveness	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
deny	O
his	O
having	O
taken	O
the	O
Piece	O
of	O
Wrapper	O
,	O
nor	O
knew	O
how	O
it	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
at	O
the	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
where	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Workman	I-pers
found	O
it	O
;	O
unless	O
he	O
brought	O
it	O
and	O
throw	O
'd	O
it	O
there	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
owing	O
him	O
a	O
Spite	O
:	O
He	O
also	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
common	O
Custom	O
,	O
and	O
allow	O
'd	O
the	O
Labourers	O
in	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
now	O
and	O
then	O
a	O
Remnant	O
of	O
Wrappers	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
Perquisite	O
.	O
And	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Workman	O
himself	O
had	O
employed	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
carry	O
out	O
Wrappers	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
practised	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
allow	O
'd	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Quantity	O
of	O
a	O
Couple	O
of	O
Yards	O
,	O
for	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
or	O
Night-Cap	O
,	O
or	O
so	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
Allowance	O
being	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
abus	O
'd	O
,	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
an	O
Order	O
made	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Commissioners	O
of	O
Warehouses	O
;	O
which	O
Order	O
had	O
been	O
printed	O
,	O
and	O
hung	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Warehouses	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
never	O
was	O
any	O
Allowance	O
for	O
the	O
taking	O
whole	O
Peices	O
,	O
or	O
such	O
Quantities	O
:	O
And	O
he	O
added	O
that	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
found	O
out	O
,	O
that	O
30000	O
Yards	O
had	O
been	O
lost	O
to	O
the	O
Company	O
,	O
the	O
last	O
Sale	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
calling	O
some	O
Persons	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
's	I-place
Queen-Hithe	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
five	O
Shillings	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
rented	O
a	O
Garret	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Father	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
that	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
about	O
her	O
Business	O
,	O
the	O
Plaister	O
of	O
the	O
Wall	O
was	O
pulled	O
down	O
and	O
the	O
Lathing	O
broken	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
for	O
her	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
missing	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
under	O
Drawer	O
of	O
a	O
Trunk	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
unlock	O
'd	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
apprehended	O
,	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
broken	O
the	O
Lathing	O
and	O
Plaistering	O
,	O
put	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Lock	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
Spring-lock	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
down	O
on	O
his	O
Knees	O
,	O
and	O
beg	O
'd	O
for	O
Mercy	O
,	O
promising	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
Work	O
for	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
pay	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
owning	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Money	O
,	O
was	O
also	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Cave	I-pers
the	O
Constable	O
who	O
apprehended	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Jenks	B-pers
,	O
of	O
Christ-Church	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Pockets	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
;	O
and	O
also	O
8	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Samuel	O
Russel	O
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
Samuel	O
Russel	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
Day	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
and	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
till	O
the	O
29th	O
;	O
at	O
which	O
time	O
(	O
he	O
being	O
Butler	O
to	O
the	O
Cloth-Workers	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
employ	O
'd	O
to	O
keep	O
the	O
Hall	O
in	O
Order	O
)	O
were	O
oblig	O
'd	O
both	O
to	O
attend	O
at	O
the	O
Hall	O
that	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
leaving	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
a	O
Canvass	O
Bag	O
,	O
lock	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Closet	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Key	O
was	O
left	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
missing	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Pockets	O
of	O
his	O
Wife	O
's	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
purpose	O
,	O
adding	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
Chest	O
which	O
was	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Chamber	O
,	O
she	O
supposed	O
her	O
Husband	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
not	O
finding	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
it	O
did	O
appear	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
concealed	O
it	O
,	O
till	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
when	O
apprehended	O
being	O
examined	O
concerning	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
let	O
a	O
Sailor	O
have	O
3	O
l.	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
was	O
all	O
gone	O
,	O
they	O
not	O
having	O
the	O
opportunity	O
to	O
find	O
her	O
from	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
May	O
till	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
Michaelmas	O
Day	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
left	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
the	O
House	O
in	O
his	O
Absence	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
publick	O
House	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Crown	O
in	O
George-Street	O
,	O
near	O
Spittle-fields	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
under	O
pretence	O
to	O
fetch	O
some	O
Linen	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Closet	O
to	O
iron	O
for	O
the	O
Children	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
thinking	O
her	O
to	O
stay	O
long	O
,	O
a	O
Person	O
coming	O
in	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
called	O
her	O
down	O
to	O
draw	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Chest	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
unlock	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
going	O
up	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
found	O
it	O
lock	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
at	O
about	O
Three	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
clearly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
But	O
recommended	O
her	O
to	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Mercy	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Knowles	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Harper	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Newington	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Waller	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Waller	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
and	O
Sarah	O
Harper	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
Prisoners	O
together	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
Goal	O
of	O
Surry	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
pass	O
'd	O
his	O
Word	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Perry	O
,	O
for	O
upwards	O
of	O
7	O
l.	O
for	O
her	O
for	O
Lodging	O
Fees	O
,	O
and	O
Bar	O
Score	O
;	O
that	O
afterwards	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
over	O
a	O
Stile	O
near	O
Newington	B-place
,	O
a	O
Man	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Sarah	O
Harper	O
took	O
his	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
Here	O
is	O
a	O
Pen-Knife	O
,	O
G-d	O
D-n	O
him	O
cut	O
his	O
Thoat	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
will	O
hang	O
us	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Man	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
enough	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Knowles	I-pers
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
swear	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
Man	O
;	O
but	O
was	O
positive	O
that	O
Sarah	O
Harper	O
,	O
took	O
his	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
sworn	O
a	O
Robbery	O
against	O
him	O
(	O
John	B-pers
Waller	I-pers
)	O
for	O
robbing	O
her	O
of	O
6	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Green	O
Purse	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
try	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
at	O
Kingston	O
.	O
The	O
Baron	O
Thompson	O
remembred	O
this	O
;	O
and	O
though	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Harris	O
was	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
but	O
a	O
bad	O
Character	O
,	O
yet	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
being	O
worse	O
,	O
rendered	O
himself	O
Notorious	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
Sworn	O
Robberies	O
upon	O
several	O
Persons	O
(	O
probably	O
only	O
for	O
the	O
reward	O
)	O
who	O
were	O
acquitted	O
as	O
Innocent	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
hang	O
'd	O
-	O
Dalton	O
:	O
The	O
Court	O
thought	O
no	O
regard	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
given	O
to	O
his	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Farren	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White-Chapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Metcalf	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Wheel	O
of	O
a	O
Dray	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
Thigh	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
left	O
Knee	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
of	O
which	O
Wound	O
he	O
languishing	O
,	O
liv	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
for	O
the	O
unlawful	O
slaying	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
Metcalf	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Cranwel	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
hearing	O
a	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
about	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
lying	O
with	O
his	O
Arm	O
before	O
the	O
Wheel	O
of	O
the	O
Dray	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Thigh	O
behind	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
stopp	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Thigh	O
was	O
broke	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
his	O
Door	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Dray	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
near	O
it	O
,	O
who	O
being	O
a	O
Lame	O
old	O
Man	O
,	O
had	O
a	O
Stick	O
,	O
or	O
Crutches	O
,	O
and	O
fearing	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
by	O
Mischief	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
Dray-Man	O
to	O
hold	O
off	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
whether	O
he	O
heard	O
him	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
answer	O
;	O
nor	O
could	O
he	O
say	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
very	O
Dark	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
empty	O
Barrels	O
on	O
the	O
Dray	O
,	O
they	O
made	O
a	O
Noise	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Burgess	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
heard	O
some	O
Body	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
the	O
Dray	O
;	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
fall	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
a	O
Crack	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
Stick	O
or	O
the	O
Bone	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
hear	O
the	O
calling	O
out	O
,	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Metcalf	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
Widow	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
her	O
Husband	O
did	O
several	O
times	O
declare	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
clapping	O
his	O
Stick	O
to	O
the	O
Wheel	O
of	O
the	O
Dray	O
,	O
the	O
Stick	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Lame	O
Leg	O
gave	O
way	O
,	O
(	O
he	O
having	O
a	O
great	O
Sore	O
on	O
his	O
Leg	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
a	O
Prize-Fighter	O
)	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
fell	O
under	O
the	O
Dray	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
charge	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
having	O
been	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
his	O
Misfortune	O
;	O
but	O
several	O
times	O
pressed	O
her	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
Prison	O
,	O
upon	O
his	O
engaging	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
in	O
Consideration	O
of	O
the	O
loss	O
of	O
time	O
,	O
he	O
sustain	O
'd	O
by	O
his	O
Imprisonment	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Distress	O
of	O
his	O
Family	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
well	O
(	O
he	O
expected	O
to	O
recover	O
it	O
)	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
get	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
Prison	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
and	O
get	O
Money	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
some	O
amends	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
Mary	B-pers
Dosey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Small	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Rayner	O
,	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
careful	O
Man	O
in	O
his	O
Business	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
in	O
their	O
Verdict	O
Chance	O
Medley	O
.	O
Esther	B-pers
Elwood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Shirts	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Linen	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Taplin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White-Chapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Thomas	B-pers
Morey	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
Field	O
or	O
open	O
Place	O
near	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1730	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Morey	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
was	O
12	O
Months	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
in	O
Little-Britain	O
,	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Shadwell	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
at	O
White-Chapel	O
Church	O
,	O
heard	O
the	O
Clock	O
strike	O
ten	O
(	O
at	O
Night	O
)	O
that	O
going	O
cross	O
the	O
Tom-Turd-Field	B-place
,	O
a	O
Man	O
stood	O
,	O
seeming	O
to	O
be	O
making	O
Water	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Man	O
asking	O
him	O
,	O
what	O
was	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
Ten	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
crossing	O
the	O
Field	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
about	O
8	O
or	O
10	O
Steps	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
stopp	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
G-d	O
D-n	O
you	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
your	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
make	O
Resistance	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
a	O
Pistol	O
within	O
five	O
Inches	O
of	O
his	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Man	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
took	O
him	O
one	O
by	O
one	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
by	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
dragg	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
Ditch	O
,	O
stripp	O
'd	O
off	O
his	O
Clothes	O
,	O
unbutton	O
'd	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
his	O
Shirt	O
,	O
ty	O
'd	O
his	O
Hands	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
ty	O
'd	O
his	O
Legs	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
him	O
;	O
where	O
he	O
lay	O
till	O
two	O
Men	O
who	O
(	O
as	O
he	O
suppos	O
'd	O
)	O
were	O
Haymakers	O
,	O
unbound	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
home	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
them	O
two	O
Pots	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
for	O
their	O
Kindness	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Pope	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
last	O
June	O
was	O
twelve	O
months	O
,	O
lodg	O
'd	O
and	O
work	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
come	O
home	O
with	O
two	O
Men	O
,	O
without	O
his	O
Clothes	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
stripp	O
'd	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
positive	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
positive	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
very	O
Man	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
him	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
several	O
Years	O
.	O
He	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
how	O
it	O
came	O
about	O
that	O
since	O
he	O
knew	O
him	O
so	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
so	O
long	O
ago	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
taken	O
him	O
up	O
before	O
?	O
He	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
him	O
since	O
,	O
till	O
lately	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
he	O
know	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
following	O
Evidences	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Thornton	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
at	O
Darking	O
in	O
Surrey	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
June	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1730.	O
and	O
was	O
never	O
absent	O
from	O
thence	O
long	O
enough	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
London	O
and	O
commit	O
that	O
Robbery	O
till	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
June	O
1731.	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
always	O
behav	O
'd	O
himself	O
very	O
honestly	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Humphreys	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
work	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
till	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
June	O
1730.	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Darking	O
to	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
always	O
bore	O
an	O
honest	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
behav	O
'd	O
himself	O
well	O
in	O
his	O
Service	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
employ	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
entrusted	O
him	O
where	O
were	O
many	O
Goods	O
of	O
Value	O
;	O
and	O
had	O
that	O
good	O
Opinion	O
of	O
him	O
as	O
to	O
make	O
no	O
scraple	O
of	O
leaving	O
her	O
Drawers	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
yet	O
never	O
miss	O
'd	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
always	O
bore	O
an	O
honest	O
Character	O
.	O
The	O
following	O
Persons	O
were	O
also	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dagg	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
work	O
'd	O
and	O
lodg	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
to	O
take	O
Money	O
for	O
Work	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
done	O
;	O
stole	O
a	O
Candlestick	O
;	O
and	O
changed	O
his	O
Shirt	O
for	O
a	O
Bricklayer	O
's	O
that	O
was	O
better	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Rule	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
for	O
twenty	O
Years	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
kept	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
at	O
Gesport	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
Bawdy-House	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
always	O
bore	O
a	O
bad	O
Character	O
;	O
no	O
Man	O
ever	O
had	O
a	O
worse	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
vile	O
,	O
blasphemous	O
,	O
desperate	O
Fellow	O
.	O
After	O
a	O
full	O
Hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Shift	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Headclothes	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Thread	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
and	O
a	O
Comb	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Davenport	I-pers
,	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Davenport	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
her	O
Servant	O
for	O
six	O
Months	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
been	O
gone	O
away	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
desired	O
that	O
she	O
might	O
be	O
with	O
her	O
till	O
she	O
get	O
a	O
Place	O
;	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
having	O
met	O
with	O
Misfortunes	O
,	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Army	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
leaving	O
her	O
at	O
her	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
staying	O
about	O
five	O
Weeks	O
,	O
at	O
her	O
Return	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
made	O
away	O
with	O
all	O
her	O
Goods	O
,	O
had	O
left	O
her	O
but	O
one	O
Shift	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Husband	O
but	O
one	O
Shirt	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
gone	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
her	O
under	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
Weeks	O
after	O
.	O
That	O
when	O
she	O
found	O
her	O
,	O
in	O
Thieving-Lane	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
her	O
Stockings	O
upon	O
her	O
Legs	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Handkerchief	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
her	O
Master	O
and	O
Mistress	O
had	O
run	O
away	O
from	O
her	O
and	O
left	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
ow	O
'd	O
her	O
Wages	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
left	O
her	O
nothing	O
to	O
subsist	O
on	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
something	O
to	O
keep	O
her	O
from	O
starving	O
.	O
And	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
following	O
Evidences	O
.	O
Olid	O
Simonds	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Years	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
entrusted	O
her	O
with	O
Things	O
of	O
great	O
value	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
found	O
her	O
very	O
just	O
and	O
honest	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
also	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
particular	O
Acquaintances	O
of	O
hers	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
always	O
heard	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Character	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
from	O
an	O
Insant	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
always	O
was	O
very	O
honest	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
lived	O
in	O
a	O
creditable	O
Service	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
occasion	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
Staffordshire	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
hired	O
to	O
supply	O
her	O
Place	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
gave	O
very	O
good	O
Satisfaction	O
in	O
the	O
Family	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
her	O
self	O
very	O
well	O
and	O
honestly	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
at	O
this	O
Evidence	O
's	O
Return	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
Sister	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
that	O
hearing	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Service	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
the	O
Prosecutrix	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
liv	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutrix	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
Character	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
get	O
her	O
Sister	O
away	O
she	O
would	O
be	O
ruined	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutrix	O
had	O
lived	O
sometimes	O
with	O
one	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
with	O
another	O
.	O
And	O
they	O
said	O
that	O
perhaps	O
when	O
her	O
Sister	O
came	O
to	O
ask	O
for	O
her	O
Wages	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
swear	O
a	O
Robbery	O
against	O
her	O
.	O
After	O
a	O
full	O
Hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
the	I-place
Evangelist	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
in	O
unlawfully	O
taking	O
and	O
bearing	O
away	O
a	O
promisory	O
Note	O
of	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
to	O
pay	O
to	O
Edgerton	B-pers
Yeates	I-pers
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
3	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
Edgerton	O
Yeates	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Saunders	O
pretending	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Attorney	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
several	O
small	O
Debts	O
owing	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
undertaken	O
to	O
get	O
them	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Pound	O
.	O
But	O
he	O
having	O
a	O
Note	O
for	O
3	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
cut	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Book	O
in	O
which	O
it	O
was	O
written	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
receive	O
it	O
himself	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
Saunders	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
demanded	O
it	O
of	O
him	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
it	O
him	O
.	O
But	O
this	O
not	O
seeming	O
to	O
be	O
proper	O
to	O
be	O
determined	O
in	O
this	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
Cause	O
was	O
dismissed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Beddoe	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
upon	O
the	O
Trial	O
of	O
Theophilus	B-pers
Cooling	I-pers
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Velvet	O
Seat	O
of	O
a	O
Chair	O
,	O
last	O
February	O
Sessions	O
,	O
he	O
not	O
charging	O
Cooling	O
with	O
stealing	O
;	O
he	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
how	O
it	O
came	O
to	O
pass	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
committed	O
and	O
indicted	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Partner	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
charge	O
him	O
with	O
stealing	O
the	O
Seat	O
?	O
He	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Cooling	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
before	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
Justice	O
Gifford	O
's	O
,	O
when	O
it	O
did	O
appear	O
by	O
the	O
Examination	O
(	O
that	O
Justice	O
Gifford	O
being	O
then	O
upon	O
the	O
Bench	O
,	O
desired	O
might	O
be	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
)	O
that	O
Benjamin	O
Beddoe	O
and	O
his	O
Partner	O
were	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
Commitment	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
charge	O
him	O
with	O
stealing	O
the	O
Seat	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Sherard	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Binns	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Richardson	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
marrying	O
a	O
second	O
Husband	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
;	O
her	O
first	O
Husband	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Binns	I-pers
,	O
being	O
alive	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Counterfeiting	O
,	O
Forging	O
,	O
and	O
Uttering	O
,	O
a	O
certain	O
Writing	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
Letter	O
of	O
Attorney	O
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
Wages	O
due	O
to	O
one	O
George	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Ship	O
Forwick	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Honourable	O
East-India	O
Company	O
.	O
It	O
did	O
appear	O
upon	O
opening	O
the	O
Cause	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
George	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
ow	O
'd	O
him	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
15	O
Guineas	O
,	O
taking	O
of	O
him	O
a	O
Letter	O
of	O
Atney	O
for	O
receiving	O
his	O
said	O
Wages	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
also	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wass	I-pers
had	O
also	O
a	O
Letter	O
of	O
Attorney	O
Posterior	O
to	O
that	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Lewis	O
's	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
any	O
legal	O
Proof	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Lewis	O
's	O
Letter	O
of	O
Attorney	O
being	O
Forg	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
order	O
'd	O
the	O
Cause	O
to	O
be	O
dismiss	O
'd	O
without	O
the	O
Defendant	O
's	O
calling	O
any	O
Evidences	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
accordingly	O
.	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
ended	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
,	O
as	O
follows	O
:	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
2.	O
John	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
and	O
Anne	B-pers
Farmer	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Jenks	O
.	O
Transportation	O
31.	O
Mary	B-pers
Abram	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Beaton	I-pers
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Bremer	I-pers
,	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Butterfield	I-pers
,	O
C-	O
K-	O
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Cornelius	I-pers
,	O
Anne	B-pers
Daggs	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Diploe	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Dorigni	I-pers
,	O
Esther	B-pers
Elwood	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Everet	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Hutchinson	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Kelly	I-pers
,	O
Anne	B-pers
Macklen	I-pers
,	O
Anne	B-pers
Maiden	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Miles	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Priestman	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Richmond	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Sheen	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Salisbury	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Timothy	B-pers
Young	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
6.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Cade	I-pers
,	O
Catherine	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Hampstead	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Lancaster	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Powis	I-pers
,	O
(	O
these	O
five	O
were	O
former	O
Convicted	O
)	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Sherard	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whip	O
'd	O
1.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
.	O
Books	O
just	O
printed	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
Joseph	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
in	O
Newgate-Street	O
.	O
LA	O
Plum	O
Volance	O
.	O
Or	O
the	O
Art	O
of	O
Short-hand	O
improved	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
most	O
Swift	O
,	O
Regular	O
,	O
and	O
Easy	O
Method	O
of	O
Shorthand-writing	O
yet	O
Extant	O
.	O
Composed	O
after	O
Fifty	O
Years	O
Practice	O
and	O
Improvement	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Art	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Observation	O
of	O
other	O
Methods	O
and	O
in	O
Study	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Fifth	O
Edition	O
,	O
with	O
Aditions	O
of	O
the	O
Terms	O
of	O
the	O
Law	O
,	O
and	O
much	O
amended	O
,	O
By	O
William	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
.	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
Life	O
and	O
Miraculous	O
Conversion	O
from	O
Popery	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Three	O
Parts	O
:	O
1	O
.	O
The	O
Glory	O
of	O
Divine	O
Grace	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
The	O
Protection	O
of	O
Divine	O
Providence	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Goodness	O
of	O
God	O
M	O
.	O
The	O
Second	O
Edition	O
.	O
Written	O
by	O
himself	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
Military	O
Discipline	O
.	O
The	O
Word	O
of	O
Command	O
,	O
and	O
Directions	O
for	O
Exercising	O
the	O
Muslces	O
and	O
Buyonet	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Carbene	O
,	O
Pistols	O
and	O
Sword	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
are	O
performed	O
by	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Horse	O
and	O
Foot	O
Guards	O
.	O
By	O
W.	O
B.	O
Gent	O
.	O
The	O
Second	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
1	O
s.	O
The	O
Singing	O
Master	O
's	O
Guide	O
to	O
his	O
Scholars	O
:	O
With	O
the	O
Psalms	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Old	O
and	O
New	O
Translations	O
;	O
the	O
Old	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
New	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
By	O
several	O
Hands	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Scornhold	O
and	O
Hopkins	O
,	O
Barton	O
,	O
Patrick	O
,	O
Tate	O
and	O
Brady	O
,	O
Milbourne	O
and	O
Sandys	O
.	O
Contriv	O
'd	O
for	O
Common	O
Use	O
:	O
With	O
the	O
Tunes	O
in	O
Two	O
Parts	O
.	O
By	O
Daniel	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Kwelm	O
in	O
Oxfordshire	O
,	O
Singing-Master	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
2s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
A	O
further	O
Guide	O
to	O
Parish	O
Clarks	O
:	O
or	O
,	O
any	O
other	O
religiously	O
and	O
devoutly	O
disposed	O
to	O
make	O
Use	O
of	O
these	O
Instructions	O
.	O
Being	O
contriv	O
'd	O
for	O
common	O
Use	O
,	O
by	O
Daniel	O
Warner	O
of	O
Ewlem	O
in	O
Oxfordshire	O
,	O
Singing-Master	O
.	O
Price	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
Art	O
of	O
Spelling	O
,	O
Containing	O
,	O
1	O
.	O
A	O
,	O
B	B-pers
,	O
C	B-pers
,	O
for	O
Children	O
,	O
consisting	O
of	O
Alphabets	O
and	O
Syllables	O
,	O
with	O
short	O
Rules	O
and	O
Examples	O
of	O
dividing	O
Words	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
Rules	O
for	O
true	O
Spelling	O
,	O
Reading	O
,	O
and	O
Writing	O
of	O
English	O
,	O
by	O
way	O
of	O
Question	O
and	O
Answer	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
Two	O
Tables	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
useful	O
Words	O
,	O
whose	O
Spelling	O
or	O
Sense	O
,	O
may	O
be	O
mistaken	O
.	O
Also	O
Christian	O
Names	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
By	O
J.	O
P.	O
M.	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
fifth	O
Edition	O
with	O
Additions	O
.	O
Price	O
9	O
d.	O
The	O
Greatness	O
of	O
the	O
Soul	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Unspeakableness	O
of	O
the	O
Loss	O
thereof	O
;	O
with	O
the	O
Causes	O
of	O
the	O
Losing	O
it	O
.	O
First	O
preached	O
in	O
Pioners-Hall	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
enlarged	O
,	O
and	O
published	O
for	O
good	O
.	O
By	O
John	B-pers
Bunyan	I-pers
.	O
The	O
2d	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
1	O
s.	O
Also	O
at	O
the	O
said	O
Shop	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
Sold	O
to	O
all	O
Stationers	O
and	O
School-masters	O
in	O
London	O
and	O
Country	O
,	O
Pieces	O
for	O
Christmas	O
,	O
Easter	O
and	O
Whitside	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
by	O
wholesale	O
and	O
retale	O
,	O
curiously	O
engraved	O
on	O
Copper-plates	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
King	O
George	O
the	O
II	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
Jerusalem	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
The	O
Temple	O
of	O
Solomon	O
.	O
4	O
.	O
Geometry	O
.	O
5	O
.	O
Adam	O
and	O
Eve	O
in	O
the	O
Garden	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
Human	O
hanged	O
.	O
7	O
.	O
Hunting-Piece	O
.	O
8	O
.	O
Grammar	O
and	O
Writing-School	O
.	O
9	O
.	O
Christ	O
's	O
Burial	O
.	O
10	O
.	O
The	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
's	O
Show	O
.	O
11	O
Moses	O
in	O
the	O
Ark	O
of	O
Bull-rushes	O
.	O
12	O
History	O
of	O
Tobit	O
.	O
13	O
Christ	O
's	O
Ascension	O
.	O
14	O
The	O
seven	O
Sciences	O
.	O
15	O
Derallis	O
and	O
Fawnis	O
.	O
16	O
History	O
of	O
Judith	O
and	O
.	O
17	O
The	O
four	O
Evangalists	O
.	O
18	O
Scool-Ball	O
.	O
19	O
Joseph	O
flying	O
into	O
Egypt	O
.	O
20	O
Crucifixion	O
;	O
And	O
many	O
others	O
in	O
whole	O
Sheets	O
and	O
half	O
Sheets	O
:	O
Likewise	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
have	O
an	O
Klegiac	O
Poem	O
in	O
Commemoration	O
of	O
his	O
late	O
Most	O
Sacred	O
Majesty	O
K.	O
George	O
,	O
engraven	O
,	O
Price	O
6	O
d.	O
Also	O
Gospel	O
Mystery	O
Emblematically	O
illustrated	O
,	O
engraven	O
on	O
a	O
large	O
Copper-plate	O
,	O
Price	O
6	O
d.	O
This	O
Day	O
is	O
publish	O
'd	O
,	O
CATO	O
Condemn	O
'd	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
the	O
Case	O
and	O
History	O
of	O
Self-Murder	O
,	O
argu	O
'd	O
and	O
Display	O
'd	O
at	O
large	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Principles	O
of	O
Reason	O
,	O
Justice	O
,	O
Law	O
,	O
Relagion	O
,	O
Fortitude	O
,	O
Love	O
of	O
ourselves	O
and	O
our	O
Country	O
,	O
and	O
Example	O
;	O
A	O
Solution	O
of	O
this	O
Problem	O
,	O
whether	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
Sense	O
,	O
Goodness	O
,	O
and	O
Courage	O
,	O
ever	O
did	O
,	O
or	O
can	O
,	O
Kill	O
Himself	O
?	O
Particularly	O
calculated	O
to	O
prevent	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
English	O
Nation	O
;	O
Occasion	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
of	O
Gray	O
's	O
Inn	O
Stabbing	O
Himself	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1730	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Instances	O
.	O
A	O
Theological	O
Lecture	O
,	O
deliver	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Oratory	O
in	O
Lincoln's-Inn	O
Fields	O
.	O
By	O
J.	O
Henley	B-pers
,	O
M.	B-pers
A	I-pers
.	I-pers
Publish	O
'd	O
that	O
at	O
the	O
Request	O
of	O
the	O
Hearers	O
.	O
Sold	O
by	O
J	O
.	O
Marshal	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
in	O
Newgate-Street	O
.	O
A	O
speedy	O
Cure	O
for	O
the	O
ITCH	O
,	O
At	O
the	O
Crown	O
and	O
Ball	O
in	O
George's-Court	O
in	O
St.	O
John's-Lane	O
,	O
near	O
Hicks's-Hall	O
,	O
is	O
Sold	O
,	O
A	O
WATER	O
which	O
perfectly	O
cures	O
the	O
ITCH	O
,	O
or	O
Itching	O
Humour	O
in	O
any	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
having	O
no	O
offensive	O
Scent	O
;	O
and	O
hath	O
been	O
prov	O
'd	O
by	O
many	O
Years	O
Experience	O
:	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Bottle	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
.	O
Prepared	O
by	O
A	O
.	O
Downing	O
,	O
Chymist	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
same	O
Place	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
,	O
The	O
true	O
Essence	O
or	O
Spirits	O
of	O
SCURVY-GRASS	O
,	O
both	O
Purging	O
and	O
Plain	O
,	O
most	O
Excellent	O
in	O
all	O
Degrees	O
of	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
,	O
at	O
8	O
d.	O
a	O
Bottle	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Great	O
Elixir	O
of	O
Life	O
,	O
called	O
DAFFY	O
's	O
ELIXIR	O
,	O
truly	O
prepared	O
from	O
the	O
best	O
Ingredients	O
,	O
very	O
useful	O
in	O
all	O
Families	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Half-pint	O
.	O
This	O
Day	O
is	O
Published	O
,	O
The	O
Fourth	O
Edition	O
of	O
A	O
PRACTICAL	O
TREATISE	O
;	O
Or	O
,	O
Second	O
Thoughts	O
on	O
the	O
Consequences	O
of	O
the	O
Venereal	O
Disease	O
,	O
in	O
Three	O
Parts	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
I	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Simple	O
Gonorrhoea	O
,	O
Gleets	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Weaknesses	O
,	O
whether	O
from	O
Venereal	O
Embraces	O
,	O
Self-pollution	O
,	O
improperly	O
called	O
Onanism	O
,	O
or	O
Natural	O
Imbecility	O
.	O
II	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Virulent	O
Gonorrhoea	O
,	O
or	O
Clap	O
.	O
III	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Venereal	O
Lues	O
,	O
or	O
Grand	O
Pox	O
.	O
Wherein	O
are	O
plainly	O
show	O
'd	O
the	O
exact	O
Degrees	O
of	O
Difference	O
;	O
with	O
their	O
Signs	O
,	O
Symptoms	O
,	O
Prognosticks	O
,	O
and	O
Cures	O
in	O
all	O
Cases	O
,	O
that	O
Beginnings	O
,	O
Progress	O
,	O
and	O
fatal	O
Periods	O
,	O
when	O
neglected	O
or	O
unskilfully	O
managed	O
;	O
and	O
how	O
their	O
absolute	O
Cure	O
,	O
without	O
Violence	O
or	O
Injury	O
,	O
is	O
compleated	O
.	O
With	O
proper	O
and	O
effectual	O
Remedies	O
,	O
in	O
their	O
several	O
Stages	O
,	O
prescribed	O
and	O
recommended	O
therein	O
.	O
With	O
some	O
Remarks	O
on	O
that	O
preposterous	O
way	O
of	O
Venary	O
with	O
Machines	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
a	O
plain	O
Discovery	O
of	O
the	O
Dangers	O
(	O
tho	O
'	O
little	O
expected	O
)	O
which	O
attend	O
that	O
vile	O
practice	O
.	O
Also	O
many	O
other	O
useful	O
Discoveries	O
relating	O
to	O
Infections	O
in	O
both	O
Sexes	O
,	O
not	O
before	O
taken	O
Notice	O
of	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
annexed	O
,	O
a	O
Vindication	O
of	O
the	O
practice	O
of	O
Salivating	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Whole	O
fitted	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
for	O
the	O
Advantage	O
of	O
Patients	O
as	O
young	O
Practitioners	O
.	O
By	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
CAM	I-pers
,	O
M.	O
D.	O
London	O
,	O
Printed	O
for	O
the	O
Author	O
;	O
and	O
sold	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
Bow-Church-Yard	O
;	O
also	O
by	O
G.	O
Strahan	O
in	O
Corn-hill	O
;	O
E.	O
Midwinter	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-Yard	O
;	O
T.	O
Corbet	O
,	O
at	O
Addison	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
without	O
Temple-Bar	O
;	O
C.	O
King	O
in	O
Westminster-Hall	O
;	O
and	O
J.	O
Hodges	O
on	O
London-Bridge	O
.	O
Price	O
stick	O
'd	O
2	O
s.	O
bound	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
To	O
Distillers	O
,	O
Jonthan	O
Read	O
Chymist	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
White-Swan	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
in	O
New-street-square	O
,	O
between	O
Shoe-Lane	O
and	O
Ferter-Lane	O
,	O
Prepares	O
and	O
Sells	O
a	O
true	O
Calcination	O
of	O
TARTAR	O
,	O
which	O
has	O
given	O
a	O
general	O
Satisfaction	O
,	O
by	O
cleansing	O
Malt-Spirits	O
from	O
all	O
their	O
rid	O
Flavour	O
,	O
rendering	O
them	O
soft	O
,	O
sweet	O
,	O
and	O
pleasant	O
,	O
fit	O
for	O
any	O
Mixture	O
,	O
improving	O
every	O
Day	O
it	O
upon	O
Trial	O
,	O
it	O
does	O
not	O
answer	O
the	O
Money	O
shall	O
be	O
repaid	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
Six	O
Pounds	O
are	O
sufficient	O
for	O
a	O
Pipe	O
,	O
and	O
require	O
but	O
one	O
Distillation	O
.	O
Price	O
Fourteen	O
Pence	O
per	O
Pound	O
Plantation-Office	O
,	O
kept	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
Agent	O
for	O
Merchants	O
,	O
Next	O
Door	O
to	O
the	O
Cutler	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
Castle-Alley	O
,	O
behind	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
London	O
,	O
a	O
Board	O
of	O
Directions	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
.	O
Several	O
hundreds	O
of	O
good	O
Countrymen	O
,	O
and	O
Servants	O
of	O
all	O
Trades	O
,	O
are	O
wanted	O
for	O
Jamaica	O
directly	O
,	O
Ships	O
will	O
Sail	O
every	O
Week	O
for	O
Jamaica	O
.	O
Good	O
able	O
Carpenters	O
,	O
Bricklayers	O
,	O
Wheelwrights	O
,	O
Blacksmiths	O
,	O
Sawyers	O
and	O
Coopers	O
,	O
shall	O
have	O
twenty-five	O
Pounds	O
yearly	O
Wages	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
all	O
Men	O
Servants	O
that	O
will	O
go	O
to	O
Jamaica	O
,	O
shall	O
be	O
entertained	O
every	O
Day	O
,	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
Vivant	O
Rex	O
&	O
Regina	O
.	O
To	O
all	O
Masters	O
of	O
Ships	O
,	O
Country-Shopkeepers	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
this	O
publick	O
Notice	O
is	O
given	O
.	O
THAT	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
DICEY	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Conjunction	O
with	O
Mr.	O
BENJAMIN	B-pers
OKELL	I-pers
(	O
to	O
whom	O
a	O
Royal	O
Patent	O
is	O
granted	O
)	O
THOMAS	B-pers
COBB	I-pers
,	O
(	O
in	O
Right	O
of	O
ELIZABETH	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
late	O
Widow	O
of	O
Mr.	O
CLUER	O
)	O
and	O
ROBERT	B-pers
RAIKES	I-pers
,	O
continue	O
,	O
and	O
jointly	O
carry	O
on	O
the	O
preparing	O
and	O
vending	O
,	O
both	O
Wholesale	O
and	O
Retail	O
,	O
that	O
excellent	O
Medicine	O
call	O
'd	O
,	O
Dr.	O
BATEMAN	O
's	O
PECTORAL	O
DROPS	O
,	O
at	O
their	O
Warehouse	O
against	O
the	O
South	O
Door	O
of	O
Bow	O
Church	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
farther	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
Church-Yard	O
from	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
London	O
;	O
at	O
which	O
Place	O
(	O
and	O
no	O
other	O
in	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
)	O
Retailers	O
may	O
be	O
furnish	O
'd	O
,	O
with	O
good	O
Allowance	O
for	O
Profit	O
,	O
by	O
directing	O
for	O
or	O
sending	O
to	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
DICEY	I-pers
or	O
THOMAS	B-pers
COBB	I-pers
and	O
Company	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
These	O
DROPS	O
carry	O
off	O
the	O
most	O
violent	O
Fever	O
,	O
if	O
taken	O
in	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
Remedies	O
for	O
those	O
that	O
are	O
afflicted	O
with	O
the	O
present	O
Distempers	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Coughs	O
,	O
Colds	O
,	O
intermitting	O
Fevers	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
It	O
gives	O
present	O
Ease	O
in	O
the	O
most	O
racking	O
Pains	O
of	O
the	O
Gout	O
and	O
Rheumatism	O
,	O
they	O
have	O
brought	O
away	O
Gravel	O
and	O
Stones	O
almost	O
as	O
big	O
as	O
Horse	O
Beans	O
from	O
divers	O
Persons	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
restored	O
Thousands	O
of	O
poor	O
Infants	O
to	O
their	O
Strength	O
and	O
Liveliness	O
,	O
that	O
have	O
been	O
reduced	O
to	O
meer	O
Skeletons	O
.	O
They	O
never	O
fail	O
giving	O
Ease	O
in	O
the	O
most	O
violent	O
Pains	O
of	O
the	O
Body	O
and	O
Limbs	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
Ailments	O
of	O
the	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
Medicines	O
in	O
all	O
manner	O
of	O
Consumptions	O
.	O
Sold	O
at	O
One	O
Shilling	O
per	O
Bottle	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
is	O
contained	O
three	O
Doses	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
same	O
Place	O
you	O
may	O
have	O
Gratis	O
,	O
a	O
Book	O
of	O
Certificates	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
you	O
'll	O
find	O
more	O
Cures	O
than	O
can	O
be	O
produc	O
'd	O
from	O
any	O
one	O
Medicine	O
,	O
since	O
the	O
first	O
Use	O
of	O
Physick	O
.	O
Lately	O
Publish	O
'd	O
,	O
THE	O
Hermit	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
The	O
unparallell	O
'd	O
Sufferings	O
and	O
surprising	O
Adventures	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Philip	B-pers
Quarll	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Englishman	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
lately	O
discovered	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Dorrington	O
,	O
a	O
Bristol	O
Merchant	O
,	O
upon	O
an	O
uninhabited	O
Island	O
in	O
the	O
South	O
Sea	O
;	O
where	O
he	O
has	O
lived	O
above	O
Fifty	O
Years	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
human	O
Assistance	O
,	O
still	O
continues	O
to	O
reside	O
,	O
and	O
will	O
not	O
come	O
away	O
.	O
Containing	B-pers
,	O
I	B-pers
.	I-pers
His	O
Conferences	O
with	O
Those	O
who	O
found	O
him	O
out	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
recited	O
the	O
most	O
material	O
Circumstances	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
;	O
as	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
born	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
educated	O
by	O
the	O
charitable	O
Contribution	O
of	O
a	O
Lady	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
Prentice	O
to	O
a	O
Locksmith	O
.	O
II	O
.	O
How	O
he	O
left	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
with	O
a	O
notorious	O
House-breaker	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
hanged	O
;	O
how	O
after	O
this	O
Escape	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Sea	O
a	O
Cabbin-Boy	O
,	O
married	O
a	O
famous	O
Where	O
,	O
listed	O
himself	O
a	O
common	O
Soldier	O
,	O
turned	O
Singing-Master	O
,	O
and	O
married	O
three	O
Wives	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
tried	O
and	O
condemned	O
at	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
.	O
III	O
.	O
How	O
he	O
was	O
pardoned	O
by	O
King	O
Charles	B-pers
II	I-pers
.	O
turned	O
Merchant	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
shipwracked	O
on	O
this	O
desolate	O
Island	O
on	O
the	O
Coast	O
of	O
Mexico	O
.	O
With	O
a	O
curious	O
Map	O
of	O
the	O
Island	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Cuts	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
B.	O
Creake	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Red	O
Bible	O
in	O
A-Mary-Lane	O
,	O
Ludgate-Street	O
,	O
near	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
Selleth	O
Bibles	O
and	O
Common-Prayers	O
,	O
French	O
or	O
English	O
,	O
of	O
all	O
Sorts	O
and	O
Sizes	O
,	O
with	O
Cuts	O
or	O
without	O
,	O
Rul	O
'd	O
or	O
Unrul	O
'd	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
Sorts	O
of	O
Bindings	O
;	O
also	O
Books	O
of	O
Devotion	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Sacrament	O
,	O
and	O
School-Books	O
of	O
all	O
Sorts	O
,	O
Wholesale	O
or	O
Retale	O
,	O
at	O
Reasonable	O
Rates	O
.	O
He	O
likewise	O
sells	O
Books	O
in	O
all	O
Faculties	O
,	O
as	O
History	O
,	O
Divinity	O
,	O
Law	O
,	O
Physick	O
,	O
Poetry	O
,	O
Plays	O
,	O
Musick	O
,	O
Mathematicks	O
,	O
Husbandry	O
,	O
Architecture	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
And	O
buyeth	O
any	O
Library	O
or	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Old	O
Books	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
same	O
Place	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
all	O
Sorts	O
of	O
Mill-Boards	O
for	O
the	O
Use	O
of	O
Bookbinders	O
,	O
Packers	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
at	O
16	O
s.	O
per	O
100	O
Weight	O
.	O
WHereas	O
I	B-pers
JOHN	I-pers
FREEMAN	I-pers
,	O
dwelling	O
in	O
Turn-wheel-Lane	O
,	O
Cannon-Street	O
,	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Beecher	O
,	O
Salter	O
,	O
have	O
been	O
for	O
10	O
Years	O
periodically	O
troubled	O
with	O
windy	O
Eructations	O
and	O
four	O
Belchings	O
;	O
likewise	O
a	O
Pain	O
that	O
pierced	O
through	O
my	O
very	O
Back	O
and	O
Loins	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Loss	O
of	O
Appetite	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
Faculty	O
of	O
Physick	O
,	O
without	O
obtaining	O
any	O
lasting	O
Relief	O
,	O
at	O
length	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
the	O
numerous	O
Cures	O
perform	O
'd	O
by	O
Mr.	O
JOHN	B-pers
MOORE	I-pers
,	O
Apothecary	O
,	O
At	O
the	O
Pestle	O
and	O
Mortar	O
in	O
Lawrence	O
Pountney	O
's	O
Lane	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
Great	O
Gates	O
on	O
the	O
Left-hand	O
from	O
Cannon-street	O
,	O
I	O
apply	O
'd	O
myself	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
has	O
effectually	O
cured	O
me	O
:	O
And	O
I	O
desire	O
this	O
may	O
be	O
published	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
this	O
only	O
Reason	O
,	O
that	O
others	O
afflicted	O
in	O
the	O
like	O
Manner	O
,	O
may	O
know	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
Relief	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
done	O
.	O
Witness	O
my	O
Hand	O
.	O
Octob	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
1730.	O
JOHN	B-pers
FREEMAN	I-pers
.	O
Note	O
,	O
The	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
is	O
removed	O
at	O
,	O
or	O
near	O
Chyrurgeon	O
's	O
Hall	O
,	O
Silver-street	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
aforesaid	O
JOHN	B-pers
MOORE	I-pers
,	O
has	O
lately	O
prepared	O
two	O
Anti-scorbutick	O
Medicines	O
,	O
being	O
Pills	O
and	O
a	O
Spirit	O
,	O
which	O
excel	O
any	O
Thing	O
yet	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Publick	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Purge	O
given	O
at	O
proper	O
Times	O
with	O
it	O
:	O
It	O
expels	O
the	O
numerous	O
Trains	O
of	O
scorbutick	O
Symptoms	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
the	O
Hypochondriac	O
and	O
Hysteric	O
Illnesses	O
have	O
their	O
Source	O
from	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
,	O
it	O
relieves	O
them	O
;	O
it	O
alters	O
and	O
changes	O
all	O
the	O
Juices	O
in	O
the	O
Human	O
Body	O
;	O
thins	O
the	O
Leutor	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
that	O
fray	O
,	O
viscid	O
,	O
congulated	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Blood	O
,	O
which	O
obstructs	O
the	O
Capillary	O
Vessels	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
Chilness	O
in	O
the	O
extream	O
Parts	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
Heat	O
in	O
Hypochondriac	O
and	O
Hysteric	O
Paroxysms	O
,	O
renovates	O
the	O
Blood	O
,	O
restores	O
decay	O
'd	O
Nature	O
,	O
chears	O
the	O
Heart	O
,	O
revives	O
the	O
Spirits	O
,	O
and	O
opens	O
Obstructions	O
of	O
the	O
Viscera	O
;	O
gives	O
Rest	O
to	O
weary	O
,	O
tired	O
,	O
and	O
worn	O
out	O
Bodies	O
;	O
it	O
invigerates	O
and	O
inkindles	O
again	O
the	O
almost	O
extinguished	O
,	O
natural	O
innate	O
Heat	O
,	O
making	O
the	O
vital	O
Flame	O
to	O
burn	O
clear	O
,	O
removing	O
Weaknesses	O
and	O
Indispositions	O
,	O
and	O
restoring	O
the	O
pristine	O
Health	O
.	O
The	O
Symptoms	O
are	O
,	O
cutaneous	O
Eruptions	O
,	O
as	O
red	O
,	O
yellow	O
,	O
or	O
black	O
Spots	O
upon	O
the	O
Arms	O
and	O
Legs	O
,	O
as	O
small	O
as	O
Flea-bites	O
,	O
sometimes	O
as	O
large	O
as	O
a	O
Grown-piece	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
the	O
Limbs	O
are	O
beset	O
with	O
rough	O
,	O
scaly	O
Swellings	O
;	O
os	O
there	O
is	O
an	O
itching	O
of	O
the	O
Skin	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
frequently	O
taken	O
for	O
what	O
is	O
vulgarly	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Itch	O
.	O
The	O
Scurvy	O
