TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
ON	O
Thursday	O
the	O
25th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
26th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
27th	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
May	O
1732	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Fifth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Fifth	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
CHILD	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1732	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
V.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
ROBERTS	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Oxford-Arms	O
in	O
Warwick-Lane	O
.	O
M	O
,	O
DCC	O
,	O
XXXII	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
Six	O
Pence	O
.	O
)	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
CHILD	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Page	O
;	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Cummins	I-pers
;	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	B-pers
Urlin	I-pers
,	O
Deputy-Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hargrove	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Leteux	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Cooms	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Humphries	I-pers
,	O
Simon	B-pers
Bockham	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Areskin	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hinds	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Stroud	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Witherington	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
,	O
Josiah	B-pers
Wallis	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Beale	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Coxson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Herring	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Juby	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Swan	I-pers
.	O
1.	O
John	B-pers
Fuller	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Margaret	I-place
New-Fish-street	I-place
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Philip	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Simon	B-pers
Slater	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
the	B-pers
Younger	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Younger	O
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
's	O
Footman	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
being	O
miss	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
examin	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Compting-house	O
,	O
lifted	O
up	O
the	O
Lid	O
of	O
the	O
Desk	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Guinea	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
2.	O
Mary	B-pers
Bluck	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
2	O
Silver-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
1	O
Enamell	O
'd	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6s	O
.	O
1	O
Snuff-box	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3s	O
.	O
2	O
Aprons	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Hood	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Godwin	I-pers
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
,	O
she	O
made	O
an	O
excuse	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
return	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
miss	O
'd	O
soon	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
following	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Aprons	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
2	O
Spoons	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Tuns	O
in	O
Long-lane	O
,	O
West-Smithfield	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
;	O
she	O
bore	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
before	O
she	O
committed	O
this	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
3	O
,	O
4	O
Edward	B-pers
Spaule	I-pers
and	O
Daniel	B-pers
Lightfoot	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
George	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
14	O
Chissels	O
,	O
an	O
Ax	O
,	O
a	O
Gouge	O
,	O
2	O
Gimblets	O
,	O
2	O
Hammers	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Stones	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Slack	I-pers
.	O
An	O
Ax	O
,	O
an	O
Iron-square	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Pincers	O
,	O
Chissels	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lindsey	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
Lock	O
,	O
2	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Nails	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Sparks	I-pers
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutors	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
Carpenter	O
s	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Work	O
at	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Well-Close-Square	B-place
.	O
They	O
left	O
their	O
Tools	O
there	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
lock	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
again	O
on	O
Monday	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
the	O
Lock	O
taken	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
Tools	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
They	O
could	O
not	O
Work	O
without	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Alehouse	O
;	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Lightfoot	O
came	O
into	O
a	O
Hog-butchers	O
Yard	O
with	O
2	O
Axes	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Iron	O
Square	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
set	O
down	O
by	O
a	O
Tub	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
without	O
saying	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
The	O
Hog-butcher	O
's	O
Men	O
at	O
first	O
thought	O
that	O
the	O
Capenters	O
were	O
coming	O
there	O
to	O
work	O
;	O
but	O
seeing	O
Lightfoot	O
come	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
saunter	O
about	O
the	O
Gate	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
that	O
Fellow	O
is	O
a	O
Thief	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
Lightfoot	O
curs	O
'd	O
and	O
swore	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
.	O
When	O
presently	O
a	O
Man	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Carpenters	O
Tools	O
were	O
stolen	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Well-Close-Square	O
.	O
The	O
Butchers	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
Spaule	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Leather-Apron	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
a	O
Nail	O
Bag	O
at	O
his	O
Back	O
.	O
The	O
Butchers	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Man	O
divided	O
themselves	O
,	O
and	O
follow	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
a	O
Distance	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
surround	O
'em	O
unawares	O
.	O
Two	O
Boys	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
going	O
from	O
Shadwell	O
to	O
White-Chapel	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
cross	O
a	O
Field	O
,	O
and	O
stop	O
by	O
the	O
Side	O
of	O
a	O
Rail	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
stoop	O
'd	O
down	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
digging	O
.	O
The	O
Butchers	O
coming	O
up	O
,	O
the	O
Boys	O
directed	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
whom	O
they	O
took	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
the	O
Tools	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
Hole	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
had	O
hid	O
'em	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
in	O
Spaule	O
's	O
Apron	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
lying	O
about	O
a	O
Yard	O
from	O
the	O
Hole	O
.	O
Notice	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Alehouse	O
were	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
were	O
drinking	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
came	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
their	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
5.	O
Mary	B-pers
Bradley	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Brudenell	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
George	I-place
Hanover-Square	I-place
,	O
a	O
Silver-Spoon	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Nutmeg-grater	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
.	O
Between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Ellis	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
Grosvenor-Street	B-place
,	O
and	O
order	O
'd	O
some	O
Tea	O
for	O
my	O
Lord	O
Pembroke	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
left	O
alone	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
the	O
Tea-spoon	O
and	O
the	O
Nutmeg-grater	O
lay	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
miss	O
'd	O
soon	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
.	O
After	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
my	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
by	O
my	O
Ld	O
Pembroke	O
's	O
Steward	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Lac'd-head	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
Room	O
in	O
the	O
Hay-Market	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
Tea-spoon	O
;	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
a	O
Nutmeg-grater	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Hodges	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
this	O
Grater	O
to	O
my	O
Father	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
4	O
s.	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Grater	O
and	O
Spoon	O
have	O
no	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
I	O
wont	O
take	O
upon	O
me	O
to	O
swear	O
they	O
are	O
mine	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
.	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
Spoon	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
Mistress	O
(	O
Mrs.	O
Ellis	O
's	O
)	O
and	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
Grater	O
to	O
be	O
hers	O
by	O
these	O
Dents	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Spoon	O
and	O
Grater	O
were	O
my	O
own	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
other	O
handsome	O
Things	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
about	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
none	O
of	O
your	O
poor	O
beggarly	O
inferior	O
sort	O
of	O
People	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
5	O
.	O
Mary	O
Bradley	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
a	O
Cambrick	O
Head	O
Laced	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
Laced	O
Tucker	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Thomas	B-pers
Earl	I-pers
of	I-pers
Pembroke	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Fitz-Williams	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
Friday	O
before	O
the	O
last	O
Birth-Day	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Work	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Laserre	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
pulling	O
this	O
Brussel	O
Lace	O
Head	O
and	O
Tucker	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
Mrs.	O
Laserre	O
if	O
she	O
knew	O
any	O
Body	O
that	O
would	O
buy	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
Price	O
was	O
14	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Weaver	O
,	O
my	O
Lady	O
Shelurn	O
's	O
Woman	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Peach	O
,	O
my	O
Lady	O
Pembrok	O
's	O
Woman	O
hearing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Laserre	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
her	O
Lady	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
Head	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Laserre	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
tell	O
her	O
that	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
waited	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
she	O
liked	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Price	O
,	O
she	O
might	O
be	O
a	O
Customer	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Peach	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
'd	O
swear	O
that	O
that	O
was	O
her	O
Lady	O
's	O
Head	O
;	O
she	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
her	O
the	O
lowest	O
Price	O
was	O
twelve	O
Guineas	O
.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Peack	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Fitz	O
.	O
Williams	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
buying	O
the	O
Head	O
.	O
I	O
hear	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
have	O
a	O
fine	O
Head	O
to	O
dispose	O
off	O
;	O
Yes	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
And	O
what	O
's	O
the	O
Price	O
?	O
Twelve	O
Guineas	O
.	O
Will	O
not	O
Eight	O
do	O
?	O
No	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Constable	O
(	O
who	O
waited	O
below	O
)	O
came	O
up	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
of	O
my	O
Acquaintance	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
Head	O
to	O
dispose	O
off	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
of	O
no	O
Body	O
so	O
proper	O
to	O
apply	O
to	O
on	O
that	O
Occasion	O
as	O
Mrs.	O
Laserre	O
my	O
Mantua-maker	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
who	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
.	O
Fitz-Williams	O
has	O
known	O
me	O
these	O
five	O
Years	O
.	O
Fitz-Williams	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
ever	O
knew	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
her	O
before	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
my	O
Lady	O
Shelburn	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
left	O
all	O
her	O
Cloaths	O
to	O
her	O
Woman	O
,	O
from	O
whom	O
she	O
had	O
this	O
Head	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
The	O
same	O
Day	O
that	O
the	O
Head	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
we	O
miss	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Lord	O
Pembroke	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
Mrs.	O
Peach	O
,	O
my	O
Lady	O
's	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
directed	O
her	O
Upstairs	O
.	O
Court	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
Witnesses	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
no	O
Opportunity	O
of	O
sending	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
Newgate	O
before	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
and	O
since	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
kept	O
close	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Condemn	O
'd	O
Hold	O
,	O
and	O
none	O
of	O
my	O
Friends	O
have	O
been	O
allowed	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Then	O
you	O
have	O
broke	O
Jail	O
it	O
seems	O
.	O
The	O
Keeper	O
had	O
reason	O
to	O
take	O
Care	O
of	O
you	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Broke	O
Jail	O
!	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
only	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Nichols	O
.	O
She	O
made	O
her	O
escape	O
,	O
disguis	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
of	O
a	O
Woman	O
who	O
came	O
frequently	O
to	O
her	O
in	O
Prison	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
another	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
secur	O
'd	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Condemn	O
'd	O
Hold	O
;	O
but	O
none	O
of	O
her	O
Acquaintance	O
were	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Liberty	O
of	O
speaking	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
6.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Holms	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Pratt	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	O
Brudenell	O
,	O
alias	O
Bradley	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
in	O
White-Chappel	O
Parish	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
Three	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
Mary	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
being	O
then	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
;	O
3	O
Silver	O
Thimbles	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
a	O
Cambrick	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
Guineas	O
,	O
2	O
half	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
35	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Linen	O
Shop	O
in	O
White-Lion-street	B-place
in	O
Goodman's-Fields	B-place
,	O
one	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Street	O
comes	O
into	O
Rosemary-Lane	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
Lodge	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
for	O
a	O
Day	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
pretending	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
Holland	O
with	O
Captain	O
Allen	O
,	O
and	O
only	O
waited	O
for	O
the	O
Ship	O
's	O
Sailing	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
recommended	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Baily	O
,	O
my	O
next	O
Door	O
Neighbour	O
.	O
About	O
Noon	O
I	O
had	O
Occasion	O
to	O
look	O
in	O
my	O
Drawers	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
Money	O
and	O
Goods	O
were	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
lock	O
'd	O
my	O
Chamber	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
down	O
Stairs	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
Chamber	O
to	O
mine	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
a	O
Man	O
came	O
to	O
them	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Baily	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
a	O
Coach	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
me	O
5	O
s.	O
for	O
five	O
Days	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
all	O
three	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
bid	O
the	O
Coachman	O
drive	O
to	O
St.	O
James's-street	O
.	O
About	O
Ten	O
at	O
Night	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
opening	O
the	O
Drawer	O
to	O
put	O
some	O
Money	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
Robb	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Spoon	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
was	O
none	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
lent	O
10	O
s.	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Baily	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
White-Lyon	O
Alehouse	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Maccartney	I-pers
(	O
with	O
whom	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
Acquaintance	O
)	O
brought	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
Lodging	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Bradley	O
went	O
for	O
the	O
Mistress	O
,	O
and	O
Holms	O
for	O
the	O
Maid	O
.	O
The	O
Mistress	O
had	O
(	O
as	O
she	O
still	O
has	O
)	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
scurvy	O
Humour	O
broke	O
out	O
in	O
her	O
Face	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
came	O
by	O
a	O
Surfeit	O
that	O
she	O
got	O
with	O
Dancing	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
for	O
Holland	O
,	O
to	O
try	O
if	O
drinking	O
the	O
Waters	O
at	O
the	O
Spaw	O
would	O
do	O
her	O
any	O
good	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
spare	O
Lodging-Room	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
for	O
any	O
more	O
than	O
Maccartney	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
recommended	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Jackson	O
for	O
a	O
Bed	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
used	O
to	O
eat	O
and	O
drink	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
in	O
5	O
Days	O
they	O
run	O
up	O
18	O
s.	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
Money	O
they	O
had	O
till	O
just	O
before	O
they	O
took	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Bradley	O
gave	O
me	O
2	O
Half-Guineas	O
to	O
take	O
my	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
her	O
3	O
s.	O
Maccartney	O
fetch	O
'd	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
2	O
Prisoners	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
Bradley	O
bid	O
the	O
Coachman	O
drive	O
to	O
St.	O
James's-street	O
directly	O
.	O
As	O
it	O
happened	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
so	O
much	O
Notice	O
of	O
the	O
Coachman	O
as	O
to	O
know	O
him	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
wore	O
a	O
blue	O
Coat	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
lame	O
in	O
one	O
Foot	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Shoe	O
was	O
cut	O
to	O
give	O
it	O
Ease	O
.	O
About	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Jackson	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
next	O
Morning	O
in	O
search	O
after	O
the	O
Coachman	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Saracen	O
's	O
Head	O
in	O
Camomile-street	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
what	O
Place	O
he	O
drove	O
those	O
two	O
Women	O
and	O
the	O
Man	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
at	O
first	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
,	O
because	O
they	O
had	O
charged	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
happened	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
.	O
But	O
after	O
a	O
little	O
Talk	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Well	O
,	O
Master	O
,	O
you	O
look	O
like	O
a	O
good	O
honest	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
'll	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
Pot	O
I	O
'll	O
tell	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
carried	O
them	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
,	O
they	O
order	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
drive	O
to	O
Billinsgate	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
took	O
Water	O
for	O
Greenwich	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
Mrs.	O
Jackson	O
of	O
this	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
out	O
the	O
Waterman	O
who	O
carried	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Greenwich	O
.	O
He	O
brought	O
us	O
to	O
the	O
Porter	O
who	O
had	O
help	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
Lodging	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Jackson	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Justice	O
for	O
a	O
Warrant	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
coming	O
back	O
,	O
Maccartney	O
happened	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
ran	O
to	O
the	O
Waterside	O
,	O
took	O
Oars	O
for	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
escaped	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
with	O
'em	O
both	O
.	O
We	O
searched	O
'em	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
find	O
nothing	O
about	O
'em	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Jackson	O
could	O
swear	O
to	O
but	O
this	O
Shilling	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Jackson	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
this	O
Shilling	O
to	O
be	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
that	O
I	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Drawer	O
;	O
it	O
looks	O
blackish	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
it	O
had	O
lain	O
in	O
Gun-powder	O
before	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
remember	O
I	O
scupled	O
it	O
and	O
made	O
this	O
Scratch	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
good	O
,	O
and	O
besides	O
,	O
here	O
's	O
a	O
little	O
Dent	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
Edge	O
.	O
Bradley	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
Newgate	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
Holms	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Friend	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
enquired	O
for	O
a	O
Lodging	O
.	O
A	O
Woman	O
who	O
was	O
there	O
told	O
us	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Brother	O
Macartney	O
had	O
an	O
Acquaintance	O
who	O
kept	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
,	O
in	O
White-Lyon-street	O
,	O
by	O
Rag-Fair	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
House	O
she	O
believed	O
we	O
might	O
lye	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
thither	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
Room	O
for	O
us	O
,	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Baily	O
,	O
the	O
Man	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
provided	O
us	O
a	O
Lodging	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
lived	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Holms	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
agreed	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Holland	O
with	O
Capt	O
.	O
Allen	O
,	O
but	O
while	O
we	O
waited	O
for	O
the	O
Ship	O
's	O
setting	O
Sail	O
,	O
we	O
happened	O
to	O
quarrel	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
threatned	O
to	O
tell	O
Mrs.	O
Jackson	O
that	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
was	O
resolv	O
'd	O
to	O
leave	O
that	O
Lodging	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
you	O
at	O
first	O
order	O
the	O
Coachman	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
you	O
were	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Hearing	O
,	O
bid	O
him	O
drive	O
to	O
Billingsgate	O
?	O
Bradley	O
.	O
Because	O
at	O
first	O
Mrs.	O
Holms	O
intended	O
t	O
o	O
go	O
to	O
her	O
Sister	O
in	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
,	O
but	O
soon	O
after	O
she	O
chang	O
'd	O
her	O
mind	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
Holms	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Bradley	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
1	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
7.	O
Mary	B-pers
Banister	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Thompson	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Simpson	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Pickering	B-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Pickering	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
George	I-place
Hanover	I-place
Square	I-place
,	O
3	O
Smocks	O
,	O
Value	O
55	O
s.	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Sheet	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pillowbier	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Dame	O
Dorrington	O
Mountague	O
;	O
a	O
Holland	O
Smock	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Ashford	I-pers
,	O
and	O
2	O
Smocks	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Hood	O
,	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Head-cloaths	O
,	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
2	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Squib	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Dame	O
Dorrington	B-pers
Mountague	I-pers
,	O
August	O
18	O
.	O
1729	O
.	O
Sarah	O
Squib	O
.	O
Last	O
August	O
was	O
2	O
Years	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
my	O
Lady	O
Mountague	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
at	O
Board	O
Wages	O
,	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
it	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
at	O
the	O
Parlour	O
Window	O
,	O
Katherine	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
(	O
whom	O
I	O
always	O
thought	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Woman	O
)	O
came	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
a	O
young	O
Woman	O
,	O
just	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
lie	O
with	O
me	O
for	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Nights	O
,	O
till	O
she	O
could	O
provide	O
herself	O
with	O
a	O
Place	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
by	O
no	O
means	O
suffer	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
,	O
for	O
People	O
would	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
let	O
out	O
my	O
Lady	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
Lodgings	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
from	O
Home	O
.	O
But	O
Mrs.	O
Newman	O
would	O
take	O
no	O
Denial	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
at	O
last	O
she	O
over-persuaded	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
staid	O
with	O
me	O
2	O
Days	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
that	O
time	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
as	O
many	O
Lies	O
as	O
this	O
Court	O
would	O
hold	O
,	O
though	O
I	O
believ	O
'd	O
them	O
all	O
at	O
first	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
liv	O
'd	O
at	O
'Squire	O
Goare	O
's	O
in	O
Great	O
Monmouth-street	O
3	O
Years	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Father	O
and	O
Mother	O
had	O
kept	O
the	O
George-Inn	O
in	O
Northampton	O
,	O
but	O
were	O
lately	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
left	O
all	O
they	O
had	O
betwixt	O
her	O
and	O
her	O
Brother	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
Master	O
of	O
a	O
Stage-Coach	O
at	O
the	O
Brook-Bar	O
in	O
Holborn	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
Lady	O
that	O
past	O
by	O
the	O
Window	O
with	O
any	O
thing	O
rich	O
in	O
her	O
Dress	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
Creature	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
such	O
another	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
2d	O
Day	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
her	O
within	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
St.	O
James	O
Market	O
to	O
get	O
something	O
for	O
Dinne	O
,	O
I	O
staid	O
about	O
2	O
Hours	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
Girl	O
had	O
been	O
these	O
to	O
tell	O
her	O
of	O
a	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Dinner	O
till	O
she	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
impudent	O
Face	O
any	O
more	O
till	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
soon	O
found	O
she	O
had	O
robbed	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
her	O
at	O
'Squire	O
Goare	O
's	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
hear	O
nothing	O
of	O
her	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
directed	O
to	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Banister	O
,	O
with	O
whom	O
she	O
had	O
liv	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
whose	O
Name	O
she	O
took	O
upon	O
her	O
self	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
By	O
her	O
means	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Service	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Duncan	O
's	O
Boarding-School	O
at	O
Islington	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
thither	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
late	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
lived	O
there	O
but	O
3	O
Weeks	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
at	O
one	O
Goddard	O
's	O
in	O
St.	O
Mary	O
lx	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
met	O
with	O
a	O
Husband	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
that	O
she	O
robbed	O
Mrs.	O
Kirby	O
before	O
she	O
robbed	O
me	O
.	O
Katherine	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
same	O
Stories	O
as	O
she	O
told	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
her	O
an	O
honest	O
Country	O
Maid	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
I	O
recommended	O
her	O
to	O
lie	O
a	O
Night	O
or	O
two	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Lady	O
Mountague	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Prosecution	O
is	O
set	O
on	O
Foot	O
by	O
my	O
Husband	O
's	O
Relations	O
,	O
on	O
purpose	O
to	O
get	O
rid	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Goddard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
Year	O
,	O
and	O
trusted	O
her	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
with	O
valuable	O
Things	O
,	O
for	O
my	O
Wife	O
takes	O
in	O
Linen	O
to	O
wash	O
for	O
Ladies	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
never	O
mist	O
any	O
thing	O
The	O
Girl	O
has	O
unhappily	O
married	O
the	O
Son	O
of	O
a	O
topping	O
Man	O
(	O
Dr.	O
Pickering	O
of	O
Tunbridge	O
,	O
who	O
keeps	O
his	O
Coach	O
and	O
four	O
)	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
her	O
Husband	O
's	O
Relations	O
heard	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
turned	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
forced	O
for	O
a	O
Livelihood	O
to	O
draw	O
Beer	O
at	O
the	O
George-Alehouse	O
in	O
St.	O
Mary	O
Ax	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
is	O
lately	O
gone	O
Abroad	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
manner	O
?	O
Goddard	O
.	O
To	O
travel	O
as	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
;	O
his	O
Friends	O
have	O
sent	O
him	O
away	O
to	O
keep	O
him	O
from	O
his	O
Wife	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
8	O
,	O
9.	O
John	B-pers
Osborn	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Longmore	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Elliot	I-pers
in	O
an	O
open	O
Field	O
near	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
a	O
Wig	O
,	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Buckles	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Desire	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
examined	O
apart	O
.	O
John	O
Elliot	O
.	O
On	O
Easter-Monday	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
about	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
from	O
Stepney	B-place
towards	O
Shadwell	B-place
;	O
I	O
was	O
followed	O
by	O
4	O
Men	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Sun-Tavern-Fields	B-place
,	O
one	O
of	O
'em	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
flash	O
'd	O
a	O
Pistol	O
close	O
to	O
my	O
Ear	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
stand	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
the	O
others	O
came	O
about	O
me	O
,	O
searched	O
my	O
Pockets	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
5	O
d.	O
robbed	O
me	O
of	O
my	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
,	O
stripped	O
off	O
my	O
Coat	O
and	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
pushed	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
off	O
my	O
Shoes	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
getting	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
when	O
one	O
who	O
stood	O
behind	O
me	O
,	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Osborn	O
,	O
whom	O
I	O
knew	O
(	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
times	O
before	O
)	O
stabbed	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
hand	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
to	O
Hopes	O
they	O
were	O
quite	O
gone	O
;	O
but	O
presently	O
I	O
heard	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
say	O
,	O
Damn	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
knows	O
I	O
'll	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
home	O
thrust	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
somebody	O
came	O
trip	O
,	O
trip	O
,	O
behind	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
turning	O
about	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
was	O
Osborn	O
.	O
He	O
stept	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
stuck	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Breast	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
.	O
I	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
left	O
me	O
again	O
.	O
Two	O
Men	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
after	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
they	O
were	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Gang	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
come	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
alive	O
still	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
called	O
to	O
me	O
I	O
made	O
no	O
Answer	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
soon	O
found	O
they	O
were	O
Friends	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
Care	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
led	O
me	O
home	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
if	O
Longmire	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
those	O
that	O
attack	O
'd	O
you	O
?	O
Elliot	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
but	O
Osborn	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Fleming	I-pers
.	O
The	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
Jemmy	O
Tripland	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
drinking	O
at	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Stepney	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
drinking	O
too	O
;	O
about	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
followed	O
,	O
though	O
with	O
no	O
Thoughts	O
of	O
robbing	O
him	O
;	O
for	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
Design	O
upon	O
another	O
Man	O
who	O
was	O
going	O
over	O
the	O
Fields	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
sitting	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Bench	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
with	O
some	O
others	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
spent	O
all	O
his	O
Money	O
yet	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
enough	O
left	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
a	O
Crown	O
Bowl	O
of	O
Punch	O
.	O
Upon	O
hearing	O
this	O
,	O
we	O
concluded	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
fittest	O
Man	O
for	O
our	O
Purpose	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
long	O
before	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
3	O
Men	O
and	O
2	O
Women	O
.	O
We	O
followed	O
at	O
a	O
Distance	O
till	O
his	O
Company	O
parted	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
mending	O
our	O
Pace	O
,	O
we	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
Sun-Tavern-Fields	O
and	O
stapp	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
some	O
Half	O
pence	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
Coat	O
and	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
Shoes	O
;	O
we	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
Osborn	O
stabb	O
'd	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
left	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
going	O
quite	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
Osborn	O
said	O
,	O
Damn	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
knows	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
go	O
buk	O
and	O
give	O
him	O
another	O
Stab	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
As	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
off	O
we	O
met	O
2	O
Men	O
who	O
went	O
towards	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
I	O
followed	O
them	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
to	O
where	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lay	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
Matter	O
enough	O
;	O
a	O
Man	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
left	O
'em	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
again	O
to	O
my	O
Companions	O
.	O
Osborn	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
his	O
own	O
ragged	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
it	O
in	O
Stepney-Fields	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
on	O
that	O
as	O
we	O
took	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
His	O
Wife	O
afterwards	O
sold	O
the	O
Coat	O
and	O
Waistcoat	O
in	O
Chick-Lane	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
never	O
tell	O
us	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
with	O
the	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
apprehended	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
my	O
Information	O
the	O
others	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
.	O
This	O
Coat	O
and	O
Waistcoat	O
were	O
all	O
bloody	O
when	O
I	O
first	O
saw	O
them	O
at	O
Osborn	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
.	O
-	O
Townsend	O
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
Coat	O
and	O
Waistcoat	O
at	O
Macdowall	O
's	O
in	O
Chick-Lane	O
,	O
he	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
readily	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Jacobs	I-pers
.	O
I	O
and	O
another	O
were	O
going	O
over	O
Sun-Tavern-Fields	O
,	O
just	O
after	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
3	O
Men	O
ran	O
by	O
us	O
;	O
my	O
Friend	O
said	O
,	O
They	O
seem	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
a	O
plaguy	O
Hurry	O
.	O
Ah	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
they	O
have	O
over	O
staid	O
their	O
time	O
I	O
suppose	O
.	O
Going	O
forward	O
,	O
we	O
saw	O
something	O
white	O
at	O
a	O
little	O
Distance	O
;	O
we	O
stept	O
up	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
Man	O
lying	O
in	O
his	O
Shirt	O
;	O
we	O
call	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
made	O
no	O
Answer	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
suppose	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
to	O
speak	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
soon	O
satisfied	O
him	O
that	O
we	O
were	O
Friends	O
.	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
my	O
Hat	O
and	O
my	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
led	O
him	O
Home	O
to	O
Shadwell-Market	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Fleming	O
.	O
Which	O
of	O
you	O
attack	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
first	O
?	O
Fleming	O
.	O
Tripland	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
took	O
his	O
Money	O
and	O
his	O
Shoes	O
,	O
Longmore	O
took	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
Osborn	O
took	O
his	O
Coat	O
and	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
but	O
gave	O
them	O
Tripland	O
to	O
hold	O
while	O
he	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
stab	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Osborn	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
Fleming	O
nor	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
this	O
Robbery	O
.	O
Longmore	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
Ship	O
but	O
that	O
same	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
Acquaintance	O
with	O
Fleming	O
.	O
Fleming	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
altogether	O
at	O
Stepney	O
all	O
that	O
Day	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Longmore	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Son	O
,	O
Longmore	O
,	O
was	O
mostly	O
at	O
Home	O
all	O
that	O
Monday	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
At	O
what	O
time	O
was	O
he	O
at	O
Home	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
?	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Longmore	I-pers
.	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
came	O
Home	O
about	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
again	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
remember	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
as	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
?	O
E.	O
L.	O
Because	O
it	O
was	O
Easter-Monday	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
And	O
where	O
was	O
he	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
Night	O
?	O
E.	O
L.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
And	O
why	O
ca	O
n't	O
you	O
remember	O
one	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
t'other	O
.	O
E.	O
L.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
at	O
Home	O
then	O
too	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
harmless	O
,	O
half-witted	O
,	O
foolish	O
Lad	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
Longmore	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Osborn	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
8	O
,	O
9	O
.	O
John	O
Osborn	O
,	O
and	O
John	O
Longmore	O
,	O
were	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Joseph	B-pers
Allam	I-pers
in	O
an	O
open	O
Field	O
near	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Wig	O
,	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
and	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
a	O
Woollen	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
Sleeves	O
with	O
Cambrick	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Buckles	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
and	O
15	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
Apr	O
.	O
12	O
.	O
10	O
.	O
And	O
Mary	B-pers
Angel	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Osborn	B-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Osborn	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
afterwards	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
,	O
receiving	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
George	I-place
in	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
and	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Joseph	O
Allam	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
got	O
pretty	O
well	O
in	O
for't	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
Home	O
;	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
way	O
I	O
met	O
some	O
of	O
these	O
Gentlemen	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
Gentlemen	O
?	O
Allam	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
'em	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
sure	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
?	O
Allam	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
who	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
seduced	O
by	O
somebody	O
or	O
other	O
that	O
pretended	O
out	O
of	O
Kindness	O
to	O
shew	O
me	O
a	O
higher	O
way	O
Home	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
got	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
they	O
stripp	O
'd	O
me	O
of	O
my	O
Coat	O
and	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
Shirt	O
,	O
and	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
Sleeves	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
whether	O
they	O
took	O
any	O
Money	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
or	O
whether	O
I	O
had	O
any	O
about	O
me	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Fleming	I-pers
.	O
I	O
and	O
Jemmy	O
Tripland	O
,	O
and	O
Osborn	O
and	O
Longmore	O
,	O
met	O
Moll	O
James	O
and	O
Black	O
Peg	O
in	O
Ratcliff-Highway	O
;	O
they	O
shew	O
'd	O
us	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
just	O
taken	O
it	O
from	O
a	O
Man	O
that	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
us	O
go	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
Women	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
would	O
fain	O
have	O
got	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
Baudy-house	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Three	B-place
Tobacco-Rolls	I-place
and	I-place
Sugar-Loaf	B-place
,	O
but	O
we	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
them	O
.	O
Osborn	O
knew	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
kept	O
a	O
Boarding-School	O
at	O
Poplar	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
telling	O
him	O
we	O
'd	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
shew	O
him	O
the	O
nighest	O
way	O
Home	O
;	O
Osborn	O
took	O
him	O
under	O
one	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
under	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
led	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Fields	O
;	O
Osborn	O
thrust	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
into	O
his	O
Mouth	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
two	O
stripp	O
'd	O
him	O
naked	O
,	O
while	O
Tripland	O
and	O
Longmore	O
stood	O
at	O
a	O
Distance	O
to	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
help	O
'd	O
us	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
to	O
the	O
Black-Boy	B-place
in	O
Well-Street	B-place
,	O
and	O
there	O
Osborn	O
gave	O
them	O
all	O
but	O
the	O
Buckles	O
to	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Angel	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Osborn	O
(	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
to	O
sell	O
for	O
us	O
;	O
Longmore	O
kept	O
the	O
Buckles	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
has	O
them	O
now	O
in	O
his	O
Shoes	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Let	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
see	O
those	O
Buckles	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
Buckles	O
.	O
Fleming	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Angel	I-pers
sold	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
in	O
Chick-Lane	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
sunk	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
us	O
but	O
8	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
the	O
Coat	O
and	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
for	O
the	O
Shoes	O
(	O
they	O
were	O
Wooden-heel	O
'd	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
1	O
s.	O
she	O
spent	O
.	O
We	O
shared	O
the	O
Money	O
equally	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
Half-a-Crown	O
a-piece	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Four	O
Half	O
Crowns	O
are	O
but	O
10s	O
.	O
and	O
you	O
say	O
she	O
gave	O
you	O
10s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
Fleming	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
mistook	O
6	O
d.	O
she	O
gave	O
us	O
but	O
8	O
s.	O
for	O
the	O
Coat	O
and	O
Waistcoat	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
the	O
Discovery	O
the	O
last	O
Day	O
of	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Tripland	I-pers
.	O
We	O
met	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
in	O
Ratcliff-Highway	O
,	O
Fleming	O
and	O
Osborn	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Friends	O
,	O
and	O
led	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Fields	O
and	O
suppos	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
and	O
Longmore	O
stood	O
at	O
a	O
lift	O
Distance	O
to	O
watch	O
.	O
We	O
carried	O
the	O
Things	O
:	O
the	O
Black-Boy	O
in	O
Well-street	O
,	O
where	O
Osborn	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
Angel	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
sold	O
'em	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
us	O
6	O
s.	O
for	O
the	O
Coat	O
and	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
for	O
the	O
Shoes	O
.	O
The	O
Cloaths	O
were	O
worth	O
Half-a-Guinea	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
sunk	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
We	O
divided	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
Share	O
and	O
Share	O
alike	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
Half-a-Crown	O
a	O
piece	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
out	O
of	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
s	O
?	O
Tripland	O
.	O
Six	O
Shillings	O
!	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
6	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Court	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
with	O
the	O
2	O
s.	O
makes	O
but	O
8	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
how	O
then	O
could	O
4	O
of	O
you	O
divide	O
Half-a	O
Crown	O
a-piece	O
?	O
Tripland	O
.	O
A	O
Mistake	O
of	O
6	O
d.	O
will	O
break	O
no	O
Damage	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
But	O
Fleming	O
says	O
it	O
was	O
8	O
s.	O
she	O
gave	O
you	O
for	O
the	O
Coat	O
and	O
Waistcoat	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Osborn	O
.	O
Tripland	O
was	O
convicted	O
here	O
and	O
transported	O
5	O
Years	O
ago	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Ogborn	I-pers
.	O
Tripland	O
.	O
'T	O
is	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
;	O
I	O
sold	O
my	O
self	O
indeed	O
7	O
Years	O
ago	O
at	O
the	O
Black-Boy	O
on	O
London-Bridge	O
.	O
Osborn	O
.	O
I	O
own	O
I	O
am	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
desire	O
to	O
dye	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
Longmore	O
is	O
innocent	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Longmore	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
Ship	O
when	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Call	O
your	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
Longmore	O
.	O
The	O
Ship	O
is	O
now	O
failed	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Witnesses	O
are	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
some	O
to	O
my	O
Reputation	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Longmore	O
six	O
Years	O
,	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
his	O
Mother	O
,	O
who	O
sells	O
old	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Harm	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
Edmund	B-pers
Newsham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
ten	O
Years	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Mother	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
my	O
Room	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Ill	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
always	O
kept	O
good	O
Hours	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
,	O
just	O
Man	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
never	O
hear	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
for	O
a	O
Robbery	O
before	O
this	O
?	O
Newsham	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
New-Prison	O
once	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
a	O
Robbery	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Body	O
appeared	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
And	O
yet	O
you	O
could	O
swear	O
that	O
you	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Arthur	B-pers
Bernfree	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
three	O
Years	O
,	O
he	O
used	O
the	O
Sea	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
Fellow	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
some	O
Suspicions	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Fleming	O
.	O
When	O
Osborn	O
gave	O
the	O
Coat	O
to	O
Mary	O
Angel	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
bloody	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
wash	O
'd	O
it	O
before	O
she	O
sold	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
chaulked	O
the	O
Wig	O
.	O
She	O
gave	O
us	O
6	O
s.	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
afterward	O
,	O
1	O
s.	O
more	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
told	O
us	O
she	O
had	O
sunk	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
said	O
before	O
that	O
she	O
gave	O
you	O
8	O
s.	O
at	O
first	O
.	O
Fleming	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
because	O
she	O
paid	O
2	O
s.	O
for	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
Osborn	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Longmore	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
Angel	O
.	O
11	O
.	O
John	O
Longmore	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Joshua	B-pers
Panton	I-pers
,	O
in	O
an	O
open	O
Place	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
in	O
Whitechapel	B-place
Parish	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
April	O
20	O
.	O
Joshua	B-pers
Panton	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
April	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mile-End	O
with	O
half	O
an	O
Anchor	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
over	O
Whitechappel-Fields	B-place
,	O
in	O
that	O
Field	O
where	O
the	O
Windmill	O
stood	O
formerly	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
paid	O
for	O
my	O
Jobb	O
?	O
It	O
was	O
then	O
near	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
Eight	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
.	O
Presently	O
several	O
Sticks	O
were	O
about	O
my	O
Ears	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Several	O
?	O
Panton	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
attacked	O
by	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Men	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
strike	O
you	O
?	O
Panton	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
struck	O
me	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
times	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
others	O
laid	O
me	O
on	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
he	O
,	O
but	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
others	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
what	O
Resistance	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
swore	O
,	O
Damn	O
him	O
,	O
Does	O
he	O
Rebel	O
?	O
Cut	O
his	O
Eyes	O
out	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
I	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
lost	O
my	O
Watch	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Court	O
.	O
Which	O
of	O
them	O
took	O
your	O
Watch	O
and	O
Money	O
?	O
Panton	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
fast	O
.	O
Court-Fast	O
?	O
Panton	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
Senses	O
left	O
,	O
I	O
lay	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
like	O
a	O
dead	O
Calf	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
dark	O
?	O
Panton	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
Moon-Light	O
?	O
Or	O
were	O
there	O
any	O
Lamps	O
?	O
Panton	O
.	O
Neither	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
open	O
Field	O
it	O
was	O
Light	O
enough	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
his	O
Face	O
as	O
plain	O
as	O
I	O
do	O
now	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Money	O
before	O
Justice	O
Philips	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Watch	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
his	O
Companions	O
had	O
sunk	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
Sunk	O
is	O
a	O
Term	O
of	O
Art	O
among	O
them	O
for	O
conceal	O
'd	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Philips	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
not	O
positive	O
.	O
He	O
described	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
such	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
then	O
swear	O
to	O
him	O
directly	O
.	O
Panton	O
.	O
Nine	O
Days	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
first	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
from	O
my	O
own	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
own	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Man	O
who	O
had	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
taken	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Philips	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
is	O
a	O
little	O
mistaken	O
in	O
that	O
particular	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Gang	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Case	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
were	O
going	O
together	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
standing	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
That	O
's	O
the	O
Man	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
a	O
Constable	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
work	O
'd	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
Ship	O
from	O
the	O
16th	O
to	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
Home	O
every	O
Night	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
worse	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
than	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
ignorant	O
,	O
literate	O
,	O
silly	O
Fellow	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Cunningham	I-pers
.	O
He	O
is	O
an	O
innocent	O
foolish	O
Boy	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
other	O
Misdemeanour	O
.	O
Two	O
or	O
three	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
swore	O
that	O
they	O
knew	O
no	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
12.	O
Robert	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Robertson	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
in	O
Shoreditch	B-place
Parish	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Feather	O
Bed	O
,	O
a	O
Bolster	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
a	O
Porridge	O
Pot	O
,	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Dish	O
,	O
a	O
Plate	O
,	O
two	O
Sauce-pans	O
,	O
three	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
a	O
Chasing-Dish	O
,	O
a	O
Pepper	B-pers
Box	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Drudging	O
Box	O
,	O
a	O
Bottle	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
April	O
26	O
.	O
about	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
Two	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
.	O
Henry	O
Watkins	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
fast	O
my	O
Doors	O
and	O
Windows	O
about	O
Ten	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
up	O
between	O
Four	O
and	O
Five	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
back	O
Window	O
was	O
broke	O
so	O
as	O
a	O
Man	O
might	O
get	O
in	O
.	O
My	O
fore	O
Window-shutter	O
was	O
unbarr	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Casement	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
my	O
Goods	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
afterwards	O
inform	O
'd	O
me	O
that	O
some	O
such	O
Goods	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
had	O
been	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
Sale	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
and	O
searched	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Lodging	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
2	O
Handkerchiefs	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
my	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
two	O
Plates	O
in	O
his	O
Room	O
.	O
On	O
farther	O
Information	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
more	O
of	O
my	O
Goods	O
in	O
Hog-lane	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
sold	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
.	O
This	O
Chasing	O
dish	O
and	O
Frying-pan	O
I	O
bought	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
A	O
Man	O
whom	O
I	O
knew	O
came	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
own	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
these	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
their	O
being	O
stolen	O
,	O
for	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
waked	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
'em	O
all	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
Room	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
had	O
extraordinary	O
Luck	O
!	O
But	O
how	O
happen	O
'd	O
it	O
that	O
you	O
never	O
enquir	O
'd	O
who	O
they	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
my	O
own	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Your	O
own	O
?	O
And	O
how	O
did	O
you	O
think	O
you	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
Wife	O
deals	O
in	O
such	O
Things	O
.	O
She	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
Words	O
over	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
she	O
ran	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
them	O
behind	O
her	O
.	O
Constable	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
little	O
Saw	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
stubbed	O
Knife	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
13	O
John	B-pers
Wakelin	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
64	O
Guineas	O
,	O
a	O
half	O
Board-piece	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
11	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Leather	O
Pocket	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
Half-penny	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Mole-skins	O
of	O
no	O
value	O
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
9	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
no	O
person	O
then	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
John	O
Richards	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Ship-Yard	O
in	O
Petty-France	B-place
,	O
Westminster	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
being	O
Ash-Wednesday	O
,	O
about	O
9	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
I	O
made	O
fast	O
my	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
my	O
Wife	O
to	O
Leaden-Hall-Market	O
,	O
leaving	O
no	O
Body	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
about	O
Noon	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
Back-Door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Staple	O
was	O
forced	O
off	O
,	O
my	O
Drawers	O
were	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Money	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
in	O
these	O
2	O
Mole-Skins	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
having	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
broke	O
open	O
a	O
House	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
that	O
he	O
frequented	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
told	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
that	O
Morning	O
chang	O
'd	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
there	O
,	O
to	O
pay	O
a	O
Crown	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
scor	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
hir	O
'd	O
a	O
Hackney-Coach	O
to	O
carry	O
him	O
to	O
Highgate	O
.	O
At	O
Highgate	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
Man	O
that	O
went	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
the	O
Coachman	O
a	O
Guinea	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
of	O
him	O
all	O
along	O
the	O
Road	O
to	O
Hackney-Common	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
from	O
thence	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
a	O
Waggon	O
for	O
Bigglesworth	O
in	O
Bedsordshire	O
.	O
I	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
thither	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
a	O
Guinea	O
for	O
a	O
Horse	O
to	O
Eston	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
7	O
Miles	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
Eaton	O
early	O
on	O
Friday	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Cock	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
best	O
Sight	O
that	O
ever	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
with	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Ale	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
there	O
's	O
special	O
gol	O
Ale	O
at	O
the	O
Cock	O
!	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Cloth	O
on	O
his	O
Back	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
as	O
he	O
took	O
my	O
Money	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
could	O
serve	O
me	O
so	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
all	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
?	O
He	O
paused	O
a	O
little	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
for	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
back	O
my	O
Mole	O
Skins	O
,	O
with	O
45	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
spent	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
given	O
it	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
besides	O
the	O
Guinea	O
for	O
Horse	O
hire	O
and	O
a	O
Guinea	O
for	O
the	O
Hackney	O
Coach	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
rode	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
6	O
Guineas	O
for	O
bearing	O
him	O
Company	O
from	O
London	O
to	O
Highgate	O
.	O
In	O
all	O
he	O
had	O
squander	O
'd	O
away	O
above	O
19	O
Guineas	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
two	O
Days	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Dulley	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Man	O
drove	O
the	O
Waggon	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
in	O
from	O
Barnet	O
to	O
Bigglesworth	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
almost	O
killed	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
19	O
Pints	O
of	O
Wine	O
and	O
a	O
Hot-pot	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
about	O
2	O
o'Clock	O
on	O
Friday	O
Morning	O
at	O
the	O
Cock	O
at	O
Eaton	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
him	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
all	O
that	O
was	O
left	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
14.	O
Edmund	B-pers
Cheesborough	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
forging	O
a	O
promissary	O
Note	O
for	O
50	O
l.	O
dated	O
July	O
2d	O
,	O
1731	O
,	O
and	O
payable	O
6	O
Months	O
after	O
Date	O
,	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Olivant	I-pers
or	O
Order	O
,	O
by	O
Richard	B-pers
Brumton	I-pers
;	O
and	O
an	O
Indorsement	O
on	O
the	O
said	O
Note	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Thomas	O
Olivant	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
indorsing	O
his	O
own	O
Name	O
thereon	O
,	O
and	O
publishing	O
the	O
said	O
Note	O
so	O
indorsed	O
,	O
knowing	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
be	O
false	O
and	O
counterfeit	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
deceive	O
and	O
defraud	O
Stephen	B-pers
Prue	I-pers
,	O
and	O
unjustly	O
to	O
charge	O
Thomas	O
Olivant	O
with	O
the	O
Payment	O
of	O
50	O
l.	O
to	O
the	O
great	O
Damage	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
Olivant	O
and	O
Stephen	O
Prue	O
.	O
Stephen	O
Prue	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22nd	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
(	O
whom	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
)	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Friend	O
of	O
his	O
who	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Dun'irk	O
,	O
wanted	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Goods	O
in	O
my	O
Way	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
his	O
Friend	O
propos	O
'd	O
to	O
pay	O
for'em	O
.	O
Here	O
's	O
a	O
promissary	O
Note	O
(	O
says	O
he	O
)	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Brumton	O
's	O
,	O
payable	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Olivant	O
at	O
six	O
Months	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Olivant	O
has	O
indors	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
both	O
good	O
Men	O
,	O
they	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Exchequer	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
the	O
Note	O
in	O
Payment	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
be	O
satisfy	O
'd	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
good	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
'd	O
leave	O
it	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
might	O
make	O
Enquiry	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Exchequet	O
,	O
and	O
enquired	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Clerks	O
there	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
Mr.	O
Brunton	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Olivant	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Note	O
of	O
theirs	O
for	O
50	O
l.	O
If	O
it	O
was	O
for	O
500	O
l	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
your	O
Money	O
would	O
be	O
safe	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
are	O
both	O
very	O
good	O
men	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
either	O
of	O
em	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
No	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
their	O
Hand	O
Writing	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
And	O
so	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
home	O
.	O
Warren	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
Warren	O
[	O
aside	O
]	O
how	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
have	O
this	O
Note	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Olivant	O
?	O
Why	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
When	O
Mr.	O
Cheesborough	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
Prosperty	O
he	O
lent	O
Mr.	O
Olivant	O
a	O
considerable	O
Sum	O
of	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
now	O
in	O
Gratitude	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Olivant	O
has	O
lent	O
him	O
this	O
Note	O
.	O
As	O
Mr.	O
Cheesborough	O
is	O
going	O
to	O
Sea	O
,	O
he	O
's	O
very	O
much	O
straiten	O
'd	O
for	O
Time	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
short	O
Delay	O
now	O
will	O
be	O
a	O
great	O
Hindrance	O
to	O
him	O
:	O
And	O
therefore	O
I	O
must	O
desire	O
you	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
a	O
resolution	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
possible	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
I	O
let	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
have	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
indors	O
'd	O
the	O
Note	O
with	O
his	O
own	O
Name	O
.	O
Two	O
Days	O
afterwards	O
,	O
having	O
some	O
Business	O
at	O
Whiteball	O
I	O
called	O
at	O
the	O
Exchequer	O
and	O
met	O
with	O
a	O
Friend	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
whom	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
before	O
.	O
He	O
brought	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
there	O
,	O
who	O
(	O
when	O
I	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
the	O
Note	O
)	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
impos	O
'd	O
on	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Note	O
was	O
neither	O
writ	O
nor	O
indors	O
'd	O
by	O
either	O
Mr.	O
Brumton	O
or	O
Mr.	O
Olivant	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Writing	O
was	O
quite	O
different	O
from	O
theirs	O
.	O
And	O
then	O
he	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
their	O
Writing	O
in	O
some	O
Books	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
I	O
procur	O
'd	O
a	O
Warrant	O
from	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Brocas	I-pers
,	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
search	O
after	O
Warren	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Warren	O
was	O
sled	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
seven	O
Stars	O
in	O
Rosebary	O
Lane	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
or	O
27th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
You	O
could	O
not	O
well	O
do	O
this	O
alone	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
have	O
some	O
Accomplices	O
.	O
And	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
own	O
that	O
the	O
Note	O
is	O
counterfeit	O
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
and	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
more	O
were	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
drawing	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Note	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Let	O
it	O
be	O
read	O
.	O
Clerk	O
of	O
the	O
Arraigns	O
reads	O
.	O
July	O
2	O
.	O
1731	O
.	O
I	O
promise	O
to	O
pay	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	O
Olivant	O
or	O
order	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
fifty	O
Pounds	O
,	O
six	O
Months	O
after	O
Date	O
,	O
for	O
value	O
receiv	O
'd	O
.	O
L.	O
50	O
-	O
per	O
Richard	O
Brumton	O
.	O
2	O
July	O
,	O
5	O
Dec.	O
At	O
the	O
Exchequer	O
Indors	O
'd	O
Thomas	O
Olivant	O
Edm	O
.	O
Cheesborough	O
Mr.	O
Walker	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
Exchequer	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
this	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Olivent	O
's	O
Writing	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
no	O
it	O
was	O
neither	O
his	O
Hand	O
nor	O
like	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
Business	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Olivant	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
well	O
acquainted	O
with	O
his	O
Writing	O
.	O
Several	O
other	O
Gentlemen	O
swore	O
that	O
the	O
Writing	O
was	O
nothing	O
like	O
Mr.	O
Olivant	O
's	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Warren	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
indorse	O
the	O
Note	O
.	O
I	O
refused	O
several	O
times	O
;	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
consented	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
some	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
with	O
his	O
Indorsement	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Pru	O
.	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
enquire	O
about	O
the	O
Note	O
and	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
enquiry	O
,	O
he	O
accepted	O
the	O
Note	O
on	O
my	O
Indorsement	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
for	O
Warren	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
them	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lost	O
Money	O
by	O
him	O
besides	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
Warren	O
apply	O
'd	O
to	O
you	O
first	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
apply	O
for	O
Goods	O
on	O
his	O
own	O
Account	O
,	O
or	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Prue	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
delivered	O
none	O
for	O
Warren	O
's	O
Use	O
.	O
but	O
all	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
Note	O
,	O
and	O
indors	O
'd	O
it	O
with	O
his	O
own	O
Name	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
Abroad	O
.	O
He	O
indeed	O
desir	O
'd	O
Warren	O
to	O
look	O
out	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
for	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
himself	O
did	O
not	O
understand	O
'em	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
not	O
having	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
indeed	O
that	O
Warren	O
was	O
too	O
cunning	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
on	O
Board	O
the	O
Ship	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
l.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
try	O
'd	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
broke	O
out	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Carlisle	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
by	O
a	O
Habeas	O
Corpus	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
hanging	O
in	O
his	O
Cell	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
avoided	O
receiving	O
the	O
Sentence	O
that	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
pass	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
others	O
capitally	O
convicted	O
Criminals	O
.	O
15.	O
William	B-pers
Woolcott	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Williwick	B-pers
,	O
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Barns	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Pardon	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
in	O
Whitechapel	B-place
Parish	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
2	O
Keys	O
,	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
a	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
April	O
5	O
.	O
William	O
Pardon	O
.	O
Between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
Red-Lion-Street	B-place
,	O
in	O
Goodman	B-place
's	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
I	O
saw	O
4	O
suspicious	O
Fellows	O
on	O
the	O
opposite	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
;	O
they	O
cross	O
'd	O
towards	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
began	O
to	O
run	O
,	O
in	O
hopes	O
to	O
avoid	O
them	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
but	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
Doors	O
farther	O
to	O
go	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
fall	O
,	O
when	O
immediately	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
got	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
others	O
about	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
cut	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
in	O
several	O
Places	O
.	O
You	O
may	O
see	O
the	O
Scars	O
.	O
I	O
struggled	O
and	O
struck	O
at	O
them	O
with	O
my	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
(	O
when	O
they	O
kept	O
my	O
Hand	O
down	O
)	O
with	O
my	O
Foot	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
my	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
,	O
2	O
Keys	O
,	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
about	O
6	O
Pennyworth	O
of	O
Halfpence	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
leaving	O
me	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
bloody	O
Condition	O
,	O
they	O
vanish	O
'd	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
thought	O
all	O
at	O
once	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
made	O
shift	O
to	O
get	O
home	O
.	O
The	O
Assault	O
was	O
so	O
sudden	O
and	O
the	O
Abuse	O
so	O
great	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
take	O
so	O
much	O
notice	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
know	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
afterwards	O
sent	O
for	O
by	O
a	O
Justice	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
on	O
an	O
Information	O
given	O
by	O
James	B-pers
Tripland	I-pers
.	O
James	O
Tripland	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Stratford	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
committed	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
As	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
began	O
to	O
run	O
,	O
I	O
set	O
my	O
Leg	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
hit	O
him	O
a	O
knock	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
with	O
a	O
Broomstick	O
,	O
and	O
Barns	O
gave	O
him	O
another	O
;	O
we	O
held	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
Wolcott	O
and	O
Stratford	O
rifled	O
him	O
.	O
We	O
sold	O
the	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
for	O
a	O
Crown	O
to	O
Nell	B-pers
Wilford	I-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
Jail	O
(	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Bromly	I-pers
)	O
she	O
's	O
one	O
that	O
buys	O
stolen	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
sells	O
'em	O
in	O
Rag	O
Fair	O
.	O
This	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
s.	O
5	O
d.	O
Halfpenny	O
,	O
that	O
we	O
took	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
equally	O
divided	O
among	O
us	O
four	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
Woolcott	O
at	O
the	O
Dunghill	O
by	O
the	O
Glass-House	O
against	O
Rag	O
Fair	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
innocent	O
of	O
this	O
Fact	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Atly	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Tripland	O
's	O
Information	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Warrant	O
to	O
take	O
Barns	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
committed	O
several	O
Robberies	O
,	O
but	O
believed	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
no	O
Danger	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
People	O
(	O
his	O
Comrades	O
)	O
were	O
in	O
safe	O
Custody	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
he	O
fear	O
'd	O
no	O
body	O
.	O
Barns	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
on	O
Chetwin	O
's	O
Information	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
on	O
Tripland	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
Tripland	O
's	O
Company	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Tripland	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
but	O
he	O
has	O
many	O
a	O
Time	O
;	O
we	O
have	O
often	O
gone	O
together	O
to	O
Shops	O
to	O
steal	O
Money	O
Boxes	O
.	O
and	O
Sugar	O
Loaves	O
,	O
and	O
such	O
kind	O
of	O
trifling	O
Things	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Weaker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
Constable	O
when	O
Barns	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
before	O
Alderman	O
Brocas	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Phillips	O
,	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
several	O
Robberies	O
but	O
said	O
the	O
People	O
were	O
safe	O
in	O
Jail	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
James	B-pers
Stratford	I-pers
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
but	O
by	O
and	O
by	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
playing	O
at	O
Skettles	O
with	O
Stratford	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
said	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
James	B-pers
Stratford	I-pers
?	O
O	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
another	O
Man	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Name	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
Barns	O
say	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
some	O
Things	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
People	O
were	O
in	O
Custody	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
name	O
Particulars	O
.	O
Barns	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Home	O
at	O
my	O
Mother	O
's	O
when	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Tripland	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
hang	O
me	O
if	O
there	O
were	O
no	O
more	O
Men	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
Transported	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
Years	O
ago	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Ogden	I-pers
,	O
Woolcott	O
.	O
Tripland	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
hang	O
50	O
before	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
hanged	O
himself	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
Transported	O
by	O
his	O
Uncle	O
's	O
Name	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Ogden	I-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
an	O
Oyster	O
Meeter	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
could	O
produce	O
the	O
Record	O
of	O
his	O
Transportation	O
,	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
of	O
some	O
Service	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
16.	O
John	B-pers
Dunstan	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Simmonds	I-pers
in	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
Parish	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Saw	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Nippers	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Players	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Compasses	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Scissars	O
,	O
a	O
Brush	O
,	O
a	O
black	O
Lead	O
Pencil	O
,	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Mother	O
of	O
Pearl	O
,	O
a	O
small	O
Wooden	O
Pully	O
,	O
12	O
Sets	O
of	O
inside	O
Ivory	O
Fan	B-pers
Sticks	I-pers
,	O
12	O
Sets	O
of	O
outside	O
Ivory	O
Fan	O
Sticks	O
,	O
3	O
engraved	O
Copper-Plates	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
William	O
Simmons	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Brown's-Court	B-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
Little-Old-Baily	B-place
.	O
There	O
is	O
an	O
empty	O
House	O
next	O
to	O
mine	O
:	O
My	O
Garret-Window	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
about	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Garret-Window	O
of	O
the	O
empty	O
House	O
was	O
found	O
open	O
too	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
was	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
Window	O
below	O
.	O
Thereupon	O
we	O
concluded	O
that	O
the	O
Rogue	O
must	O
get	O
in	O
that	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
been	O
lurking	O
in	O
that	O
empty	O
House	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Nights	O
before	O
,	O
we	O
suspected	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
search	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
a	O
selling	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
in	O
Field-Lane	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Wharton	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
is	O
a	O
Fanstick	O
Maker	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
mend	O
Shoes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
his	O
Tenant	O
,	O
and	O
lodge	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
under	O
the	O
Garret	O
that	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
About	O
Two	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Noise	O
over	O
my	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
my	O
Landlord	O
was	O
got	O
up	O
to	O
work	O
betimes	O
(	O
for	O
he	O
works	O
in	O
the	O
Garret	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
do	O
I	O
too	O
)	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
rise	O
till	O
Five	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Garret	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
thing	O
that	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
was	O
my	O
Knife	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
these	O
Shoes	O
.	O
I	O
calls	O
up	O
my	O
Landlord	O
;	O
Landlord	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
my	O
old	O
Shoes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
ruined	O
!	O
He	O
looks	O
about	O
,	O
And	O
so	O
am	O
I	O
too	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
.	O
We	O
presently	O
thought	O
the	O
Fellow	O
that	O
had	O
lain	O
in	O
the	O
empty	O
House	O
was	O
the	O
Thief	O
.	O
And	O
so	O
away	O
goes	O
I	O
to	O
Field-Lane	O
,	O
for	O
you	O
must	O
note	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
these	O
Fellows	O
steal	O
Shoes	O
,	O
they	O
sell	O
them	O
in	O
or	O
about	O
Field-Lane	O
or	O
Rag-Fair	O
,	O
but	O
Boats	O
they	O
carry	O
to	O
Charing-Cross	O
.	O
As	O
good	O
Luck	O
would	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
soon	O
met	O
with	O
my	O
Chap	O
at	O
one	O
of	O
those	O
Shops	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
Vamp	O
up	O
old	O
Shoes	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
offering	O
one	O
of	O
these	O
Pairs	O
to	O
Sale	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
suppose	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
offer	O
the	O
other	O
Pair	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
being	O
suspected	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
sky	O
'd	O
the	O
Soles	O
,	O
ready	O
for	O
new	O
soleing	O
.	O
I	O
collar	O
'd	O
my	O
Gentleman	O
;	O
he	O
immediately	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Alehouse	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
every	O
thing	O
easy	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
compound	O
Felony	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
search	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
himself	O
took	O
these	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Fare-sticks	O
,	O
this	O
pair	O
of	O
Nippers	O
,	O
this	O
Pully	O
,	O
and	O
Knife	O
and	O
Brush	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
Pockets	O
;	O
and	O
this	O
Saw	O
and	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
we	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
empty	O
House	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barber	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
we	O
would	O
but	O
have	O
Patience	O
till	O
his	O
Sister	O
came	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
impeach	O
his	O
Accomplices	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
Body	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
but	O
himself	O
.	O
At	O
another	O
time	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
empty	O
House	O
all	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Fellows	O
came	O
and	O
robbed	O
the	O
next	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
dropp	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
see	O
3	O
Men	O
go	O
up	O
the	O
Yard	O
between	O
2	O
and	O
3	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
the	O
Watchman	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
a	O
Calf	O
run	O
in	O
there	O
?	O
Barber	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
the	O
Watchman	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
3	O
Men	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
a	O
Calf	O
?	O
Barber	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
some	O
Talk	O
about	O
a	O
Calf	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
Remembrance	O
I	O
understood	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
only	O
an	O
idle	O
pretence	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
he	O
that	O
said	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
the	O
Watchman	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Shaw	O
.	O
Such	O
a	O
thing	O
might	O
happen	O
,	O
for	O
Calves	O
are	O
driven	O
to	O
Smithfield	O
at	O
all	O
Hours	O
of	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
come	O
from	O
on	O
Board	O
the	O
Dursley-Galley	O
at	O
Deptford	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
drink	O
at	O
the	O
Horse-shoe	O
in	O
Fetter-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
,	O
having	O
no	O
Lodging	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
laid	O
down	O
in	O
that	O
empty	O
House	O
to	O
sleep	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
waked	O
with	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
out	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
3	O
Men	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
them	O
they	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
dropp	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
17	O
,	O
18.	O
Edward	B-pers
Spaul	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Spaw	B-pers
(	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
)	O
and	O
Michael	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
in	O
White-Chappel	B-place
Parish	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
2	O
Porridge-pots	O
,	O
2	O
Sauce-pans	O
,	O
1	O
Srew-pan	O
,	O
a	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
3	O
Aprons	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
old	O
Rags	O
,	O
April	O
21	O
.	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
19	O
.	O
And	O
Sarah	B-pers
Warfield	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Goodman's-Yard	B-place
in	O
the	O
Minories	B-place
,	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
Wash-house	O
joining	O
to	O
my	O
Dwelling-house	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
about	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
every	O
thing	O
safe	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
my	O
Wash-house	O
was	O
untiled	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
might	O
be	O
12	O
or	O
14	O
Tiles	O
taken	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
2	O
Porridge-pots	O
,	O
2	O
Sauce	O
pans	O
,	O
a	O
Srew-pan	O
,	O
a	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
3	O
Aprons	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Bundle	O
of	O
Linen	O
Rags	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
put	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Pots	O
.	O
The	O
outside	O
Rag	O
(	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
others	O
were	O
wrapt	O
)	O
was	O
a	O
Rag	B-pers
I	I-pers
had	O
used	O
about	O
the	O
House	O
so	O
many	O
times	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
again	O
(	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
that	O
I	O
found	O
)	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Warfield	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
back	O
Lane	O
by	O
Rag-Fair	O
,	O
over-against	O
the	O
Hog-house	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Tripland	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
with	O
Spaul	O
and	O
Shaw	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Black-Boy	O
in	O
Well-street	O
,	O
till	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
we	O
went	O
together	O
into	O
Goodman's-Yard	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Place	O
pailed	O
in	O
,	O
where	O
some	O
Houses	O
were	O
building	O
;	O
Shaw	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
Pails	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
handed	O
a	O
Ladder	O
over	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Help	O
of	O
which	O
we	O
got	O
over	O
too	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
the	O
Ladder	O
after	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
raised	O
it	O
up	O
against	O
the	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
.	O
Our	O
first	O
Design	O
was	O
to	O
steal	O
Lead	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
stuck	O
so	O
hard	O
,	O
that	O
in	O
pulling	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Mortar	O
sell	O
thro	O
'	O
into	O
the	O
Wash-house	O
upon	O
the	O
Brass	O
Porridge	O
pots	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
perceiving	O
,	O
we	O
thought	O
the	O
Pots	O
would	O
be	O
a	O
better	O
Booty	O
than	O
the	O
Lead	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
untiled	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Wash-house	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
Ladder	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
Spaul	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
Goods	O
up	O
to	O
us	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
had	O
got	O
what	O
we	O
thought	O
convenient	O
,	O
we	O
haul	O
'd	O
the	O
Ladder	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
it	O
again	O
against	O
the	O
Pails	O
:	O
Spaul	O
went	O
over	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
and	O
Shaw	O
handed	O
the	O
Things	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
followed	O
;	O
we	O
carried	O
them	O
all	O
to	O
Warfield	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
her	O
Husband	O
keeps	O
a	O
Smith	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
Acquaintance	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
We	O
knock	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Fore-Door	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Man	O
within	O
(	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
who	O
he	O
was	O
)	O
bid	O
us	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Back-Door	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
did	O
;	O
you	O
go	O
down	O
Steps	O
to	O
the	O
Back-Door	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Warfield	I-pers
open	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
us	O
;	O
I	O
and	O
Shaw	O
handed	O
the	O
Things	O
down	O
to	O
Spaul	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
Light	O
?	O
Could	O
you	O
see	O
her	O
Face	O
?	O
Tripland	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Candle	O
on	O
the	O
Steps	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
knew	O
her	O
before	O
.	O
At	O
7	O
the	O
same	O
Morning	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
at	O
the	O
Black-Boy	O
in	O
Well-street	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
to	O
Newgate	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Afternoon	O
Spaul	O
and	O
Shaw	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
my	O
Dividend	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
a	O
Groat	O
more	O
would	O
have	O
come	O
to	O
my	O
Share	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
oblig	O
'd	O
to	O
spend	O
1	O
s.	O
at	O
Warfield	O
's	O
House	O
when	O
she	O
paid	O
'em	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
From	O
Newgate	O
I	O
was	O
remov	O
'd	O
to	O
Clerkenwell	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
made	O
an	O
Evidence	O
.	O
A	O
Warrant	O
was	O
afterwards	O
granted	O
to	O
search	O
Warfield	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
thither	O
with	O
an	O
Officer	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
Tripland	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
Prosecutrix	O
there	O
then	O
?	O
Tripland	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
before	O
.	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
by	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
picked	O
out	O
a	O
Rag	O
that	O
was	O
mine	O
from	O
a	O
Heap	O
of	O
other	O
Rags	O
that	O
lay	O
in	O
a	O
Corner	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
Up-stairs	O
,	O
and	O
every	O
thing	O
look	O
'd	O
so	O
miserable	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
expect	O
to	O
find	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
there	O
that	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
got	O
it	O
here	O
?	O
Pro	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
but	O
be	O
laughed	O
at	O
for	O
bringing	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
hither	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
mistaken	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
proper	O
to	O
be	O
produced	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
could	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Pro	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
safely	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
in	O
particular	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
dry	O
'd	O
my	O
House	O
with	O
it	O
many	O
and	O
many	O
a	O
time	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Shaw	O
run	O
down	O
Blue-Anchor	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Man	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
ran	O
too	O
,	O
and	O
assisted	O
in	O
taking	O
him	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Hodson	I-pers
.	O
At	O
Aldgate	O
I	O
saw	O
Spaul	O
and	O
Lightfoot	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
I	O
followed	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
were	O
there	O
,	O
Lightfoot	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
himself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
2	O
Men	O
that	O
frequented	O
the	O
Black-Boy	O
in	O
Well-Street	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
the	O
Name	O
and	O
Description	O
of	O
but	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
I	O
should	O
forget	O
'em	O
both	O
if	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
two	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Rolfe	I-pers
went	O
thither	O
directly	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
to	O
prevent	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
I	O
hipp	O
'd	O
to	O
Rolfe	O
,	O
who	O
,	O
on	O
purpose	O
,	O
walk	O
'd	O
at	O
a	O
little	O
Distance	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
ow	O
'd	O
me	O
a	O
Dram	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Quartern	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
for	O
another	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
then	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
others	O
,	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
the	O
Description	O
that	O
Lightfoot	O
had	O
given	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
sure	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
he	O
.	O
By	O
and	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Creatures	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
Mick	O
!	O
Mick	O
!	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
what	O
have	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
Name	O
sake	O
here	O
?	O
My	O
Name	O
is	O
Mick	O
too	O
,	O
here	O
's	O
to	O
you	O
Namesake	O
sure	O
we	O
are	O
not	O
Namesake	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
Surname	O
too	O
?	O
My	O
Name	O
is	O
Michael	B-pers
Hodson	I-pers
!	O
No	O
,	O
says	O
one	O
,	O
his	O
Name	O
is	O
Michael	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
;	O
then	O
I	O
found	O
I	O
was	O
right	O
.	O
Soon	O
after	O
this	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
sate	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Womens	O
Laps	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Give	O
me	O
a	O
Kiss	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
going	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
kiss	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
paid	O
my	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
go	O
too	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
Sight	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
search	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
was	O
weary	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
returning	O
home	O
,	O
when	O
accidentally	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
perceiving	O
I	O
took	O
Notice	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
ran	O
down	O
Blue-Anchor-Yard	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
faint	O
with	O
running	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
drop	O
'd	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
White-Swan	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Webb	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Shaw	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
Tripland	O
but	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
on	O
Lightfoot	O
's	O
Information	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
Tripland	O
heard	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
this	O
Robbery	O
.	O
Spaul	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
Lightfoot	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
Tripland	O
knew	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
hang	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
thousand	O
Lives	O
.	O
Shaw	O
.	O
Fleming	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
himself	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
this	O
Burglary	O
along	O
with	O
Tripland	O
.	O
Fleming	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
saw	O
Tripland	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
but	O
where	O
he	O
went	O
afterwards	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Prison	O
then	O
.	O
Justice	O
Philips	O
.	O
Shaw	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
says	O
,	O
was	O
not	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
this	O
Burglary	O
,	O
but	O
on	O
Lightfoot	O
's	O
Information	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Petticoat-Lane	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Hodson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Sarah	B-pers
Warfield	I-pers
these	O
14	O
or	O
15	O
Years	O
,	O
she	O
bore	O
an	O
honest	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
suspected	O
of	O
buying	O
stolen	O
Goods	O
,	O
nor	O
do	O
I	O
think	O
she	O
would	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
Thing	O
Fleming	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
Tripland	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
sold	O
in	O
Petticoat-Lane	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Tripland	O
do	O
n't	O
say	O
now	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
sold	O
to	O
Sarah	B-pers
Warfield	I-pers
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
receiv	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
tells	O
you	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
by	O
7	O
o'Clock	O
the	O
same	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
Shaw	O
and	O
Spaul	O
brought	O
him	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
his	O
Share	O
.	O
Justice	O
Philips	O
.	O
Tripland	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
granted	O
a	O
Search	O
Warrant	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
hardly	O
expected	O
to	O
find	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
at	O
Warfield	O
's	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
Custom	O
to	O
carry	O
'em	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
sell	O
them	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
she	O
receiv	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
Fleming	O
.	O
Tripland	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
carry	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
Sarah	O
Warfield	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
her	O
Husband	O
.	O
Tripland	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
I	O
tell	O
you	O
so	O
?	O
Fleming	O
.	O
At	O
Bridewell	O
.	O
Tripland	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
said	O
any	O
such	O
Thing	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
Spaul	O
and	O
Shaw	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
And	O
acquitted	O
Warfield	O
.	O
20.	O
Joshua	B-pers
Floyd	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
slaying	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Convent-Garden	I-place
,	O
John	B-pers
Urly	I-pers
,	O
aged	O
9	O
Years	O
,	O
by	O
driving	O
2	O
Horses	O
,	O
Harness	O
'd	O
to	O
a	O
loaded	O
Dray	O
,	O
whereby	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
receiv	O
'd	O
one	O
mortal	O
Bruise	O
in	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
dy	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Child	O
was	O
sitting	O
at	O
a	O
Bench	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
along	O
with	O
a	O
Dray	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
drove	O
so	O
close	O
to	O
the	O
Houses	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Off-wheel	O
broke	O
down	O
the	O
Bench	O
,	O
and	O
wedged	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
Head	O
up	O
against	O
an	O
Iron-Grate	O
;	O
the	O
Blood	O
gush	O
'd	O
from	O
his	O
Neck	O
,	O
his	O
Nose	O
,	O
and	O
Eyes	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
dy	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
Spot	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
21	O
,	O
22.	O
Robert	B-pers
Head	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Shirts	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Tireman	I-pers
,	O
3	O
Aprons	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hide	I-pers
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
Marsh	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Head	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
23.	O
John	B-pers
Spindle	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Feather	O
Bed	O
,	O
2	O
Pillows	O
,	O
a	O
Quilt	O
,	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
a	O
Jacket	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Cotton	O
Shirts	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Ship	B-place
call	I-place
'd	I-place
the	I-place
Isabella	I-place
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
24.	O
Mary	B-pers
Ketcher	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Shirts	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Linen	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
25.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Burnham	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
19	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Iron	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
26.	O
William	B-pers
Burchett	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
17	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Iron	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
27.	O
William	B-pers
Headly	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
900	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Governor	B-pers
and	O
Company	B-pers
of	I-pers
the	I-pers
York-Buildings	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
28.	O
Ann	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
and	O
a	O
Holland-Cap	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Paris	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
29	O
,	O
30	O
,	O
31.	O
Henry	B-pers
Defoe	I-pers
,	O
Abraham	O
D'angre	O
,	O
and	O
Daniel	B-pers
Defoe	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Owen	B-pers
Plumstead	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
a	O
Wig	O
,	O
a	O
Brass	O
Tobacco	O
Box	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
and	O
Buckles	O
,	O
and	O
15	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
.	O
Owen	O
Plumstead	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
in	O
Hare-Street	B-place
in	O
Brick-Lane	B-place
;	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
by	O
whom	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
got	O
drunk	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
lock	O
'd	O
out	O
o'Saturday	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
Hare-Street	O
.	O
They	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
Walk	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
gone	O
a	O
little	O
Way	O
,	O
Harry	B-pers
Defoe	I-pers
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Will	O
you	O
buy	O
these	O
Davy	O
?	O
No	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
his	O
own	O
old	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
other	O
Shoes	O
on	O
;	O
soon	O
after	O
,	O
we	O
met	O
3	O
young	O
Fellows	O
,	O
whom	O
we	O
knew	O
,	O
they	O
talk	O
'd	O
with	O
us	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
us	O
good	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
up	O
Hare-Street	O
again	O
;	O
says	O
Daniel	B-pers
Defoe	I-pers
,	O
Here	O
's	O
a	O
Man	O
asleep	O
,	O
let	O
's	O
see	O
if	O
he	O
has	O
got	O
any	O
Money	O
.	O
And	O
then	O
D'angre	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
in	O
the	O
Man	O
's	O
Pocket	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
3	O
d.	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
was	O
between	O
1	O
and	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
;	O
I	O
speak	O
nothing	O
but	O
the	O
Truth	O
before	O
God	O
Almighty	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Dram	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
left	O
'em	O
in	O
George-Street	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Morean	I-pers
,	O
Hugh	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Mae	I-pers
.	O
As	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
Hare-Street	O
between	O
1	O
and	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Defoe	I-pers
pass	O
'd	O
us	O
,	O
look	O
'd	O
us	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
forward	O
;	O
he	O
knew	O
us	O
all	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
farther	O
,	O
a	O
Man	O
was	O
lying	O
drunk	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
.	O
Daniel	O
stopp	O
'd	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
this	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
Hey	O
!	O
God	O
darm	O
ye	O
!	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
I	O
where	O
for	O
?	O
He	O
had	O
hardly	O
spoke	O
,	O
when	O
2	O
Men	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
Hip	O
!	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
over	O
to	O
'em	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
drunken	O
Man	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
we	O
knew	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
had	O
on	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Shoes	O
too	O
.	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
our	O
Remembrance	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
a-cross	O
the	O
Way	O
to	O
see	O
who	O
they	O
were	O
that	O
hip	O
'd	O
to	O
Daniel	O
,	O
we	O
knew	O
them	O
all	O
four	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
3	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
David	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
They	O
began	O
to	O
pick	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
we	O
left	O
'em	O
,	O
but	O
suspecting	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
,	O
some	O
design	O
upon	O
the	O
drunken	O
Man	O
,	O
we	O
stood	O
at	O
a	O
little	O
Distance	O
and	O
watch	O
'd	O
'em	O
,	O
we	O
saw	O
'em	O
all	O
go	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
rifle	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
go	O
off	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
raised	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
waked	O
him	O
;	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
Shoes	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Body	O
had	O
been	O
near	O
him	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
Wood	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
time	O
we	O
left	O
him	O
,	O
till	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
again	O
.	O
We	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
who	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
?	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
all	O
Weaver	O
s	O
in	O
Spittle-Fields	B-place
,	O
and	O
the	O
3	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
taken	O
about	O
5	O
o'Clock	O
that	O
Morning	O
at	O
a	O
Brandy-Shop	O
in	O
Winsord-Street	O
.	O
Several	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
most	O
of	O
them	O
Weavers	O
,	O
appear	O
'd	O
in	O
behalf	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
they	O
knew	O
no	O
harm	O
of	O
them	O
before	O
this	O
time	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
consequently	O
not	O
put	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
32.	O
John	B-pers
Crotch	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Yarmouth	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Wig	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Maxey	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
John	O
Maxey	O
.	O
Going	O
along	O
Lime-street	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
standing	O
at	O
Pewterer	O
's	O
Hall-Gate	O
,	O
and	O
humming	O
a	O
Song	O
,	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
at	O
'em	O
by	O
the	O
Light	O
of	O
a	O
Lamp	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
'em	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
pass	O
'd	O
'em	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
,	O
Shall	O
us	O
go	O
?	O
And	O
the	O
other	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
Yes	O
.	O
They	O
follow	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Fenchurch-street	B-place
,	O
one	O
of	O
'em	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
clapp	O
'd	O
his	O
Hand	O
to	O
my	O
Mouth	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
snatch	O
'd	O
off	O
my	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
;	O
but	O
presently	O
return	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
whom	O
I	O
held	O
fast	O
,	O
Damn	O
you	O
,	O
why	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
come	O
along	O
?	O
and	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stabb	O
'd	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
afterwards	O
sent	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
stealing	O
another	O
Hat	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
sell	O
to	O
the	O
very	O
Man	O
who	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
before	O
to	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
lost	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
as	O
your	O
Lordship	O
is	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
33	O
,	O
34.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Eaves	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Oaks	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Sign	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jarvis	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
,	O
April	O
9	O
.	O
Eaves	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
Oaks	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
35.	O
Mary	B-pers
Bright	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
May	O
18	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
36.	O
Edward	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
in	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
Parish	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Dish	O
,	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Spoon	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Earthen	O
Porringer	O
,	O
April	O
23	O
.	O
about	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
37.	O
Jeremy	B-pers
Dawkins	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Box	O
Iron	O
,	O
a	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Tea	O
Spoon	O
,	O
April	O
22	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
38	O
,	O
39.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Ferryman	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ferryman	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Curtain	O
,	O
a	O
Pillow	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
in	O
their	O
Lodging	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Geo	B-pers
.	I-pers
Stevens	I-pers
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
40.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
in	O
Aldgate	B-place
Parish	O
4	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
4	O
Silver	O
Salts	O
,	O
3	O
Silver	O
Casters	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Judith	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
May	O
22	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
Waterman	O
,	O
was	O
hired	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
Burr-street	B-place
to	O
the	O
Unicorn	B-place
in	O
Fleet-street	B-place
,	O
but	O
never	O
delivered	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
41.	O
William	B-pers
Beat	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bed	O
and	O
a	O
Blanket	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
;	O
and	O
2	O
Hammers	O
,	O
a	O
Bag	O
,	O
36	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Beef	O
,	O
and	O
16	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Pork	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
May	O
6	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
42.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Guy	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Robert	B-pers
Johnston	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silver-hilted	O
Sword	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
May	O
11	O
.	O
And	O
43.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Wallis	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Guy	B-pers
,	O
alias	O
Palmer	B-pers
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
an	O
Ivory	O
Snuff-box	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Porrester	I-pers
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Johnston	I-pers
,	O
May	O
10	O
.	O
Robert	O
Johnston	O
.	O
My	O
Moather-in-Law	O
is	O
an	O
and	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
lik	O
your	O
Loardship	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
tull	O
Bellinsgat	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
tack	O
Water	O
for	O
Datford	O
.	O
I	O
drank	O
a	O
Mug	O
of	O
Ale	O
at	O
Bellinsgat	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
came	O
back	O
tull	O
Wastminster	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
it	O
was	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
I	O
caud	O
in	O
at	O
William	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
's	O
Hoose	O
at	O
Charing-Cross	B-place
for	O
a	O
hauporth	O
of	O
Snuff	O
.	O
Will	O
ye	O
tack	O
a	O
Dram	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
says	O
Taylor	O
?	O
I	O
donna	O
care	O
an	O
I	O
do	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
lattle	O
out	O
of	O
Oarder	O
.	O
And	O
what	O
shall	O
it	O
be	O
,	O
Sir	O
?	O
says	O
he	O
;	O
Why	O
e'en	O
what	O
ye	O
will	O
your	O
sell	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
fell	O
'd	O
me	O
out	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Rum	O
.	O
And	O
what	O
is	O
to	O
pay	O
now	O
,	O
Sir	O
?	O
says	O
I	O
;	O
Not	O
a	O
Farthing	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
taud	O
ye	O
I	O
wad	O
give	O
ye	O
a	O
Dram	O
.	O
Then	O
it	O
shanna	O
go	O
bare-ars	O
'd	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
Let	O
us	O
have	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
something	O
that	O
you	O
like	O
best	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Dram	O
of	O
Anniseed	O
is	O
as	O
bealing	O
as	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
then	O
let	O
it	O
be	O
Anniseed	O
,	O
sir	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
.	O
And	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
lattle	O
back	O
Place	O
where	O
the	O
Soldiers	O
leave	O
the	O
Arms	O
,	O
and	O
Hannah	B-pers
Wallis	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prasoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bare	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
sat	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
by	O
me	O
.	O
Now	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
Wanno	O
ye	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
Drom	O
?	O
No	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
just	O
now	O
tacken	O
one	O
.	O
Well	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
canno	O
drink	O
your	O
sell	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
.	O
And	O
then	O
Taylor	O
came	O
with	O
the	O
Anuiseed	O
,	O
he	O
fill	O
'd	O
a	O
Glass	O
and	O
drank	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
the	O
rest	O
upon	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
again	O
to	O
some	O
Customers	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
tuck	O
out	O
my	O
Box	O
to	O
tack	O
a	O
pickle	O
of	O
snuff	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
intull	O
my	O
Pocket	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
see	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
reach	O
'd	O
over	O
the	O
Table	O
to	O
fell	O
a	O
Glass	O
,	O
she	O
packt	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
her	O
take	O
it	O
?	O
Johnston	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Loard	O
,	O
I	O
donna	O
see	O
her	O
tack	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
want	O
awa	O
prasently	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
mist	O
it	O
the	O
Minute	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
And	O
I	O
caw	O
'd	O
out	O
to	O
Taylor	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
