TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
6th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
7th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
9th	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
September	O
1732	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Sixth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Seventh	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
CHILD	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1732	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VII	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
ROBERTS	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Oxford-Arms	O
in	O
Warwick-Lane	O
.	O
M	O
,	O
DCC	O
,	O
XXXII	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
Six	O
Pence	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
CHILD	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Recorder	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
Urlin	O
,	O
Deputy-Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Gurney	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bateman	I-pers
,	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Horvit	I-pers
,	O
Williams	B-pers
Norton	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Holloway	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Jacob	B-pers
Brevicks	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Ansley	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bumpstead	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
Edmund	B-pers
Hewit	I-pers
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Linford	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Osgood	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Abbot	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Clarkson	I-pers
,	O
Arthur	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Huggit	I-pers
.	O
1	O
,	O
2.	O
James	B-pers
Brothwick	I-pers
and	O
David	B-pers
Brothwick	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linen	O
Bag	O
,	O
8	O
Portugal	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
28	O
l.	O
16	O
s.	O
1	O
Portugal	O
Piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
two	O
Portugal	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
one	O
Portugal	O
Piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Spanish	O
Pistole	O
,	O
17	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
12	O
Moidores	O
,	O
2	O
Quarter	O
Moidores	O
,	O
5	O
Broad	O
Pieces	O
,	O
a	O
half	O
Broad	O
Piece	O
,	O
44	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
double	O
Guinea	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Jeffries	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Pistols	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
42	O
s.	O
3	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
a	O
Snuff	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Whip	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jeffries	I-pers
;	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Pistols	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
l.	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Pickfoot	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Jeffries	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
July	O
19	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jeffries	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Brother	O
and	O
I	O
are	O
Partners	O
in	O
Trade	O
in	O
our	O
House	O
on	O
Snow-hill	B-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
James	O
was	O
my	O
Book-keeper	O
,	O
and	O
David	O
is	O
his	O
Brother	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
James	O
into	O
my	O
Service	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
about	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
June	O
meeting	O
with	O
another	O
Book	O
keeper	O
,	O
who	O
I	O
thought	O
was	O
sitter	O
for	O
my	O
Business	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
James	O
warning	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
leave	O
my	O
Service	O
that	O
Day	O
I	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
July	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
in	O
a	O
Bag	O
119	O
l.	O
19	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
bad	O
Guinea	O
in	O
my	O
Desk	O
,	O
besides	O
a	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
2	O
Pair	O
of	O
Pistols	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
my	O
Parlour	O
a	O
Silver-hilted	O
Sword	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
in	O
those	O
Places	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
Stairs	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
my	O
Desk	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
Goods	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
James	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
.	O
I	O
presently	O
got	O
Advertisements	O
printed	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
a	O
Friend	O
Post	O
towards	O
Harwich	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
My	O
Friend	O
left	O
Advertisements	O
at	O
several	O
Places	O
as	O
he	O
rode	O
along	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
taken	O
at	O
Chelmsford	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Swai	I-pers
.	O
One	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Joshua	O
's	O
Advertisements	O
being	O
left	O
at	O
my	O
Shop	O
in	O
Burst-wood	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
read	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
recollected	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
such	O
a	O
Man	O
as	O
was	O
therein	O
described	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
pass	O
by	O
my	O
Shop	O
the	O
same	O
Morning	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
2	O
of	O
my	O
Journeymen	O
,	O
and	O
followed	O
them	O
to	O
Brilerecay	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
5	O
Miles	O
.	O
We	O
heard	O
such	O
Men	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
meet	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
though	O
I	O
searched	O
all	O
the	O
Alehouses	O
in	O
the	O
Town	O
;	O
we	O
pursued	O
them	O
to	O
Chelmsford	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
Cock	O
and	O
Coach	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
them	O
early	O
next	O
Morning	O
.	O
I	O
read	O
over	O
the	O
Advertisement	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
James	O
hold	O
up	O
his	O
Head	O
(	O
for	O
they	O
both	O
held	O
their	O
Heads	O
down	O
)	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
see	O
if	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
the	O
Description	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
I	O
believed	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
was	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
wished	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
never	O
done	O
it	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
upwards	O
of	O
110	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
Brace	O
of	O
Pistols	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Brace	O
of	O
Pistols	O
upon	O
his	O
Brother	O
David	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
broken	O
Silver-hilted	O
Sword	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Bundle	O
which	O
David	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
J	O
.	O
B	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
first	O
came	O
in	O
was	O
the	O
Bundle	O
in	O
any	O
Body	O
's	O
Hands	O
,	O
or	O
was	O
it	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
you	O
or	O
not	O
?	O
Swain	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
in	O
David	O
's	O
Lap	O
,	O
or	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
as	O
he	O
sat	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Sword	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
J	O
.	O
B.	O
was	O
the	O
Sword	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Situation	O
[	O
Condition	O
-	O
was	O
the	O
Blade	O
broken	O
]	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
now	O
?	O
Swain	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
J	O
.	O
B	O
.	O
Were	O
the	O
Pistols	O
loaded	O
?	O
Swain	O
.	O
No	O
Mr.	O
Jeffries	O
.	O
This	O
Sword	O
was	O
whole	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Parlour	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Master	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Swain	O
,	O
took	O
me	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
pursue	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Hearing	O
at	O
Billericay	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
forward	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
Horses	O
at	O
Midnight	O
,	O
and	O
followed	O
them	O
to	O
Chelmsford	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
found	O
'em	O
next	O
Morning	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
saw	O
us	O
,	O
they	O
hung	O
down	O
their	O
Heads	O
;	O
says	O
my	O
Master	O
to	O
James	O
,	O
Hold	O
up	O
your	O
Head	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
may	O
see	O
if	O
you	O
answer	O
the	O
Description	O
in	O
the	O
Advertisement	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
that	O
you	O
are	O
the	O
Men	O
;	O
yes	O
,	O
answer	O
'd	O
James	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
be	O
indeed	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
wish	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
about	O
110	O
l.	O
taken	O
from	O
James	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Watch	O
and	O
a	O
Snuff-box	O
and	O
3	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
.	O
When	O
Mr.	O
Jeffries	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
James	O
why	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Pistols	O
?	O
And	O
James	O
said	O
,	O
We	O
were	O
resolutely	O
bent	O
to	O
lose	O
our	O
Lives	O
rather	O
than	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
.	O
J	O
.	O
B	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
the	O
Pistols	O
and	O
Sword	O
were	O
taken	O
not	O
with	O
a	O
Design	O
to	O
hurt	O
any	O
Body	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
to	O
strike	O
Terror	O
.	O
D.	O
E.	O
Was	O
not	O
the	O
Bundle	O
from	O
whence	O
the	O
Sword	O
as	O
taken	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
when	O
you	O
came	O
in	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
you	O
had	O
the	O
Bundle	O
under	O
your	O
Arm	O
.	O
Swain	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
Smith	O
went	O
in	O
together	O
,	O
David	O
then	O
had	O
the	O
bundle	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
lay	O
on	O
his	O
Lap	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
Arm	O
on	O
it	O
thus	O
-	O
J	O
.	O
B	O
.	O
It	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
they	O
bid	O
my	O
Brother	O
take	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
carry	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
it	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
.	O
Francis	O
nut	O
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
about	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Swain	O
,	O
a	O
Periwig	O
maker	O
of	O
Burntwood	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
with	O
an	O
Advertisement	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
Cock	O
and	O
Coach	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
Assistance	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
first	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
a	O
Minute	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
they	O
were	O
buying	O
2	O
Whips	O
of	O
a	O
Sadler	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
hired	O
two	O
Horse	O
for	O
Colchester	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
James	O
I	O
was	O
come	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
up	O
for	O
robbing	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
a	O
Hair	O
Merchant	O
,	O
on	O
Snow-Hill	O
.	O
The	O
Neighbours	O
said	O
,	O
Take	O
care	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
put	O
Pistols	O
.	O
I	O
demanded	O
the	O
Pistols	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
let	O
me	O
take	O
them	O
quietly	O
,	O
and	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
much	O
surprized	O
;	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
are	O
not	O
the	O
Person	O
you	O
need	O
not	O
be	O
afraid	O
,	O
for	O
you	O
can	O
come	O
to	O
no	O
harm	O
;	O
I	O
wish	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
show	O
you	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
all	O
the	O
Effects	O
,	O
and	O
will	O
produce	O
them	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
handful	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
particulars	O
of	O
which	O
I	O
wrote	O
down	O
for	O
my	O
own	O
Security	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
eight	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Foreign	O
Gold	O
of	O
3	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
each	O
,	O
I	O
piece	O
of	O
5	O
Moidores	O
,	O
2	O
pieces	O
of	O
36	O
s.	O
each	O
,	O
1	O
double	O
Guinea	O
,	O
12	O
Moidores	O
,	O
and	O
45	O
Guineas	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Jeffries	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
those	O
Guineas	O
was	O
not	O
good	O
.	O
J.	O
Smith	O
.	O
1	O
Spanish	O
Pistole	O
,	O
5	O
Broad	O
Pieces	O
of	O
23.	O
each	O
,	O
half	O
a	O
Broad	O
Piece	O
of	O
11	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
2	O
Quarter	O
Moidores	O
,	O
3	O
Bank-Notes	O
,	O
1	O
for	O
100	O
l.	O
1	O
for	O
50	O
l.	O
and	O
1	O
for	O
40	O
l.	O
Mr.	O
Jeffries	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
put	O
those	O
Notes	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
F.	O
Smith	O
.	O
1	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
1	O
Silver	O
Snuff-Box	O
with	O
a	O
spotted	O
Shell	O
,	O
3	O
Mourning	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
Pistols	O
;	O
and	O
all	O
these	O
Things	O
he	O
said	O
were	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
his	O
Master	O
Jeffries	O
.	O
My	O
Assistant	O
took	O
another	O
Pair	O
of	O
Pistols	O
from	O
David	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Who	O
had	O
the	O
Bundle	O
?	O
F.	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
either	O
in	O
David	O
's	O
Lap	O
,	O
or	O
lay	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
D.	O
B	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
order	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Bundle	O
and	O
carry	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
?	O
F.	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Stock	I-pers
.	O
I	O
assisted	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
seemed	O
much	O
concerned	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
first	O
the	O
Bundle	O
was	O
on	O
David	O
's	O
Knees	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
preseurly	O
laid	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
Goods	O
taken	O
from	O
James	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Pistols	O
from	O
David	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
hear	O
the	O
Charge	O
,	O
Prisoners	O
;	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
your	O
Defence	O
?	O
J	B-pers
.	I-pers
B	I-pers
.	I-pers
'T	O
is	O
easy	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
Man	O
who	O
knows	O
his	O
own	O
Innocence	O
to	O
find	O
Words	O
to	O
defend	O
himself	O
;	O
but	O
how	O
difficult	O
a	O
Task	O
is	O
this	O
for	O
one	O
who	O
,	O
like	O
me	O
,	O
is	O
loaded	O
with	O
Guilt	O
?	O
One	O
who	O
is	O
sensible	O
of	O
having	O
committed	O
a	O
Crime	O
of	O
so	O
high	O
a	O
Nature	O
against	O
two	O
kind	O
and	O
generous	O
Masters	O
.	O
Yet	O
I	O
hope	O
there	O
are	O
some	O
Circumstances	O
of	O
Alleviation	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
appeal	O
to	O
my	O
Master	O
himself	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
,	O
during	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
his	O
Service	O
,	O
behaved	O
myself	O
with	O
Honesty	O
and	O
Integrity	O
in	O
all	O
Thing	O
,	O
except	O
in	O
this	O
one	O
unhappy	O
Instance	O
.	O
'T	O
is	O
not	O
possible	O
to	O
declare	O
with	O
what	O
a	O
Compulsion	O
on	O
my	O
own	O
Mind	O
I	O
committed	O
this	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
Strugglings	O
I	O
felt	O
in	O
my	O
Soul	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
overcome	O
and	O
yielded	O
to	O
the	O
Temptation	O
.	O
My	O
Master	O
having	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
provided	O
himself	O
with	O
another	O
Book-keeper	O
,	O
I	O
applied	O
to	O
the	O
Honourable	O
John	B-pers
Drummond	I-pers
,	O
by	O
whose	O
Means	O
I	O
was	O
recommended	O
as	O
a	O
Book-keeper	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Woodny	O
,	O
a	O
Scotch	O
Factor	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Woodny	O
requir	O
'd	O
200	O
l.	O
Security	O
;	O
my	O
Master	O
Jeffries	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
Character	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
bound	O
for	O
any	O
Man	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
having	O
no	O
Friend	O
in	O
London	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
be	O
so	O
free	O
with	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
desire	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
bound	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
Mr.	O
Woodny	O
's	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
no	O
Prospect	O
of	O
any	O
other	O
Service	O
.	O
Then	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
the	O
base	O
Thought	O
of	O
wronging	O
my	O
Master	O
enter	O
'd	O
my	O
Soul	O
.	O
Poverty	O
and	O
Want	O
appear	O
'd	O
frightful	O
to	O
my	O
Imagination	O
,	O
and	O
raised	O
a	O
Multitude	O
of	O
false	O
Reasonings	O
and	O
Suggestions	O
,	O
which	O
at	O
length	O
prevailed	O
over	O
me	O
;	O
Words	O
can	O
not	O
express	O
the	O
Terrors	O
that	O
attended	O
my	O
Guilt	O
.	O
How	O
often	O
was	O
I	O
upon	O
the	O
point	O
of	O
returning	O
to	O
my	O
Master	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Dread	O
of	O
Shame	O
still	O
prevented	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
hurried	O
me	O
on	O
to	O
my	O
Ruin	O
!	O
When	O
the	O
Persons	O
who	O
took	O
us	O
entered	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
we	O
made	O
no	O
Resistance	O
,	O
but	O
peaceably	O
surrendered	O
our	O
selves	O
to	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
readily	O
delivered	O
up	O
every	O
thing	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
wrongfully	O
taken	O
.	O
As	O
for	O
my	O
Brother	O
I	O
hope	O
he	O
will	O
not	O
suffer	O
for	O
my	O
Crime	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
ignorant	O
of	O
.	O
D.	O
B.	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
on	O
my	O
Brother	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
we	O
went	O
away	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
Walk	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
accordingly	O
met	O
him	O
about	O
5	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Time	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
own	O
Disposal	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Pistols	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Bundle	O
to	O
carry	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
I	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
Sword	O
put	O
up	O
in	O
that	O
Bundle	O
so	O
as	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
seen	O
?	O
Swain	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Bundle	O
of	O
soul	O
Linen	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
Shirts	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Sword-blade	O
was	O
broke	O
off	O
pretty	O
short	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
David	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
James	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
3.	O
Faith	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Sheets	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Mandevile	I-pers
,	O
July	O
3	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
4.	O
Mary	B-pers
Alder	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
Value	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Byrom	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
10	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
5.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Farrant	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
marrying	O
Mary	B-pers
Humphries	I-pers
,	O
his	O
former	O
Wife	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
being	O
then	O
alive	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
6.	O
George	B-pers
Innis	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
Value	O
37	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Bracknel	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
8	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
7.	O
Robert	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
Value	O
1	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
August	O
18	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
8.	O
Richard	B-pers
James	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
14	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Turenag	O
,	O
Val	O
.	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
,	O
Aug.	O
21	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
9.	O
John	B-pers
Cane	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bywater	I-pers
,	O
July	O
20	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
10.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Table-cloth	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Yardly	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
8	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
11.	O
Anne	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Table-cloth	O
and	O
a	O
Shift	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Seymour	I-pers
,	O
September	O
2	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
12.	O
Richard	B-pers
How	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Saw	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Debden	I-pers
,	O
July	O
15	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
13.	O
William	B-pers
Lilly	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
,	O
August	O
5	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
14.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hobbs	I-pers
of	O
Shoreditch	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
1	O
Broad	O
Piece	O
,	O
2	O
Guineas	O
,	O
a	O
half	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
44	O
s.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Sparks	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Edw	B-pers
Fuller	I-pers
,	O
July	O
7	O
.	O
Philip	O
Sparks	O
.	O
My	O
Mother	O
lodged	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Fuller	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
did	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Box	O
under	O
my	O
Mother	O
's	O
Bed	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
told	O
in	O
there	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
following	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
often	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
Mother	O
,	O
was	O
suspected	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
examined	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
and	O
sign	O
'd	O
her	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
15.	O
Catharine	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
of	O
Aldersgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Great	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
2	O
Table	O
Cloths	O
,	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Books	O
,	O
one	O
called	O
the	O
Holy	O
Bible	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
the	O
History	O
of	O
Moll	O
Flanders	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
,	O
July	O
6	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
miss	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
examined	O
,	O
and	O
confessed	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
16.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Powis	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Brewer	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
steal	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
Joseph	O
Brewer	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Raven	B-place
Alehouse	I-place
in	O
Fetter-Lane	B-place
;	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
Cellar	O
Window	O
next	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
with	O
two	O
folding	O
Doors	O
and	O
a	O
Flap	O
,	O
I	O
open	O
those	O
Doors	O
and	O
take	O
up	O
the	O
Flap	O
or	O
Plank	O
to	O
let	O
down	O
my	O
Drink	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
those	O
Doors	O
you	O
may	O
either	O
go	O
directly	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
or	O
the	O
Ground-floor	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
all	O
over	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Ground-floor	O
I	O
have	O
likewise	O
a	O
Back-door	O
which	O
goes	O
into	O
my	O
Yard	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
parted	O
by	O
a	O
low	O
Wall	O
from	O
my	O
Neighbour	O
Mr.	O
Ashley	O
's	O
[	O
Astly	O
]	O
Yard	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
drinking	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
on	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
it	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
I	O
made	O
fast	O
all	O
my	O
Doors	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
between	O
2	O
and	O
3	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
Watch	O
call	O
'd	O
me	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
my	O
Cellar-door	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
We	O
search	O
'd	O
my	O
House	O
without	O
finding	O
the	O
Thief	O
,	O
but	O
then	O
seeing	O
the	O
Back-door	O
open	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Ashley	O
's	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
under	O
a	O
Dresser	O
in	O
a	O
Shed	O
.	O
We	O
examin	O
'd	O
his	O
Pockets	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
these	O
2	O
Spikes	O
,	O
all	O
these	O
Picklock-Keys	O
,	O
this	O
Wax-Candle	O
,	O
this	O
Lancet	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
to	O
let	O
People	O
Blood	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Iron-pin	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
the	O
Pin	O
of	O
my	O
Cellar-Window	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
Locksmith	O
by	O
Trade	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
cast	O
last	O
March	O
was	O
a	O
Twelvemonth	O
for	O
Transportation	O
;	O
but	O
his	O
Father	O
who	O
lives	O
in	O
good	O
Credit	O
,	O
made	O
Friends	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
his	O
Punishment	O
here	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
made	O
several	O
Pins	O
;	O
is	O
there	O
any	O
Mark	O
upon	O
this	O
Pin	O
that	O
you	O
can	O
swear	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
yours	O
?	O
Brewer	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
;	O
it	O
fits	O
the	O
Key	O
and	O
the	O
Iron-bar	O
of	O
my	O
Window	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
over-night	O
and	O
key	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
Cellar-door	O
open	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
But	O
has	O
it	O
no	O
particular	O
Mark	O
that	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
by	O
?	O
For	O
one	O
Pin	O
may	O
be	O
like	O
another	O
.	O
Brewer	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
this	O
,	O
that	O
after	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
said	O
,	O
Now	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
.	O
And	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
look	O
on	O
my	O
Till	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
by	O
several	O
Marks	O
that	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
an	O
Attempt	O
to	O
break	O
it	O
open	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
.	O
Hearing	O
an	O
Outcry	O
of	O
Thieves	O
between	O
2	O
and	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
Bed	O
and	O
came	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Ashley	O
's	O
Yard	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
dark	O
then	O
?	O
Graham	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
not	O
Day-light	O
enough	O
to	O
distinguish	O
a	O
Man	O
's	O
Countenance	O
?	O
Graham	B-pers
No	I-pers
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
then	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
who	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
Ashley	O
's	O
Yard	O
?	O
Graham	O
.	O
The	O
People	O
brought	O
Candles	O
;	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
got	O
Spits	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Leg	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
For	O
God	O
's	O
Sake	O
do	O
n't	O
use	O
me	O
thus	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
surrender	O
myself	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
hurt	O
him	O
much	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
have	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
so	O
much	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
walk	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
wish	O
I	O
may	O
die	O
of	O
my	O
Wounds	O
before	O
I	O
come	O
to	O
be	O
try	O
'd	O
,	O
for	O
my	O
poor	O
Father	O
's	O
Sake	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
have	O
requited	O
him	O
so	O
ill	O
for	O
his	O
Kindness	O
in	O
getting	O
me	O
off	O
from	O
Transportion	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
these	O
Scissars	O
and	O
this	O
Pin	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
him	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
that	O
Pin	O
when	O
you	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
?	O
Graham	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
before	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Billers	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Alderman	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Use	O
of	O
this	O
Lancet	O
?	O
and	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
very	O
audaciously	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
let	O
People	O
Blood	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
After	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
Accomplices	O
?	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
acted	O
by	O
my	O
self	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
desire	O
to	O
suffer	O
by	O
my	O
self	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
Pin	O
was	O
found	O
?	O
Who	O
heard	O
me	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
those	O
Words	O
the	O
Minute	O
the	O
Pin	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
you	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
when	O
you	O
was	O
brought	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Dighten	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
present	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
now	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Lugg	I-pers
,	O
Watchman	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
beat	O
one	O
a	O
Clock	O
all	O
was	O
safe	O
at	O
Mr	O
.	O
Brewer	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
past	O
two	O
,	O
I	O
preserv	O
'd	O
[	O
observ	O
'd	O
]	O
the	O
Iron-bar	O
of	O
his	O
Cellar-Window	O
was	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Pin	O
was	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
Mr	O
.	O
Brewer	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
stand	O
and	O
watch	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
.	O
I	O
suppose	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
heard	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
got	O
out	O
backwards	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
;	O
but	O
we	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Ashley	O
's	O
Yard	O
.	O
William	B-pers
T.	I-pers
I	I-pers
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
3	O
Days	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
could	O
commit	O
such	O
erroneous	O
Crimes	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
nothing	O
vex	O
'd	O
him	O
so	O
much	O
,	O
as	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
Presence	O
of	O
Mind	O
to	O
throw	O
the	O
Pin	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
for	O
nothing	O
had	O
so	O
great	O
an	O
Effect	O
upon	O
him	O
as	O
their	O
finding	O
that	O
Pin	O
.	O
He	O
felt	O
such	O
a	O
sudden	O
Damp	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
struck	O
with	O
Death	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Astly	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
an	O
Out-cry	O
of	O
Thieves	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
along	O
my	O
Mother	O
's	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Shed	O
.	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
to	O
my	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
Thief	O
was	O
in	O
our	O
Yard	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
taken	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
under	O
a	O
Dresser	O
with	O
a	O
Board	O
put	O
before	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Pin	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
upon	O
finding	O
the	O
Pin	O
?	O
Astly	O
.	O
Not	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Could	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
any	O
other	O
Way	O
into	O
your	O
Yard	O
than	O
over	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wall	O
?	O
Astly	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
for	O
none	O
of	O
our	O
Doors	O
were	O
open	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
over	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
away	O
about	O
12	O
,	O
very	O
much	O
fuddled	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
Woman	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Astley	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
somebody	O
coming	O
along	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
talking	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
backwards	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
a	O
spiteful	O
,	O
malicious	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
said	O
to	O
be	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
concealing	O
Mr.	O
Hossel	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
try	O
'd	O
for	O
stealing	O
Bank	O
Notes	O
.	O
As	O
for	O
the	O
Things	O
that	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
all	O
Materials	O
that	O
I	O
use	O
in	O
my	O
Trade	O
as	O
a	O
Locksmith	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
use	O
the	O
Lancet	O
in	O
that	O
way	O
too	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
used	O
that	O
as	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
studied	O
Blooding	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Parts	O
of	O
Surgery	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
making	O
Locks	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Billers	I-pers
,	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
robb	O
'd	O
a	O
Kinsman	O
of	O
his	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
No	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
can	O
hang	O
him	O
,	O
there	O
's	O
40	O
l.	O
for	O
you	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
17.	O
James	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
of	O
St.	O
Mary	O
le	O
Bow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
forging	O
and	O
causing	O
to	O
be	O
forged	O
(	O
after	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
June	O
1729	O
)	O
a	O
certain	O
Writing	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Last	O
Will	O
and	O
Testament	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
defraud	O
Mary	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
of	O
his	O
Wages	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
publishing	O
the	O
said	O
Will	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
forged	O
,	O
August	O
20	O
.	O
The	O
Council	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
opened	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
who	O
frequently	O
lent	O
Money	O
to	O
Sailors	O
;	O
that	O
't	O
is	O
customary	O
for	O
the	O
Sailors	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Will	O
to	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
whom	O
they	O
borrow	O
Money	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
John	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
having	O
enter	O
'd	O
himself	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Bridgewater	O
,	O
in	O
Service	O
of	O
the	O
East-India	O
Company	O
,	O
did	O
really	O
make	O
a	O
Will	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
sign	O
'd	O
Nov.	O
30	O
.	O
1726	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
returning	O
safe	O
from	O
this	O
Voyage	O
,	O
did	O
go	O
a	O
second	O
Voyage	O
for	O
the	O
East-Indies	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Ship	O
Forbidge	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Gosprit	I-pers
Master	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
Voyage	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
hearing	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
Widow	O
Mary	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
had	O
made	O
any	O
Will	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
intended	O
to	O
administer	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
published	O
this	O
second	O
Will	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
true	O
Will	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
sign	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
1728	O
,	O
and	O
witnessed	O
by	O
Newton	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Macafy	I-pers
,	O
who	O
were	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
the	O
first	O
Will	O
.	O
That	O
this	O
second	O
Will	O
being	O
the	O
same	O
in	O
all	O
Respects	O
as	O
the	O
first	O
,	O
except	O
in	O
the	O
Date	O
of	O
the	O
Year	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
it	O
is	O
mentioned	O
,	O
that	O
John	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
was	O
then	O
a	O
Sailor	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Bridgewater	O
;	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
second	O
,	O
the	O
Word	O
Bridgewater	O
seems	O
to	O
be	O
eras	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
Words	O
are	O
interlin	O
'd	O
in	O
a	O
different	O
Hand	O
and	O
Ink	O
,	O
Now	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Ship	O
Forbidge	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Gosprit	I-pers
Master	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
will	O
endeavour	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
this	O
pretended	O
second	O
Will	O
is	O
no	O
other	O
than	O
the	O
first	O
Will	O
alter	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Date	O
and	O
the	O
Ship	O
's	O
Name	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
on	O
November	O
30	O
.	O
1728	O
,	O
when	O
this	O
second	O
Will	O
was	O
said	O
to	O
be	O
sign	O
'd	O
in	O
London	O
by	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
John	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
down	O
at	O
Gravesend	O
,	O
receiving	O
his	O
River-pay	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
therefore	O
it	O
is	O
done	O
without	O
the	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
and	O
is	O
false	O
and	O
forged	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
original	O
Will	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
I	O
brought	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
Perogative-Office	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
Clerk	O
to	O
the	O
Register	O
.	O
It	O
has	O
been	O
pleaded	O
in	O
Behalf	O
of	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
.	O
[	O
Then	O
the	O
Will	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
agreed	O
with	O
the	O
Copy	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Was	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Widow	O
of	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
John	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
to	O
receive	O
the	O
Wages	O
due	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
with	O
this	O
Will	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Probat	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
the	O
Money	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
Here	O
Mrs.	O
Robinson	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
know	O
John	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
?	O
Newton	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
Look	O
on	O
that	O
Paper	O
;	O
what	O
is	O
it	O
?	O
Robinson	O
.	O
'T	O
is	O
the	O
Will	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
.	O
Council	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
execute	O
it	O
?	O
Robinson	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
I	O
sign	O
'd	O
my	O
Name	O
.	O
Here	O
it	O
is	O
as	O
a	O
Witness	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
Where	O
?	O
Robinson	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
Queen's-Head	O
Alley	O
,	O
in	O
Wapping	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
ago	O
?	O
Robinson	O
.	O
About	O
4	O
Years	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
't	O
was	O
but	O
4	O
Years	O
ago	O
?	O
What	O
Ship	O
did	O
John	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
then	O
belong	O
to	O
?	O
Robinson	O
.	O
The	O
Forbidge	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Why	O
this	O
proves	O
the	O
second	O
Will	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
Here	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Macafy	I-pers
;	O
Is	O
that	O
your	O
Mark	O
?	O
Macafy	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
Who	O
Signed	O
that	O
Will	O
?	O
Macafy	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
one	O
they	O
called	O
John	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
sign	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
him	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
Where	O
?	O
Macafy	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
When	O
?	O
Macafy	O
.	O
About	O
4	O
Years	O
ago	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
more	O
such	O
Witnesses	O
?	O
Council	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
some	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
John	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
was	O
several	O
Miles	O
from	O
London	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
that	O
the	O
second	O
Will	O
is	O
said	O
to	O
be	O
Signed	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Philpot	I-pers
.	O
The	O
deceased	O
John	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
was	O
my	O
Son-in-Law	O
,	O
he	O
ow	O
'd	O
me	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
threatned	O
to	O
Trouble	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
him	O
afraid	O
to	O
come	O
on	O
Shore	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
kept	O
on	O
Board	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Philpot	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
Time	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Then	O
you	O
might	O
as	O
well	O
have	O
said	O
nothing	O
.	O
-	O
Barns	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Flying-Horse	O
at	O
Gravesend	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Day	O
as	O
John	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
received	O
his	O
River-Pay	O
for	O
the	O
Forbidge	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
our	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
there	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
the	O
-	O
[	O
He	O
pauses	O
,	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wass	I-pers
prompts	O
him	O
]	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
1728	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
And	O
how	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
remember	O
so	O
exactly	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
30th	O
Day	O
?	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
particular	O
Reason	O
for	O
it	O
?	O
Might	O
it	O
not	O
have	O
been	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
?	O
Barns	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
last	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
Month	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wass	I-pers
.	O
Remember	O
the	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
Month	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
November	O
[	O
aside	O
to	O
Ann	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
]	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Flying	O
Horse	O
at	O
Gravesend	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
used	O
our	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
the	O
River-Pay	O
of	O
the	O
Ship	O
Forbidge	O
was	O
paid	O
there	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
November	O
;	O
and	O
Ward	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
both	O
lay	O
there	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
Officer	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
here	O
's	O
this	O
Man	O
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wass	I-pers
,	O
prompts	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
.	O
A	O
Gentleman	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
too	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Swear	O
those	O
two	O
Persons	O
.	O
[	O
Th	O
sworn	O
.	O
]	O
Now	O
what	O
did	O
you	O
hear	O
him	O
say	O
?	O
Officer	O
.	O
He	O
bid	O
them	O
remember	O
the	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
Month	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
named	O
some	O
Day	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
forget	O
what	O
Day	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Gentleman	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
,	O
Remember	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
J.	O
Wass	O
.	O
Suppose	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Harm	O
in	O
that	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
No	O
harm	O
,	O
Sir	O
?	O
When	O
a	O
Man	O
's	O
Life	O
is	O
at	O
Stake	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
to	O
put	O
Words	O
in	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
Mouths	O
,	O
and	O
direct	O
them	O
what	O
to	O
swear	O
?	O
Officer	O
take	O
him	O
into	O
Custody	O
.	O
Wass	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
-	O
Court	O
.	O
Take	O
him	O
away	O
to	O
Newgate	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
order	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
his	O
Indictment	O
.	O
18.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Thorn	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
marrying	O
John	B-pers
Green	I-pers
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Second	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
present	O
Majesty	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
Magdalen	I-place
Old	I-place
Fish-street	I-place
,	O
her	O
former	O
Husband	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Howell	I-pers
,	O
to	O
whom	O
she	O
was	O
married	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
in	O
the	O
7th	O
Year	O
of	O
King	O
George	O
I.	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	O
.	O
Brides	O
,	O
being	O
then	O
living	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Farley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
my	O
Cousin	O
John	B-pers
Howell	I-pers
married	O
in	O
the	O
Fleet	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
10	O
Years	O
ago	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
an	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
a	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
live	O
together	O
as	O
Man	O
and	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
never	O
bedded	O
her	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Langdon	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
I	O
saw	O
John	B-pers
Howell	I-pers
alive	O
in	O
Hertfordshire	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
married	O
her	O
second	O
Husband	O
as	O
a	O
Widow	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Howell	O
.	O
John	O
Green	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
July	O
9	O
.	O
1729.	O
at	O
St.	O
Mary	O
Magdalen	O
's	O
Old	O
Fish-street	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
Parson	O
's	O
Name	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
an	O
Apprentice	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
a	O
little	O
Estate	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
demand	O
a	O
Quarter	O
's	O
Rent	O
of	O
her	O
Brother	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
none	O
,	O
for	O
her	O
Husband	O
Howell	O
was	O
alive	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Here	O
,	O
you	O
Husband	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
your	O
nown	O
Child	O
.	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
?	O
You	O
are	O
my	O
lawful	O
Husband	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Howell	I-pers
,	O
and	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
another	O
Wife	O
.	O
You	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
never	O
bedded	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Howell	I-pers
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
he	O
's	O
no	O
Husband	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
20	O
l.	O
a	O
Year	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
sold	O
5	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
your	O
Name	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
your	O
Use	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
had	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
now	O
because	O
my	O
Brother	O
wo	O
n't	O
let	O
you	O
have	O
any	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
you	O
want	O
to	O
turn	O
me	O
off	O
.	O
But	O
you	O
are	O
my	O
lawful	O
Husband	O
,	O
I	O
say	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
Man	O
but	O
you	O
.	O
John	O
Green	O
.	O
How	O
can	O
that	O
be	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
received	O
10	O
l.	O
on	O
Account	O
of	O
a	O
Bastard-Child	O
that	O
you	O
had	O
before	O
I	O
married	O
you	O
?	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
19	O
.	O
*	O
Peter	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privatly	O
stealing	O
6	O
l.	O
6	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Wall	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
her	O
Husband	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wall	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Christ-church	I-place
,	O
July	O
8	O
.	O
*	O
See	O
the	O
Tryal	O
of	O
Peter	O
Bell	O
in	O
the	O
Sessions-Paper	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
P.	O
4	O
.	O
Ann	O
Wall	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
buying	O
a	O
Peck	O
of	O
Peas	O
in	O
Newgate-market	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
last	O
Day	O
of	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Hand	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Butcher	O
stopt	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
3	O
Farthings	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lost	O
6	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
3	O
Farthings	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Pocket	O
was	O
cut	O
.	O
Allen	B-pers
Spencel	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
my	O
Stall	O
,	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
o	O
'	O
Saturday-night	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
cry	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
cryed	O
stop	O
Thief	O
too	O
.	O
I	O
seized	O
him	O
directly	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
his	O
Hands	O
was	O
shut	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
him	O
open	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Money	O
drop	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
3	O
Farthings	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
whose	O
Money	O
it	O
was	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
none	O
of	O
his	O
.	O
Ann	O
Wall	O
.	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
but	O
6	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
3	O
Farthings	O
.	O
Spencel	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
dropt	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
3	O
Farthings	O
;	O
for	O
there	O
were	O
2	O
Half-Crowns	O
,	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Sixpence	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
Farthings	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
20.	O
Ann	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pocket-Book	O
,	O
1	O
Promissary	O
Note	O
for	O
20	O
l.	O
dated	O
Octob	O
.	O
9	O
.	O
1731	O
.	O
Sign	O
'd	O
by	O
Rob	B-pers
Ashley	I-pers
;	O
1	O
Note	O
dated	O
Jan.	O
7	O
.	O
1731.	O
for	O
100	O
l.	O
Sign	O
'd	O
Wm	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
;	O
one	O
Note	O
dated	O
March	O
6	O
.	O
1731.	O
for	O
20	O
l.	O
Signed	O
Eliz	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
;	O
one	O
Note	O
dated	O
April	O
6	O
.	O
1732	O
,	O
for	O
52	O
l.	O
9	O
s.	O
Signed	O
Thomas	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
;	O
and	O
one	O
Note	O
dated	O
May	O
13	O
.	O
1732.	O
for	O
8	O
l.	O
8	O
s.	O
Signed	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Williams	O
;	O
all	O
payable	O
to	O
Evan	B-pers
Hughs	I-pers
,	O
or	O
Order	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Evan	B-pers
Hughs	I-pers
,	O
July	O
9	O
.	O
Evan	B-pers
Hughs	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Sunday-Noon	O
I	O
locked	O
my	O
Pocket-Book	O
with	O
the	O
Notes	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
Bureau	O
,	O
which	O
stands	O
in	O
my	O
Chambers	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
15.	O
in	O
Clifford	O
's	O
Inn	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Dine	O
with	O
the	O
Dean	O
of	O
Durham	O
at	O
Chelsea	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
usually	O
do	O
on	O
Sundays	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
's	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
returned	O
from	O
thence	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Gray	O
,	O
the	O
Dean	O
's	O
Brother	O
,	O
about	O
8	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
Home	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
Laundress	O
waiting	O
for	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Gardens	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Chambers	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Drawers	O
of	O
my	O
Bureau	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
Floor	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
acquainted	O
her	O
Sister	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
who	O
advised	O
her	O
to	O
leave	O
every	O
thing	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
lock	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
so	O
accordingly	O
.	O
In	O
this	O
Condition	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
Room	O
;	O
my	O
Drawers	O
were	O
tumbled	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Pocket-book	O
with	O
all	O
the	O
Notes	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
advertis	O
'd	O
'em	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Reward	O
for	O
whoever	O
brought	O
'em	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Richard	B-pers
Morson	I-pers
,	O
Banker	O
in	O
Lombard-street	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
about	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
Custom-house	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
Attorney	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
in	O
Red-lion-Court	O
in	O
Cursitor	O
's	O
Alley	O
;	O
my	O
Man	O
has	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
Ann	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Woman	O
of	O
the	O
Town	O
,	O
has	O
got	O
such	O
a	O
Pocket-case	O
,	O
with	O
such	O
Notes	O
as	O
you	O
have	O
advertised	O
.	O
His	O
Man	O
at	O
tended	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
the	O
Pocket-Case	O
had	O
the	O
King's-Arms	O
and	O
City	O
Arms	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
found	O
me	O
out	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
by	O
Letters	O
in	O
the	O
Case	O
,	O
directed	O
for	O
Evan	B-pers
Hughs	I-pers
,	O
at	O
his	O
Seat	O
in	O
the	O
Long-Room	O
in	O
the	O
Custom-House	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
from	O
Justice	O
Giffard	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Graham	O
to	O
the	O
Rummer	O
and	O
Horse-shoe	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
Pocket-Case	O
with	O
Notes	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
found	O
such	O
a	O
one	O
.	O
Graham	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
Constable	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
whom	O
she	O
called	O
Broadon	O
P	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Says	O
she	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
walk	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
Publick	O
,	O
but	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
fetch	O
'em	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
willing	O
to	O
trust	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
followed	O
her	O
close	O
to	O
her	O
Lodgings	O
.	O
There	O
she	O
told	O
us	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
's	O
Tester	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
'em	O
accordingly	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
'em	O
on	O
a	O
Bench	O
in	O
Gray's-Inn-Walks	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
James	O
Warner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Hides	O
,	O
in	O
Charles-street	O
,	O
Covent-Garden	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
very	O
merry	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
Reason	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
Reason	O
enough	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
had	O
found	O
that	O
in	O
Gray's-Inn	O
Walks	O
that	O
would	O
make	O
her	O
merry	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
then	O
tell	O
me	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
Bed	O
with	O
her	O
-	O
I	O
and	O
the	O
Landlady	O
searched	O
her	O
Pockets	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Pocket-Case	O
and	O
Notes	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Eliz	B-pers
Hansor	I-pers
.	O
That	O
Day	O
was	O
Sev'n-night	O
before	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
Coffee-House	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Publick	O
Room	O
shewed	O
the	O
Case	O
and	O
Notes	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
Gray's-Inn	O
Walks	O
.	O
A	O
Gentleman	O
there	O
look	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
Notes	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
These	O
are	O
of	O
Value	O
to	O
the	O
Owner	O
,	O
but	O
of	O
none	O
to	O
you	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
sealed	O
them	O
up	O
.	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Hide	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
breakfasted	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
complaining	O
of	O
the	O
Head-ach	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
'd	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
a	O
Walk	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
came	O
Home	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
found	O
a	O
Pocket-Case	O
and	O
Notes	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
shewn	O
'em	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Hanson	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
shewed	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Warner	O
reckon	O
'd	O
the	O
Notes	O
up	O
to	O
300	O
l.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
21.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Pardoe	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Davil	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
Sept.	O
2	O
.	O
Eliz	B-pers
Davil	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
into	O
my	O
Service	O
this	O
Day	O
was	O
Sev'n-night	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
2	O
other	O
Girls	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
her	O
lye	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
they	O
should	O
spoil	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Victualling	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
a	O
Porringers	O
of	O
Silver	O
in	O
a	O
Day	O
,	O
during	O
the	O
Time	O
of	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Fair	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
one	O
Pint	O
Porringer	O
with	O
12	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
Paper	O
with	O
6	O
l.	O
into	O
my	O
Drawers	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
her	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
clean	O
Pair	O
of	O
Rolls	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Drawers	O
,	O
to	O
roll	O
my	O
Legs	O
,	O
for	O
you	O
must	O
know	O
I	O
am	O
pretty	O
weighty	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Legs	O
are	O
apt	O
to	O
swell	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
me	O
the	O
Rolls	O
,	O
my	O
Cook	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
Come	O
down	O
ye	O
Bitch	O
,	O
and	O
pare	O
the	O
Turmips	O
.	O
So	O
down	O
she	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Son	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Drawers	O
being	O
open	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
cut	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
all	O
my	O
Money	O
;	O
however	O
,	O
the	O
Pint	O
Porringer	O
was	O
safe	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
6	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
Paper	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
and	O
by	O
and	O
by	O
she	O
came	O
up	O
again	O
to	O
lace	O
my	O
Scays	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
the	O
Paper	O
was	O
missing	O
.	O
Lord	O
,	O
bless	O
me	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
wonder	O
who	O
could	O
do	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
,	O
upon	O
examining	O
her	O
closely	O
,	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
given	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
young	O
Fellow	O
,	O
who	O
persuaded	O
her	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
Knife	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
kill	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
get	O
my	O
Money	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Ye	O
Bitch	O
,	O
this	O
will	O
serve	O
me	O
but	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
the	O
Fellow	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
brought	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
cleared	O
him	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Price	I-pers
.	O
As	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
she	O
owned	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Moidore	O
and	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
in	O
Silver	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
22	O
.	O
*	O
Mary	B-pers
Tomlin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bartholomew	I-place
the	I-place
Great	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Seagood	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Day-time	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
others	O
being	O
then	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
laced	O
Cambrick	O
Head	O
and	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
25	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Hat	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Seagood	I-pers
,	O
July	O
27	O
.	O
*	O
Mary	O
Tomlin	O
was	O
try	O
'd	O
last	O
Sessions	O
.	O
Vid	O
.	O
Sessions-Paper	O
,	O
Numb	O
.	O
6.	O
p.	O
171	O
.	O
Henry	O
Seagood	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Little	B-place
Bartholomew-Close	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
at	O
Noon	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
Sash	O
of	O
my	O
Ground-room	O
next	O
the	O
Yard	O
shut	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Goods	O
lock	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
my	O
Drawers	O
;	O
but	O
returning	O
in	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
Sash	O
pull	O
'd	O
down	O
,	O
my	O
Locks	O
broke	O
,	O
the	O
Drawers	O
upon	O
the	O
Floor	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Apparel	O
and	O
Linen	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
15	O
l.	O
A	O
Girl	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
a	O
Creature	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
there	O
?	O
And	O
the	O
Creature	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
's	O
that	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
ye	O
Bitch	O
,	O
or	O
some	O
such	O
Words	O
.	O
The	O
Girl	O
shew	O
'd	O
us	O
which	O
Way	O
she	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
follow	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
Long-lane	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Pagl	I-pers
.	O
I	O
sell	O
Old-Cloaths	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
'd	O
buy	O
any	O
old	O
Gowns	O
;	O
and	O
with	O
that	O
she	O
threw	O
down	O
a	O
Bundle	O
with	O
these	O
4	O
rich	O
Gowns	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
laced	O
Head-cloths	O
and	O
Ruffles	O
.	O
She	O
asked	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
d.	O
for	O
the	O
Russels	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
honestly	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
stepping	O
out	O
to	O
call	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
she	O
run	O
down	O
Seacoal-lane	O
.	O
Eliz	B-pers
Drake	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Yard	O
behind	O
his	O
Door	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
ye	O
do	O
there	O
?	O
says	O
I	O
.	O
What	O
's	O
that	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
ye	O
Drapgaiiows	O
Toad	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
she	O
went	O
off	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
23.	O
Charles	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Soldier	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bartholomew	I-place
the	I-place
Less	I-place
.	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Walter	B-pers
Wade	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
drawn	O
Sword	O
,	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
Right	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Breadth	O
of	O
2	O
Inches	O
,	O
and	O
Depth	O
of	O
1/4	O
of	O
an	O
Inch	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
other	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
inside	O
Part	O
of	O
his	O
Right-Hand-Wrist	O
of	O
the	O
Breadth	O
of	O
3	O
Inches	O
,	O
and	O
Depth	O
of	O
1	O
Inch	O
June	O
8	O
.	O
of	O
which	O
mortal	O
Wounds	O
he	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
July	O
following	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Bush	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Man-in-the-Moon	B-place
Alehouse	I-place
,	O
in	O
Ironmonger	B-place
Row	I-place
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Quartered	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
himself	O
very	O
civilly	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
trusted	O
him	O
to	O
draw	O
Drink	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
was	O
Quarter	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
next	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
between	O
3	O
and	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
drunk	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
first	O
refused	O
to	O
draw	O
him	O
any	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
3	O
Pints	O
,	O
one	O
after	O
another	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
then	O
grew	O
extreamly	O
troublesome	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Deceased	O
swore	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
carry	O
him	O
out	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
struggled	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
beat	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
violently	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
into	O
his	O
own	O
Room	O
;	O
the	O
Deceased	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
pull	O
'd	O
him	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
shut	O
it	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
staid	O
there	O
damning	O
his	O
Blood	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
persuaded	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
down	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
drawn	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
frighted	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
away	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
thing	O
farther	O
done	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
being	O
very	O
troublesome	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
out	O
.	O
They	O
struggled	O
in	O
the	O
Entry	O
,	O
and	O
fought	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Coat	O
was	O
torn	O
;	O
the	O
Deceased	O
beat	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
dragg	O
'd	O
him	O
about	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
some	O
Time	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
while	O
we	O
got	O
the	O
Deceased	O
out	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
down	O
with	O
a	O
drawn	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
pass	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Deceased	O
.	O
We	O
got	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
shut	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
got	O
out	O
o'th	O
'	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
the	O
Deceased	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Hair	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
he	O
let	O
go	O
his	O
Hold	O
,	O
got	O
up	O
went	O
a	O
little	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
down	O
again	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
afterwards	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Hospital	O
,	O
where	O
his	O
Hand	O
was	O
cut	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
died	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
was	O
very	O
Rusoulous	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Cut	O
over	O
the	O
Head	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
's	O
all	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
24.	O
Henry	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Catherines	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Saint	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Shagreen	O
Case	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
an	O
Agate	O
handle	O
Knife	O
and	O
Fork	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
2	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
s.	O
1	O
Silver	O
Buckle	O
set	O
with	O
Stones	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
s.	O
2	O
Silver	O
Chains	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
3	O
Girdles	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Saint	I-pers
,	O
July	O
9	O
.	O
about	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
William	O
Saint	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
Servant	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
July	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
at	O
Sheerness	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
Boat	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
While	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
Wife	O
were	O
at	O
Ghent	O
in	O
Flanders	O
,	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Riddle	I-pers
(	O
who	O
I	O
left	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Catherines	I-place
)	O
informing	O
me	O
that	O
my	O
House	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
by	O
my	O
Man	O
Harry	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
Post-Chaise	O
to	O
Dunkirk	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
sent	O
my	O
Wife	O
Home	O
in	O
a	O
Vessel	O
before	O
me	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
Home	O
,	O
he	O
owned	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
New-Prison	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
upon	O
the	O
House	O
by	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
2	O
Poles	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
into	O
the	O
Garret-window	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday-night	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
20	O
Hours	O
;	O
that	O
(	O
when	O
Riddle	O
went	O
out	O
on	O
Sunday-morning	O
)	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
every	O
Room	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
ransackled	O
all	O
the	O
Drawers	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
really	O
broke	O
14	O
or	O
15	O
Locks	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Riddle	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
smoaking	O
my	O
Pipe	O
about	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
o	O
'	O
Sunday-night	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
Madam	O
Saint	O
's	O
Neighbours	O
sent	O
me	O
Word	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Street-door	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
Captain	O
Saint	B-pers
had	O
sent	O
me	O
a	O
Letter	O
before	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Man	O
Harry	O
was	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
Harry	O
's	O
doings	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
searching	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
his	O
Hat	O
in	O
the	O
Garret	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Hammer	O
and	O
Gimblet	O
under	O
the	O
Bed-Quilt	O
up	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
.	O
The	O
Garret-door	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Panes	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Garret-window	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
next	O
Day	O
by	O
a	O
Young	O
Man	O
,	O
who	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Cooper	O
's	O
over	O
against	O
Capt	O
.	O
Saint	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
He	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Garret-window	O
by	O
2	O
Poles	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
sot	O
a	O
Top	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
till	O
his	O
Companion	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
2	O
Panes	O
of	O
Glass	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Garret-Window	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
open	O
'd	O
it	O
and	O
got	O
in	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Fellow	O
,	O
his	O
Companion	O
,	O
staid	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
down	O
the	O
same	O
way	O
as	O
he	O
came	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
himself	O
got	O
in	O
about	O
10	O
or	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
there	O
till	O
next	O
Day	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
this	O
Pocket-Piece	O
,	O
and	O
Pocket-Bottle	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Desk	O
;	O
this	O
Hat	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Closet	O
;	O
and	O
this	O
Purse	O
with	O
a	O
Silver	O
Scissars-Chain	O
;	O
these	O
Girdles	O
and	O
Buckles	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Drawers	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
sont	O
the	O
Captain	O
Word	B-pers
of	O
what	O
had	O
happen	O
'd	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Saint	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Flanders	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Saint	O
,	O
when	O
,	O
Riddle	O
sent	O
me	O
Word	O
that	O
my	O
Man	O
had	O
broke	O
open	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
my	O
Goods	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
Stone	O
Buttle	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Silver	O
Girdle	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
Drawers	O
in	O
my	O
Fore-Room	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
is	O
my	O
Purse	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
Things	O
that	O
are	O
in	O
it	O
are	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Drawers	O
in	O
my	O
Back-Room	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
25.	O
William	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Loveday	I-pers
,	O
by	O
throwing	O
her	O
against	O
a	O
Chair	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
Means	O
she	O
receiv	O
'd	O
one	O
mortal	O
Bruise	O
on	O
her	O
Breast	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
instantly	O
dy	O
'd	O
,	O
July	O
15	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
Rachel	B-pers
Wallis	I-pers
.	O
As	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Child	O
,	O
about	O
12	O
Years	O
old	O
,	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
swept	O
the	O
Dust	O
in	O
her	O
Eyes	O
:	O
The	O
Child	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
why	O
she	O
did	O
so	O
?	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
call	O
'd	O
her	O
impudent	O
saucy	O
Slut	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
Pleasure	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
do	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
then	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
?	O
and	O
the	O
Child	O
told	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
bid	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
Names	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
abusive	O
:	O
With	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Arm	O
to	O
lead	O
her	O
out	O
;	O
she	O
struggled	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
hit	O
her	O
Foot	O
against	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
fell	O
with	O
her	O
Breast	O
upon	O
a	O
low	O
Chair	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
with	O
her	O
Head	O
against	O
the	O
Grates	O
.	O
She	O
got	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
hurt	O
herself	O
sadly	O
;	O
she	O
turn	O
'd	O
pale	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
sent	O
immediately	O
for	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
who	O
let	O
her	O
Blood	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
dy	O
'd	O
in	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
.	O
She	O
would	O
frequently	O
be	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
pretend	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
Fits	O
to	O
fright	O
us	O
.	O
Miss	O
Rogers	O
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
sent	O
me	O
down	O
Stairs	O
for	O
a	O
Chair	O
and	O
a	O
Shovel	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
swept	O
the	O
Dust	O
in	O
my	O
Eyes	O
.	O
Pray	O
do	O
n't	O
sweep	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
Eyes	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
will	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
because	O
it	O
's	O
my	O
Pleasure	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
'll	O
tell	O
my	O
Father	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
for	O
you	O
know	O
he	O
wont	O
suffer	O
such	O
Things	O
;	O
if	O
we	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
,	O
you	O
ought	O
to	O
acquaint	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
'll	O
correct	O
us	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
care	O
a	O
Pin	O
for	O
you	O
nor	O
your	O
Father	O
neither	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
.	O
And	O
then	O
my	O
Father	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
?	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
always	O
the	O
Trade	O
,	O
says	O
my	O
Father	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
am	O
cut	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
;	O
you	O
can	O
never	O
let	O
the	O
Children	O
alone	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
do	O
so	O
again	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
My	O
Father	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
then	O
she	O
should	O
not	O
stay	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
any	O
longer	O
.	O
But	O
she	O
would	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
my	O
Father	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
ill	O
Words	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
my	O
Father	O
took	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Arm	O
to	O
lead	O
her	O
out	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
very	O
full	O
of	O
Liquor	O
,	O
and	O
stagger	O
'd	O
much	O
;	O
her	O
Foot	O
hitch	O
'd	O
against	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
fell	O
with	O
her	O
Stomach	O
against	O
the	O
Chair	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
with	O
her	O
Temple	O
against	O
the	O
Grate	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Froster	I-pers
,	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
sitting	O
on	O
her	O
Backside	O
,	O
with	O
her	O
Head	O
leaning	O
betwixt	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Knees	O
;	O
I	O
let	O
her	O
Blood	O
,	O
she	O
bled	O
freely	O
about	O
an	O
Ounce	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
flag	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
she	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
dy	O
'd	O
presently	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
Bruise	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
of	O
her	O
Head	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Kirkpatrick	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
had	O
a	O
small	O
Fracture	O
in	O
her	O
Scull	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Breast-bone	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
depress	O
'd	O
,	O
which	O
might	O
suffocate	O
the	O
Lungs	O
so	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
breathe	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
little	O
Matter	O
will	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
Elizabeth	O
Loveday	O
dy	O
'd	O
accidentally	O
.	O
26.	O
Francis	B-pers
Walford	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Stanley	I-pers
,	O
by	O
abetting	O
,	O
aiding	O
,	O
comforting	O
and	O
maintaining	O
Thomas	B-pers
Darby	I-pers
(	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
who	O
with	O
a	O
Shovel	O
made	O
of	O
Iron	O
and	O
Wood	O
,	O
did	O
strike	O
the	O
said	O
William	B-pers
Stanley	I-pers
on	O
the	O
right	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
thereby	O
gave	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Bruise	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
mortal	O
Bruise	O
he	O
languish	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
August	O
following	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
d	O
'd	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Bragnall	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Elmstreet	B-place
in	O
Grays-Inn-Lane	B-place
,	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
where	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
liv	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
were	O
standing	O
at	O
their	O
Door	O
and	O
I	O
at	O
mine	O
,	O
about	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Darby	I-pers
(	O
who	O
since	O
escap	O
'd	O
from	O
the	O
Constable	O
)	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
were	O
both	O
Labourers	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Aldridge	O
the	O
Bricklayer	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
rebuilding	O
a	O
House	O
just	O
by	O
.	O
The	O
Labourers	O
sat	O
up	O
their	O
Screen	O
before	O
the	O
Deceas'd	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
to	O
screen	O
some	O
Rubbish	O
;	O
says	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
wo	O
n't	O
screen	O
your	O
Rubbish	O
upon	O
my	O
Ground	O
.	O
Damn	O
you	O
for	O
a	O
Son	O
of	O
a	O
Bitch	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
will	O
,	O
said	O
the	O
Labourers	O
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
said	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
It	O
's	O
hard	O
that	O
we	O
ca	O
n't	O
stand	O
at	O
our	O
own	O
Door	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
mouthful	O
of	O
Air	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
must	O
be	O
choaked	O
with	O
your	O
Dust	O
.	O
Damn	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
Bitch	O
,	O
said	O
they	O
,	O
go	O
in	O
and	O
send	O
your	O
Buck	O
cut	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
'll	O
thrash	O
him	O
.	O
With	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
kick	O
'd	O
their	O
Screen	O
down	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
set	O
it	O
up	O
again	O
nearer	O
his	O
Door	O
than	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
begun	O
to	O
screen	O
their	O
Rubbish	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
such	O
a	O
Dust	O
that	O
I	O
ran	O
up	O
to	O
shut	O
my	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
the	O
Blow	O
was	O
given	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
how	O
it	O
happen	O
'd	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
very	O
bloody	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
came	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
Candle	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
out	O
again	O
presently	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
Villain	O
,	O
you	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
past	O
11	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
but	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
past	O
9	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
to	O
my	O
Neighbour	O
's	O
Clock	O
to	O
see	O
.	O
Says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Damn	O
your	O
Blood	O
,	O
you	O
black	O
Bitch	O
,	O
go	O
in	O
and	O
send	O
your	O
Husband	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
lick	O
him	O
again	O
to	O
his	O
Heart	O
's	O
Content	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Fleming	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Labourers	O
gave	O
gross	O
Language	O
to	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
.	O
He	O
kick	O
'd	O
their	O
Screen	O
down	O
;	O
they	O
set	O
it	O
up	O
again	O
higher	O
to	O
his	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
great	O
Dust	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
shut	O
our	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
out	O
,	O
saw	O
Thomas	B-pers
Darby	I-pers
strike	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
with	O
a	O
Spade	O
Edgeways	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
said	O
,	O
Fetch	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
cut	O
me	O
down	O
the	O
Head	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Paskin	I-pers
.	O
There	O
being	O
a	O
great	O
Mob	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
say	O
,	O
If	O
he	O
had	O
used	O
me	O
as	O
he	O
did	O
Tom	B-pers
Darby	I-pers
,	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
serv	O
'd	O
him	O
as	O
bad	O
or	O
worse	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Stanly	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Namesake	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Relation	O
to	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
about	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
;	O
Aye	O
,	O
says	O
my	O
Wife	O
,	O
you	O
stay	O
out	O
till	O
a	O
fine	O
time	O
of	O
Night	O
;	O
here	O
your	O
Neighbour	O
has	O
been	O
murder	O
'd	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Sadler	O
,	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
Coming	O
home	O
on	O
July	O
7.	O
about	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
in	O
my	O
Surgery	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
Wound	O
in	O
the	O
upper-part	O
of	O
his	O
Head	O
to	O
the	O
Scull	O
,	O
but	O
without	O
any	O
bad	O
Symptoms	O
of	O
Vomiting	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
In	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
Weeks	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
near	O
healed	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
omitted	O
coming	O
to	O
be	O
drest	O
for	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Days	O
.	O
I	O
enquir	O
'd	O
the	O
Reason	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
told	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
Melancholy	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
;	O
but	O
his	O
Friend	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
it	O
only	O
proceeded	O
from	O
his	O
being	O
frighted	O
at	O
hearing	O
me	O
talk	O
of	O
an	O
Exsoliatim	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
thought	O
was	O
something	O
terrible	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
assured	O
his	O
Friend	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
only	O
a	O
slight	O
Operation	O
,	O
and	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
the	O
Nature	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
might	O
come	O
off	O
with	O
a	O
Plaister	O
;	O
but	O
still	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
afraid	O
to	O
come	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
he	O
was	O
better	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
only	O
advis	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
keep	O
on	O
the	O
Plaister	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
August	O
Word	O
was	O
sent	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
a	O
bad	O
Symptom	O
,	O
and	O
advis	O
'd	O
that	O
a	O
Physician	O
might	O
be	O
sent	O
for	O
.	O
I	O
propos	O
'd	O
a	O
Trefining	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
opening	O
the	O
Scull	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
Friends	O
were	O
all	O
against	O
it	O
.	O
However	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
another	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
come	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
dy	O
'd	O
about	O
4	O
next	O
Morning	O
.	O
I	O
open	O
'd	O
his	O
Scull	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Membranes	O
of	O
the	O
Brain	O
inflamed	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
an	O
Incision	O
in	O
the	O
Brain	O
,	O
and	O
discharg	O
'd	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
faetid	O
corrupted	O
Matter	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
generally	O
occasion	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
Shock	O
or	O
Blow	O
of	O
something	O
heavy	O
and	O
which	O
I	O
thought	O
was	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
his	O
Melancholy	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
If	O
he	O
had	O
come	O
regularly	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
drest	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
that	O
his	O
Death	O
might	O
not	O
probably	O
have	O
been	O
prevented	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Sadler	O
.	O
I	O
doubt	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
all	O
the	O
Chance	O
we	O
had	O
for	O
saving	O
his	O
Life	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
to	O
have	O
open	O
'd	O
his	O
Scull	O
sooner	O
.	O
Dr.	O
Smithson	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
Fit	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
stupid	O
,	O
dull	O
,	O
and	O
almost	O
senseless	O
.	O
Trefining	O
(	O
or	O
as	O
the	O
old	O
Term	O
is	O
,	O
Trepaning	O
)	O
was	O
propos	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
Mother	O
said	O
,	O
She	O
had	O
rather	O
he	O
should	O
die	O
quietly	O
than	O
go	O
thro	O
'	O
that	O
barbarous	O
Operation	O
.	O
As	O
this	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
suffer	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
fear	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
past	O
Relief	O
,	O
except	O
a	O
brisk	O
Purge	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
Effect	O
.	O
I	O
try	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
work	O
'd	O
till	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
ceas	O
'd	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
Convulsions	O
at	O
One	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
rubbing	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
of	O
his	O
Forehead	O
;	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
there	O
lies	O
his	O
Hurt	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
'll	O
find	O
it	O
under	O
the	O
Membranes	O
of	O
the	O
Brain	O
.	O
Another	O
Surgeon	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
come	O
till	O
7	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
dy	O
'd	O
at	O
4	O
.	O
A	O
Piece	O
of	O
his	O
Scull	O
being	O
taken	O
off	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
an	O
Inflamation	O
on	O
the	O
Membranes	O
of	O
the	O
Brain	O
.	O
The	O
Surgeon	O
thrust	O
his	O
Instrument	O
in	O
,	O
opposite	O
to	O
the	O
Wound	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
issued	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
yellow	O
corrupted	O
Matter	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Consequence	O
of	O
the	O
Blow	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
came	O
out	O
and	O
struck	O
Darby	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
times	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
27	O
,	O
28.	O
Charles	B-pers
Patrick	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Meads	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Joseph	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
in	O
a	O
Field	O
or	O
open	O
Place	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
Value	O
16	O
s.	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
Value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Pocket	O
Looking-glass	O
,	O
Value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Knee	O
Buckle	O
,	O
Value	O
3	O
s.	O
2	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Foreign	O
Silver	O
,	O
Value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Cotton	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
Value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
17	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bon	I-place
,	O
July	O
2	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Mary	B-pers
Cooling	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Mother-of	O
Pearl	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Silver	O
Rim	O
,	O
Value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Steel	O
Toothpick-Case	O
,	O
Value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Toothpick	O
,	O
Value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Fan	O
,	O
Value	O
1	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Mary	O
le	O
Bon	O
,	O
July	O
10	O
.	O
First	O
Indictment	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
a	O
Frenchman	O
,	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
was	O
sworn	O
to	O
interpret	O
betwixt	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Joseph	O
Andrews	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
attack	O
'd	O
near	O
the	O
Bason	B-place
in	O
Marybon-fields	B-place
by	O
4	O
Lads	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
one	O
in	O
a	O
white	O
Frock	O
,	O
held	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
my	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
push	O
'd	O
it	O
against	O
my	O
Forehead	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
understand	O
what	O
they	O
said	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
O	O
my	O
God	O
!	O
O	O
my	O
Dear	O
!	O
Then	O
the	O
other	O
three	O
fell	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
little	O
one	O
beat	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
with	O
the	O
Pistol	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
all	O
got	O
about	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
off	O
my	O
Shoe-buckles	O
,	O
took	O
away	O
my	O
Hat	O
,	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
my	O
Pocket	O
Looking-glass	O
,	O
my	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
6	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
2	O
French	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Silver	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
24	O
Sols	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
12	O
Sols	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
were	O
going	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
just	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
getting	O
up	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
came	O
back	O
and	O
took	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
Knee	O
Buckles	O
,	O
thinking	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
gave	O
me	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Knocks	O
on	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
left	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
,	O
one	O
Kirk	O
,	O
a	O
Bailiff	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
at	O
such	O
a	O
time	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
.	O
And	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
lose	O
a	O
Watch	O
?	O
said	O
he	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
Yes	O
.	O
He	O
shewed	O
me	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
if	O
that	O
was	O
mine	O
?	O
And	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
fetch	O
'd	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
pawn	O
.	O
Kirk	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
Marks	O
of	O
his	O
Watch	O
?	O
And	O
he	O
describ	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
Maker	O
's	O
Name	O
was	O
Lugg	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
String	O
that	O
match	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
String	O
of	O
the	O
Watch	O
.	O
Sutton	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
the	O
robbing	O
this	O
Man	O
in	O
Marybon-fields	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
Sutton	O
's	O
Information	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
Watch	O
at	O
the	O
Rose	O
in	O
Stanhope-street	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
pawn	O
'd	O
for	O
38	O
s.	O
which	O
I	O
paid	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
and	O
Wils	O
Booth	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
2	O
Prisoners	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
near	O
the	O
new	O
Bason	O
in	O
Marybon-fields	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoe-Buckles	O
,	O
a	O
Knee-Buckle	O
,	O
a	O
Pocket-Glass	O
,	O
a	O
Pocket-Piece	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
;	O
for	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
was	O
all	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
.	O
Patrick	O
presented	O
the	O
Pistol	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
all	O
fell	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
down	O
,	O
tore	O
off	O
his	O
Knee-Buckle	O
with	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
Garter	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swears	O
,	O
not	O
that	O
he	O
left	O
the	O
Knee-Buckle	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
were	O
all	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
you	O
were	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
one	O
turn	O
'd	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
rising	O
.	O
Sutton	O
.	O
Booth	O
took	O
the	O
Watch	O
and	O
Glass	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Pocket-Piece	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
That	O
Day	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
(	O
which	O
is	O
6	O
Weeks	O
ago	O
)	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
Paddington-Fair	O
with	O
the	O
2	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
parting	O
with	O
them	O
near	O
my	O
Lord	O
Bingly	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
gone	O
far	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
apprehended	O
by	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Men	O
,	O
who	O
carried	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Brock	O
*	O
,	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
(	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
examin	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
Justice	O
)	O
Tom	B-pers
How	I-pers
,	O
Will	O
James	O
,	O
and	O
Will	O
Pember	O
took	O
my	O
Informaion	O
in	O
Writing	O
.	O
I	O
lay	O
that	O
Night	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
along	O
with	O
Tom	B-pers
How	I-pers
,	O
and	O
next	O
Morning	O
they	O
carried	O
me	O
before	O
Justice	O
Robe	O
.	O
*	O
Alias	O
Brogdon	O
Poplet	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Those	O
People	O
ought	O
not	O
to	O
take	O
upon	O
them	O
to	O
prepare	O
and	O
draw	O
up	O
Informatons	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
settle	O
among	O
themselves	O
whatever	O
they	O
design	O
the	O
Informist	O
shall	O
swear	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
or	O
in	O
this	O
Court	O
.	O
Informations	O
are	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
before	O
a	O
proper	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Publick	O
may	O
be	O
satisfied	O
,	O
that	O
no	O
unfair	O
Practices	O
have	O
been	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
.	O
Patrick	O
.	O
Whither	O
did	O
we	O
go	O
after	O
the	O
Robbery	O
?	O
Sutton	O
.	O
To	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
before	O
,	O
there	O
we	O
had	O
2	O
full	O
Pots	O
of	O
Beer	O
.	O
From	O
thence	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms	O
,	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Laurence-Lane	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
lay	O
all	O
4	O
in	O
one	O
Bed	O
.	O
I	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
Watch	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Hargrove	I-pers
,	O
for	O
38	O
s.	O
at	O
a	O
House	O
near	O
Clare-Market	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
nor	O
the	O
Pawnbroker	O
.	O
I	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
Hat	O
for	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
the	O
Shoe-Buckles	O
for	O
3	O
s.	O
near	O
Hicks	O
's	O
Hall	O
,	O
and	O
Will	O
Booth	O
sold	O
the	O
Pocket-Piece	O
for	O
10	O
d.	O
William	B-pers
Noon	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Pawnbroker	O
's	O
Man	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
positively	O
that	O
Sutton	O
brought	O
the	O
Watch	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
only	O
as	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
at	O
Kirk	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
in	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
July	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
Numb	O
.	O
441.	O
made	O
by	O
Love	O
(	O
or	O
Lugg	O
)	O
.	O
I	O
deliver	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Kirk	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
paid	O
me	O
38	O
s.	O
Evan	B-pers
Bedward	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
charg	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
New-Prison	O
,	O
but	O
Sutton	O
not	O
being	O
committed	O
,	O
he	O
absconded	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Will	O
Booth	O
was	O
made	O
an	O
Evidence	O
in	O
his	O
room	O
.	O
Will	O
Booth	O
.	O
We	O
all	O
met	O
at	O
one	O
Buck	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
Gin-shop	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
use	O
to	O
drink	O
;	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
we	O
went	O
towards	O
the	O
Bason	O
in	O
Marybon-fields	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
met	O
this	O
French	O
Gentleman	O
.	O
Patrick	O
held	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
they	O
struggled	O
,	O
and	O
Patrick	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
with	O
the	O
Pistol	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Copper	O
Pocket-Piece	O
,	O
and	O
Glass	O
;	O
Sutton	O
took	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
Meeds	O
took	O
his	O
Shoe-buckles	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Knee-Buckle	O
,	O
and	O
tore	O
the	O
Garter	O
off	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
went	O
over	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
and	O
hid	O
the	O
Hat	O
by	O
a	O
Bank	O
;	O
so	O
to	O
the	O
Two	O
Brewers	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
had	O
2	O
Pots	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
King's-Arms	O
in	O
Laurence-Lane	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
all	O
lay	O
in	O
one	O
Bed	O
for	O
1	O
s.	O
Next	O
Morning	O
Sutton	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Three	O
Cocks	O
,	O
near	O
Hicks's-Hall	O
,	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
Hat	O
for	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Buckles	O
in	O
Chick-Lane	O
for	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
the	O
Watch	O
by	O
Clare-Market	O
for	O
38	O
s.	O
and	O
I	O
sold	O
the	O
Pocket-Piece	O
for	O
10	O
d.	O
in	O
Holborn	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
over	O
the	O
Water	O
,	O
kept	O
by	O
Meeds	O
's	O
Mother	O
's	O
Acquaintance	O
;	O
there	O
we	O
eat	O
Bread	O
and	O
Butter	O
and	O
Cucumbers	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
Bottled-Ale	O
,	O
and	O
shared	O
the	O
Money	O
:	O
We	O
threw	O
away	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
the	O
Knee-Buckle	O
over	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
Church	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Pocket-Glass	O
over	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Holborn	O
.	O
Patrick	O
.	O
Where	O
were	O
we	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
the	O
Robbery	O
?	O
Booth	O
.	O
At	O
Buck	O
's	O
Gin	O
shop	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
all	O
met	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
we	O
use	O
to	O
be	O
Night	O
and	O
Day	O
.	O
Patrick	O
.	O
At	O
what	O
Hour	O
was	O
the	O
Robbery	O
committed	O
?	O
Booth	O
.	O
About	O
9	O
or	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
Patrick	O
.	O
After	O
we	O
were	O
taken	O
,	O
Will	O
James	O
,	O
Tom	B-pers
How	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Pember	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Thief-Takers	O
,	O
sat	O
drinking	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
Will	O
James	O
call	O
'd	O
me	O
aside	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Evidence	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
had	O
treated	O
Sutton	O
with	O
Fowls	O
,	O
and	O
next	O
Morning	O
they	O
gave	O
him	O
leave	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
his	O
Father	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
get	O
me	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Reward	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
bound	O
Body	O
for	O
Body	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
out	O
of	O
Prison	O
the	O
Day	O
after	O
the	O
Sessions	O
.	O
Meeds	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
several	O
Persons	O
to	O
my	O
Character	O
.	O
Tho	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
.	O
Meeds	O
is	O
a	O
Plaisterer	O
;	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
last	O
Year	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
well	O
.	O
Jos	O
.	O
Martin	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
3	O
Years	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
go	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
return	O
at	O
Night	O
in	O
his	O
working	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
work	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
when	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
100	O
l.	O
worth	O
of	O
my	O
Lord	O
Grantham	O
's	O
Goods	O
under	O
my	O
Care	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
miss	O
'd	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Lorain	O
Haycock	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
these	O
15	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
always	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Neighbourhood	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
heard	O
the	O
least	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
been	O
married	O
a	O
Year	O
,	O
and	O
follow	O
'd	O
his	O
Plaistering	O
Business	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Paget	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
8	O
Years	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
frequently	O
seen	O
him	O
pass	O
by	O
to	O
his	O
Work	O
,	O
and	O
repass	O
.	O
He	O
always	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bauk	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Waterman	O
;	O
I	O
take	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Goods	O
under	O
my	O
Care	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
2	O
Years	O
(	O
within	O
these	O
4	O
Years	O
)	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
miss	O
'd	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
he	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
go	O
about	O
his	O
Plaistering	O
Work	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
Second	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Cowling	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
Return	O
from	O
Marybon	O
,	O
4	O
Men	O
met	O
me	O
by	O
my	O
Lord	O
Bingly	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Cavendish-square	B-place
;	O
I	O
stept	O
aside	O
to	O
give	O
'em	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
holding	O
up	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
cry	O
'd	O
Stand	O
;	O
or	O
I	O
'll	O
shoot	O
you	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Head	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
not	O
Rogues	O
indeed	O
.	O
But	O
presently	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
threw	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
turn	O
'd	O
up	O
my	O
Coats	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
it	O
off	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
a	O
Mother-of-Pearl	O
Snuff-Box	O
lin	O
'd	O
with	O
Silver	O
,	O
a	O
Fan	O
,	O
a	O
Toothpick-Case	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Toothpick	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
fetch	O
'd	O
before	O
Justice	O
Robe	O
to	O
own	O
my	O
Box	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
brought	O
there	O
by	O
one	O
William	B-pers
How	I-pers
from	O
St.	O
Ann	O
's	O
.	O
William	B-pers
How	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Baker	O
;	O
but	O
my	O
Wife	O
keeps	O
a	O
Chandler's-shop	O
,	O
and	O
sells	O
a	O
Dram	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
Sutton	O
and	O
Booth	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
2	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Shop	O
to	O
drink	O
;	O
they	O
staid	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Sutton	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Patrick	O
call	O
'd	O
me	O
aside	O
into	O
the	O
Entry	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
lend	O
them	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
on	O
this	O
Box	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
paid	O
me	O
for	O
the	O
Liquor	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
Tom	B-pers
How	I-pers
and	O
2	O
other	O
Men	O
came	O
about	O
8	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
enquir	O
'd	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
receiv	O
'd	O
such	O
a	O
Box	O
of	O
Booth	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
'em	O
I	O
had	O
such	O
a	O
Box	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
before	O
Justice	O
Robe	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
deliver	O
'd	O
the	O
Box	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
knew	O
Sutton	O
had	O
good	O
Friends	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
I	O
thought	O
the	O
Box	O
had	O
been	O
his	O
own	O
.	O
Sutton	O
.	O
We	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
by	O
Scavender	O
[	O
Cavendish	O
]	O
Square	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
off	O
her	O
Pocket	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Fan	O
and	O
a	O
gilt	O
Snuff-Box	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
odd	O
Things	O
.	O
We	O
tore	O
the	O
Fan	O
and	O
the	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
We	O
attack	O
'd	O
her	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Owen	O
's	O
(	O
the	O
Half-way	O
House	O
from	O
Marybon	O
)	O
she	O
stept	O
aside	O
,	O
Patrick	O
held	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
scream	O
'd	O
;	O
Meeds	O
hit	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
she	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
cut	O
off	O
her	O
Pocket	O
.	O
I	O
kept	O
the	O
Snuff-Box	O
all	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
next	O
Morning	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Gin-shop	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
Will	O
How	O
's	O
.	O
Booth	O
.	O
We	O
met	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
by	O
Scavenger-square	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
one	O
to	O
t'other	O
,	O
Let	O
's	O
rob	O
her	O
.	O
Patrick	O
held	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
Sure	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
not	O
Rogues	O
?	O
Yes	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
are	O
,	O
said	O
we	O
.	O
Sutton	O
hit	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
Sutton	O
?	O
for	O
he	O
swears	O
it	O
was	O
Meed	O
.	O
Booth	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
safely	O
swear	O
it	O
was	O
Sutton	O
.	O
Besides	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
a	O
Pocket-Piece	O
from	O
her	O
with	O
a	O
V	O
o	O
'	O
top	O
o	O
n't	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
went	O
over	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
sat	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
Grass	O
,	O
search	O
'd	O
the	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
tore	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
Sutton	O
kept	O
the	O
Box	O
all	O
Night	O
.	O
Next	O
Morning	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Gin-shop	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
Will	O
How	O
's	O
;	O
Sutton	O
and	O
Patrick	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
How	O
,	O
and	O
borrow	O
'd	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
Box	O
.	O
Patrick	O
.	O
While	O
we	O
were	O
at	O
Will	O
How	O
's	O
,	O
Sutton	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
Box	O
from	O
his	O
Sister	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
would	O
treat	O
us	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
29	O
,	O
30	O
,	O
31.	O
Charles	B-pers
Patrick	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Meeds	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
's	I-place
Hanover-square	I-place
,	O
were	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
and	O
Viner	B-pers
White	I-pers
of	O
the	O
same	O
Place	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Blackstone	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Pocket	O
,	O
Value	O
1	O
d.	O
2	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
Value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
Linen	O
Apron	O
,	O
Value	O
1	O
s.	O
an	O
Iron	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
Value	O
1	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
Value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
4	O
Guineas	O
,	O
June	O
28	O
.	O
Dorothy	O
Blackstone	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
Gravener	B-place
[	I-place
Grosvenor	I-place
]	I-place
Street	I-place
,	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
attack	O
'd	O
by	O
5	O
Street-Robbers	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
held	O
out	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
Stand	O
.	O
I	O
knowing	O
some	O
Chairmen	O
were	O
near	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
for	O
Assistance	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
that	O
had	O
the	O
Pistol	O
struck	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
with	O
the	O
but-end	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
me	O
sadly	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
took	O
away	O
my	O
Pocket	O
with	O
4	O
Guineas	O
,	O
4	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
a	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Steps	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
when	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
turned	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
off	O
my	O
Apron	O
.	O
tho	O
'	O
the	O
others	O
desired	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
If	O
I	O
can	O
judge	O
(	O
considering	O
the	O
Fright	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
)	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
[	O
Viner	O
White	O
]	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
my	O
Apron	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
's	O
a	O
Case	O
of	O
Life	O
and	O
Death	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
for	O
the	O
World	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
indeed	O
a	O
Moonlight	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
dark	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
away	O
thro	O
'	O
Grosvenor	B-pers
Meuse	I-pers
.	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
the	O
Chair-men	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
lost	O
'em	O
.	O
Booth	O
.	O
Sutton	O
and	O
I	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
went	O
round	O
Grosvenor-Square	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
no	O
body	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
Patrick	O
and	O
Meeds	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
before	O
her	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
Little	O
George-street	O
,	O
and	O
stopt	O
her	O
.	O
Says	O
she	O
,	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
?	O
And	O
,	O
says	O
Patrick	O
,	O
What	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
saucy	O
?	O
And	O
with	O
that	O
he	O
cut	O
her	O
over	O
the	O
Head	O
with	O
his	O
Pistol	O
.	O
So	O
that	O
the	O
Blood	O
ran	O
down	O
.	O
She	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
and	O
Meeds	O
cut	O
her	O
Pocket	O
off	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
3	O
Guineas	O
,	O
an	O
old	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
no	O
more	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
Meeds	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
had	O
finger	O
'd	O
her	O
Pocket	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
bid	O
me	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
As	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
Viner	O
White	O
turned	O
back	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
her	O
Apron	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
a	O
Lamp	O
in	O
Piccadilly	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Things	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
3	O
Guineas	O
.	O
We	O
threw	O
the	O
Gloves	O
over	O
the	O
Rails	O
of	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Gin	O
shop	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
,	O
over-against	O
Short	O
's	O
Gardens	O
(	O
where	O
we	O
knew	O
the	O
People	O
usually	O
got	O
up	O
by	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
)	O
There	O
we	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
for	O
Half	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Gin	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
till	O
8	O
or	O
9	O
a	O
Clock	O
;	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Goat	O
in	O
Newport-Market	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
some	O
Steaks	O
for	O
Breakfast	O
.	O
Viner	O
White	O
.	O
Booth	O
has	O
ow	O
'd	O
me	O
a	O
spite	O
ever	O
since	O
I	O
beat	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Skettle-Ground	O
.	O
Sutton	O
.	O
We	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
in	O
Grosvenor-street	O
by	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Little	O
George-street	O
.	O
Patrick	O
struck	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
with	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
her	O
down	O
.	O
Meeds	O
cut	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
3	O
Guineas	O
,	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
went	O
over	O
White-Conduit	O
Field	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
to	O
a	O
Gin-shop	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
pawned	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
nothing	O
else	O
taken	O
from	O
her	O
?	O
Sutton	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
nothing	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutrix	O
swears	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
does	O
Booth	O
too	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
you	O
turned	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
her	O
Apron	O
.	O
Sutton	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
now	O
I	O
think	O
o	O
n't	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
32	O
.	O
33	O
,	O
34	O
,	O
35.	O
Charles	B-pers
Patrick	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Meeds	I-pers
,	O
was	O
a	O
fourth	O
Time	O
;	O
Viner	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
;	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Clerk	O
,	O
in	O
an	O
open	O
Place	O
or	O
Field	O
near	O
the	O
High	O
way	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silver	O
Snuff-box	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Gold	O
ring	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
3	O
Iron	O
Keys	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
Guinea	O
,	O
two	O
Half-Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
July	O
17	O
.	O
James	O
Smith	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
about	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
London	B-place
to	O
Kentish-Town	B-place
,	O
I	O
met	O
5	O
Boys	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
held	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
my	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
If	O
you	O
speak	O
a	O
word	O
,	O
you	O
're	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
.	O
Deliver	O
your	O
Money	O
,	O
Doctor	O
!	O
I	O
answer	O
'd	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
your	O
Power	O
,	O
do	O
with	O
me	O
as	O
you	O
please	O
.	O
Then	O
3	O
of	O
them	O
rifled	O
me	O
of	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
Half-Guineas	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
Snuff-box	O
in	O
my	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
thinking	O
to	O
save	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
flung	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Ditch	O
.	O
They	O
observed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
flung	O
into	O
the	O
Ditch	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
Nothing	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
my	O
Word	O
,	O
for	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
stopping	O
down	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Snuff-box	O
.	O
They	O
felt	O
about	O
my	O
Waistcoat	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
there	O
?	O
And	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Only	O
some	O
Drugs	O
for	O
poor	O
People	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
so	O
dark	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
sure	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
are	O
any	O
of	O
those	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
,	O
W.	O
Booth	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
the	O
4	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
at	O
Buck	O
's	O
Gin-shop	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
all	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
Night	O
we	O
concluded	O
to	O
go	O
a	O
robbing	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
up	O
Tottenham-Court	O
Road	O
,	O
and	O
near	O
the	O
Halfway-house	O
,	O
betwixt	O
Hampstead	O
,	O
and	O
Kentish-Town	O
,	O
we	O
met	O
this	O
Parson	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Patrick	O
had	O
one	O
Pistol	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
another	O
.	O
Patrick	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Parson	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
stand	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
searching	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Pockets	O
,	O
took	O
out	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
some	O
Halfpence	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Farthings	O
;	O
and	O
Meeds	O
searching	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
found	O
3	O
Half	O
Guineas	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Parson	O
throw	O
something	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
asking	O
him	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
he	O
threw	O
away	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
away	O
nothing	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
but	O
you	O
have	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
;	O
and	O
stooping	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Silver	O
Snuff	O
box	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Vaughan	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
afterwards	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
Creature	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
brought	O
us	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
an	O
old-fashion	O
'd	O
Box	O
,	O
all	O
wroughted	O
at	O
Top	O
.	O
While	O
the	O
others	O
were	O
examining	O
the	O
Parson	O
's	O
Pockets	O
,	O
Vaughan	O
and	O
White	O
stood	O
threatning	O
to	O
shoot	O
him	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Head	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
stand	O
still	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
'll	O
say	O
that	O
for	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
easy	O
.	O
Smith	O
.	O
Not	O
so	O
easy	O
as	O
you	O
think	O
for	O
.	O
White	O
.	O
Was	O
I	O
there	O
?	O
Booth	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Patrick	O
.	O
Who	O
held	O
the	O
Pistol	O
to	O
the	O
Parson	O
?	O
Booth	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
.	O
Patrick	O
.	O
Of	O
what	O
Size	O
were	O
they	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
you	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
all	O
Boys	O
of	O
a	O
small	O
Size	O
.	O
White	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
known	O
Booth	O
but	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
,	O
by	O
playing	O
at	O
Skettles	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
happening	O
to	O
meet	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
Home	O
,	O
I	O
bore	O
him	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Way	O
we	O
met	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
the	O
Parson	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
they	O
intended	O
to	O
rob	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
several	O
People	O
to	O
my	O
Reputation	O
.	O
Tho	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
10	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
Harm	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
Smith	O
by	O
Trade	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
work	O
'd	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Babh	I-pers
.	O
