TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
12th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
13th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
14th	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
September	O
1733	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Sixth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Seventh	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
JOHN	B-pers
BARBER	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1733	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VII	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
WILFORD	O
,	O
behind	O
the	O
Chapter-House	O
,	O
near	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
.	O
M	O
,	O
DCC	O
,	O
XXXIII	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
Six	O
Pence	O
)	O
Where	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
the	O
former	O
Numbers	O
in	O
the	O
present	O
Mayoralty	O
.	O
The	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
JOHN	B-pers
BARBER	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Mr	O
Baron	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
Urlin	O
,	O
Deputy-Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wootton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Chetwin	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Kite	I-pers
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Percher	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Cripple	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Westlock	I-pers
,	O
Basil	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Beard	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Budge	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
,	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Burchett	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Brasset	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Chubb	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bramly	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Barret	I-pers
,	O
Simon	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Simmonds	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Millet	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Turvin	I-pers
.	O
1	O
,	O
2	O
,	O
3.	O
John	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
,	O
Abraham	B-pers
Pearse	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
brass	O
Stew-pan	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Alexander	I-pers
,	O
July	O
17	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Porridge	O
pot	O
,	O
a	O
Sauce-pan	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jacobus	B-pers
Pitt	I-pers
,	O
July	O
17	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
4	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Laws	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Watch	O
and	O
three	O
silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Burridge	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hicks	I-pers
's	O
House	O
,	O
Aug.	O
21	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
laced	O
Head-clothes	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Christie	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Jane	O
Curridge	O
,	O
Aug.	O
10	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
5.	O
John	B-pers
Basset	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Carton	I-pers
,	O
June	O
28	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
granted	O
him	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
his	O
Indictment	O
.	O
6	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jonas	I-pers
*	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	B-pers
Jonas	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Buckles	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hurtley	I-pers
,	O
June	O
28	O
.	O
*	O
Jonas	O
was	O
try	O
'd	O
on	O
two	O
Indictments	O
in	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
one	O
for	O
robbing	O
William	B-pers
Banks	I-pers
in	O
Stepney-Fields	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Tilt	O
of	O
a	O
Boat	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
or	O
both	O
.	O
See	O
the	O
Sessions	O
Paper	O
,	O
Number	O
V.	O
Pages	O
131	O
and	O
151	O
.	O
W.	O
Hartly	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
returning	O
homeward	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
ease	O
myself	O
in	O
a	O
Ditch	O
in	O
White-Horse-Field	B-place
,	O
in	O
Radcliff	B-place
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
sultry	O
hot	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Shoes	O
(	O
which	O
were	O
new	O
)	O
drawing	O
my	O
Feet	O
,	O
I	O
pull	O
'd	O
them	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
slapping	O
my	O
Hat	O
over	O
my	O
Face	O
,	O
I	O
laid	O
down	O
and	O
fell	O
asleep	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
waked	O
by	O
Somebody	O
's	O
twitching	O
my	O
Hat	O
away	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
the	O
Loop	O
of	O
it	O
about	O
my	O
Finger	O
.	O
I	O
started	O
up	O
upon	O
my	O
Breech	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
God	O
!	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
where	O
's	O
my	O
Shoes	O
and	O
Buckles	O
?	O
Says	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
not	O
far	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
There	O
goes	O
he	O
that	O
has	O
got	O
'em	O
,	O
and	O
pointed	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
running	O
off	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
Hat	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
followed	O
him	O
barefoot	O
.	O
He	O
dropp	O
'd	O
my	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
jump	O
'd	O
over	O
a	O
Bank	O
into	O
a	O
Garden	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
Now	O
are	O
not	O
you	O
a	O
Rascal	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
to	O
rob	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
his	O
Clothes	O
?	O
You	O
think	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
Devil	O
and	O
all	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
is	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
tight	O
and	O
clean	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
after	O
the	O
other	O
Man	O
,	O
who	O
followed	O
at	O
a	O
Distance	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Jack	O
!	O
where	O
'	O
the	O
Man	O
's	O
Shoes	O
?	O
but	O
he	O
sheer	O
'd	O
off	O
.	O
Then	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
'll	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
Rag-Fair	O
,	O
plausible	O
you	O
may	O
find	O
him	O
a	O
selling	O
them	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
collar	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
from	O
one	O
Place	O
to	O
another	O
under	O
that	O
Pretence	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
wanted	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
get	O
off	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
got	O
Help	O
and	O
secured	O
him	O
.	O
Sam	B-pers
Clemson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
Tustle	O
just	O
by	O
our	O
Door	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Damn	O
you	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
you	O
're	O
no	O
Officer	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
tip	O
you	O
up	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
loose	O
my	O
Collar	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
held	O
him	O
'till	O
an	O
Officer	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Colvert	I-pers
,	O
came	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Colvert	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
offered	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
Shoes	O
and	O
Buckles	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
who	O
presently	O
knew	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
out	O
?	O
Did	O
not	O
I	O
commit	O
you	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
more	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
ago	O
?	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
7.	O
John	B-pers
Bromley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
525	O
Guineas	O
,	O
5	O
Moidores	O
,	O
2	O
half	O
Moidores	O
,	O
1	O
Broad	O
Piece	O
,	O
value	O
23	O
s.	O
a	O
quarter	O
Broad	O
Piece	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
5	O
quarter	O
Guineas	O
,	O
1	O
Portugal	O
Piece	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s	O
40	O
l.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
8	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Canvas	O
Bag	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Purse	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Thread	O
Purse	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dyer	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
August	O
the	O
2d	O
last	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Dyer	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Turner	O
's	O
Shop	O
just	O
without	O
Newgate	B-place
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
my	O
Apprentice	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
served	O
me	O
six	O
Years	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
an	O
Elopement	O
from	O
me	O
about	O
this	O
time	O
Twelvemonth	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
his	O
returning	O
home	O
after	O
above	O
four	O
Months	O
Absence	O
,	O
I	O
forgave	O
him	O
what	O
was	O
past	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
my	O
Wife	O
to	O
Harrow	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
my	O
Daughter	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
away	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
an	O
Hour	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
before	O
my	O
Return	O
;	O
that	O
upon	O
missing	O
him	O
they	O
had	O
some	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
Drawers	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
they	O
inform	O
'd	O
my	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Sheppard	O
,	O
of	O
what	O
had	O
happen	O
'd	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
leave	O
your	O
Drawers	O
lock	O
'd	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Dyer	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
that	O
very	O
Morning	O
I	O
took	O
10	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Drawers	O
,	O
and	O
lock	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
all	O
the	O
rest	O
were	O
fast	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
my	O
Return	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
all	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
In	O
one	O
Drawer	O
there	O
was	O
between	O
70	O
and	O
80	O
l.	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
500	O
Guineas	O
from	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
third	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
Drawer	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
my	O
Wife	O
had	O
laid	O
up	O
several	O
remarkable	O
Pieces	O
for	O
my	O
Children	O
,	O
Crowns	O
,	O
Half-crowns	O
,	O
Silver	O
Groat	O
,	O
Three-pences	O
,	O
Two-Pences	O
and	O
Pennies	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
were	O
all	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
about	O
five	O
Hours	O
after	O
,	O
with	O
all	O
the	O
Money	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
except	O
15	O
l.	O
4	O
s.	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
laid	O
out	O
in	O
buying	O
a	O
great	O
Coat	O
,	O
Whip	O
,	O
Boots	O
,	O
Sputs	O
,	O
a	O
Trunk	O
to	O
put	O
the	O
Money	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
odd	O
Things	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
Pursu't	O
of	O
him	O
towards	O
Harwich	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
Kent	O
by	O
others	O
who	O
followed	O
him	O
in	O
Dover	O
Road	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
till	O
the	O
Saturday	O
following	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
broke	O
open	O
my	O
Drawers	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
my	O
Money	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hancock	I-pers
.	O
Two	O
Hours	O
after	O
the	O
Robbery	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Sheppard	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
robbed	O
his	O
Master	O
of	O
5	O
or	O
600	O
l.	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
Pursuit	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
It	O
happen	O
'd	O
that	O
I	O
took	O
Post	O
horse	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Inn	O
as	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
second	O
Stage	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
Dartford	O
in	O
Kent	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
such	O
a	O
Person	O
as	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
but	O
just	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Inn	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
hardly	O
he	O
got	O
40	O
Yards	O
off	O
.	O
I	O
follow	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
two	O
Miles	O
he	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
by	O
another	O
Person	O
who	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
Start	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Inn	O
at	O
Dartford	O
.	O
John	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
how	O
do	O
ye	O
do	O
?	O
-	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
?	O
says	O
he	O
again	O
.	O
God	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
John	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
glad	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
;	O
where	O
is	O
the	O
Money	O
?	O
'T	O
is	O
in	O
that	O
Trank	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
how	O
much	O
there	O
was	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
told	O
it	O
yet	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
intended	O
to	O
tell	O
it	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
Rochester	O
.	O
Upon	O
searching	O
I	O
found	O
there	O
was	O
546	O
l.	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
the	O
Trunk	O
,	O
besides	O
other	O
Money	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
Seal	O
with	O
which	O
I	O
scal	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
Trunk	O
He	O
confess	O
'd	O
very	O
readily	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
come	O
home	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
sat	O
up	O
there	O
all	O
Night	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
could	O
serve	O
his	O
Master	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
propos	O
'd	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
the	O
Money	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
his	O
Master	O
was	O
a	O
good	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
intended	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
Master	O
Returns	O
in	O
Goods	O
for	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
designing	O
to	O
go	O
directly	O
to	O
France	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
to	O
Legborn	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
send	O
over	O
Bermudas	O
Hats	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
.	O
It	O
seems	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
Money	O
in	O
his	O
Clothes	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Trunk	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
afterwards	O
sent	O
to	O
Maidstone	O
Goal	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
he	O
was	O
removed	O
hither	O
by	O
a	O
Habe	O
Corpus	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
8.	O
John	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ashwell	I-pers
,	O
by	O
throwing	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
striking	O
him	O
with	O
both	O
his	O
Hands	O
and	O
Feet	O
on	O
the	O
Stomach	O
,	O
Breast	O
,	O
Belly	O
,	O
Sides	O
,	O
and	O
Groin	O
,	O
and	O
thereby	O
giving	O
him	O
several	O
mortal	O
Wounds	O
and	O
Bruises	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
'till	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Month	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Prayer	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
against	O
him	O
were	O
examined	O
separately	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Eastmend	O
.	O
About	O
two	O
Months	O
ago	O
on	O
a	O
Sunday	O
,	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
Nag	O
's	O
Head	O
Tavern	O
Door	O
in	O
Prince's-street	B-place
,	I-place
by	O
Drury-lane	B-place
,	O
where	O
I	O
ply	O
as	O
a	O
Porter	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
Porters	O
coming	O
along	O
Prince's-street	O
,	O
one	O
was	O
the	O
Porter	O
at	O
the	O
Swan	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
John	B-pers
Sudlow	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Porter	O
to	O
the	O
Ship	O
behind	O
the	O
Exchange	O
Sudlow	O
pick	O
'd	O
up	O
a	O
Six-pence	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
Porter	O
,	O
Look	O
here	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
found	O
Six-pence	O
.	O
Some	O
Irishmen	O
,	O
of	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
,	O
coming	O
behind	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
what	O
Sudlow	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
Six-pence	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
yes	O
.	O
Why	O
then	O
,	O
says	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
mine	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
,	O
says	O
Sudlow	O
,	O
has	O
it	O
any	O
Mark	O
?	O
Damn	O
you	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
have	O
it	O
.	O
Well	O
then	O
,	O
says	O
Sudlow	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
'll	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
damn	O
you	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Irishman	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
have	O
it	O
without	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
'll	O
have	O
as	O
much	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
Bones	O
.	O
Sudlow	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
,	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Six-pence	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
it	O
he	O
knock	O
'd	O
Sudlow	O
down	O
with	O
a	O
Stick	O
,	O
though	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Provocation	O
given	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Irishmen	O
fell	O
upon	O
him	O
too	O
:	O
Some	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
Sticks	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
any	O
;	O
so	O
they	O
all	O
fell	O
to	O
fighting	O
:	O
Sudlow	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
abus	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
in	O
the	O
Head	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
his	O
Head	O
dress	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
coming	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
they	O
fell	O
upon	O
him	O
afresh	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
was	O
then	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
Tavern	O
Door	O
in	O
his	O
Waistcoat	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
no	O
Sword	O
nor	O
Stick	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Work	O
;	O
and	O
seeing	O
how	O
they	O
abused	O
Sudlow	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
barrarous	O
Villains	O
these	O
are	O
to	O
use	O
a	O
poor	O
Man	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Manner	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
Occasion	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
step	O
'd	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Damn	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
Rascal	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
Chatter	O
?	O
At	O
this	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
began	O
to	O
strip	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
before	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
his	O
Clothes	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
his	O
Arms	O
were	O
pinion	O
'd	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
being	O
part	O
out	O
and	O
part	O
in	O
the	O
Sleeves	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
fell	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
against	O
the	O
Bench	O
with	O
his	O
Fist	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
Blow	O
the	O
Deceas'd	O
's	O
Lip	O
was	O
cut	O
thro	O
'	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
,	O
holding	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
up	O
against	O
the	O
Bench	O
with	O
his	O
Knee	O
,	O
beat	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
violent	O
Manner	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
kick	O
'd	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Belly	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
his	O
Belly	O
was	O
broke	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
At	O
first	O
you	O
said	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
only	O
in	O
his	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
you	O
swear	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
pulling	O
his	O
Coat	O
off	O
when	O
I	O
struck	O
him	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
Clothes	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Had	O
I	O
any	O
Stick	O
?	O
Eastmead	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
say	O
you	O
had	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Was	O
I	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
abusing	O
the	O
Porter	O
that	O
found	O
the	O
Six-pence	O
?	O
Eastmead	O
.	O
You	O
was	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
the	O
Irishmen	O
who	O
made	O
the	O
Riot	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
you	O
strike	O
the	O
Porter	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
offer	O
to	O
strike	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
or	O
give	O
him	O
any	O
Provocation	O
?	O
Eastmead	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
only	O
going	O
to	O
pull	O
off	O
his	O
Waistcoat	O
to	O
defend	O
himself	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
threaten	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
Edw	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
.	O
When	O
the	O
Porter	O
had	O
pick	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
more	O
Irishmen	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
'em	O
demanded	O
the	O
Six-pence	O
.	O
The	O
Porter	O
told	O
them	O
it	O
was	O
true	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
a	O
Six-pence	O
,	O
but	O
ask	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
how	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
theirs	O
,	O
except	O
they	O
could	O
tell	O
what	O
Marks	O
it	O
had	O
?	O
They	O
swore	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
stand	O
for	O
Marks	O
;	O
but	O
Mark	O
,	O
or	O
no	O
Mark	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
held	O
up	O
a	O
Stick	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
strike	O
the	O
Porter	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
,	O
rather	O
than	O
be	O
beat	O
,	O
gave	O
the	O
Six-pence	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
who	O
,	O
notwithstanding	O
this	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
it	O
,	O
knock	O
'd	O
the	O
Porter	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
beat	O
him	O
unmercifully	O
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
being	O
just	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
Tavern	O
Door	O
,	O
bid	O
them	O
not	O
murder	O
the	O
poor	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
barbarous	O
to	O
abuse	O
him	O
in	O
that	O
Manner	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Damn	O
you	O
,	O
what	O
Business	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
chatter	O
?	O
and	O
with	O
that	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
open	O
'd	O
his	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
pull	O
it	O
off	O
;	O
but	O
while	O
his	O
Arms	O
were	O
pinn	O
'd	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
pulling	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Waistcoat	O
Sleeves	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
fell	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
backwards	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
at	O
least	O
a	O
dozen	O
Blows	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
made	O
no	O
Defence	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
because	O
his	O
Arms	O
were	O
confin	O
'd	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
positive	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
did	O
not	O
strike	O
?	O
Andrews	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
offer	O
to	O
lift	O
up	O
his	O
Hand	O
to	O
strike	O
one	O
Blow	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
strike	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
?	O
Andrews	O
.	O
No	O
Body	O
else	O
struck	O
him	O
once	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Senses	O
in	O
half	O
a	O
dozen	O
Blows	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
punch	O
'd	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
and	O
Stomach	O
,	O
and	O
kick	O
'd	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Belly	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
no	O
Body	O
endeavour	O
to	O
prevent	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
from	O
abusing	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Manner	O
?	O
Andrews	O
.	O
No	O
Body	O
dar	O
'd	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
off	O
.	O
for	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Companions	O
were	O
all	O
so	O
desperate	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
all	O
that	O
came	O
in	O
their	O
way	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
I	O
hold	O
him	O
up	O
with	O
my	O
Knee	O
?	O
Andrews	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
observe	O
that	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
Prince's-Street	O
together	O
,	O
when	O
a	O
Man	O
pick	O
'd	O
up	O
Six-pence	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
another	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
Jack	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
good	O
Luck	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
found	O
Six-pence	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Irishmen	O
over-hearing	O
what	O
was	O
said	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
claim	O
'd	O
the	O
Six-pence	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
fell	O
upon	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
all	O
went	O
to	O
fighting	O
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
said	O
to	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
wo	O
n't	O
murder	O
the	O
Man	O
!	O
And	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
Damn	O
you	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
Chatter	O
?	O
I	O
'll	O
settle	O
you	O
presently	O
:	O
Upon	O
which	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
began	O
to	O
pull	O
off	O
his	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
half	O
off	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
fell	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
threw	O
him	O
upon	O
the	O
Nag's-Head	O
Bench	O
,	O
cut	O
his	O
Lip	O
by	O
dashing	O
his	O
Hand	O
in	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
punch	O
'd	O
and	O
kick	O
'd	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Breast	O
and	O
Belly	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
did	O
not	O
strike	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Sutton	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
for	O
his	O
Hands	O
were	O
not	O
at	O
Liberty	O
;	O
-	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
struck	O
at	O
him	O
with	O
such	O
Violence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
struck	O
his	O
Hand	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Sash	O
window	O
of	O
the	O
Nag's-Head	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
,	O
seeing	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
thro	O
'	O
Prince's-Street	O
,	O
halted	O
at	O
the	O
Nag's-Head	O
Door	O
.	O
Two	O
Porters	O
coming	O
along	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
pick	O
'd	O
up	O
Six-pence	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
said	O
,	O
We	O
'll	O
have	O
a	O
full	O
Pot	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Irishmen	O
who	O
were	O
quarrelling	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
's	O
my	O
Six-pence	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
who	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
There	O
's	O
no	O
swearing	O
to	O
Money	O
;	O
but	O
afterwards	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Irishman	O
,	O
who	O
presently	O
(	O
to	O
reward	O
him	O
for	O
his	O
Civility	O
)	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
all	O
went	O
to	O
fighting	O
,	O
till	O
at	O
last	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
who	O
found	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
was	O
laid	O
for	O
dead	O
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
seeing	O
this	O
,	O
went	O
over	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
murder	O
the	O
Man	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
him	O
down	O
on	O
a	O
Bench	O
betwixt	O
two	O
Posts	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
Posture	O
was	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
struck	O
him	O
?	O
Brooks	O
.	O
Posture	O
?	O
He	O
was	O
in	O
no	O
Posture	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
he	O
stood	O
as	O
I	O
do	O
now	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
Hands	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
pulling	O
off	O
his	O
Waistcoat	O
-	O
He	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
red	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
a	O
green	O
Waistcoat	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
But	O
did	O
he	O
offer	O
to	O
strike	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Brooks	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
done	O
it	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
proviso	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
would	O
have	O
given	O
him	O
Liberty	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
fell	O
upon	O
him	O
before	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
his	O
Arms	O
clear	O
from	O
his	O
Waistcoat	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Sudlow	I-pers
.	O
Going	O
along	O
Prince	O
's	O
Street	O
with	O
another	O
Porter	O
,	O
I	O
stoop	O
'd	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
Six-pence	O
.	O
Luck	O
Thee	O
here	O
I	O
says	O
I	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
found	O
Six-pence	O
.	O
What	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
best	O
Thee	O
found	O
Six-pence	O
?	O
that	O
's	O
good	O
Luck	O
indeed	O
,	O
let	O
's	O
have	O
a	O
full	O
Pot	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Some	O
Men	O
follow	O
'd	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Six-pence	O
,	O
which	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
knock	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
with	O
a	O
Stick	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
several	O
Sticks	O
among	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dennis	I-pers
,	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
dy	O
'd	O
on	O
Friday	O
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
I	O
open	O
'd	O
his	O
Body	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Braise	O
six	O
Inches	O
long	O
in	O
the	O
Groin	O
a	O
little	O
above	O
the	O
O	O
Pubs	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
opening	O
the	O
Abdoman	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Intestines	O
were	O
forced	O
into	O
the	O
Scrotum	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
turned	O
black	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Stench	O
was	O
very	O
offensive	O
This	O
Rupture	O
was	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
impossible	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
that	O
condition	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
hinder	O
'd	O
all	O
the	O
Operations	O
of	O
Nature	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
neither	O
make	O
Urine	O
nor	O
go	O
to	O
Stool	O
,	O
but	O
whatever	O
he	O
took	O
in	O
could	O
have	O
no	O
Passage	O
taro	O
'	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
must	O
have	O
been	O
discharged	O
again	O
at	O
his	O
Mouth	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
must	O
have	O
lain	O
in	O
violent	O
Torment	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ashwell	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
my	O
Husband	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
brought	O
home	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Evening	O
in	O
a	O
sad	O
Condition	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
cut	O
and	O
wounded	O
in	O
his	O
Face	O
and	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
bruised	O
in	O
several	O
Parts	O
of	O
his	O
Body	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
his	O
private	O
Parts	O
were	O
swell	O
'd	O
up	O
bigger	O
than	O
my	O
two	O
Fists	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Godfrey	O
,	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Guards	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
order	O
'd	O
some	O
Stuff	O
to	O
bathe	O
him	O
with	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
abate	O
the	O
Swelling	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
poor	O
Husband	O
was	O
in	O
such	O
Torment	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
rest	O
Night	O
nor	O
Day	O
,	O
but	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
like	O
a	O
Woman	O
in	O
Labour	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Time	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
home	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Time	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
Morning	O
following	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Passage	O
below	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
went	O
to	O
Stool	O
or	O
Urine	O
the	O
natural	O
way	O
,	O
but	O
all	O
came	O
up	O
at	O
his	O
Mouth	O
;	O
and	O
before	O
this	O
happen	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
as	O
good	O
a	O
State	O
of	O
Health	O
as	O
any	O
Man	O
in	O
this	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
my	O
Aunt	O
's	O
in	O
Rosemary-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
into	O
Prince	O
's	O
Street	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
Mob	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
quarrelling	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
over	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
there	O
with	O
his	O
Coat	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Waistcoat	O
was	O
all	O
dirty	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
Kennel	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
?	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
beat	O
two	O
of	O
your	O
Country	O
Teagues	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
I	O
'll	O
beat	O
out	O
for	O
a	O
Third	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
struck	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
Inllargger	O
'd	O
over	O
the	O
Kennel	O
,	O
but	O
recover	O
'd	O
my	O
self	O
,	O
I	O
struck	O
at	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
giving	O
way	O
fell	O
backwards	O
against	O
the	O
Bench	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
how	O
or	O
other	O
,	O
the	O
Nag's-Head	O
Window	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
afraid	O
thev	O
'd	O
keep	O
me	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
Damage	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
off	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
's	O
plain	O
had	O
no	O
design	O
to	O
quarrel	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
pull	O
off	O
a	O
Stitch	O
of	O
my	O
Clothes	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
As	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
examin	O
'd	O
a	O
part	O
,	O
let	O
those	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
be	O
examin	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Manner	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Macdonald	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Fray	O
in	O
Prince's-Street	O
,	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
at	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
.	O
A	O
young	O
Man	O
coming	O
by	O
the	O
George	B-pers
Alehouse	I-pers
,	O
stoop	O
'd	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
six-pence	O
.	O
Another	O
Man	O
demanded	O
it	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
George	O
;	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Lynch	O
,	O
who	O
keeps	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
shut	O
the	O
Door	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
a	O
Mob	O
gathering	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
general	O
Quarrel	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
side	O
drove	O
t'other	O
into	O
Drury-Lane	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Into	O
Drury-Lane	O
?	O
Macdonald	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
into	O
Prince's-Street	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Soldier	O
)	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
dirty	O
pickle	O
indeed	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Hog-Sty	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Water	O
in	O
the	O
Land	O
or	O
the	O
Kennel	O
.	O
And	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
whom	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
before	O
,	O
-	O
Court	O
.	O
Then	O
look	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
sure	O
that	O
's	O
he	O
?	O
Macdonald	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
him	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
and	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
?	O
Macdonald	O
.	O
Not	O
before	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
him	O
very	O
well	O
now	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
?	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
beating	O
two	O
Irish	O
Teagues	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
the	O
Third	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
that	O
he	O
struck	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
Deceased	O
struck	O
him	O
first	O
?	O
Macdonald	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
another	O
Man	O
came	O
with	O
a	O
Stick	O
and	O
cut	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
over	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
him	O
reel	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Blood	O
run	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
O	O
fie	O
for	O
Shame	O
!	O
Two	O
upon	O
one	O
!	O
Then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
struck	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Mob	O
edged	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
Well	O
done	O
,	O
Soldier	O
!	O
In	O
the	O
Scuffle	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
fell	O
back	O
over	O
a	O
Bench	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Head	O
fell	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Nag's-Head	O
Window	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
hearing	O
the	O
Window	O
broke	O
,	O
went	O
off	O
for	O
fear	O
they	O
should	O
make	O
him	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
And	O
you	O
swear	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
gave	O
the	O
first	O
Blow	O
?	O
Macdonald	O
.	O
Upon	O
my	O
Oath	O
,	O
Madam	O
,	O
he	O
struck	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
twice	O
before	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
touch	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Here	O
are	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
have	O
sworn	O
the	O
direct	O
contrary	O
:	O
I	O
say	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
Who	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Is	O
there	O
any	O
Body	O
can	O
prove	O
you	O
were	O
there	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Macdonald	O
I	O
'll	O
bring	O
ten	O
thousand	O
People	O
to	O
my	O
Reputation	O
;	O
you	O
may	O
enquire	O
my	O
Character	O
of	O
the	O
best	O
Quality	O
in	O
England	O
,	O
in	O
Duke-Street	O
or	O
Lincolns-Inn-Fields	O
-	O
There	O
were	O
a	O
hundred	O
People	O
heard	O
me	O
cry	O
,	O
Fie	O
for	O
Shame	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
But	O
are	O
any	O
of	O
those	O
People	O
here	O
?	O
You	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
did	O
any	O
of	O
you	O
see	O
this	O
Witness	O
there	O
?	O
All	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
we	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
hear	O
he	O
swears	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
gave	O
the	O
first	O
Blow	O
?	O
All	O
.	O
'T	O
is	O
false	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
strike	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
his	O
Arms	O
were	O
pinion	O
'd	O
down	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
strike	O
a	O
Blow	O
from	O
first	O
to	O
last	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
He	O
swears	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
said	O
,	O
He	O
had	O
beat	O
two	O
Teagues	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
beat	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
Third	O
.	O
All	O
.	O
No	O
such	O
Words	O
were	O
spoke	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
were	O
there	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
.	O
Macdonald	O
.	O
And	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
from	O
the	O
Beginning	O
to	O
the	O
End	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
And	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
endeavour	O
to	O
pull	O
off	O
his	O
Waistcoat	O
?	O
Macdonald	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Is	O
there	O
any	O
one	O
of	O
your	O
own	O
Witnesses	O
that	O
can	O
prove	O
your	O
being	O
there	O
?	O
Macdonald	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
there	O
's	O
Mary	B-pers
Murphy	I-pers
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Call	O
her	O
in	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Murphy	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Prince's-Street	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Quarrel	O
from	O
the	O
Beginning	O
to	O
the	O
End	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
George	O
with	O
some	O
Irishmen	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
to	O
take	O
their	O
Leave	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
more	O
of	O
their	O
Countrymen	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Digneil	O
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Affer	I-pers
,	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
whose	O
Name	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
but	O
by	O
Sight	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Look	O
about	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
here	O
?	O
Murphy	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
and	O
Dignell	O
and	O
Affer	O
went	O
away	O
before	O
the	O
Quarrel	O
begun	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
Men	O
staid	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
George	B-pers
Door	I-pers
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
handle	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
drop	O
any	O
.	O
While	O
they	O
were	O
there	O
,	O
two	O
Men	O
came	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
Six-pence	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
others	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
Six	O
pence	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
with	O
that	O
he	O
up	O
with	O
a	O
Stick	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
two	O
Couple	O
of	O
them	O
fell	O
to	O
fighting	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
the	O
Deceased	O
there	O
?	O
Murphy	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
Crowd	O
in	O
a	O
Soldier	O
's	O
Coat	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Waistcoat	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
strike	O
the	O
Deceased	O
?	O
Murphy	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
as	O
to	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
Crowd	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
Deceased	O
strike	O
him	O
?	O
Murphy	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Nobody	O
strike	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
one	O
Macdonald	O
?	O
Murphy	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
-	O
This	O
is	O
he	O
with	O
the	O
black	O
Brows	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
Business	O
does	O
he	O
follow	O
?	O
Murphy	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
,	O
except	O
he	O
's	O
a	O
Clergyman	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
A	O
Clergyman	O
!	O
Murphy	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
's	O
in	O
another	O
Dress	O
now	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Does	O
he	O
use	O
to	O
appear	O
in	O
a	O
Clergy-man	O
's	O
Dress	O
?	O
Murphy	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
's	O
the	O
common	O
Dress	O
he	O
walks	O
the	O
Streets	O
in	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
there	O
?	O
Officer	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
he	O
makes	O
a	O
Sign	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
winks	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
by	O
that	O
,	O
Sir	O
?	O
-	O
Upon	O
your	O
Oath	O
,	O
Woman	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
here	O
?	O
Murphy	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
very	O
dirty	O
coming	O
from	O
Drury-lane	O
with	O
a	O
Mob	O
behind	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
struck	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
twice	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
him	O
stgger	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Before	O
he	O
was	O
struck	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Kent	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
but	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
recovering	O
struck	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
fell	O
back	O
against	O
a	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
it	O
with	O
his	O
Head	O
.	O
Another	O
Man	O
struck	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
with	O
an	O
Oak	O
Stick	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
his	O
Head	O
bleed	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Was	O
this	O
before	O
or	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
struck	O
the	O
Deceased	O
?	O
Kent	O
.	O
Before	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
And	O
after	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
struck	O
him	O
twice	O
?	O
Kent	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
fell	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
not	O
because	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
struck	O
him	O
twice	O
;	O
for	O
,	O
auseems	O
,	O
he	O
bore	O
that	O
patiently	O
,	O
but	O
because	O
other	O
Man	O
afterwards	O
came	O
and	O
broke	O
his	O
Head	O
.	O
-	O
Did	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Witnesses	O
see	O
any	O
Body	O
strike	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
Stick	O
?	O
All	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
nor	O
with	O
any	O
Thing	O
else	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Conner	I-pers
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
Throng	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
full	O
of	O
Dirt	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
?	O
Matter	O
!	O
you	O
Rascal	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
to	O
fight	O
?	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
him	O
say	O
nothing	O
of	O
beating	O
two	O
Teagues	O
?	O
Conner	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
struck	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Blows	O
,	O
and	O
beat	O
him	O
over	O
the	O
Kennel	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
off	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Three	O
or	O
four	O
Blows	O
!	O
Conner	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
another	O
Man	O
knocked	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
down	O
with	O
a	O
Stick	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Mob	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
O	O
fye	O
,	O
that	O
's	O
too	O
much	O
!	O
two	O
to	O
one	O
!	O
Then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
struck	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
who	O
fell	O
with	O
his	O
Head	O
through	O
the	O
Window	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Conner	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
upon	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Clothes	O
were	O
all	O
dirty	O
.	O
King	O
's	O
Witnesses	O
.	O
His	O
Clothes	O
were	O
not	O
dirty	O
,	O
nor	O
was	O
he	O
at	O
all	O
in	O
Drink	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Jury	O
that	O
sat	O
upon	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Days	O
after	O
Mr.	O
Macdonald	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
wish	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
before	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
Deceased	O
gave	O
the	O
first	O
Blow	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
But	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
acquainted	O
the	O
Jury	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
knew	O
you	O
were	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
an	O
Irishman	O
too	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Macdonald	I-pers
.	O
While	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
were	O
fighting	O
,	O
another	O
Man	O
knocked	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
down	O
with	O
a	O
Stick	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
rising	O
again	O
knocked	O
the	O
Deceased	O
backward	O
through	O
the	O
Nag's-Head	O
Window	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
talking	O
together	O
;	O
the	O
Deceased	O
struck	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
tumbled	O
down	O
the	O
Kennel	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
the	O
Deceased	O
struck	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Man	O
broke	O
his	O
Head	O
with	O
a	O
Stick	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
beat	O
the	O
Deceased	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Because	O
another	O
Man	O
broke	O
his	O
Head	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
,	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
Drawer	O
at	O
the	O
Nag's-Head	O
.	O
Some	O
Irishmen	O
were	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
George	B-pers
Alehouse	I-pers
Door	I-pers
,	O
which	O
is	O
kept	O
by	O
an	O
Irishman	O
.	O
A	O
Porter	O
came	O
by	O
and	O
found	O
Six-pence	O
;	O
the	O
Irishmen	O
claim	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
They	O
fell	O
to	O
fighting	O
.	O
The	O
Porter	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
abus	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
asked	O
them	O
,	O
Why	O
they	O
used	O
the	O
Man	O
so	O
barbarously	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
wanted	O
,	O
or	O
why	O
he	O
chatter	O
'd	O
?	O
Upon	O
which	O
the	O
Deceased	O
went	O
to	O
pull	O
off	O
his	O
Waistcoat	O
;	O
but	O
while	O
his	O
Arms	O
were	O
pinion	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
fell	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
beat	O
him	O
unmercifully	O
upon	O
the	O
Stomach	O
and	O
Belly	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
did	O
not	O
strike	O
one	O
Blow	O
,	O
first	O
or	O
last	O
;	O
nor	O
did	O
any	O
Body	O
else	O
strike	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
nor	O
was	O
his	O
Head	O
bloody	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
John	B-pers
Macdonald	I-pers
there	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
saw	O
Murphy	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
If	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Part	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
that	O
was	O
abused	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
far	O
from	O
being	O
a	O
Provocation	O
sufficient	O
to	O
justify	O
the	O
other	O
in	O
killing	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
only	O
a	O
lawful	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
commendable	O
Action	O
;	O
and	O
where	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
Provocation	O
given	O
the	O
Law	O
implies	O
Malice	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
that	O
maliciously	O
kills	O
another	O
,	O
is	O
guilty	O
of	O
Murder	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
9.	O
Isabel	B-pers
Banister	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Jones	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
four	O
Peticoats	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Creed	I-pers
,	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
Aug.	O
13	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
10.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
(	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
two	O
Wigs	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
8	O
s.	O
three	O
Hats	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jacob	B-pers
Kendall	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Bury	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Jacob	B-pers
Kendall	I-pers
,	O
June	O
17	O
.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Kendall	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
King's-Arms	B-place
in	O
Burr-street	B-place
:	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Bar	O
between	O
Eleven	O
and	O
Twelve	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
The	O
Wigs	O
cost	O
me	O
ten	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
not	O
10	O
Pence	O
the	O
worse	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
Newell	O
.	O
Between	O
Eleven	O
and	O
Twelve	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
,	O
Abel	O
[	O
Abraham	O
]	O
Gibson	O
and	O
Tom	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
[	O
Roberts	O
]	O
and	O
I	O
going	O
by	O
the	O
King's-Arms	O
,	O
look	O
'd	O
in	O
and	O
saw	O
Nobody	O
in	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
unhasp	O
'd	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
two	O
Wigs	O
and	O
four	O
Hats	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
Sue	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
who	O
sold	O
them	O
all	O
(	O
as	O
she	O
told	O
us	O
)	O
for	O
19	O
s.	O
Sue	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
and	O
Bess	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
were	O
going	O
to	O
Stocks-Market	O
,	O
Newell	O
and	O
Roberts	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
after	O
us	O
on	O
Tower-Hill	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
'em	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
stay	O
,	O
but	O
Bess	O
went	O
back	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
Wigs	O
and	O
Hats	O
after	O
me	O
to	O
Stocks-Market	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
sold	O
'em	O
for	O
19	O
s.	O
the	O
Wigs	O
to	O
a	O
Barber	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Hats	O
to	O
a	O
Hatter	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
Newell	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
on	O
another	O
Information	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
quarrelling	O
,	O
he	O
'peach	O
'd	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
Spite	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
11.	O
John	B-pers
Olave	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Peat	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
four	O
gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
two	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
three	O
Tea-Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
Shillings	O
,	O
June	O
11	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Peat	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lye	O
in	O
a	O
low	O
Room	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	B-place
;	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
Doors	O
all	O
fast	O
,	O
but	O
about	O
Two	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
the	O
Watch	O
call	O
'd	O
me	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
were	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
.	O
My	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
were	O
taken	O
off	O
the	O
Bed	O
where	O
I	O
lay	O
.	O
A	O
little	O
Boy	O
(	O
Wm	B-pers
Newell	I-pers
)	O
afterwards	O
inform	O
'd	O
me	O
who	O
did	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
me	O
a-bed	O
?	O
and	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
No	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
felt	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
had	O
taken	O
more	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
were	O
frighted	O
by	O
Somebody	O
's	O
calling	O
up	O
a	O
Midwife	O
next	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
what	O
we	O
had	O
got	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
Newell	O
.	O
Between	O
One	O
and	O
Two	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
knew	O
a	O
House	O
where	O
we	O
could	O
get	O
in	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
listed	O
me	O
over	O
the	O
Spikes	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
struck	O
back	O
the	O
Lock	O
of	O
the	O
Yard	O
Door	O
and	O
let	O
him	O
in	O
.	O
The	O
Kitchen	O
Window	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Paper	O
stuck	O
over	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
tore	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
struck	O
back	O
the	O
Lock	O
of	O
that	O
Door	O
too	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
both	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
Rachel	B-pers
Oram	I-pers
.	O
Sue	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Newell	O
brought	O
the	O
Things	O
over	O
the	O
Water	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
me	O
then	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
I	O
met	O
them	O
at	O
play	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
had	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
Rachel	B-pers
Oram	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Olave	I-pers
,	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Wig	O
,	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
and	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Mackey	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Ship	B-place
Mary	I-place
,	O
July	O
26	O
.	O
J.	O
Mackey	O
.	O
As	O
my	O
Mate	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
asleep	O
in	O
my	O
Cabbin	O
we	O
were	O
surprized	O
by	O
a	O
Light	O
.	O
I	O
started	O
up	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Aba	O
!	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
there	O
?	O
He	O
jump	O
'd	O
half	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Cabin	O
Window	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
catch	O
'd	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Legs	O
and	O
haul	O
'd	O
him	O
in	O
again	O
.	O
A	O
Wherry	O
lay	O
at	O
the	O
Ship	O
's	O
Stern	O
to	O
put	O
the	O
Things	O
in	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
a	O
Dark	O
Lanthorn	O
and	O
a	O
Penknife	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
12.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
gold	O
Ring	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Till	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
15	O
.	O
Mary	O
Till	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Chandler	O
's	O
Shop	O
in	O
Scotland-yard	B-place
,	O
and	O
this	O
good	O
Woman	O
that	O
pick	O
'd	O
my	O
Pocket	O
is	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Vanbritton	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
suckling	O
my	O
Child	O
,	O
she	O
comes	O
in	O
and	O
asks	O
for	O
a	O
Dram	O
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Edson	I-pers
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
Pray	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Robinson	O
,	O
be	O
pleas	O
'd	O
to	O
serve	O
yourself	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
she	O
took	O
a	O
Dram	O
and	O
came	O
and	O
cower	O
'd	O
herself	O
down	O
by	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
something	O
jink	O
,	O
and	O
catch	O
'd	O
her	O
Hand	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
only	O
in	O
Accidence	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
never	O
intrusted	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
any	O
Thing	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
a	O
Tuesday	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
next	O
Morning	O
I	O
told	O
Mrs.	O
Olive	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
how	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
my	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
afterwards	O
comes	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
says	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Robinson	O
is	O
fuddled	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
drove	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
her	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
wish	O
she	O
do	O
n't	O
lay	O
this	O
Ring	O
to	O
my	O
Charge	O
.	O
Whereof	O
I	O
sent	O
to	O
her	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
sent	O
me	O
Word	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
my	O
Ring	O
,	O
or	O
Satisfaction	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
insisted	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
do	O
insist	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
because	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
Hand	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
it	O
was	O
clench	O
'd	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
But	O
why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
open	O
her	O
Hand	O
to	O
see	O
whether	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Ring	O
or	O
not	O
?	O
M.	O
Till	O
.	O
Its	O
all	O
one	O
for	O
that	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
as	O
many	O
good	O
Things	O
as	O
another	O
;	O
I	O
ha	O
n't	O
liv	O
'd	O
so	O
long	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
for	O
nothing	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
what	O
belongs	O
to	O
the	O
Law	O
better	O
than	O
any	O
Body	O
can	O
tell	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
Hand	O
in	O
any	O
Body	O
's	O
Pocket	O
,	O
whether	O
I	O
take	O
any	O
Thing	O
out	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
say	O
its	O
a	O
Robbery	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
That	O
,	O
indeed	O
,	O
is	O
more	O
than	O
the	O
Court	O
knew	O
before	O
.	O
Olive	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Master	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Room	O
in	O
her	O
Shift	O
,	O
though	O
it	O
's	O
well	O
known	O
he	O
has	O
got	O
a	O
W	O
ife	O
and	O
five	O
Children	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
as	O
how	O
they	O
had	O
had	O
some	O
Words	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
got	O
a	O
Ring	O
upon	O
her	O
Finger	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
little	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
it	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
she	O
soap	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
bath	O
'd	O
her	O
Hand	O
in	O
Suds	O
.	O
Laud	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
like	O
Mrs.	O
Till	O
's	O
Ring	O
.	O
Gode	O
daum	O
you	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
she	O
never	O
bade	O
such	O
an	O
a	O
Ring	O
in	O
her	O
Leef	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
her	O
Master	O
had	O
the	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
sent	O
to	O
borrow	O
three	O
Rings	O
to	O
see	O
whether	O
I	O
would	O
swear	O
my	O
parjur	O
'd	O
Oath	O
upon	O
the	O
wrong	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
told	O
Mrs.	O
Till	O
how	O
and	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Edson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
good	O
Woman	O
's	O
Hand	O
in	O
Mrs.	O
Till	O
's	O
Pocket	O
,	O
whereof	O
Mrs.	O
Till	O
said	O
,	O
There	O
's	O
no	O
Pears	O
in	O
that	O
Pot	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drunk	O
?	O
A.	O
Edson	O
.	O
Not	O
so	O
drunk	O
as	O
that	O
comes	O
to	O
,	O
neither	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
wo	O
n't	O
swear	O
but	O
I	O
touch	O
'd	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
Hand	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
change	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
Lap	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
never	O
see	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
look	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
drop	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
she	O
turn	O
'd	O
her	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Pocket	O
.	O
M.	O
Till	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
two	O
Months	O
before	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
Ring	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Vanbritton	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
has	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
14	O
Years	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
her	O
with	O
all	O
I	O
had	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Creature	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
a	O
good	O
Customer	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
has	O
laid	O
out	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
Shillings	O
in	O
a	O
Week	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
Fault	O
she	O
had	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
let	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
entice	O
her	O
to	O
get	O
drunk	O
at	O
her	O
Shop	O
.	O
-	O
Pointer	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
swear	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
she	O
could	O
be	O
revenged	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
be	O
content	O
to	O
be	O
rack	O
'd	O
to	O
Death	O
next	O
Moment	O
.	O
-	O
And	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
say	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
her	O
Revenge	O
of	O
the	O
Beast	O
if	O
she	O
swore	O
thro	O
'	O
a	O
two	O
Inch	O
Board	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
granted	O
her	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
her	O
Indictment	O
.	O
13.	O
Mary	B-pers
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Tremain	I-pers
*	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Par	I-pers
,	O
July	O
14	O
.	O
*	O
She	O
and	O
her	O
Husband	O
were	O
convicted	O
in	O
October	O
1732	O
,	O
of	O
paying	O
counterfeit	O
Money	O
in	O
Bartholomew	O
Fair	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
fined	O
two	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
both	O
were	O
to	O
suffer	O
three	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
the	O
Sessions	O
Paper	O
for	O
that	O
Year	O
,	O
Numb	O
.	O
VIII	O
.	O
page	O
246	O
.	O
About	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
before	O
it	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
Shirt	O
out	O
of	O
pawn	O
;	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
went	O
up	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Watch	O
then	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
Counter	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
she	O
paid	O
him	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
Hurry	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
Enquiry	O
found	O
it	O
at	O
another	O
Pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
pledged	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
her	O
Husband	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
14.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Abram	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Pewter	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Jonas	B-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Durand	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
14	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
15.	O
Susan	B-pers
Rambridge	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Guinea	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Long	I-pers
,	O
July	O
19	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
16.	O
Ann	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Snuff-box	O
,	O
a	O
Mob	O
,	O
and	O
8	O
s.	O
8	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Newby	I-pers
,	O
August	O
21	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
17.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Watch	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dibly	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Clerk	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
2	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
18.	O
Ann	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
three	O
Shifts	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
22	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
19	O
,	O
20.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Huddlestone	I-pers
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
July	O
6	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
21.	O
Jane	B-pers
Flood	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
June	O
22	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
22.	O
John	B-pers
Riles	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
9	O
Iron	O
hoops	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Felix	B-pers
Calvert	I-pers
,	O
Esq	B-pers
;	I-pers
and	O
Comp	B-pers
.	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
Comp	O
.	O
July	O
10	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
23	O
,	O
24.	O
Jane	B-pers
Maddox	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Catherine	B-pers
,	O
otherwise	B-pers
Jane	I-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jeremy	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
July	O
24	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
25.	O
Richard	B-pers
Wassey	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
50	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Gatlin	I-pers
,	O
August	O
10	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
26.	O
Martha	B-pers
Weston	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Shirts	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Arnot	I-pers
,	O
July	O
10	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
27.	O
William	B-pers
Wilbert	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
nine	O
Guineas	O
,	O
two	O
Moidores	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Bunch	O
of	O
human	O
Hair	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Fitz	B-pers
William	I-pers
Ferran	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Sherman	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Fitz	B-pers
William	I-pers
Ferran	I-pers
,	O
June	O
27	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
28.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Perkins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Will	B-pers
Perkins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Perkins	I-pers
,	O
in	O
their	O
House	O
,	O
Sept.	O
1	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
29	O
,	O
30.	O
Mark	B-pers
Biggs	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Christopher	B-pers
Keightly	I-pers
,	O
(	O
two	O
Boy	O
s	O
)	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
four	O
gold	O
Necklaces	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Manners	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
August	O
31	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Manners	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
four	O
gold	O
Necklaces	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Shew-glass	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Hours	O
after	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
Ned	B-pers
Langford	I-pers
,	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Shew-glass	O
again	O
,	O
which	O
making	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
alarm	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
out	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
this	O
Wire	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
he	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
draw	O
Things	O
out	O
of	O
Shew-glasses	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
carry	O
'd	O
before	O
Justice	O
Deveil	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
stole	O
the	O
Necklaces	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Marrian	I-pers
in	O
Mint-Street	O
.	O
-	O
Here	O
Langford	O
is	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Edw	B-pers
Langford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
13	O
last	O
Christmas	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Suppose	O
now	O
,	O
you	O
should	O
not	O
swear	O
the	O
Truth	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
will	O
become	O
of	O
you	O
?	O
Langford	O
.	O
Why	O
,	O
really	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
read	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Bible	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
's	O
Death	O
in	O
this	O
World	O
,	O
and	O
Damnation	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
?	O
Langford	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
went	O
a	O
Thieving	O
together	O
.	O
Chriss	O
Keightly	O
lifted	O
up	O
the	O
Shew-glass	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
gold	O
Necklaces	O
out	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
large	O
one	O
and	O
three	O
little	O
ones	O
,	O
we	O
sold	O
them	O
all	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Marrian	I-pers
in	O
Mint-Street	O
,	O
for	O
34	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
we	O
divided	O
11	O
s.	O
a	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
spent	O
the	O
odd	O
Money	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
Bigs	O
do	O
?	O
Langford	O
.	O
He	O
stood	O
still	O
on	O
t'other	O
side	O
the	O
Shew-glass	O
.	O
He	O
knew	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
at	O
Thieving	O
;	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
justly	O
know	O
that	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
that	O
very	O
Shew-glass	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Langford	O
's	O
Information	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
other	O
Boys	O
a-Bed	O
,	O
at	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
about	O
twelve	O
at	O
Night	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
several	O
silver	O
Things	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
next	O
Morning	O
.	O
we	O
took	O
Marrian	O
.	O
Keightly	O
.	O
This	O
Rogue	O
,	O
Langford	O
,	O
will	O
swear	O
any	O
Body	O
's	O
Life	O
away	O
for	O
a	O
Farthing	O
:	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
know	O
me	O
steal	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
a	O
Pin	O
,	O
you	O
Rogue	O
?	O
Langford	O
.	O
Not	O
before	O
this	O
Time	O
.	O
Keightly	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
Body	O
see	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
?	O
Lang	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
none	O
of	O
us	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
the	O
Shew-glass	O
stand	O
,	O
was	O
it	O
within	O
the	O
Shop	O
or	O
without	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Part	O
without	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
but	O
more	O
within	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Necklaces	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
inner	O
Part	O
.	O
The	O
Lock	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
-	O
Marrian	O
is	O
in	O
Surrey	O
Goal	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
Biggs	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Keightly	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
31.	O
Daniel	B-pers
George	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	B-pers
Little	I-pers
Daniel	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
silver	O
Instrument	O
Cases	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
two	O
silver	O
handle	O
Knives	O
,	O
two	O
silver	O
Scissors	O
,	O
two	O
silver	O
Ear-pickers	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
steel	O
Nippers	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Triquet	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
August	O
28	O
.	O
Stephen	O
Triquet	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Toy-shop	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	B-place
.	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
Instrument-Cases	O
with	O
Instruments	O
in	O
them	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Shew-glass	O
,	O
August	O
28.	O
Edw	B-pers
Langford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
and	O
Little	O
Daniel	O
saw	O
the	O
Shew-glass	O
open	O
'd	O
to	O
show	O
some	O
Things	O
to	O
some	O
Gentlemen	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
about	O
Noon	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
waited	O
till	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
the	O
Glass	O
was	O
not	O
lock	O
'd	O
afterwards	O
,	O
Daniel	O
lifted	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Things	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
Marrian	O
in	O
the	O
Mint	O
,	O
for	O
18	O
s.	O
Mr.	O
Deveil	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Manners	O
having	O
taken	O
Langford	O
on	O
suspicion	O
,	O
brought	O
him	O
before	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
nothing	O
being	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
send	O
him	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
as	O
an	O
idle	O
loose	O
Boy	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
this	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
others	O
,	O
and	O
inform	O
'd	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
four	O
other	O
Boys	O
,	O
who	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
lodg	O
'd	O
together	O
at	O
the	O
Two-Brewers	O
,	O
in	O
Maynard-Street	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Is	O
not	O
that	O
House	O
suppress	O
'd	O
yet	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Deveil	O
.	O
He	O
inform	O
'd	O
me	O
that	O
John	B-pers
Marrian	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Mint	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
who	O
receiv	O
'd	O
what	O
they	O
stole	O
.	O
Marrian	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
House	O
being	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
silver	O
and	O
gold	O
Toys	O
were	O
found	O
under	O
a	O
Plank	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
14	O
or	O
15	O
l.	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
them	O
all	O
for	O
3	O
l.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
lay	O
but	O
two	O
Nights	O
at	O
the	O
Two-Brewers	O
,	O
and	O
Langford	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
Boy	O
s	O
lay	O
there	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
those	O
Boys	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
charg	O
'd	O
me	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
clear	O
himself	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
32	O
,	O
33.	O
John	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	B-pers
Mollying	I-pers
Jack	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	B-pers
Jack	I-pers
the	I-pers
Hatter	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Glass-bottle	O
tipp	O
'd	O
with	O
Silver	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Paul	B-pers
Gerard	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
August	O
29	O
.	O
Paul	O
Gerard	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
from	O
my	O
Shew-glass	O
in	O
my	O
Shop-window	O
,	O
next	O
to	O
Northumberland-House	B-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	B-place
;	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
them	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
they	O
were	O
over	O
the	O
Water	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Langford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
sell	O
some	O
Ribbon	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
in	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-Yard	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
look	O
out	O
for	O
a	O
Gold-watch	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
together	O
,	O
to	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
the	O
Glass-case	O
unlock	O
'd	O
,	O
Mullying	O
Jack	O
lifted	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
silver	O
Snuff-mull	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Smelling-bottle	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
Jack	O
the	O
Hatter	O
stood	O
by	O
to	O
watch	O
.	O
We	O
sold	O
the	O
Mull	O
to	O
Marrian	O
for	O
9	O
s.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
John	O
Mills	O
,	O
and	O
John	O
Walker	O
,	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
Stock-clasps	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
Tobacco-stopper	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
silver	O
Stock-buckle	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Alcock	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
September	O
1	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
Tea-tongs	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
three	O
silver	O
Girdle-buckles	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
silver	O
Stock-buckle	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Alcock	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
September	O
1	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
George	I-pers
,	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
eleven	O
Tea-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
33	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Alcock	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
Sept.	O
1	O
.	O
J.	O
Alcock	O
.	O
These	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Shew-glass	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Justice	O
Deveil	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
Ned	B-pers
Langford	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Nimble	O
Jack	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
me	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
had	O
stolen	O
all	O
these	O
Things	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Shop	O
at	O
Cripple-gate	B-place
.	O
By	O
his	O
Information	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
Beds	O
,	O
at	O
one	O
Evans	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
keeps	O
the	O
Two-Brewers	O
,	O
in	O
Maynard-Street	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Langford	O
,	O
here	O
are	O
several	O
Persons	O
Lives	O
at	O
stake	O
,	O
you	O
ought	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
cautious	O
of	O
what	O
you	O
swear	O
.	O
You	O
were	O
ask	O
'd	O
in	O
a	O
former	O
Trial	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
you	O
are	O
now	O
before	O
another	O
Jury	O
,	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
proper	O
to	O
ask	O
you	O
again	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Consequence	O
of	O
swearing	O
falsely	O
?	O
Langford	O
.	O
Nay	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
say	O
it	O
's	O
Damnation	O
in	O
t'other	O
World	O
.	O
The	O
Day	O
after	O
we	O
robb	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Triquet	O
,	O
I	O
and	O
Jack	O
the	O
Hatter	O
,	O
and	O
Mollying	O
Jack	O
,	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
Moorfields	O
,	O
and	O
passing	O
by	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
says	O
Mollying	O
Jack	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
lay	O
a	O
Shilling	O
,	O
that	O
Shew-glass	O
will	O
lift	O
up	O
.	O
It	O
wo	O
n't	O
,	O
says	O
Jack	O
the	O
Hatter	O
.	O
You	O
lye	O
but	O
it	O
will	O
,	O
says	O
t'other	O
Jack	O
.	O
Let	O
's	O
go	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
then	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
lifted	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
these	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
Stock-clasps	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
stood	O
by	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
if	O
any	O
Body	O
was	O
a	O
coming	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Marrian	I-pers
's	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
all	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
6	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Then	O
Jack	O
the	O
Hatter	O
and	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Place	O
,	O
he	O
lifted	O
up	O
the	O
Glass	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Tea-tongs	O
,	O
three	O
Girdle-buckles	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
half	O
of	O
the	O
Stock-buckle	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
between	O
3	O
and	O
4	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
the	O
Gentlewoman	O
was	O
drinking	O
Tea	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
behind	O
the	O
Shop	O
.	O
We	O
carry	O
'd	O
these	O
Things	O
to	O
Marrian	O
too	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
all	O
for	O
10	O
s.	O
And	O
the	O
same	O
Afternoon	O
I	O
met	O
Little	O
Daniel	O
.	O
and	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Shop	O
;	O
but	O
a	O
Woman	O
looking	O
out	O
at	O
a	O
Draper	O
's	O
Shop	O
over-against	O
us	O
,	O
we	O
waited	O
for	O
her	O
going	O
in	O
;	O
but	O
a	O
Dray	O
stopping	O
just	O
before	O
the	O
Draper	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
,	O
and	O
Daniel	O
lifted	O
up	O
the	O
Shew-glass	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
these	O
two	O
Bunches	O
of	O
Spoons	O
,	O
fix	O
in	O
one	O
Bunch	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
Marrian	O
,	O
for	O
17	O
s.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
Mills	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
others	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
34.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Firminer	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
two	O
Calves-Skins	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dagly	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
June	O
,	O
30	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
35.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
gold	O
Ear-rings	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Yards	O
of	O
Lace	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Cam	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
10	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
36.	O
John	B-pers
Maxey	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
7	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Tea	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bolby	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
August	O
31	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
37	O
,	O
38.	O
William	B-pers
Macroy	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Stodhart	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Mary	B-pers
Painter	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Willow-Walk	B-place
,	I-place
near	O
Chelsea	B-place
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
a	O
Cap	O
,	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
June	O
30	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
39.	O
John	B-pers
Cosin	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	B-pers
Cousins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Thistleworth	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Haydon	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
's	O
Travelling-box	O
,	O
with	O
Vials	O
,	O
Gallipots	O
,	O
Instruments	O
,	O
Spirits	O
,	O
Balsam	O
,	O
3	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
l.	O
18	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
June	O
29	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
40	O
,	O
41.	O
Mary	B-pers
Denny	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Bridget	B-pers
Clayton	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
18	O
Yards	O
of	O
Muslin	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rives	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
July	O
3	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
42.	O
Robert	B-pers
Letts	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eleven	O
Grains	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Winsmore	I-pers
,	O
September	O
7	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Hats	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
July	O
13	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
43	O
,	O
44	O
,	O
45.	O
George	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
Laurence	B-pers
Grace	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Smithson	I-pers
*	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
(	O
with	O
+	O
Thomas	B-pers
Whithy	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	B-pers
Woodby	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Gordon	I-pers
in	O
Lincoln's-Inn-Fields	B-place
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
a	O
Wig	O
,	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
d.	O
July	O
28	O
.	O
*	O
Smithson	O
was	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
William	B-pers
West	I-pers
and	O
Andrew	B-pers
Curd	I-pers
,	O
for	O
a	O
Burglary	O
in	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
See	O
Sessions	O
Paper	O
.	O
Numb	O
.	O
III	O
.	O
Page	O
67.	O
and	O
in	O
May	O
following	O
he	O
and	O
others	O
were	O
try	O
'd	O
for	O
robbing	O
John	B-pers
Violane	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
John	B-pers
Frazier	I-pers
's	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
stealing	O
Rich	O
.	O
Cock	O
's	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
;	O
and	O
+	O
Thomas	B-pers
Whithy	I-pers
was	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
it	O
,	O
those	O
three	O
Trials	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
See	O
Sessions	O
Paper	O
,	O
Numb	O
V.	O
page	O
148	O
,	O
149	O
.	O
The	O
Witnesses	O
(	O
at	O
the	O
Desire	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
)	O
were	O
examined	O
a-part	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gordon	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
just	O
at	O
Midnight	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
crossing	O
Lincoln's-Inn-Fields	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
set	O
upon	O
by	O
five	O
Men	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
clear	O
Star-light	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
very	O
plainly	O
.	O
Grace	O
came	O
up	O
first	O
,	O
took	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
Collar	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Damn	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
Dog	O
,	O
stand	O
,	O
and	O
deliver	O
your	O
Money	O
;	O
if	O
you	O
speak	O
a	O
Word	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
.	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
him	O
very	O
hard	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
.	O
Two	O
others	O
then	O
rifled	O
my	O
Pockets	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
taking	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
a	O
short	O
Man	O
in	O
a	O
Cap	O
and	O
a	O
blue	O
Jacket	O
,	O
whom	O
I	O
take	O
to	O
be	O
Richardson	O
,	O
came	O
behind	O
me	O
,	O
struck	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
Arm	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
over	O
my	O
Shoulder	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
.	O
-	O
Him	O
and	O
Grace	O
I	O
remember	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
Smithson	O
.	O
-	O
Grace	O
held	O
me	O
fast	O
,	O
but	O
took	O
nothing	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Grace	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
it	O
after	O
the	O
Robbery	O
before	O
you	O
saw	O
me	O
?	O
Gordon	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
.	O
You	O
were	O
then	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
I	O
and	O
Tom	B-pers
Whithy	I-pers
agreed	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Lincoln's-Inn	O
Fields	O
together	O
.	O
Richardson	O
,	O
indeed	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
agree	O
to	O
rob	O
,	O
but	O
Grace	O
swore	O
by	O
God	O
he	O
'd	O
attack	O
the	O
first	O
Man	O
he	O
met	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Grace	O
collar	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
Whithy	O
and	O
I	O
search	O
'd	O
his	O
Pockets	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
5	O
d.	O
Court	O
.	O
Who	O
took	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
?	O
Watson	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
Grace	O
struck	O
him	O
over	O
the	O
Hand	O
with	O
an	O
Oak-Stick	O
.	O
Gordon	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
Cap	O
and	O
blue	O
Jacket	O
that	O
did	O
both	O
.	O
Watson	O
.	O
Its	O
true	O
,	O
Richardson	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
blue	O
Jacket	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
had	O
us	O
to	O
have	O
gone	O
a	O
Robbing	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
leave	O
you	O
then	O
before	O
the	O
Robbery	O
?	O
Watson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
was	O
behind	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
distant	O
?	O
Watson	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
within	O
Reach	O
of	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
.	O
Gordon	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
behind	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
my	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
.	O
Watson	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
about	O
twelve	O
a	O
Clock	O
on	O
Friday	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
one	O
a	O
Clock	O
next	O
Morning	O
we	O
attack	O
'd	O
a	O
Man	O
(	O
Mr.	O
Spencely	O
)	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
taken	O
by	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
to	O
Clerkenwell	O
.	O
Roger	B-pers
Leak	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Watchman	O
at	O
the	O
upper	O
End	O
of	O
Bedford-Row	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
Mr.	O
Spencely	O
call	O
out	O
,	O
Watch	O
!	O
stop'em	O
!	O
-	O
Richardson	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Linen	O
Cap	O
and	O
blue	O
Jacket	O
,	O
came	O
running	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
stopp	O
'd	O
him	O
between	O
the	O
upper	O
End	O
of	O
Featherstone-Buildings	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
upper	O
End	O
of	O
Hand-Alley	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Spencely	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
taken	O
Watson	O
himself	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
about	O
One	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Slack	I-pers
.	O
And	O
between	O
One	O
and	O
Two	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
hard	O
by	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
Richardson	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Gordon	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Shorter	I-pers
.	O
Watson	O
declar	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
New-Prison	O
,	O
that	O
Richardson	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
this	O
Robbery	O
.	O
Watson	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
not	O
willing	O
to	O
rob	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
Shorter	O
.	O
He	O
,	O
indeed	O
,	O
said	O
so	O
at	O
last	O
,	O
-	O
and	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
why	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
put	O
Richardson	O
in	O
his	O
first	O
Information	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
save	O
him	O
.	O
Smithson	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
have	O
drank	O
in	O
Watson	O
's	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
Peg	B-pers
Yately	I-pers
,	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
inform	O
'd	O
against	O
me	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
in	O
New	O
Prison	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
half	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Gin	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
assur	O
'd	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
nothing	O
against	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
his	O
first	O
Information	O
which	O
he	O
made	O
before	O
Justice	O
Robe	O
.	O
Watson	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
Justice	O
Robe	O
's	O
Clerk	O
,	O
that	O
we	O
all	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Night-House	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
then	O
another	O
House	O
in	O
Shug-L	O
ane	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
to	O
Lincoln's-Inn-Fields	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
nam	O
'd	O
all	O
their	O
Names	O
to	O
the	O
Clerk	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
forgot	O
Smithson	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
his	O
Name	O
is	O
interlin	O
'd	O
.	O
Smithson	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
under	O
Misfortunes	O
before	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Richardson	O
from	O
a	O
Child	O
;	O
his	O
Parents	O
live	O
in	O
Eagle-street	O
,	O
Soho	O
;	O
he	O
follows	O
no	O
Employment	O
,	O
but	O
lives	O
with	O
his	O
Father	O
,	O
who	O
has	O
an	O
Estate	O
to	O
support	O
his	O
Family	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
Ill	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
-	O
but	O
I	O
ha	O
n't	O
seen	O
him	O
much	O
for	O
these	O
last	O
six	O
Months	O
.	O
Another	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
from	O
Sea	O
eight	O
or	O
ten	O
Months	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
Misfortune	O
to	O
fall	O
into	O
this	O
ill	O
Company	O
.	O
Some	O
others	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Ill	O
of	O
Richardson	O
before	O
this	O
Time	O
.	O
Watson	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Richardson	O
several	O
Years	O
;	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
three	O
Months	O
in	O
Clerkenwell	O
Bridewell	O
for	O
a	O
Street-Robbery	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Indictment	O
we	O
were	O
discharged	O
-	O
After	O
I	O
had	O
made	O
my	O
first	O
Information	O
before	O
Justice	O
Robe	O
,	O
several	O
Thief-Catchers	O
,	O
-	O
there	O
's	O
George	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
my	O
Lord	O
Vaughan	O
,	O
for	O
one	O
,	O
-	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
New-Prison	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
me	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
make	O
me	O
make	O
another	O
Information	O
before	O
Justice	O
Midford	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
down	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
New-Prison	O
.	O
-	O
These	O
Thief-Catchers	O
will	O
do	O
any	O
Thing	O
for	O
Money	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Upon	O
your	O
Oath	O
was	O
Richardson	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
?	O
Watson	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Was	O
Green	O
?	O
Watson	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
And	O
Smithson	O
?	O
Watson	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
present	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
appear	O
'd	O
very	O
willing	O
to	O
screen	O
Richardson	O
.	O
Has	O
Nobody	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
persuade	O
you	O
not	O
to	O
swear	O
against	O
him	O
?	O
Watson	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
Attorney	O
came	O
to	O
New-Prison	O
,	O
and	O
enquir	O
'd	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Bowl	O
of	O
Punch	O
,	O
and	O
bad	O
me	O
sit	O
down	O
and	O
drink	O
heartily	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
that	O
Bowl	O
was	O
out	O
we	O
had	O
another	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
Richardson	O
's	O
Father	O
was	O
a	O
good	O
'Sponsible	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
clear	O
Richardson	O
,	O
and	O
leave	O
him	O
out	O
in	O
my	O
Information	O
,	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
better	O
for	O
me	O
than	O
I	O
could	O
expect	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
do	O
any	O
Thing	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
without	O
hurting	O
myself	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
save	O
him	O
without	O
hurting	O
myself	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
but	O
say	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
offer	O
to	O
bribe	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
better	O
for	O
me	O
than	O
I	O
expected	O
.	O
-	O
And	O
others	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
afterwards	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
Account	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
An	O
Attorney	O
do	O
this	O
!	O
What	O
was	O
his	O
Name	O
?	O
Watson	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
cramp	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
Name	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
remember	O
it	O
just	O
now	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
Man	O
;	O
he	O
's	O
a	O
tall	O
Man	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Court	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
ago	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
stood	O
in	O
that	O
Place	O
.	O
Officer	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
his	O
Name	O
Wimpry	O
?	O
Watson	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
Name	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Call	O
him	O
into	O
Court	O
.	O
Officer	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wimpry	O
,	O
an	O
Attorney	O
!	O
-	O
He	O
do	O
n't	O
answer	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Go	O
,	O
see	O
if	O
he	O
's	O
in	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Publick	O
Houses	O
hereabout	O
.	O
Then	O
an	O
Officer	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
brought	O
Mr.	O
Wimpry	O
into	O
Court	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Here	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
charg	O
'd	O
with	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
suborn	O
Evidence	O
.	O
This	O
Witness	O
swears	O
you	O
treated	O
him	O
with	O
two	O
Bowls	O
of	O
Punch	O
in	O
New-Prison	O
.	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
better	O
for	O
him	O
than	O
he	O
expected	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
clear	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Richardson	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wimpry	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
such	O
Design	O
,	O
nor	O
ever	O
told	O
him	O
any	O
such	O
Thing	O
.	O
-	O
Indeed	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
Punch	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
publick	O
Company	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
40	O
People	O
present	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
you	O
treat	O
him	O
then	O
?	O
Wimpry	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
only	O
out	O
of	O
Curiosity	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
an	O
Attorney	O
?	O
Wimpry	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
ought	O
to	O
be	O
struck	O
off	O
the	O
Roll	O
for	O
this	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
,	O
before	O
you	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
Court	O
;	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
find	O
Two	O
to	O
be	O
Securities	O
for	O
your	O
Appearance	O
here	O
at	O
next	O
Sessions	O
I	O
'll	O
commit	O
you	O
.	O
Thereupon	O
Mr.	O
Richardson	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Father	O
)	O
and	O
another	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Securities	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
accepted	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
three	O
Prisoners	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Grace	I-pers
,	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Francis	B-pers
Spencely	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Linen	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
July	O
28	O
.	O
F.	O
Spencely	O
.	O
Between	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
Brownlow-street	B-place
in	O
Holbourn	B-place
,	O
I	O
was	O
attack	O
'd	O
by	O
three	O
Persons	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
positive	O
that	O
Grace	O
was	O
among	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
Richardson	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
blue	O
Jacket	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Lord	O
Watson	O
-	O
this	O
little	O
hump-back	O
'd	O
Evidence	O
-	O
run	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
struck	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
Stick	O
.	O
I	O
reel	O
'd	O
against	O
a	O
Stationer	O
's	O
Bulk	O
,	O
but	O
presently	O
recovering	O
my	O
self	O
,	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
my	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
follow	O
'd	O
them	O
up	O
Brownlow-Street	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
Upper-end	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
next	O
Bedford-Row	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
this	O
little	O
Hump-back	O
.	O
Watson	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
Robbery	O
in	O
Lincolns-Inn-Fields	O
,	O
we	O
some	O
how	O
lost	O
John	B-pers
Smithson	I-pers
.	O
And	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
we	O
run	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
Richardson	O
pick	O
'd	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
.	O
We	O
seeing	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
People	O
being	O
not	O
far	O
off	O
,	O
we	O
run	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Grace	O
got	O
clear	O
,	O
but	O
Richardson	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
taken	O
;	O
he	O
by	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Richardson	O
afterwards	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
nail	O
'd	O
the	O
Call	O
of	O
his	O
Wipe	O
,	O
and	O
ding	O
'd	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
afraid	O
,	O
God	O
damn	O
'em	O
!	O
that	O
some	O
of	O
'em	O
had	O
nail	O
'd	O
it	O
again	O
-	O
That	O
is	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Man	O
's	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
drop	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
afraid	O
that	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Watch	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
up	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Watchmen	O
then	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
former	O
Trial	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
place	O
were	O
Richardson	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
he	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
by	O
the	O
Duty-stamp	O
upon	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
46	O
,	O
47.	O
George	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
*	O
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Simonds	I-pers
+	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Philip	B-pers
Turst	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
Field	O
near	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
a	O
Knee-Buckle	O
,	O
a	O
Hat	O
and	O
a	O
Wig	O
,	O
July	O
15	O
.	O
*	O
Sutton	O
was	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
C.	O
Patrick	O
and	O
W.	O
Meads	O
,	O
V.	O
White	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Sept.	O
1732	O
.	O
See	O
Sessions	O
Paper	O
for	O
that	O
Year	O
,	O
Numb	O
.	O
VII	O
p.	O
185	O
,	O
187	O
,	O
188	O
+	O
Simonds	O
was	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Rowly	O
Turner	O
and	O
David	B-pers
Deffy	I-pers
,	O
who	O
were	O
convicted	O
of	O
a	O
Street	O
Robbery	O
in	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
See	O
the	O
Sessions-Paper	O
,	O
Numb	O
.	O
III	O
.	O
p.	O
57	O
.	O
P.	O
Turst	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
Evening	O
,	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
over	O
Marybone-Fields	B-place
,	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
at	O
Paddington	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
stop	O
'd	O
,	O
by	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
Men	O
,	O
who	O
knock	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
of	O
my	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Knee-buckle	O
.	O
They	O
beat	O
and	O
bruis	O
'd	O
me	O
so	O
unmercifully	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
light-headed	O
for	O
a	O
Week	O
afterwards	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
Moon-shiny	O
light	O
Evening	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
disorder	O
'd	O
by	O
their	O
ill	O
Usage	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Some	O
Persons	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
that	O
Field	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
,	O
upon	O
who	O
,	O
I	O
go	O
a	O
Warrant	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
;	O
but	O
none	O
of	O
my	O
Things	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
.	O
Coming	O
out	O
of	O
Marybone-Fields	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Evening	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Sutton	O
and	O
Baker	O
*	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
going	O
in	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
Characters	O
of	O
Sutton	O
and	O
Baker	O
,	O
I	O
concluded	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
upon	O
some	O
Mischief	O
.	O
In	O
three	O
Quarters	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
so	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Turst	O
,	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Brother	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Turst	O
's	O
Wig	O
,	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Field	O
where	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
done	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Turst	O
,	O
If	O
he	O
should	O
know	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Persons	O
who	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
?	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
,	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Suttons	O
(	O
for	O
there	O
's	O
two	O
Brothers	O
of	O
them	O
)	O
if	O
not	O
both	O
.	O
*	O
James	O
Baker	O
,	O
otherwise	O
Stick-in-the-Mud	O
was	O
try	O
'd	O
with	O
Philip	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
in	O
July	O
1732	O
,	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Catherine	B-pers
Burkett	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
.	O
See	O
the	O
Sessions-Paper	O
for	O
that	O
Year	O
,	O
Numb	O
.	O
VI	O
.	O
p.	O
172	O
.	O
Turst	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
heard	O
they	O
frequented	O
those	O
Fields	O
-	O
i	O
do	O
n't	O
deny	O
but	O
I	O
might	O
say	O
so	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
Bruised	O
,	O
that	O
my	O
Senses	O
were	O
almost	O
gone	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
what	O
I	O
said	O
.	O
Berry	O
.	O
In	O
his	O
Affidavit	O
,	O
made	O
before	O
Justice	O
Mercar	O
,	O
he	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
the	O
two	O
Alexanders	O
,	O
Thomas	O
and	O
James	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Stick-in-the-Mud	O
,	O
were	O
the	O
Men	O
who	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
all	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
swore	O
positively	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
Men	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
James	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Alexander	I-pers
were	O
the	O
other	O
three	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
describ	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Clothes	O
before	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
.	O
Turst	O
.	O
The	O
Bruises	O
they	O
gave	O
me	O
,	O
made	O
my	O
Memory	O
so	O
bad	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
if	O
ever	O
I	O
shall	O
have	O
my	O
Senses	O
again	O
.	O
Berry	O
.	O
He	O
could	O
remember	O
them	O
well	O
enough	O
before	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
Sutton	O
's	O
Mother	O
.	O
Justice	O
Mercer	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
first	O
very	O
much	O
out	O
of	O
order	O
,	O
and	O
complained	O
of	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
took	O
his	O
information	O
.	O
H	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
ten	O
a	O
Clock	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Burying	O
ground	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
attack	O
'd	O
by	O
several	O
Person	O
,	O
who	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
abus	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
Sutton	O
and	O
Simonds	O
were	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
Men	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
strongly	O
suspected	O
Baker	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
Alexanders	O
.	O
He	O
describ	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Clothes	O
,	O
that	O
Sutton	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
dark	O
Olive	B-pers
Coat	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Simonds	O
in	O
a	O
black	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
remember	O
'd	O
their	O
Faces	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
taken	O
,	O
they	O
answer	O
'd	O
his	O
Description	O
.	O
Turst	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
my	O
Senses	O
then	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
And	O
yet	O
you	O
could	O
give	O
a	O
right	O
Description	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
-	O
You	O
could	O
remember	O
that	O
one	O
had	O
an	O
Olive	B-pers
Coat	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
a	O
black	O
Waistcoat	O
.	O
Josiah	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
five	O
Persons	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
the	O
two	O
Alexanders	O
and	O
Baker	O
.	O
At	O
first	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
brought	O
in	O
Sutton	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
an	O
Olive	B-pers
Coat	I-pers
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
's	O
the	O
Man	O
who	O
struck	O
me	O
and	O
threw	O
me	O
down	O
.	O
Next	O
I	O
produced	O
Simonds	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
black	O
Waistcoat	O
)	O
and	O
he	O
declared	O
that	O
Simonds	O
was	O
another	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
have	O
a	O
Care	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
very	O
cautions	O
of	O
what	O
he	O
swore	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Mens	O
Lives	O
were	O
at	O
stake	O
.	O
His	O
answer	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Waker	I-pers
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
taken	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Turst	O
describ	O
'd	O
Simonds	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
a	O
black	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
Sutton	O
in	O
an	O
Olive	B-pers
Coat	I-pers
,	O
and	O
they	O
being	O
taken	O
in	O
such	O
Clothes	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
present	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
certain	O
both	O
to	O
Simonds	O
and	O
to	O
Sutton	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
desired	O
to	O
be	O
cautions	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
Mens	O
Lives	O
were	O
at	O
Stake	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
positive	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
afterwards	O
buzz	O
'd	O
in	O
our	O
Neighbourhood	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
about	O
making	O
the	O
Matter	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
his	O
Wife	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Sutton	O
had	O
indeed	O
been	O
with	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
more	O
honour	O
than	O
to	O
take	O
Money	O
to	O
stop	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Woman	O
who	O
keeps	O
the	O
Crow	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
Sutton	O
's	O
Mother	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
together	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
one	O
or	O
the	O
other	O
told	O
you	O
is	O
no	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Is	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
here	O
?	O
Waker	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
here	O
's	O
Mrs.	O
Turst	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Turst	O
,	O
has	O
Sutton	O
's	O
Mother	O
had	O
any	O
Conversation	O
with	O
your	O
Husband	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Turst	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
twice	O
at	O
our	O
House	O
,	O
after	O
my	O
Husband	O
had	O
sworn	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
And	O
did	O
she	O
desire	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
Prosecute	O
,	O
or	O
at	O
least	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
favourable	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Turst	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Law	O
should	O
take	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
her	O
not	O
to	O
trouble	O
him	O
any	O
farther	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
Time	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
intreated	O
for	O
her	O
Son	O
,	O
and	O
protested	O
he	O
was	O
innocent	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Husband	O
told	O
her	O
as	O
before	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Law	O
should	O
take	O
place	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
afterwards	O
at	O
the	O
Crow	O
Alehouse	O
or	O
any	O
where	O
else	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Rolson	I-pers
.	O
Two	O
or	O
three	O
Days	O
before	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Sutton	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
buying	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Pistols	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
Broker	O
's	O
in	O
High-Holbourn	O
.	O
Rovert	O
Draper	O
.	O
The	O
Morning	O
after	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wig	O
and	O
this	O
Pistol	O
in	O
the	O
Field	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Sheldon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Broker	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
in	O
High-Holbourn	O
.	O
About	O
ten	O
Weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
two	O
Men	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Case	O
of	O
Pistols	O
.	O
I	O
shew	O
'd	O
them	O
a	O
pair	O
,	O
they	O
look	O
'd	O
on	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Price	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
10	O
s.	O
or	O
10	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
I	O
forget	O
which	O
,	O
they	O
laid	O
them	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Man	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
dear	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
no	O
less	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
Shilling	O
Earnest	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
fetch	O
them	O
before	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
Night	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
?	O
Sheldon	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
ever	O
saw	O
them	O
before	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
At	O
what	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
Day	O
were	O
those	O
three	O
Men	O
at	O
your	O
Shop	O
?	O
Sheldon	O
.	O
About	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
Day	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Draper	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
sure	O
that	O
Sutton	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
Men	O
you	O
saw	O
looking	O
on	O
the	O
Pistols	O
in	O
Sheldon	O
's	O
Shop	O
?	O
Draper	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
At	O
what	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
Day	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Draper	O
.	O
About	O
one	O
a-Clock	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Shew	O
that	O
Pistol	O
to	O
Sheldon	O
.	O
Sheldon	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
those	O
Pistols	O
I	O
sold	O
to	O
those	O
three	O
Persons	O
that	O
Day	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Simonds	O
.	O
Enquire	O
into	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
Berry	O
,	O
Draper	O
,	O
and	O
Sheldon	O
;	O
they	O
live	O
by	O
nothing	O
but	O
taking	O
Mens	O
Lives	O
away	O
.	O
Berry	O
.	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
Brick-Field	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
other	O
loose	O
Fellows	O
frequently	O
take	O
up	O
their	O
Lodging	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
40	O
of	O
'em	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
come	O
any	O
Day	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
you	O
'll	O
be	O
sure	O
of	O
seeing	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
We	O
do	O
n't	O
desire	O
to	O
meet	O
'em	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
you	O
'll	O
bring	O
'em	O
hither	O
,	O
we	O
shall	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
see	O
'em	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
48.	O
Ann	B-pers
Soames	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	B-pers
Soanes	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Gold-Rings	O
,	O
four	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
four	O
Suits	O
of	O
Head-Clothes	O
,	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
and	O
34	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Cope	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Marter	I-pers
,	O
June	O
27	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Cope	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Marter	O
's	O
(	O
a	O
Linen-Draper	O
)	O
in	O
Audley-street	B-place
,	O
Grosvenor-Square	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
7	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
with	O
a	O
young	O
Lady	O
,	O
whom	O
I	O
nurse	O
for	O
my	O
Lord	O
Albemarle	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
my	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
lock	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Deal-box	O
in	O
my	O
Chamber	O
,	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
my	O
Box	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
4	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
4	O
Suits	O
of	O
Head-Clothes	O
,	O
4	O
pair	O
of	O
Russles	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
and	O
34	O
Guineas	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
taken	O
about	O
4	O
a	O
Clock	O
next	O
Morning	O
at	O
the	O
World's-End	O
,	O
at	O
Newington-Butts	O
.	O
My	O
Rings	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Money	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
deliver	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
confess	O
'd	O
were	O
mine	O
.	O
-	O
Philips	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Square	O
with	O
the	O
Nurse	O
and	O
the	O
young	O
Lady	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
return	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Cope	O
found	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
among	O
the	O
Hackney-Coachmen	O
,	O
and	O
enquir	O
'd	O
if	O
they	O
knew	O
who	O
had	O
carry	O
'd	O
such	O
a	O
Fare	O
.	O
By	O
eleven	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Coachman	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
such	O
a	O
Person	O
in	O
Brook-street	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Vine	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
treated	O
him	O
.	O
Thence	O
he	O
drove	O
her	O
to	O
London-Bridge	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
bought	O
two	O
gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
to	O
the	O
World's-End	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
World's-End	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
her	O
and	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
their	O
Shifts	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
they	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
shut	O
the	O
Sash	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Man	O
and	O
Woman	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
came	O
in	O
their	O
Places	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
What	O
I	O
wanted	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
my	O
Business	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Body	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
but	O
themselves	O
.	O
But	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
getting	O
over	O
the	O
Pails	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
,	O
Nanny	O
?	O
says	O
I	O
.	O
Fellow	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
not	O
.	O
And	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
I	O
perceived	O
she	O
was	O
fumbling	O
with	O
her	O
Fingers	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
Rings	O
off	O
.	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
Watchman	O
,	O
and	O
searching	O
her	O
,	O
found	O
31	O
Guineas	O
,	O
a	O
half	O
Crown	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
whose	O
Money	O
that	O
was	O
?	O
and	O
she	O
