TOKEN	NE
THE	O
TRYALS	O
AND	O
CONDEMNMATION	O
OF	O
Several	O
Persons	O
for	O
Murders	O
,	O
Felonies	O
and	O
Burglaries	O
:	O
Which	O
began	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
July	O
1679	O
,	O
and	O
ended	O
on	O
Fryday	O
the	O
18th	O
.	O
at	O
the	O
Sessions-house	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bayly	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
those	O
that	O
are	O
Condemn	O
'd	O
,	O
Burn	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
Transported	O
and	O
to	O
be	O
whipt	O
.	O
AS	O
ALSO	O
Of	O
the	O
Tryals	O
of	O
Sir	O
George	O
Wakeman	O
,	O
Mr.	O
James	O
Corker	O
,	O
William	O
Rumley	O
and	O
William	O
Marshal	O
:	O
all	O
which	O
were	O
Charged	O
with	O
HIGH	O
TREASON	O
.	O
ELIAS	B-pers
Hutchings	I-pers
,	O
was	O
arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Watch	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
Octob	O
.	O
valued	O
at	O
4	O
l.	O
10.	O
s.	O
From	O
Mr.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Broxton	I-pers
.	O
And	O
for	O
another	O
6.l	O
.	O
from	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Fenton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
one	O
lost	O
at	O
Church	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
positive	O
proof	O
of	O
their	O
being	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
pretended	O
he	O
bought	O
one	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
which	O
was	O
hanged	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
of	O
one	O
that	O
was	O
a	O
stranger	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
whose	O
name	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
:	O
But	O
by	O
reason	O
he	O
could	O
make	O
no	O
proof	O
thereof	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
his	O
apprehending	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
18	O
.	O
Watches	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
Katherine	B-pers
Tumince	I-pers
,	O
for	O
murdering	O
her	O
Bastard	O
Male	O
Child	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
hid	O
under	O
rubbish	O
in	O
a	O
Garret	O
:	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
were	O
examined	O
:	O
She	O
made	O
little	O
defence	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
murther	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Two	O
little	O
Boy	O
es	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fairchild	I-pers
and	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Langhorn	I-pers
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
Mr.	O
Henry	B-pers
Prowns	I-pers
Chamber	O
of	O
Barnards-Inn	B-place
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
two	O
Rings	O
and	O
some	O
Money	O
:	O
Langhorn	O
was	O
cleared	O
by	O
reason	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
present	O
with	O
Fairchild	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Rings	O
and	O
mony	O
;	O
only	O
happened	O
to	O
meet	O
him	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
helped	O
him	O
to	O
spend	O
it	O
:	O
Fairchild	O
confest	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Key	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
the	O
Rings	O
and	O
Mony	O
there	O
being	O
but	O
little	O
evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
onely	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Hews	I-pers
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Horse	O
of	O
8l	O
.	O
value	O
,	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Timothy	B-pers
Penniston	I-pers
,	O
for	O
setting	O
New	B-place
prison	I-place
on	O
Fire	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
very	O
great	O
suspitions	O
of	O
the	O
the	O
truth	O
thereof	O
;	O
one	O
swore	O
positively	O
,	O
that	O
Peniston	O
offered	O
him	O
50.s	O
.	O
to	O
set	O
the	O
prison	O
on	O
fire	O
before	O
7	O
a	O
Clock	O
next	O
morning	O
;	O
and	O
another	O
testified	O
he	O
offered	O
him	O
10.l	O
.	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
him	O
such	O
an	O
Engine	O
for	O
making	O
Granadoes	O
as	O
he	O
should	O
direct	O
.	O
However	O
he	O
brought	O
several	O
sufficient	O
Witnesses	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
at	O
St.	O
Albans	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
cleared	O
.	O
Allen	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
for	O
driving	O
a	O
Cart	O
over	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Niccols	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Child	O
in	O
Newgate	B-place
street	I-place
,	O
on	O
July	O
the	O
5th	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Death	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
reason	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
witnesses	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
casually	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
cleared	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wilmot	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Davenport	I-pers
,	O
for	O
Coining	O
new	O
mill	O
'd	O
half	O
Crowns	O
,	O
positive	O
proof	O
was	O
made	O
hereof	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
Landlord	O
and	O
Landlady	O
positively	O
swearing	O
they	O
saw	O
them	O
Coin	O
several	O
half	O
Crowns	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
several	O
swore	O
they	O
had	O
made	O
several	O
stamps	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
pretended	O
was	O
for	O
the	O
dyals	O
of	O
Watches	O
;	O
they	O
made	O
little	O
defence	O
,	O
save	O
only	O
their	O
Landlord	O
had	O
formerly	O
been	O
crack-brained	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
ought	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
Evidence	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
declare	O
it	O
sooner	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Court	O
found	O
that	O
no	O
reason	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
Objected	O
against	O
their	O
evidence	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
of	O
High	O
Treason	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Frances	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Tankard	O
of	O
value	O
5.	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Cup	O
of	O
5.	O
s.	O
value	O
,	O
from	O
Edward	B-pers
Gibbs	I-pers
,	O
was	O
cleared	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lambert	I-pers
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Tankard	O
in	O
Cornhil	B-place
,	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Tankard	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Traby	I-pers
worth	O
4	O
l.	O
10.	O
s.	O
which	O
he	O
sold	O
for	O
40.s	O
.	O
and	O
positive	O
proof	O
made	O
thereof	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
for	O
steeling	O
a	O
Tankard	O
,	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Susanna	B-pers
Car	I-pers
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Peticoat	O
of	O
6.	O
d.	O
value	O
and	O
5.l	O
.	O
from	O
Susanna	B-pers
Silby	I-pers
,	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4.d	O
.	O
Capt	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Winchworth	I-pers
,	O
and	O
his	O
Brother	B-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
June	O
coming	O
from	O
Chiswick	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
near	O
the	B-place
Lord	I-place
of	I-place
Holland	I-place
's	I-place
walk	I-place
,	O
was	O
set	O
upon	O
by	O
5	O
Highway-men	O
,	O
who	O
,	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
stopt	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
secured	O
the	O
Coachman	O
,	O
who	O
did	O
not	O
assist	O
,	O
they	O
presented	O
a	O
Pistol	O
at	O
the	O
Captain	O
which	O
he	O
put	O
by	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
smart	O
Encounter	O
for	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Highway-men	O
were	O
wounded	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
taken	O
,	O
the	O
rest	O
run	O
away	O
:	O
The	O
Capt	O
.	O
and	O
his	O
Brother	O
had	O
no	O
hurt	O
,	O
except	O
the	O
loss	O
of	O
a	O
white	O
Beaver	O
,	O
valued	O
at	O
3	O
l.	O
for	O
which	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
this	O
day	O
arraigned	O
;	O
viz	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Tasker	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Gowin	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Buttler	I-pers
;	O
there	O
were	O
many	O
Circumstances	O
to	O
believe	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
guilty	O
,	O
positive	O
proof	O
was	O
made	O
of	O
Gowing	O
's	O
being	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
presented	O
the	O
Pistol	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
silly	O
pretences	O
to	O
perswade	O
the	O
Court	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
Fellony	O
and	O
Robbery	O
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
set	O
by	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Needham	I-pers
arraigned	O
for	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Hine	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
,	O
did	O
there	O
desire	O
Mr.	O
Nich	O
Purisoy	O
to	O
help	O
her	O
to	O
a	O
New-England	O
Shilling	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
taking	O
out	O
a	O
Box	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
she	O
immediately	O
popt	O
her	O
hand	O
therein	O
and	O
pointing	O
with	O
her	O
Fore-Finger	O
,	O
cryed	O
,	O
here	O
's	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
's	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
out	O
her	O
hand	O
(	O
one	O
that	O
stood	O
by	O
perceived	O
)	O
she	O
had	O
conveighed	O
a	O
Guinny	O
from	O
thence	O
in	O
the	O
Palm	O
of	O
her	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
popt	O
her	O
hand	O
into	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
taxed	O
,	O
she	O
made	O
many	O
strange	O
Protestations	O
that	O
she	O
touched	O
none	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
searcht	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
her	O
;	O
all	O
which	O
was	O
positively	O
proved	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
she	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
deny	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
make	O
no	O
defence	O
or	O
bring	O
any	O
proof	O
of	O
her	O
honesty	O
,	O
so	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
were	O
arraigned	O
for	O
robbing	O
Henry	B-pers
Jevern	I-pers
,	O
Esquire	O
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
July	O
of	O
a	O
Beaver-Hat	O
,	O
and	O
Hat	O
band	O
,	O
they	O
both	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
stabbing	O
his	O
Child	B-pers
in	O
the	O
small	O
of	O
the	O
back	O
with	O
a	O
knife	O
,	O
several	O
of	O
his	O
Neighbours	O
gave	O
evidence	O
of	O
his	O
honesty	O
,	O
he	O
pleaded	O
that	O
he	O
threw	O
the	O
Knife	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
throw	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Cubbards	O
head	O
,	O
but	O
throwing	O
short	O
,	O
hit	O
the	O
Child	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
proof	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
was	O
cleared	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
French	I-pers
,	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Mr.	B-pers
Child	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mr	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
the	O
5th	O
.	O
and	O
the	O
13th	O
.	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
of	O
several	O
quantities	O
of	O
Cloaths	O
and	O
Linnen	O
,	O
and	O
7l	O
.	O
in	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
refused	O
to	O
plead	O
though	O
the	O
Court	O
several	O
times	O
intreated	O
him	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
obstinately	O
refused	O
;	O
whereupon	O
sentence	O
was	O
pronounced	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
Prest	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
presently	O
put	O
in	O
Execution	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
into	O
the	O
Court	O
almost	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
helpt	O
up	O
by	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
he	O
at	O
last	O
pleaded	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
was	O
against	O
him	O
found	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
proved	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
pawned	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
rest	O
;	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
much	O
against	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
could	O
bring	O
no	O
proof	O
of	O
his	O
honesty	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
4	O
little	O
boy	O
es	O
each	O
about	O
8	O
years	O
old	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wats	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
were	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
48	O
bottles	O
of	O
Ale	O
,	O
from	O
Francis	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
in	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
the	O
4th	O
of	O
July	O
.	O
Which	O
they	O
confessed	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
immediately	O
by	O
the	O
common	O
Hangman	O
whipt	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
Ruth	B-pers
Webber	I-pers
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Tankard	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
in	O
Nicolas-lane	B-place
;	O
She	O
was	O
last	O
Sessions	O
transported	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
positive	O
proof	O
of	O
her	O
confessing	O
when	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
having	O
but	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Clerk	I-pers
,	O
for	O
indeavouring	O
to	O
burn	O
M.	B-pers
Selby	I-pers
s	O
house	O
his	O
Mistriss	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	B-place
the	O
15th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
'T	O
was	O
positively	O
proved	O
he	O
set	O
Flax	O
on	O
fire	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
burn	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
reason	O
it	O
took	O
uo	O
effect	O
he	O
was	O
only	O
fined	O
100l	O
.	O
and	O
judged	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
next	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
,	O
on	O
Thursday	O
at	O
the	O
Exchange	O
,	O
Saturday	O
,	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Paper	O
on	O
his	O
Forehead	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
fault	O
writ	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Fryday	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
July	O
1679	O
;	O
Upon	O
Fryday	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
July	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
General	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
were	O
tryed	O
Sir	O
George	B-pers
Wakeman	I-pers
,	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Marshal	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	B-pers
Rumley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Corker	B-pers
,	O
the	O
first	O
named	O
being	O
Physician	O
to	O
her	O
Majesty	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
three	O
supposed	O
to	O
be	O
Romish	O
Priest	O
s	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
be	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
late	O
Plot	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
arraigned	O
:	O
The	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
matters	O
charged	O
against	O
these	O
persons	O
,	O
especially	O
Sir	O
George	O
Wakeman	O
,	O
had	O
raised	O
so	O
vast	O
and	O
general	O
an	O
expectation	O
as	O
drew	O
an	O
infinite	O
number	O
of	O
people	O
to	O
hear	O
their	O
Tryals	O
;	O
where	O
were	O
,	O
besides	O
the	O
Magistracy	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
,	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
Judges	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
learned	O
Counsel	O
,	O
who	O
managed	O
the	O
Evidence	O
:	O
Their	O
Tryals	O
begun	O
about	O
eight	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
lasted	O
till	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
which	O
time	O
was	O
protracted	O
the	O
longer	O
by	O
that	O
special	O
Grace	O
and	O
Favour	O
the	O
Court	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
in	O
giving	O
them	O
leave	O
to	O
make	O
their	O
full	O
defence	O
with	O
all	O
the	O
Freedom	O
they	O
could	O
desire	O
,	O
in	O
speaking	O
for	O
themselves	O
,	O
which	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
did	O
in	O
set	O
Speeches	O
very	O
largely	O
,	O
and	O
producing	O
their	O
Witnesses	O
.	O
The	O
Indictments	O
against	O
them	O
were	O
large	O
,	O
as	O
is	O
usual	O
in	O
such	O
Cases	O
of	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
the	O
effect	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
together	O
had	O
conspired	O
to	O
destroy	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
to	O
subvert	O
the	O
Government	O
,	O
to	O
raise	O
an	O
Army	O
,	O
to	O
bring	O
in	O
Popery	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Particulars	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
Evidence	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
that	O
was	O
tryed	O
was	O
Sir	O
George	O
Wakeman	O
;	O
they	O
all	O
pleaded	O
not	O
guilty	O
to	O
their	O
Iudictments	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
issue	O
the	O
Jury	O
being	O
sworn	O
,	O
the	O
Indictments	O
were	O
read	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
matters	O
therein	O
charged	O
,	O
opened	O
by	O
the	O
Kings	O
's	O
Counsel	O
.	O
The	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
Dr.	O
Oates	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Bedloe	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Dugdale	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Prance	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Tenison	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
first	O
examined	O
about	O
what	O
they	O
knew	O
of	O
the	O
Plot	O
in	O
general	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
they	O
gave	O
account	O
according	O
to	O
what	O
they	O
deposed	O
against	O
Mr.	O
Langhorn	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
already	O
published	O
;	O
the	O
main	O
charge	O
against	O
Sir	O
G.	O
Wakeman	O
,	O
was	O
for	O
being	O
hired	O
for	O
15000	O
l.	O
whereof	O
5000	O
paid	O
,	O
to	O
poyson	O
the	O
King	O
.	O
The	O
Witness	O
declared	O
no	O
great	O
acquaintance	O
with	O
Sir	O
George	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
an	O
entry	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Books	O
belonging	O
to	O
their	O
Provincials	O
,	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
Proposal	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
receipt	O
of	O
so	O
much	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
certain	O
proof	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
as	O
also	O
a	O
Letter	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
written	O
to	O
one	O
Ashby	O
,	O
wherein	O
after	O
some	O
directions	O
given	O
him	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
his	O
health	O
,	O
advice	O
was	O
therein	O
given	O
of	O
the	O
present	O
design	O
.	O
But	O
After	O
several	O
strict	O
Examinations	O
of	O
the	O
several	O
matters	O
charged	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
in	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
others	O
tryed	O
for	O
small	O
Thefts	O
,	O
but	O
cleared	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
others	O
tryed	O
for	O
small	O
Thefts	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
here	O
omit	O
.	O
In	O
all	O
there	O
were	O
9	O
Condemned	O
to	O
dye	O
,	O
7	O
Men	O
and	O
2	O
Women	O
,	O
2	O
for	O
Coining	O
,	O
one	O
for	O
Murther	O
,	O
4	O
for	O
Robbing	O
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
one	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Horse	O
and	O
one	O
for	O
Stealing	O
several	O
Watches	O
,	O
9	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
hand	O
,	O
4	O
to	O
be	O
transported	O
,	O
6	O
Whipt	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Sessions	O
was	O
Adjourned	O
till	O
Fryday	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
day	O
were	O
Tryed	O
the	O
Persons	O
hereafter	O
mentioned	O
.	O
