TOKEN	NE
THE	O
TRUE	O
NARRATIVE	O
OF	O
THE	O
PROCEDINGS	O
AT	O
The	O
Sessions-House	O
IN	O
THE	O
OLD-BAILY	O
Which	O
began	O
on	O
Thursday	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
this	O
February	O
last	O
past	O
,	O
and	O
Ended	O
on	O
Monday	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
March	O
following	O
1679	O
Giving	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
Remarkable	O
Trials	O
there	O
,	O
viz	O
for	O
Murder	O
,	O
Fellonies	O
and	O
Burglaries	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
with	O
a	O
particular	O
Relation	O
of	O
their	O
Names	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
places	O
of	O
their	O
Committing	O
their	O
Facts	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
those	O
Condemned	O
to	O
dye	O
,	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
hand	O
,	O
Transported	O
and	O
to	O
be	O
whipt	O
.	O
And	O
also	O
of	O
the	O
Trial	O
and	O
Condemnation	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
seven	O
which	O
broke	O
out	O
of	O
Prison	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
the	O
22th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Baker	O
alias	O
Hoskins	O
a	O
Jesuite	O
,	O
which	O
offered	O
monies	O
to	O
a	O
Servant	O
Maid	O
to	O
set	O
her	O
Masters	O
houses	O
on	O
fire	O
,	O
in	O
two	O
several	O
places	O
where	O
she	O
lived	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
remarkable	O
Trials	O
The	O
first	O
that	O
was	O
Indicted	O
and	O
Arraigned	O
was	O
on	O
Sarah	B-pers
Good	I-pers
,	O
for	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
Company	O
,	O
of	O
two	O
more	O
,	O
both	O
Men	O
,	O
coming	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
often	O
before	O
done	O
,	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Sammuel	B-pers
Dod	I-pers
a	O
Vintner	O
living	O
in	O
Saint	B-place
Botolphs	I-place
without	I-place
Bishops-Gate	I-place
,	O
and	O
there	O
calling	O
for	O
several	O
sorts	O
of	O
Liquors	O
,	O
had	O
brought	O
them	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
one	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
Bole	O
,	O
two	O
silver	O
standing	O
Cups	O
the	O
which	O
they	O
watching	O
their	O
opportunity	O
,	O
conveyed	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
to	O
several	O
Goldsmiths	O
in	O
London	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
plain	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
unquestionably	O
had	O
the	O
Plate	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
charged	O
positively	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
likewise	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Dram	O
Cup	O
,	O
from	O
Roger	B-pers
Reading	I-pers
of	O
the	O
same	O
Parish	O
,	O
the	O
which	O
she	O
confessed	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
that	O
Fellony	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
former	O
.	O
William	B-pers
West	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
and	O
Arraigned	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
by	O
force	O
and	O
Arms	O
,	O
did	O
Felloniously	O
take	O
and	O
bear	O
away	O
thirteen	O
Yards	O
of	O
Chamblet	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Chattels	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Adkins	I-pers
,	O
taking	O
it	O
off	O
from	O
the	O
Stall	O
Grate	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
running	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
long	O
after	O
,	O
was	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Confederates	O
betrayed	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
confess	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
sold	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
for	O
his	O
part	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
of	O
his	O
Gang	O
had	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
Case	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
an	O
old	O
Offendor	O
,	O
once	O
burnt	O
in	O
the	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
out	O
of	O
Newgate	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
but	O
one	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
in	O
the	O
Company	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
her	O
Confederate	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
one	O
Henry	B-pers
Beacon	I-pers
in	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Eastcheap	I-place
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Campaign	O
Coat	O
,	O
did	O
Felloniously	O
take	O
and	O
bare	O
away	O
,	O
a	O
large	O
Coat	O
,	O
vallued	O
at	O
thirty-five	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Circumstance	O
sworn	O
to	O
were	O
thus	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
bidding	O
money	O
for	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
privately	O
conveyed	O
the	O
Coat	O
away	O
for	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Indicted	O
,	O
the	O
Apprentice	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
understanding	O
that	O
his	O
Master	O
could	O
take	O
the	O
money	O
they	O
had	O
hidden	O
,	O
followed	O
them	O
to	O
call	O
them	O
back	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
on	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
thought	O
they	O
were	O
pursued	O
,	O
the	O
now	O
Prisoner	O
slipped	O
into	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
and	O
the	O
Man	O
went	O
back	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Mr.	O
Beacon	O
no	O
sooner	O
,	O
looking	O
over	O
his	O
Coats	O
,	O
but	O
missed	O
one	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
by	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Coat	O
dropped	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
Room	O
or	O
Box	O
,	O
where	O
this	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
;	O
the	O
which	O
no	O
sooner	O
being	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
charged	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
offered	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
in	O
Composition	O
adding	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
she	O
were	O
Committed	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
woman	O
,	O
the	O
meaning	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
because	O
she	O
had	O
lately	O
received	O
her	O
Pardon	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
that	O
Mercy	O
for	O
a	O
warning	O
,	O
upon	O
this	O
Evidence	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Fellony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susanna	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
taking	O
away	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
from	O
one	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Ballard	I-pers
a	O
Sempstress	O
,	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
fourteen	O
pounds	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
one	O
large	O
Scarf	O
,	O
three	O
laced	O
Cravats	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Linnens	O
;	O
the	O
which	O
she	O
pawned	O
for	O
an	O
inconsiderable	O
value	O
the	O
which	O
upon	O
her	O
being	O
taxed	O
withal	O
she	O
confessed	O
,	O
as	O
likewise	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
adjudged	O
to	O
be	O
above	O
twelve	O
years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
yet	O
had	O
followed	O
that	O
Trade	O
of	O
Thieving	O
a	O
considerable	O
time	O
upon	O
the	O
Confession	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Fellony	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
Martha	B-pers
Hair	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hicks	I-pers
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
28	O
Yards	O
of	O
flowered	O
Silk	O
,	O
vallued	O
at	O
fourteen	O
pounds	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
Edward	B-pers
Rigby	I-pers
,	O
the	O
former	O
viz	O
.	O
Edwards	O
alledged	O
she	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
Hair	O
,	O
and	O
Hair	O
affirmed	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
Hicks	O
,	O
who	O
likewise	O
confirmed	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
but	O
having	O
a	O
Pardon	O
for	O
Transportation	O
since	O
the	O
Fellony	O
committed	O
although	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
yet	O
remained	O
upon	O
the	O
former	O
Sentence	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
transported	O
between	O
this	O
and	O
Easter	O
next	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
felloniously	O
bearing	O
away	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
four	O
Shifts	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
pieces	O
of	O
Linnen	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Chattels	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hammond	I-pers
of	O
Cheswick	B-place
,	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
confessed	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
who	O
attested	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
ten	O
pence	O
.	O
Frances	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
one	O
Benson	B-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Fellony	O
and	O
Robbery	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
setting	O
upon	O
the	O
Coach	O
of	O
Justice	B-pers
Northy	I-pers
,	O
a	O
little	O
beyond	O
Bow	B-place
,	O
wherein	O
was	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
Son	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Gentlewoman	O
;	O
and	O
did	O
use	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
most	O
barbarous	O
manner	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
having	O
forced	O
them	O
to	O
submit	O
to	O
save	O
their	O
Lives	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Mr	O
Northe	O
the	O
younger	O
,	O
one	O
Necklace	O
of	O
Pearl	O
,	O
vallued	O
at	O
one	O
hundred	O
and	O
od	O
pounds	O
as	O
likewise	O
4	O
shillings	O
or	O
thereabouts	O
in	O
monies	O
,	O
his	O
Cravat	O
,	O
and	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
his	O
Mother	O
,	O
her	O
Scarf	O
,	O
and	O
Rings	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
vallue	O
,	O
but	O
whilst	O
they	O
were	O
ransacking	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
a	O
Servant	O
of	O
the	O
Juststices	O
being	O
sent	O
to	O
meet	O
it	O
,	O
found	O
it	O
standing	O
in	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
Men	O
upon	O
their	O
Guard	O
,	O
came	O
up	O
close	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
the	O
matter	O
was	O
,	O
whereupon	O
they	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
incompass	O
him	O
the	O
which	O
he	O
being	O
Aware	O
of	O
,	O
bid	O
them	O
stand	O
off	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
pressing	O
on	O
,	O
he	O
with	O
his	O
stick	O
knocked	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
himself	O
knocked	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
disabled	O
by	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
on	O
Foot	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
seven	O
in	O
number	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
very	O
dark	O
their	O
Phisiogmonies	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
so	O
well	O
discovered	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
charge	O
them	O
positively	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
Anderson	O
and	O
Benson	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
sworn	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Necklace	O
of	O
Pearl	O
,	O
Scarf	O
and	O
Rings	O
being	O
offered	O
to	O
pawn	O
and	O
fall	O
,	O
by	O
Phillips	O
and	O
Harris	O
,	O
as	O
likewise	O
Phillips	O
being	O
flatly	O
charged	O
to	O
bethere	O
by	O
the	O
party	O
that	O
was	O
knocked	O
down	O
,	O
they	O
two	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Banister	I-pers
was	O
brought	O
to	O
his	O
Trial	O
,	O
for	O
Burglary	O
and	O
Fellony	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
in	O
the	O
Absence	O
of	O
one	O
Abigal	B-pers
Jenison	I-pers
break	O
into	O
her	O
Lodging	O
Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
felloniously	O
bear	O
away	O
one	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
twelve	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
two	O
Silver	O
Potringers	O
,	O
one	O
Silver	O
Salt	O
,	O
six	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Inkhorne	O
;	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Plate	O
being	O
no	O
sooner	O
missed	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
suspected	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
warrant	O
being	O
granted	O
to	O
search	O
his	O
Lodging	O
,	O
the	O
Salt	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
strict	O
Examination	O
did	O
confess	O
where	O
he	O
sould	O
and	O
disposed	O
of	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
Court	O
he	O
denied	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
delivered	O
to	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
womans	O
Son	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
the	O
Gentlewoman	O
Lodged	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
appear	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
found	O
in	O
several	O
stories	O
,	O
the	O
Verdict	O
passed	O
against	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
Fellony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
James	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
right	O
worshipful	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
Knight	O
,	O
and	O
Alderman	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
scituate	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Christ	B-place
church	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Ward	I-place
of	I-place
Farrington	I-place
within	I-place
,	O
and	O
conveying	O
thence	O
in	O
moneys	O
six	O
hundred	O
seventy	O
five	O
pounds	O
,	O
after	O
his	O
being	O
committed	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
moneys	O
himself	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
by	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
certain	O
false	O
Keys	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
delivered	O
the	O
greatest	O
part	O
thereof	O
to	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
;	O
and	O
did	O
likewise	O
discover	O
where	O
three	O
hundred	O
and	O
od	O
pounds	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
money	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
for	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
It	O
was	O
conveyed	O
away	O
by	O
a	O
third	O
person	O
;	O
but	O
in	O
Court	O
he	O
denied	O
the	O
taking	O
it	O
away	O
for	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
seeing	O
a	O
positive	O
Proof	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
own	O
Confession	O
in	O
Newgate	O
sworn	O
to	O
,	O
he	O
again	O
confessed	O
the	O
Robbery	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
parties	O
that	O
were	O
his	O
Confederates	O
,	O
had	O
gotten	O
false	O
Keys	O
,	O
not	O
only	O
to	O
the	O
outward	O
Dore	O
but	O
also	O
to	O
the	O
Closet	O
where	O
the	O
money	O
lay	O
,	O
by	O
means	O
or	O
an	O
Impression	O
he	O
had	O
gotten	O
of	O
the	O
true	O
Keys	O
in	O
Clay	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
his	O
Confederates	O
came	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
he	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
Stairs	O
with	O
a	O
Candle	O
to	O
hearken	O
if	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Family	O
were	O
stirring	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
efected	O
about	O
five	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
himself	O
being	O
Footman	O
to	O
Sir	O
William	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
plain	O
and	O
positive	O
proof	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Fellony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Tobias	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Killing	O
Mr.	B-pers
Simonds	I-pers
in	O
Gardeners	B-place
Lane	I-place
in	I-place
King-street	I-place
Westminster	I-place
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
proved	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Brother	O
had	O
watched	O
for	O
the	O
Party	O
diceased	O
,	O
not	O
only	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
watch	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
the	O
said	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
peep	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
he	O
Lodged	O
,	O
who	O
no	O
sooner	O
coming	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
cried	O
Oh	O
!	O
and	O
thereupon	O
drew	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
likewise	O
did	O
the	O
deceased	O
and	O
making	O
several	O
Passes	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Brother	O
stood	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
drawn	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
them	O
be	O
parted	O
till	O
Simonds	O
being	O
run	O
in	O
four	O
Inches	O
deep	O
,	O
staggering	O
a	O
while	O
,	O
fell	O
down	O
and	O
died	O
upon	O
the	O
spot	O
.	O
This	O
Murther	O
was	O
thought	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
in	O
the	O
revenging	O
an	O
affront	O
put	O
upon	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Talbot	I-pers
a	O
common	O
Strumpet	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
likewise	O
Indicted	O
as	O
accessary	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
had	O
taken	O
away	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
unrig	O
'd	O
her	O
at	O
a	O
certain	O
Tavern	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
heard	O
to	O
swear	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
his	O
Throat	O
cut	O
in	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
days	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
walked	O
London	O
Streets	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
if	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
that	O
should	O
do	O
it	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
Upon	O
all	O
these	O
circumstances	O
Butler	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
wilful	O
Murther	O
;	O
but	O
by	O
reason	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
proved	O
against	O
the	O
said	O
Talbot	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
incence	O
or	O
hire	O
the	O
said	O
Butler	O
to	O
do	O
the	O
Cruel	O
exploit	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Gale	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Fellony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
Frances	B-pers
Peck	I-pers
a	O
Hosier	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Magnes	I-place
,	O
and	O
conveying	O
thence	O
Stockens	O
to	O
the	O
vallue	O
of	O
fourty	O
pounds	O
,	O
about	O
thirty	O
pair	O
of	O
them	O
being	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
buthe	O
being	O
a	O
Brother	O
by	O
Profession	O
,	O
his	O
Neighbours	O
giving	O
Testimony	O
for	O
his	O
Truth	O
,	O
and	O
child	O
behaviour	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
and	O
his	O
wife	B-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Pepper	I-pers
and	O
his	O
Wife	B-pers
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Clipping	O
,	O
and	O
diminishing	O
the	O
Currant	O
and	O
lawful	O
Coin	O
of	O
England	O
which	O
the	O
Law	O
makes	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
the	O
circumstance	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
thus	O
,	O
Clarks	O
Wife	O
often	O
coming	O
to	O
one	O
Coniers	O
a	O
Grocers	O
,	O
was	O
wont	O
to	O
bring	O
several	O
pieces	O
of	O
Clipped	O
moneys	O
,	O
and	O
change	O
them	O
,	O
for	O
buing	O
two	O
penniworth	O
of	O
Wares	O
at	O
the	O
most	O
,	O
which	O
raised	O
a	O
suspicion	O
in	O
the	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
acquainted	O
his	O
Master	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
who	O
getting	O
a	O
Warrant	O
,	O
searched	O
Clark	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
found	O
several	O
rubbing	O
Stones	O
,	O
Files	O
and	O
Crucibles	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
his	O
Wives	O
purse	O
some	O
clipped	O
moneys	O
,	O
and	O
Clippings	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
proceeding	O
to	O
search	O
Peppers	O
house	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
a	O
pot	O
,	O
full	O
of	O
Souse	O
,	O
a	O
Bag	O
of	O
money	O
containing	O
about	O
eleven	O
pounds	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
pounds	O
was	O
Clipped	O
money	O
,	O
as	O
likewise	O
several	O
pieces	O
in	O
the	O
Sale-Box	O
,	O
all	O
which	O
in	O
Court	O
he	O
utterly	O
disowned	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
positive	O
proof	O
against	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
their	O
Clipping	O
,	O
only	O
giving	O
presumptions	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Randal	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
who	O
in	O
the	O
Company	O
of	O
six	O
more	O
,	O
broke	O
the	O
Goale	O
of	O
Newgate	B-place
on	O
the	O
22th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
being	O
retaken	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
and	O
brought	O
upon	O
his	O
Trial	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Keepers	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
locked	O
him	O
up	O
with	O
the	O
rest	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
Masters	O
chamber	O
on	O
the	O
common	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
left	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
safely	O
Fettered	O
,	O
but	O
having	O
two	O
Saw-knives	O
,	O
two	O
Plough	O
coulters	O
,	O
conveighed	O
to	O
them	O
by	O
their	O
Confederates	O
they	O
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
21th	O
of	O
February	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
began	O
to	O
force	O
the	O
stones	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
exceeding	O
large	O
and	O
cramped	O
with	O
several	O
ponderous	O
Dogs	O
of	O
Iron	O
yet	O
were	O
so	O
dexterous	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
saw	O
off	O
all	O
their	O
Irons	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
large	O
breach	O
in	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
and	O
sliding	O
down	O
by	O
a	O
Rope	O
,	O
made	O
their	O
escapes	O
,	O
leaving	O
two	O
bound	O
behind	O
them	O
,	O
who	O
refused	O
to	O
comply	O
with	O
that	O
Fellony	O
,	O
the	O
Knives	O
,	O
Fetters	O
and	O
Coulters	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Escape	O
so	O
undeniable	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Fellony	O
,	O
his	O
former	O
commitment	O
was	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Chamber	O
of	O
Mark	B-pers
Trent	I-pers
Esq	O
.	O
of	O
New-Inn	B-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
Compny	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
three	O
hundred	O
pounds	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
Executed	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
last	O
Sessions	O
of	O
which	O
indictment	O
he	O
was	O
also	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Hoskins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Nailor	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Carpenter	I-pers
,	O
were	O
severally	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Popish	O
Priests	O
or	O
Jesuits	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
that	O
took	O
his	O
Trial	O
was	O
Baker	O
,	O
alias	O
Hoskins	O
,	O
against	O
whom	O
Doctor	O
Oats	O
gave	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
Mass	O
,	O
and	O
consecrate	O
the	O
Host	O
at	O
several	O
places	O
in	O
his	O
Priestly	O
Vestments	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
that	O
gave	O
Evidence	O
,	O
was	O
one	O
Mary	O
Dove	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
positively	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
Confess	O
,	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
Mass	O
,	O
Christen	O
and	O
the	O
like	O
;	O
at	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Statertons	O
in	O
Duke-street	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
lived	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
since	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
removed	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Edwards	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
offered	O
her	O
moneys	O
,	O
to	O
set	O
her	O
Masters	O
house	O
on	O
Fire	O
,	O
forcing	O
it	O
into	O
her	O
Lap	O
,	O
as	O
likewise	O
he	O
repeated	O
the	O
same	O
offer	O
to	O
her	O
when	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
that	O
Service	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
come	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
Esquire	O
Bradshaw	O
,	O
in	O
Crane-Court	O
in	O
Fleet	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
in	O
several	O
Habits	O
;	O
especially	O
with	O
Cords	O
about	O
him	O
like	O
a	O
Porter	O
,	O
upon	O
this	O
Evidence	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
,	O
Nailer	O
,	O
alias	O
carpenter	O
,	O
wholly	O
submitted	O
to	O
the	O
favour	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
because	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
possitive	O
proof	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
a	O
Priest	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Timothy	B-pers
Crady	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Grady	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Holder	I-pers
and	O
his	O
Wife	B-pers
upon	O
the	O
Kings	O
Highway	O
between	O
nine	O
or	O
ten	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
them	O
monies	O
rings	O
and	O
a	O
Compaign	O
Coat	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
vallue	O
,	O
between	O
Southtown	B-place
and	O
Hays	B-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
Oxbridg	I-place
,	O
But	O
about	O
two	O
days	O
after	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
apprehended	O
in	O
St.	O
Gileses	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
;	O
the	O
Campaign	O
then	O
being	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
Timothy	B-pers
Greedy	I-pers
,	O
who	O
in	O
Court	O
confessed	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
excusing	O
the	O
others	O
as	O
not	O
accessary	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
some	O
what	O
positive	O
against	O
Edward	B-pers
Greedy	I-pers
,	O
he	O
with	O
his	O
Brother	O
Timothy	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Fellony	O
and	O
Robbery	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
proof	O
being	O
weak	O
against	O
Richardson	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Frances	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felloniously	O
taking	O
,	O
and	O
bearing	O
away	O
a	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
vallued	O
at	O
five	O
pounds	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
fellony	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
in	O
all	O
twenty-five	O
persons	O
condemned	O
to	O
die	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
eighteen	O
Men	O
and	O
seven	O
women	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
William	O
Woodward	O
,	O
William	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
Evans	O
Wood	O
,	O
George	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Braford	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
Tobian	O
Butler	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
alias	O
Heskins	O
,	O
Timwothy	O
Grady	O
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Grady	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Earnly	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Hoskins	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Banister	I-pers
,	O
Randal	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
Frances	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
Susan	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hicks	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Good	I-pers
,	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Green	I-pers
.	O
There	O
were	O
four	O
burn	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
hand	O
,	O
five	O
to	O
be	O
whipt	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
