TOKEN	NE
THE	O
ACCCOUNT	O
Of	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
Remarkable	O
TRYALS	O
That	O
were	O
Tryed	O
at	O
the	O
Sessions-house	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
At	O
the	O
Sessions	O
holden	O
there	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
Country	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
begun	O
on	O
Friday	O
the	O
Tenth	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
September	O
,	O
and	O
ending	O
on	O
Munday	O
the	O
Thirteenth	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
:	O
with	O
a	O
particular	O
Relation	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
committed	O
on	O
the	O
Bridge	O
.	O
AND	O
THE	O
Tryal	O
and	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Cellier	I-pers
the	O
Popish	O
Midwife	O
:	O
With	O
the	O
Number	O
of	O
those	O
Condemned	O
to	O
Die	O
,	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
Whipt	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
.	O
FIrst	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
,	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
were	O
Arraigned	O
and	O
brought	O
upon	O
their	O
Tryals	O
,	O
for	O
Breaking	O
and	O
Robbing	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Richard	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Mercer	O
upon	O
the	B-place
Bridge	I-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Olives	I-place
Southwark	I-place
;	O
the	O
manner	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
as	O
follows	O
:	O
The	O
two	O
persons	O
before-mentioned	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
being	O
Sabbath	O
day	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
supposed	O
,	O
having	O
Intelligence	O
that	O
Mr.	O
King	O
and	O
all	O
his	O
Family	O
(	O
except	O
his	O
Maid-servant	O
,	O
by	O
name	O
Joan	B-pers
Elge	I-pers
)	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Church	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
Maid	O
peeping	O
through	O
the	O
Key-hole	O
,	O
demanded	O
what	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
?	O
their	O
answer	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
were	O
friends	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Kings	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
needs	O
speak	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
the	O
Maid	O
replyed	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
within	O
:	O
to	O
which	O
Sutton	O
answered	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
he	O
were	O
newly	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Countrey	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Air	O
was	O
not	O
agreeing	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
sick	O
coming	O
over	O
the	O
Bridge	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
stay	O
till	O
Mr.	O
King	O
come	O
home	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
opened	O
it	O
and	O
let	O
them	O
in	O
,	O
they	O
telling	O
her	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
Masters	O
Cozens	O
,	O
and	O
seemed	O
much	O
to	O
admire	O
the	O
Furniture	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
commending	O
it	O
above	O
whatever	O
they	O
saw	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
;	O
the	O
Woman	O
still	O
feigning	O
herself	O
sick	O
:	O
and	O
so	O
cunning	O
were	O
they	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
believe	O
the	O
Wench	O
,	O
though	O
she	O
several	O
times	O
affirmed	O
there	O
was	O
none	O
at	O
home	O
but	O
her	O
self	O
;	O
till	O
asking	O
for	O
a	O
Vault	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
up	O
stairs	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
going	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
staid	O
but	O
a	O
very	O
short	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
coming	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
went	O
seemingly	O
to	O
kiss	O
the	O
Maid	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
clapt	O
his	O
hands	O
to	O
her	O
Throat	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
He	O
came	O
for	O
Money	O
;	O
at	O
which	O
surprize	O
she	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
Woman	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
God	O
dam	O
her	O
cut	O
her	O
Throat	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
both	O
of	O
them	O
falling	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
bound	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
searching	O
for	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
found	O
one	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
they	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
cut	O
her	O
Throat	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
with	O
strugling	O
got	O
her	O
hands	O
loose	O
,	O
and	O
wrested	O
the	O
Knife	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
hands	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
binding	O
her	O
faster	O
,	O
upon	O
promise	O
she	O
would	O
no	O
more	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
left	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Trunks	O
and	O
Chests	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
one	O
Silver	O
Bason	O
,	O
six	O
Silver	O
Plates	O
,	O
two	O
dozen	O
of	O
Spoons	O
,	O
two	O
Tankards	O
,	O
one	O
Sugar-dish	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
shop-door	O
,	O
got	O
a	O
hundred	O
and	O
ninety	O
seven	O
pounds	O
in	O
money	O
;	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
time	O
they	O
were	O
plundering	O
,	O
the	O
Maid	O
got	O
loose	O
,	O
though	O
all	O
bloody	O
,	O
shut	O
her	O
self	O
into	O
a	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
cryedout	O
Thieves	O
,	O
Murther	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
coming	O
,	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
but	O
t	O
're	O
they	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
now	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Cellar-windows	O
upon	O
the	O
Piles	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Woman	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
shortly	O
after	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
got	O
off	O
in	O
a	O
Boat	O
;	O
upon	O
searching	O
of	O
him	O
there	O
was	O
about	O
fifteen	O
pounds	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
breaches	O
the	O
rest	O
they	O
onely	O
removed	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
no	O
opportunity	O
of	O
carrying	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
Upon	O
their	O
Tryals	O
they	O
pleaded	O
both	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
next	O
was	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Salter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
fields	I-place
,	O
who	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
being	O
an	O
Aider	O
and	O
Abetter	O
to	O
one	O
Henry	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
now	O
fled	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Murthering	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Dobson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
manner	O
thus	O
:	O
They	O
being	O
together	O
at	O
Lieutenant	O
Griffin	O
's	O
Chamber	O
in	O
the	O
Meuse	B-place
,	O
happened	O
to	O
fall	O
out	O
about	O
a	O
wager	O
of	O
a	O
Guiney	O
,	O
which	O
caused	O
Dobson	O
to	O
give	O
Lee	O
the	O
Lye	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
:	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
seeing	O
that	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
pacific	O
the	O
quarrel	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
he	O
could	O
any	O
ways	O
hinder	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
closed	O
with	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
party	O
dead	O
had	O
wrested	O
the	O
others	O
Sword	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
whereupon	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Salter	O
interposing	O
,	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
desist	O
but	O
Lee	O
being	O
inraged	O
;	O
snatched	O
Salters	O
Sword	O
from	O
his	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
over	O
his	O
Shoulder	O
ran	O
Dobson	O
into	O
the	O
body	O
,	O
just	O
under	O
the	O
left	O
pap	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Wound	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
instant	O
he	O
dyed	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
not	O
the	O
least	O
suspition	O
of	O
Malice	O
proved	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Tibia	B-pers
Hog	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
Indian	O
Silk	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Suttel	I-pers
Indian	O
gown	O
seller	O
in	O
the	O
New	B-place
Exchange	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Strand	I-place
:	O
she	O
coming	O
to	O
his	O
shop	O
,	O
cheapned	O
several	O
parcels	O
of	O
silk	O
,	O
and	O
thereby	O
took	O
the	O
opportunity	O
whilst	O
they	O
were	O
busi	O
,	O
to	O
slip	O
two	O
pieces	O
under	O
her	O
Coats	O
,	O
valued	O
at	O
ten	O
pounds	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
perceived	O
by	O
a	O
youth	O
that	O
stood	O
in	O
an	O
opposite	O
shop	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Suttel	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
,	O
whereupon	O
she	O
dropped	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
she	O
denyed	O
that	O
ever	O
she	O
touched	O
,	O
or	O
had	O
any	O
such	O
parcel	O
of	O
Silk	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
so	O
plain	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Duffer	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Westwood	I-pers
a	O
Barber	O
in	O
Holbourn	B-place
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
eight	O
Razers	O
,	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
Cizars	O
,	O
three	O
Napkins	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Beard-irons	O
,	O
one	O
Perriwig	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
The	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
were	O
both	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
by	O
his	O
former	O
Confession	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
a	O
Witness	O
whom	O
he	O
sold	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Razers	O
to	O
,	O
though	O
Newgate	O
had	O
taught	O
him	O
the	O
impudence	O
to	O
deny	O
his	O
former	O
asseveration	O
;	O
yet	O
upon	O
the	O
testimony	O
that	O
was	O
given	O
against	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Bucknal	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
Murthering	O
her	O
Male	O
Bastard-childe	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
manner	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
as	O
ensues	O
.	O
She	O
living	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
and	O
lodging	O
with	O
another	O
woman	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
found	O
her	O
pains	O
come	O
fast	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
arose	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
other	O
being	O
so	O
fast	O
a	O
sleep	O
that	O
she	O
perceived	O
it	O
not	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
swore	O
)	O
and	O
was	O
by	O
her	O
self	O
delivered	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
so	O
secretly	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
heard	O
some	O
noise	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
repli	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
bought	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
one	O
penny	O
worth	O
of	O
Damsons	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
by	O
eating	O
them	O
she	O
had	O
surfeited	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
the	O
which	O
had	O
caus	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
Vomit	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
answer	O
her	O
Bed-fellow	O
went	O
to	O
sleep	O
:	O
she	O
taking	O
the	O
opportunity	O
thereof	O
,	O
thrust	O
the	O
Child	O
between	O
the	O
Bed	O
and	O
the	O
Mat	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
afterwards	O
found	O
:	O
Upon	O
Examination	O
she	O
denied	O
that	O
she	O
any	O
way	O
made	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Childe	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
stillborn	O
,	O
which	O
availed	O
her	O
not	O
;	O
for	O
upon	O
the	O
reading	O
of	O
the	O
Act	O
of	O
Parliament	O
made	O
to	O
prevent	O
such	O
Cruelties	O
,	O
she	O
having	O
none	O
to	O
justifie	O
that	O
is	O
was	O
Still-born	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Murther	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Bishopsgate-street	B-place
London	I-place
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
a	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
robbing	O
his	O
Lodging	O
,	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Doors	O
and	O
Desks	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
two	O
Callico	O
Pillowbeers	O
,	O
two	O
Tablecloths	O
,	O
several	O
Curtains	O
and	O
Valens	O
;	O
besides	O
Apparel	O
,	O
as	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
Scarfs	O
and	O
Hoods	O
,	O
as	O
likewise	O
Thread	O
and	O
Gimp	O
,	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
pounds	O
;	O
thishe	O
effected	O
one	O
Morning	O
before	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
were	O
stirring	O
,	O
carrying	O
them	O
clear	O
off	O
without	O
the	O
least	O
discovery	O
,	O
leaving	O
one	O
that	O
he	O
pretended	O
was	O
his	O
Wife	O
in	O
bed	O
the	O
mean	O
while	O
.	O
And	O
also	O
several	O
Pick-lock	O
Keys	O
were	O
found	O
that	O
would	O
open	O
all	O
the	O
House-doors	O
,	O
Trunks	O
,	O
Chests	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
fastenings	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
and	O
was	O
so	O
impudent	O
as	O
not	O
long	O
after	O
to	O
send	O
a	O
Messenger	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
things	O
he	O
had	O
by	O
over-haste	O
forgot	O
,	O
whereupon	O
by	O
the	O
directions	O
of	O
the	O
Messenger	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
upon	O
Trial	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
who	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
arresting	O
he	O
onely	O
had	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
and	O
no	O
body	O
else	O
,	O
the	O
Jurors	O
gave	O
their	O
Verdict	O
against	O
him	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cleverard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Edmonds	I-place
Lombard-street	I-place
,	O
was	O
arraigned	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
as	O
Clipper	O
of	O
the	O
current	O
and	O
lawful	O
Coyn	O
of	O
this	O
Realm	O
,	O
bringing	O
several	O
clipp	O
'd	O
Half-crowns	O
newly	O
clipped	O
to	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
,	O
mix	O
'd	O
with	O
other	O
large	O
Money	O
,	O
to	O
change	O
for	O
Guineas	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
further	O
enquiry	O
found	O
where	O
she	O
Lodged	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
her	O
possession	O
was	O
found	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
small	O
Sheers	O
,	O
Clippings	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
suchlike	O
things	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
said	O
was	O
her	O
Husband	O
's	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
working	O
Silver-smith	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
used	O
them	O
in	O
his	O
employ	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
proof	O
of	O
her	O
clipping	O
any	O
piece	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Conway	I-pers
and	I-pers
Mary	I-pers
his	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
and	O
Mary	O
his	O
Wife	O
were	O
tried	O
for	O
robbing	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bale	I-pers
of	O
Islington	B-place
in	O
the	O
day-time	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
Anne	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
a	O
little	O
Girl	O
,	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
of	O
her	O
Life	O
.	O
They	O
being	O
Vagrant	O
s	O
,	O
came	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Bale	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
lodge	O
them	O
in	O
his	O
Out-house	O
or	O
Shed	O
that	O
adjoyned	O
to	O
his	O
Dwelling-house	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
consented	O
to	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
to	O
requite	O
him	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
watching	O
the	O
opportunity	O
of	O
his	O
Absence	O
,	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
through	O
a	O
hole	O
in	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
alleadge	O
was	O
broke	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
sending	O
the	O
little	O
Girl	O
out	O
for	O
Bread	O
and	O
Cheese	O
,	O
having	O
first	O
stilled	O
her	O
from	O
crying	O
,	O
by	O
Threats	O
and	O
Promises	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
space	O
they	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
several	O
Hoods	O
,	O
Scarfs	O
,	O
Dressings	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
like	O
,	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
Breeches	O
and	O
Doublet	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
Moneys	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
other	O
things	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
shortly	O
apprehended	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
committed	O
to	O
Newgate	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
proof	O
upon	O
their	O
Tryals	O
being	O
very	O
plain	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
latter	O
being	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
found	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
took	O
her	O
Tryal	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver-Tankard	O
from	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Par	I-pers
in	O
Covent-garden	B-place
valued	O
at	O
eight	O
Pounds	O
and	O
upwards	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
sold	O
to	O
a	O
Goldsmiths	O
Wife	O
for	O
Five	O
Pounds	O
or	O
thereabouts	O
.	O
Her	O
taking	O
of	O
it	O
away	O
was	O
thus	O
:	O
She	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
none	O
but	O
a	O
Maid-servant	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
she	O
related	O
,	O
that	O
meeting	O
her	O
Mistress	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
,	O
she	O
ordered	O
her	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
stay	O
there	O
till	O
she	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
withal	O
desired	O
the	O
Maid	O
to	O
fetch	O
her	O
a	O
Tankard	O
of	O
Ale	O
;	O
which	O
she	O
refusing	O
,	O
she	O
again	O
requested	O
her	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
some	O
small	O
Beer	O
,	O
the	O
which	O
whirlst	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
fetch	O
,	O
she	O
opened	O
the	O
Cupboard	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Tankard	O
thence	O
,	O
and	O
e	O
're	O
the	O
Maid	O
returned	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
This	O
being	O
proved	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
and	O
Tryed	O
,	O
for	O
Robbing	O
her	O
Master	B-pers
of	O
of	O
Four	O
pound	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
which	O
she	O
said	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
to	O
debauch	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
appearing	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Call	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
White-Reed	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Worley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
fields	I-place
,	O
of	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
Gown	O
,	O
Pinners	O
,	O
Dressings	O
,	O
Stocking	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
which	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
upon	O
plain	O
Evidence	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Eleaventh	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
,	O
being	O
Saturday	O
,	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
was	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cellier	I-pers
brought	O
upon	O
her	O
Trial	O
,	O
being	O
taken	O
up	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
by	O
a	O
Bench	O
warrant	O
,	O
granted	O
for	O
that	O
purpose	O
by	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
for	O
publishing	O
a	O
scandalous	O
Libel	O
,	O
entituled	O
,	O
Malice	O
defeated	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
not	O
onely	O
several	O
private	O
men	O
scandalized	O
,	O
but	O
also	O
the	O
whole	O
Government	O
and	O
Laws	O
of	O
the	O
Nation	O
.	O
Several	O
Witnesses	O
came	O
in	O
against	O
her	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
Author	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
handed	O
the	O
Copy	O
to	O
the	O
Press	O
,	O
paying	O
ten	O
shillings	O
a	O
ream	O
for	O
printing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Printer	O
swore	O
that	O
he	O
printed	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
Ssheets	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
were	O
contain	O
'd	O
the	O
matter	O
and	O
substance	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
long	O
,	O
importing	O
that	O
she	O
the	O
said	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cellier	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
to	O
Peter	B-pers
Cellier	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
had	O
published	O
in	O
her	O
said	O
scandalous	O
Libel	O
,	O
that	O
Racks	O
and	O
Tortures	O
were	O
used	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
Catholicks	O
confess	O
a	O
Plot	O
when	O
there	O
was	O
none	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Praunce	O
and	O
one-Corrale	O
a	O
Coachman	O
were	O
so	O
served	O
in	O
Newgate	O
;	O
farther	O
laying	O
the	O
inhumane	O
Murther	O
of	O
his	O
late	O
Majesty	O
to	O
the	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
Protestants	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Evidence	O
were	O
Devils	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
men	O
;	O
with	O
several	O
Reflections	O
upon	O
some	O
Peers	O
of	O
this	O
Realm	O
:	O
to	O
all	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Ignorance	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
Author	O
of	O
the	O
Book	O
,	O
though	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
she	O
had	O
confessed	O
and	O
owned	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
proof	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Peny	I-pers
swore	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
of	O
her	O
at	O
her	O
own	O
house	O
in	O
Arundel-street	B-place
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
giving	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
the	O
sum	O
of	O
four	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
owned	O
to	O
him	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
own	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
Author	O
of	O
the	O
Libel	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
after	O
her	O
having	O
made	O
a	O
long	O
Apology	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
gave	O
the	O
Jury	O
their	O
Charge	O
,	O
who	O
going	O
out	O
and	O
staying	O
about	O
half	O
,	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Misdemeanour	O
or	O
Trespass	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
ordered	O
into	O
Custody	O
under	O
the	O
jurisdiction	O
of	O
the	O
Keeper	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
said	O
Libels	O
that	O
could	O
be	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
house	O
or	O
elsewhere	O
appertaining	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
were	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
secured	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
Fined	O
one	O
Thousand	O
pound	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
kept	O
in	O
Prison	O
till	O
that	O
be	O
paid	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
to	O
stand	O
Three	O
several	O
times	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
,	O
First	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
May-pole	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
Secondly	O
,	O
in	O
Convent-garden	O
,	O
Thirdly	O
,	O
at	O
Charing-cross	O
;	O
her	O
Books	O
being	O
to	O
be	O
Burnt	O
in	O
her	O
view	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
to	O
find	O
Sureties	O
for	O
her	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
during	O
Life	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hains	I-pers
,	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
tried	O
for	O
robbing	O
one	O
Herbert	B-pers
of	O
several	O
pieces	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
Pounds	O
.	O
The	O
Indictment	O
lay	O
for	O
taking	O
them	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
in	O
St.	O
Bartholmew's-lane	O
;	O
but	O
in	O
Court	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
possitively	O
swear	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
notorious	O
Beggar	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thought	O
a	O
whipping	O
might	O
reform	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
Ten	O
pence	O
.	O
There	O
received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
these	O
persons	O
following	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
George-Coles	O
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
,	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Sutton	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Bucknall	I-pers
,	O
Tibby	O
Hagg	O
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Conuway	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Dubaer	I-pers
,	O
Isabel	B-pers
Gaudin	I-pers
,	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Wilkason	I-pers
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Crook	I-pers
Burnt	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Haines	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Roe	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Cute	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
Whiped	O
.	O
