TOKEN	NE
THE	O
TRYALS	O
At	O
the	O
SESSIONS	O
In	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
,	O
Which	O
began	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
and	O
Goale	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
December	O
,	O
and	O
ended	O
on	O
Thursday	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
giving	O
a	O
full	O
and	O
satisfactory	O
Relation	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
remarkable	O
Circumstances	O
that	O
happened	O
in	O
each	O
Tryal	O
,	O
as	O
that	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
for	O
Firing	O
her	O
Masters	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Sancey	I-pers
for	O
Robbing	O
a	O
French	O
Marquess	O
,	O
and	O
Wounding	O
his	O
Steward	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
;	O
as	O
also	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
those	O
Condemned	O
to	O
Dye	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
Transported	O
,	O
and	O
Whipped	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
upon	O
two	O
several	O
Indictments	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
,	O
for	O
setting	O
fire	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
day	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
then	O
a	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
circumstances	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
were	O
these	O
,	O
That	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
before-mentioned	O
,	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
of	O
the	O
clock	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Tapster	O
,	O
and	O
informed	O
him	O
that	O
she	O
smelt	O
a	O
grievous	O
smoak	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
demanded	O
of	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
burning	O
?	O
who	O
answered	O
,	O
nothing	O
but	O
Coals	O
;	O
with	O
this	O
,	O
she	O
not	O
being	O
satisfied	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
informed	O
him	O
how	O
that	O
she	O
believed	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
on	O
fire	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
smoak	O
that	O
made	O
her	O
coff	O
extreamly	O
,	O
yet	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
there	O
could	O
be	O
no	O
smoak	O
perceived	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Tapster	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
soon	O
discovered	O
that	O
the	O
upper	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
light	O
fire	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
consternation	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
ran	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
and	O
with	O
the	O
assistance	O
of	O
several	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
had	O
the	O
good	O
luck	O
to	O
extinguish	O
the	O
flame	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
consumed	O
several	O
Trunks	O
,	O
and	O
burnt	O
quite	O
through	O
the	O
floor	O
:	O
during	O
which	O
space	O
the	O
now	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
directly	O
to	O
another	O
Garret	O
,	O
and	O
opening	O
a	O
box	O
,	O
found	O
that	O
on	O
fire	O
likewise	O
,	O
upon	O
these	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
denying	O
to	O
carry	O
water	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
suspected	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
farther	O
search	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
broken	O
open	O
the	O
Trunk	O
,	O
and	O
tying	O
up	O
the	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
of	O
Erasmus	B-pers
Armstrong	I-pers
in	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
Aprons	O
,	O
had	O
thrown	O
them	O
into	O
a	O
Neighbours	O
yard	O
.	O
As	O
likewise	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
away	O
three	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Jacobus	O
.	O
These	O
circumstances	O
being	O
proved	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
both	O
the	O
Indictments	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
for	O
seting	O
fire	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
the	O
Tapsters	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
Gold	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
took	O
her	O
Tryal	O
for	O
Murthering	O
her	O
Male	O
Bastard	O
Child	O
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
lately	O
come	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
had	O
got	O
her	O
a	O
Service	O
,	O
her	O
Mistress	O
not	O
perceiving	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
but	O
lodged	O
a	O
little	O
Girl	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
was	O
delivered	O
without	O
the	O
knowledge	O
of	O
any	O
,	O
and	O
rising	O
early	O
next	O
morning	O
went	O
about	O
her	O
occasions	O
,	O
leaving	O
the	O
Child	O
dead	O
in	O
the	O
bed	O
with	O
her	O
Mistresses	O
Daughter	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
conjectured	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
smothered	O
it	O
with	O
the	O
Bed-cloaths	O
,	O
the	O
which	O
the	O
Girl	O
waking	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Child	O
in	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
whereuponseveral	O
Neighbours	O
coming	O
in	O
,	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
.	O
Upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
she	O
pleaded	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
still	O
born	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Ashmore	I-pers
,	O
upon	O
promise	O
of	O
Marriage	O
so	O
far	O
prevailed	O
as	O
to	O
deflour	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
the	O
reading	O
of	O
the	O
Statute	O
in	O
that	O
case	O
made	O
and	O
provided	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Murther	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Sancey	I-pers
a	O
Frenchman	O
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
feloniously	O
entring	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
a	O
French	B-pers
Marquess	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
fields	I-place
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
own	O
Confession	O
before	O
Justice	O
Floyd	O
,	O
was	O
this	O
,	O
first	O
the	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
Murther	O
and	O
Thieves	O
,	O
cryed	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
Marquesses	O
Lodging	O
,	O
whereupon	O
rising	O
and	O
running	O
thither	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
lower	O
doors	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Marquesses	O
Steward	O
weltring	O
in	O
his	O
Blood	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
Knife	O
lying	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
finding	O
no	O
man	O
there	O
beside	O
,	O
he	O
searched	O
about	O
,	O
(	O
there	O
being	O
then	O
several	O
come	O
to	O
his	O
assistance	O
)	O
and	O
to	O
the	O
Celler	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
all	O
besmeared	O
with	O
the	O
Stewards	O
Blood	O
,	O
who	O
being	O
carried	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
did	O
confess	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
four	O
more	O
had	O
a	O
design	O
to	O
rob	O
the	O
Marquess	O
,	O
they	O
having	O
not	O
long	O
since	O
robbed	O
him	O
of	O
400	O
Guini	O
's	O
.	O
Upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
he	O
pleaded	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
by	O
chance	O
,	O
not	O
knowing	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
business	O
,	O
yet	O
that	O
served	O
not	O
his	O
turn	O
,	O
for	O
although	O
he	O
carried	O
away	O
nothing	O
,	O
as	O
being	O
timely	O
prevented	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
time	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
barbarously	O
wounding	O
Henry	B-pers
Atley	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Latham	I-place
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
the	O
substance	O
of	O
the	O
Tryal	O
thus	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
setting	O
upon	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Alley	O
,	O
bid	O
him	O
deliver	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
refusing	O
,	O
he	O
drew	O
out	O
Pistol	O
and	O
shot	O
him	O
through	O
the	O
wrift	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
wound	O
he	O
languished	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
second	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
dyed	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
very	O
strong	O
presumption	O
against	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
positive	O
proof	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Susanna	B-pers
Haselwood	I-pers
received	O
her	O
Tryal	O
for	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Lupton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
out	O
Holland-sheet	O
,	O
a	O
Table	O
Cloath	O
,	O
a	O
pinner	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
being	O
by	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
taken	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
ever	O
she	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
she	O
pretended	O
she	O
lodged	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
she	O
threw	O
down	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
dropped	O
several	O
Picklock	O
keys	O
in	O
the	O
Chimney	O
corner	O
.	O
Upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
she	O
denyed	O
that	O
she	O
ever	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
proof	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
four	O
shillings	O
and	O
six	O
pence	O
.	O
Benjamine	B-pers
Wilcason	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Shift	O
,	O
several	O
Napkins	O
,	O
Table-cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Linnen	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
house	O
neer	O
Paul	B-place
's	I-place
Wharf	I-place
,	O
and	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
to	O
all	O
Felonies	O
within	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
his	O
Clergy	O
;	O
and	O
thereupon	O
was	O
burnt	O
in	O
the	O
hand	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Doughty	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Cows	I-pers
,	O
were	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
from	O
Walter	B-pers
Briscoe	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
valued	O
at	O
five	O
pounds	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
pleaded	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Briscow	O
's	O
Wife	O
had	O
given	O
the	O
Tankard	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Doughty	O
,	O
who	O
;	O
as	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Marquiss	O
of	O
Winchester	O
,	O
for	O
some	O
Kindnesses	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
obliged	O
her	O
in	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
often	O
opportun	O
'd	O
Cows	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Hat-maker	O
by	O
Trade	O
,	O
to	O
deliver	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
Doughty	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
He	O
should	O
come	O
to	O
no	O
damage	O
by	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
part	O
to	O
makehim	O
amends	O
for	O
the	O
service	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
by	O
keeping	O
of	O
her	O
company	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
farther	O
gratifie	O
him	O
,	O
or	O
words	O
to	O
that	O
effect	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
he	O
delivered	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
sold	O
to	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
,	O
in	O
whose	O
hands	O
Briscowe	O
found	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Proof	O
to	O
contradict	O
the	O
womans	O
delivering	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Lant	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
of	O
Silks	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
twelve	O
pounds	O
,	O
from	O
a	O
Mercer	B-pers
.	O
Her	O
Plea	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
another	O
had	O
stollen	O
the	O
same	O
and	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
being	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
stole	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
afterwards	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
custody	O
,	O
she	O
having	O
been	O
a	O
notorious	O
Shoplift	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
times	O
pardoned	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
murdering	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
a	O
Watchman	O
,	O
in	O
Ivy-lane	B-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Parish	I-place
of	I-place
Saint	I-place
Faiths	I-place
,	O
London	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
this	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
company	O
of	O
Whitticar	O
and	O
Watson	O
,	O
condemned	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
Pater	O
Noster	O
Row	O
in	O
May	O
last	O
about	O
three	O
of	O
the	O
clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
their	O
way	O
made	O
such	O
a	O
noise	O
as	O
made	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
then	O
upon	O
his	O
Stand	O
,	O
question	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
endeavour	O
to	O
stop	O
them	O
;	O
whereupon	O
they	O
resisted	O
,	O
and	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
make	O
their	O
Escapes	O
,	O
Whitticar	O
striking	O
up	O
Smith	O
's	O
heels	O
,	O
and	O
Watson	O
beating	O
down	O
the	O
Lanthorn	O
of	O
another	O
Watchman	O
there	O
assisting	O
;	O
which	O
made	O
Smith	O
the	O
deceased	O
coller	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
Watson	O
snatching	O
away	O
his	O
Staff	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
same	O
knocked	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
they	O
all	O
made	O
their	O
Escape	O
.	O
The	O
blow	O
was	O
so	O
violent	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
broke	O
Smith	O
's	O
Scull	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Wound	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Oath	O
of	O
the	O
Chirurgeon	O
,	O
he	O
died	O
within	O
the	O
space	O
of	O
four	O
months	O
after	O
:	O
When	O
as	O
they	O
having	O
notice	O
that	O
the	O
Parties	O
that	O
had	O
done	O
the	O
Fact	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	O
James	O
Clerkenwel	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
apprehended	O
,	O
Watson	O
and	O
Whitticar	O
,	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
being	O
condemned	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
:	O
But	O
against	O
the	O
now	O
Prisoner	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
positive	O
Proof	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
of	O
their	O
company	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
he	O
meddled	O
in	O
the	O
Affair	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Maurlin	I-pers
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
were	O
severally	O
Tryed	O
,	O
for	O
Stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Huetson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolfs	I-place
without	I-place
Algate	I-place
;	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
stealing	O
of	O
a	O
Quart-pot	O
,	O
valued	O
at	O
1	O
shil	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
which	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
swore	O
,	O
she	O
conveyed	O
away	O
in	O
a	O
bundle	O
of	O
Linnen	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
to	O
wash	O
:	O
Her	O
Plea	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Maid	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
since	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
that	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
for	O
the	O
Jeasts	O
sake	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
heard	O
on	O
both	O
hands	O
,	O
it	O
proved	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
people	O
that	O
prosecuted	O
kept	O
an	O
ill	O
house	O
;	O
So	O
that	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
,	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
The	O
latter	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
Tablecloaths	O
,	O
Napkins	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
several	O
pieces	O
of	O
Plate	O
and	O
Moneys	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
a	O
Nurse	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
most	O
remarkable	O
passage	O
sn	O
this	O
Trial	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Fellow	O
coming	O
to	O
testifie	O
in	O
the	O
behalf	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
no	O
such	O
Goods	O
as	O
were	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
lost	O
,	O
himself	O
knowing	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
her	O
possession	O
,	O
having	O
taken	O
an	O
Inventory	O
of	O
all	O
during	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
her	O
Husbands	O
absence	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
fain	O
to	O
lend	O
the	O
woman	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
his	O
Shirts	O
to	O
wear	O
.	O
But	O
in	O
his	O
earnest	O
discourse	O
Swearing	O
an	O
Oath	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
obliged	O
him	O
to	O
pay	O
12	O
d.	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
One	O
John	B-pers
Bullion	I-pers
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
Tryed	O
as	O
a	O
Popish	O
Priest	O
;	O
But	O
Pleading	O
he	O
had	O
formerly	O
been	O
tryed	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
before	O
a	O
Judge	O
of	O
an	O
Assize	O
and	O
there	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
his	O
Trial	O
was	O
put	O
off	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	B-pers
Lumley	I-pers
being	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Recusancy	O
,	O
brought	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Divine	O
Service	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
the	O
Sacrament	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Church	O
of	O
England	O
;	O
and	O
thereupon	O
Order	O
was	O
given	O
for	O
the	O
withdrawing	O
the	O
said	O
Indictment	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
Five	O
Condemned	O
;	O
viz	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
Frances	B-pers
Small	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Lant	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Sancey	I-pers
.	O
Four	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Three	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
.	O
Two	O
to	O
be	O
Whipt	O
.	O
And	O
so	O
the	O
Session	O
concluded	O
.	O
