TOKEN	NE
THE	O
TRUE	O
NARRATIVE	O
OF	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
The	O
Sessions-House	O
IN	O
THE	O
OLD-BALY	O
,	O
Which	O
began	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
October	O
,	O
and	O
ended	O
on	O
Fryday	O
the	O
15	O
following	O
.	O
Giving	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
Remarkable	O
Trials	O
there	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
For	O
Murder	O
,	O
Fellonies	O
and	O
Burglaries	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
with	O
a	O
particular	O
Relation	O
of	O
their	O
Names	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
places	O
of	O
their	O
committing	O
their	O
Facts	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
those	O
Condemned	O
to	O
die	O
,	O
Burn	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
Transported	O
and	O
to	O
be	O
whipt	O
.	O
THe	O
first	O
was	O
Catherine	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Dodson	I-pers
,	O
Tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
eleven	O
Yards	O
of	O
Lawn	O
,	O
vallued	O
at	O
nine	O
shillings	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
seventeenh	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
living	O
in	O
St	B-place
,	I-place
Lawrence	I-place
Jury	I-place
,	O
the	O
manner	O
thus	O
,	O
She	O
coming	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
to	O
his	O
Shop-door	O
,	O
alighted	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Linnen	O
Cloth	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
her	O
opportunity	O
conveyed	O
the	O
Goods	O
aforesaid	O
into	O
her	O
Coat	O
,	O
or	O
some	O
other	O
private	O
place	O
and	O
then	O
pretending	O
a	O
dislike	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
she	O
found	O
none	O
for	O
her	O
turn	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Coach	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Turner	O
missing	O
his	O
Lawn	O
followed	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
search	O
found	O
it	O
dropped	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
.	O
She	O
pleaded	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
full	O
Evidence	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Fellony	O
.	O
A	O
second	O
Indictment	O
was	O
preferred	O
against	O
her	O
by	O
one	O
Mr	B-pers
,	I-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
of	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
vallued	O
at	O
four	O
pound	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Scarff	O
vallued	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Buttons	O
vallued	O
at	O
one	O
shilling	O
.	O
She	O
coming	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
in	O
Southampton-Building	B-place
,	O
took	O
a	O
Lodging	O
,	O
pretending	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Husband	O
living	O
in	O
Grays-Inn	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
having	O
been	O
there	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
desired	O
tohave	O
a	O
Tankard	O
of	O
Beer	O
set	O
by	O
her	O
Bedside	O
,	O
the	O
which	O
being	O
done	O
,	O
she	O
very	O
fairly	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
getting	O
up	O
betimes	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
and	O
departed	O
.	O
The	O
Tankard	O
was	O
afterwards	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
Goldsmiths	O
hands	O
to	O
whom	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
,	O
her	O
Plea	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
only	O
borrowed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
intended	O
to	O
restore	O
it	O
again	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
frivilous	O
excuse	O
being	O
common	O
with	O
such	O
kind	O
of	O
People	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
clearly	O
proved	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
this	O
also	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Whittaker	I-pers
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Murthering	O
one	O
Isaack	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
a	O
Watchman	O
in	O
Ivy-Lane	B-place
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
manner	O
thus	O
,	O
several	O
persons	O
about	O
3	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
coming	O
down	O
Paternoster	O
Row	O
,	O
made	O
a	O
noise	O
and	O
seemed	O
very	O
unruly	O
as	O
they	O
came	O
along	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Deceased	O
and	O
another	O
Watchman	O
being	O
upon	O
their	O
Stands	O
,	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
stop	O
them	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
the	O
rexamining	O
them	O
,	O
or	O
having	O
them	O
before	O
the	O
Constable	O
to	O
give	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
their	O
business	O
at	O
such	O
an	O
unseasonable	O
time	O
;	O
whereupon	O
they	O
resisted	O
and	O
fell	O
to	O
scuffling	O
with	O
the	O
Watchman	O
;	O
whitraker	O
striking	O
up	O
one	O
of	O
their	O
Heels	O
,	O
and	O
Watkins	O
beating	O
down	O
the	O
others	O
Lanthorn	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Dispute	O
grew	O
very	O
hot	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
after	O
some	O
hard	O
Scuffle	O
with	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
Watkins	O
got	O
up	O
his	O
Staff	O
and	O
struck	O
him	O
a	O
blow	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
knocking	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Wound	O
he	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
22	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
pleaded	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
first	O
assaulted	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
Fruterer	O
s	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
about	O
their	O
lawful	O
occasions	O
to	O
buy	O
Fruit	O
in	O
Newgate	O
Market	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Chirurgion	O
giving	O
in	O
upon	O
Oath	O
that	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
his	O
Skill	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
died	O
of	O
the	O
Wound	O
,	O
whereupon	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Murther	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hull	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Bag	O
vallued	O
at	O
two	O
pence	O
and	O
twentyeight	O
pounds	O
of	O
monies	O
numbered	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
monies	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Hadcock	I-pers
of	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
she	O
being	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
opportunity	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
Keys	O
of	O
a	O
Trunck	O
that	O
stood	O
under	O
her	O
Masters	O
Bed	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
mony	O
was	O
and	O
opening	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
permitting	O
some	O
other	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
conveyed	O
the	O
Monies	O
thence	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
missing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
being	O
taxed	O
,	O
she	O
confessed	O
that	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Man	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
monies	O
was	O
not	O
lost	O
that	O
day	O
they	O
supposed	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
upon	O
Evidence	O
of	O
the	O
Trunks	O
being	O
opened	O
.	O
the	O
Lock	O
overshot	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
one	O
but	O
she	O
admitted	O
into	O
the	O
Chamber	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
stood	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Fellony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Nicholson	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Watch	O
vallued	O
at	O
twenty-two	O
shillings	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
the	O
manner	O
thus	O
,	O
he	O
coming	O
into	O
his	O
Shop	O
offered	O
to	O
sell	O
a	O
Watch	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
reason	O
it	O
was	O
broak	O
was	O
not	O
willing	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
charge	O
of	O
mending	O
it	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
bought	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
looking	O
well	O
about	O
him	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
stolen	O
another	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
A	O
second	O
Indictment	O
was	O
preferred	O
against	O
him	O
and	O
one	O
George	B-pers
Granger	I-pers
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murthering	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Dimblebe	I-pers
,	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Marriot	O
of	O
Hampton-Court	B-place
where	O
the	O
Murther	O
was	O
Committed	O
,	O
the	O
manner	O
of	O
which	O
barbarous	O
exploit	O
was	O
thus	O
;	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Confession	O
of	O
Nicholson	O
that	O
Granger	O
upon	O
some	O
falling	O
out	O
between	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
bidden	O
him	O
fourty	O
shillings	O
to	O
Murther	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
something	O
else	O
not	O
named	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
consented	O
to	O
undertake	O
the	O
Villanous	O
Exploit	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
convenient	O
times	O
made	O
three	O
several	O
Attempts	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
Heart	O
failed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
often	O
he	O
told	O
Granger	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
who	O
encouraged	O
him	O
as	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
fourth	O
time	O
following	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
dark	O
Room	O
on	O
the	O
sixteenth	O
of	O
September	O
lost	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Carpenter	O
by	O
Trade	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
Ax	O
felled	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
his	O
Scull	O
was	O
broak	O
in	O
several	O
places	O
;	O
whether	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
any	O
more	O
Blowes	O
is	O
not	O
certain	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
he	O
left	O
him	O
weltering	O
in	O
his	O
Blood	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
by	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Cole	O
who	O
came	O
in	O
quest	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
quite	O
senseless	O
,	O
lived	O
only	O
two	O
days	O
afterwards	O
but	O
never	O
spoke	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
Nicholson	O
fled	O
towards	O
London	O
,	O
which	O
gave	O
suspicion	O
of	O
his	O
Guilt	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
being	O
pursued	O
he	O
was	O
heard	O
of	O
at	O
Kingston	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
Half-moon	O
there	O
,	O
had	O
offered	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
Watch	O
he	O
afterwards	O
sold	O
in	O
Westminster	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Upan	O
his	O
Trial	O
he	O
persisted	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Murther	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
solemnly	O
Affirm	O
Granger	O
hired	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
other	O
Testimony	O
than	O
his	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
produced	O
to	O
prove	O
his	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
and	O
peaceable	O
Inclination	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
and	O
Nicholson	O
according	O
to	O
his	O
Confession	O
,	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Murther	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Gibbons	I-pers
was	O
Arraigned	O
and	O
tried	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
the	O
manner	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
being	O
by	O
Profession	O
a	O
Taylor	O
,	O
and	O
working	O
with	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Grimes	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Pauls	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
put	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Cloathes	O
to	O
alter	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
coming	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
not	O
being	O
done	O
,	O
he	O
fell	O
to	O
Cursing	O
and	O
Swearing	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
(	O
as	O
he	O
alledged	O
the	O
Taylors	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
were	O
many	O
of	O
them	O
at	O
work	O
)	O
fell	O
a	O
hollowing	O
at	O
him	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
Goose	O
that	O
stood	O
upon	O
the	O
Board	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Deceaseds	O
Head	O
,	O
which	O
missing	O
him	O
he	O
afterwards	O
threw	O
the	O
Sheers	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
the	O
Point	O
of	O
them	O
thorow	O
his	O
Hat	O
into	O
his	O
Head	O
;	O
making	O
there	O
a	O
deep	O
wound	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
sworn	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
afterwards	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
saying	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
enough	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
more	O
.	O
Of	O
this	O
Wound	O
Smith	O
languished	O
,	O
often	O
Vomitting	O
Blood	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
21th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
dyed	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
prove	O
he	O
dyed	O
not	O
of	O
that	O
Wound	O
but	O
of	O
a	O
Feavour	O
and	O
in	O
Order	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
produced	O
several	O
Chirurgions	O
who	O
opened	O
the	O
Body	O
yet	O
notwithstanding	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Markland	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Markland	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Markland	I-pers
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Clipping	O
,	O
and	O
Filing	O
of	O
his	O
Majesties	O
Coin	O
,	O
the	O
lawful	O
monies	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
100	O
of	O
Elizabeth	O
shillings	O
,	O
100	O
of	O
King	O
Charles	B-pers
the	O
first	O
his	O
Shillings	O
and	O
one	O
hundred	O
of	O
his	O
Half-Crowns	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Raplh	O
Markland	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
not	O
only	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
often	O
helped	O
him	O
to	O
Clip	O
several	O
parcels	O
of	O
moneys	O
to	O
the	O
vallue	O
of	O
100	O
pounds	O
,	O
or	O
thereabouts	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
22	O
shillings	O
of	O
Clippedmonies	O
for	O
20	O
of	O
Broad	O
,	O
and	O
thereby	O
had	O
made	O
Exchange	O
for	O
considerable	O
sums	O
.	O
Several	O
Clipping	O
Blocks	O
were	O
likewise	O
upon	O
search	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
Anns	I-place
Black	I-place
Fryers	I-place
and	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheers	O
for	O
Clipping	O
,	O
lately	O
made	O
for	O
him	O
by	O
a	O
Cutler	O
in	O
Southwark	O
found	O
hid	O
in	O
the	O
Nettles	O
in	O
Georges-fields	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
sold	O
several	O
parcels	O
of	O
melted	O
Silver	O
to	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
in	O
the	O
Mint	O
.	O
Against	O
Gregory	O
it	O
was	O
sworn	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Clippings	O
of	O
Markland	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
he	O
received	O
them	O
to	O
melt	O
down	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
Refiner	O
by	O
Trade	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
supplied	O
him	O
with	O
monies	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
being	O
attested	O
by	O
a	O
Servant	O
of	O
Marcklands	O
who	O
had	O
not	O
only	O
carried	O
Clipped	O
monies	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
Exchange	O
,	O
but	O
likewise	O
saw	O
his	O
Master	O
weigh	O
and	O
deliver	O
Clippings	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Against	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Markland	I-pers
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
filed	O
several	O
shillings	O
to	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
20	O
or	O
thereabouts	O
,	O
but	O
against	O
her	O
there	O
was	O
but	O
single	O
Evidence	O
.	O
And	O
against	O
Ann	B-pers
Marckland	I-pers
none	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
after	O
the	O
Court	O
had	O
given	O
the	O
Jury	O
their	O
Charge	O
punctually	O
to	O
every	O
circumstance	O
,	O
they	O
only	O
found	O
Ralph	B-pers
Marckland	I-pers
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Neal	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Hornsey	B-place
on	O
the	O
eighteenth	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Company	O
of	O
eleven	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
Vallue	O
of	O
fifty	O
pounds	O
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
Robbery	O
upon	O
evidence	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Fellony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Priscilla	B-pers
Winn	I-pers
was	O
also	O
found	O
Guilty	O
upon	O
her	O
Trial	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Porringer	O
from	O
David	B-pers
Lockly	I-pers
vallued	O
at	O
50	O
shillings	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
Nobility	O
and	O
Gentry	O
appeared	O
upon	O
their	O
Indictments	O
for	O
Recusancy	O
many	O
person	O
of	O
Honour	O
and	O
worth	O
conforming	O
to	O
the	O
Church	O
of	O
England	O
in	O
all	O
the	O
particulars	O
of	O
the	O
Protestant	O
Religion	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
continued	O
upon	O
Bail	O
to	O
Answer	O
the	O
same	O
at	O
the	O
next	O
General	O
Sessions	O
to	O
be	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
&	O
c.	O
There	O
were	O
in	O
all	O
8	O
that	O
received	O
Sentance	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
Viz	O
.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Markland	I-pers
,	O
Frances	B-pers
Nicholson	I-pers
,	O
Catherine	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Dodson	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Neal	I-pers
,	O
Priscila	B-pers
Win	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hull	I-pers
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Whittaker	I-pers
,	O
and	O
three	O
to	O
be	O
whip	O
'd	O
.	O
