TOKEN	NE
THE	O
TRYAL	O
and	O
CONDEMNATION	O
OF	O
Several	O
Notorious	O
Malefactors	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
Sessions	O
of	O
OYER	O
and	O
TERMINER	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
.	O
Beginning	O
May	O
20	O
1681	O
.	O
Ending	O
the	O
21	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Month	O
.	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
House	O
IN	O
THE	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
.	O
With	O
the	O
Names	O
of	O
those	O
that	O
received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
hand	O
,	O
Transported	O
and	O
to	O
be	O
whipt	O
.	O
And	O
more	O
especially	O
the	O
Tryal	O
of	O
the	O
Maid	O
that	O
Killed	O
the	O
Apprentice	O
in	O
Shoe-lane	O
.	O
Together	O
with	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
a	O
Parsons	O
Wife	O
,	O
that	O
Committed	O
a	O
Murther	O
in	O
the	O
like	O
manner	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Cornwall	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
upon	O
an	O
Indictment	O
,	O
for	O
killing	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
,	O
near	O
Hornsey	B-place
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
:	O
the	O
Circumstances	O
sworn	O
to	O
in	O
Court	O
were	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
bought	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Wood	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
coming	O
to	O
fetch	O
,	O
complained	O
of	O
his	O
hard	O
Bargain	O
,	O
desiring	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
some	O
Over-plus	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
denying	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
,	O
upon	O
Words	O
that	O
passed	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
struck	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
which	O
her	O
Husband	O
observing	O
,	O
snatched	O
a	O
Well-hook	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
throwing	O
down	O
his	O
bundle	O
of	O
Wood	O
,	O
took	O
out	O
his	O
Prong	O
or	O
Forked-stick	O
on	O
which	O
he	O
carried	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
the	O
Deceased	O
three	O
Blows	O
over	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
the	O
last	O
of	O
which	O
broak	O
his	O
Skull	O
.	O
So	O
that	O
the	O
Wound	O
being	O
given	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
he	O
dyed	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Instant	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Pleaded	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
strike	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Proof	O
being	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ellenor	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
were	O
tryed	O
for	O
Stealing	O
35	O
yards	O
of	O
black	O
Silk	O
Lace	O
,	O
layed	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
five	O
pounds	O
,	O
they	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Ridgly	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Lace-man	O
in	O
St	B-place
Edmunds	I-place
Lumber-street	I-place
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Black	O
and	O
Gold	O
Lace	O
,	O
but	O
whilst	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
busied	O
in	O
shewing	O
them	O
several	O
Patterns	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
put	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
peice	O
in	O
her	O
Coat	O
,	O
but	O
doing	O
it	O
in	O
hast	O
,	O
one	O
end	O
hung	O
out	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
discovered	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Lace	O
found	O
about	O
them	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
having	O
been	O
a	O
notorious	O
Shoplift	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Fellony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Messenger	I-pers
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
upon	O
an	O
Indictment	O
of	O
Murther	O
for	O
making	O
away	O
her	O
Bastard	O
male	O
Infant	O
,	O
the	O
manner	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
by	O
too	O
much	O
Familiarity	O
with	O
a	O
Fellow	O
that	O
promised	O
her	O
Marriage	O
proved	O
with	O
Chid	O
,	O
the	O
which	O
she	O
carried	O
so	O
close	O
that	O
none	O
perceived	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
delivered	O
alone	O
,	O
she	O
got	O
up	O
betimes	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
and	O
hid	O
her	O
Child	O
under	O
certain	O
Boards	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Cellar	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
very	O
Ill	O
,	O
her	O
Mistriss	O
suspected	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
sending	O
for	O
a	O
Midwife	O
found	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
Delivered	O
,	O
the	O
which	O
she	O
notwithstanding	O
denied	O
for	O
a	O
good	O
Space	O
:	O
But	O
in	O
conclusion	O
Confessed	O
it	O
and	O
shewed	O
them	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
disposed	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
taken	O
,	O
up	O
a	O
small	O
Orifice	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Breast	O
on	O
't	O
.	O
So	O
that	O
after	O
the	O
Reading	O
of	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
King	O
James	O
,	O
made	O
for	O
the	O
prevention	O
of	O
such	O
Murthers	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Murthering	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Infant	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Alice	B-pers
Enterys	I-pers
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
Killing	O
Philip	B-pers
Avery	I-pers
,	O
Apprentice	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Rogers	O
a	O
Shoe-maker	O
,	O
in	O
Shoe	B-place
lane	I-place
,	O
which	O
happened	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Evidence	O
after	O
this	O
manner	O
,	O
they	O
being	O
both	O
Servant	O
s	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Rogers	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
some	O
small	O
difference	O
happened	O
between	O
about	O
3	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
being	O
pacified	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
they	O
began	O
to	O
play	O
with	O
one	O
another	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Youth	O
about	O
25	O
years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
striking	O
her	O
over	O
the	O
Shoulders	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
supposed	O
in	O
Jest	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
Shop-Knife	O
and	O
pushed	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
lay	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
feared	O
she	O
would	O
Cut	O
him	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
answerd	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
designed	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
she	O
could	O
have	O
accomplished	O
it	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
sooner	O
said	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
rushing	O
in	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
run	O
it	O
two	O
Inches	O
deep	O
into	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
of	O
his	O
Belly	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Wound	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
he	O
dyed	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
Sworn	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
asked	O
,	O
Why	O
she	O
did	O
it	O
?	O
Her	O
Answer	O
was	O
that	O
she	O
wished	O
it	O
had	O
done	O
him	O
worse	O
mischief	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
although	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
of	O
Murther	O
Yet	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Man-slaughter	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquisition	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Wingreen	I-pers
,	O
took	O
his	O
Tryal	O
being	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
valued	O
at	O
6	O
pounds	O
from	O
one	O
Edward	B-pers
Tranter	I-pers
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
in	O
street	O
,	O
the	O
which	O
was	O
Sworn	O
against	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Servant	O
Maids	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
by	O
the	O
Testimony	O
of	O
his	O
Neighbours	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
they	O
pretended	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
stolen	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
honest	O
and	O
industrious	O
man	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Boy	O
of	O
about	O
8	O
years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
eleven	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
seven	O
shillings	O
in	O
silver	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	B-pers
s	O
Pocket	O
near	O
St.	B-place
Dunstans	I-place
Church	I-place
,	O
and	O
Convicted	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
by	O
his	O
own	O
Confession	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Scale-beam	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Custom-house	O
,	O
and	O
prosecuted	O
by	O
one	B-pers
that	O
he	O
had	O
pawned	O
it	O
to	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
Insufficient	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Randal	B-pers
Barber	I-pers
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
Stealing	O
several	O
Deal	O
Boards	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Carpenter	B-pers
s	O
Yard	O
,	O
in	O
Cook-lane	B-place
near	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
it	O
being	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
Mile-end-Green	O
Watch	O
with	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
upon	O
his	O
Back	O
(	O
though	O
he	O
pleaded	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
)	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
,	O
having	O
an	O
Indictment	O
prefer	O
'd	O
against	O
her	O
for	O
Robbery	O
Committed	O
by	O
her	O
about	O
4	O
years	O
since	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
,	O
living	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Pauls	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Confessing	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
the	O
Goods	O
(	O
consisting	O
of	O
Plate	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
worth	O
of	O
six	O
pounds	O
)	O
in	O
Ireland	O
,	O
adding	O
it	O
was	O
neither	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Plate	O
not	O
hers	O
but	O
appertained	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Hardigame	O
,	O
living	O
at	O
Chattam	O
as	O
indeed	O
it	O
did	O
prove	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
:	O
So	O
that	O
by	O
reason	O
of	O
a	O
wrong	O
Name	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Saxby	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Indictment	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
for	O
opening	O
with	O
Pick-lock	O
Keys	O
,	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
one	O
Edward	B-pers
Day	I-pers
,	O
living	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
Bashaw	I-place
,	O
and	O
then	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
entering	O
to	O
seek	O
for	O
booty	O
whilst	O
the	O
other	O
watched	O
without	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
in	O
Service	O
Time	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
people	O
were	O
gone	O
to	O
Church	O
;	O
but	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
coming	O
by	O
accidentally	O
and	O
mistrusting	O
their	O
design	O
,	O
seized	O
them	O
both	O
with	O
the	O
Picklocks	O
about	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
alledged	O
they	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
having	O
been	O
pardoned	O
for	O
Transportation	O
about	O
2	O
years	O
since	O
,	O
and	O
both	O
of	O
them	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
Notorious	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
being	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
9	O
Sheep	O
,	O
within	O
8	O
mile	O
of	O
Hartford	O
,	O
and	O
selling	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
Butcher	O
in	O
St	O
Giles	O
,	O
upon	O
full	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Convicted	O
of	O
Fellony	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Abyss	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
of	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Hawkshead	I-pers
in	O
Hartfordshire	O
.	O
The	O
Indictment	O
being	O
laid	O
only	O
as	O
a	O
Fellony	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
Plate	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
pounds	O
,	O
was	O
brought	O
out	O
of	O
Hartfordshire	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
Possession	O
of	O
those	O
to	O
whom	O
they	O
had	O
disposed	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	O
Giles	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
plain	O
and	O
positive	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
on	O
the	O
15	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
broke	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
latter	O
confessing	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
in	O
conclusion	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Luke	I-pers
a	O
Ministers	O
Wife	O
was	O
Tryed	O
upon	O
an	O
Indictment	O
for	O
Murther	O
,	O
committed	O
on	O
the	O
body	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Edmunds	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
her	O
Servant	O
,	O
caused	O
by	O
excessive	O
beating	O
,	O
the	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
about	O
the	O
20	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
which	O
time	O
he	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
15	O
of	O
May	O
and	O
then	O
dyed	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
it	O
being	O
proved	O
his	O
excessive	O
bruises	O
occasioned	O
and	O
his	O
Death	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Man-Slaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
Dickason	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Popish	O
Priest	O
,	O
who	O
pretends	O
himself	O
Chaplain	O
to	O
the	O
Portugal	O
Embassador	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
Condemn	O
'd	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
for	O
perverting	O
one	O
Martha	O
Cook	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Protestant	O
to	O
the	O
Romish	O
Religion	O
,	O
having	O
obtained	O
his	O
Majesties	O
Pardon	O
,	O
pleaded	O
the	O
same	O
upon	O
his	O
Knees	O
,	O
and	O
presented	O
the	O
Court	O
with	O
Gloves	O
as	O
is	O
usual	O
in	O
such	O
Cases	O
,	O
having	O
only	O
ten	O
days	O
allowed	O
him	O
to	O
Transport	O
himself	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
Sen.	O
And	O
one	O
Harris	B-pers
,	O
who	O
were	O
lately	O
Committed	O
to	O
Newgate	O
by	O
Order	O
of	O
Councel	O
,	O
made	O
their	O
Prayers	O
by	O
way	O
of	O
humble	O
petition	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
might	O
be	O
either	O
Bailed	O
or	O
brought	O
to	O
their	O
Tryals	O
this	O
Sessions	O
,	O
but	O
against	O
the	O
latter	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
objected	O
that	O
the	O
Kings	O
Attorney	O
General	O
was	O
not	O
ready	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
his	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
wanting	O
at	O
present	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
late	O
Scribe	O
to	O
Mother	O
Cellier	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
accused	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Dangerfield	O
for	O
speaking	O
Seditious	O
Words	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
committed	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
put	O
in	O
Bail	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
eleven	O
Condemned	O
in	O
all	O
;	O
viz	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Abbis	I-pers
,	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hewet	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Messenger	I-pers
,	O
Alice	B-pers
Enterys	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
Elinor	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Clements	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Luke	I-pers
,	O
two	O
burnt	O
in	O
the	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
to	O
be	O
whipt	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
ended	O
this	O
Session	O
.	O
