TOKEN	NE
The	O
TRYAL	O
and	O
CONDEMNATION	O
OF	O
Several	O
Notorious	O
Malefactors	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
Sessions	O
of	O
OYER	O
and	O
TERMINER	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
:	O
Beginning	O
August	O
the	O
31	O
.	O
Ending	O
September	O
the	O
1	O
.	O
1681	O
.	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
House	O
IN	O
THE	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
:	O
With	O
the	O
Names	O
of	O
those	O
that	O
receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
Transported	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
be	O
Whipt	O
.	O
Together	O
with	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
proceedings	O
against	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Earl	O
of	O
Shaftsbury	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Lord	O
Howard	O
Baron	O
of	O
Escreek	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wilmore	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Whittaker	O
,	O
all	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
the	O
Tower	O
.	O
ANN	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
,	O
a	O
notorious	O
offender	O
received	O
her	O
Tryal	O
for	O
stealing	O
several	O
parcels	O
of	O
Linnen-Cloth	O
,	O
Silk	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
vallue	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Alhollows	I-place
the	I-place
less	I-place
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
for	O
the	O
most	O
part	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
custody	O
,	O
the	O
which	O
she	O
aleadged	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
failing	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tried	O
For	O
Murdering	O
her	O
Bastard	O
Male-Infant	O
,	O
and	O
hiding	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
Desk	O
,	O
the	O
which	O
she	O
refused	O
to	O
confess	O
,	O
till	O
search	O
was	O
made	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
declared	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
bestowed	O
it	O
,	O
desiring	O
the	O
people	O
to	O
be	O
good	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
Still-born	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
not	O
calling	O
any	O
to	O
her	O
Labor	O
,	O
to	O
testify	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
King	O
James	O
,	O
which	O
there	O
was	O
read	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Murder	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Martyn	I-pers
a	O
French	O
Merchant	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
killing	O
one	O
Monsieur	B-pers
Rainbow	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
S	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
22	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
they	O
having	O
been	O
formerly	O
Dealers	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
Drinking	O
at	O
a	O
Tavern	O
,	O
fell	O
to	O
high	O
Words	O
,	O
which	O
occasioned	O
Blows	O
,	O
and	O
finally	O
the	O
Drawing	O
of	O
their	O
Swords	O
,	O
when	O
making	O
several	O
Passes	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
wounded	O
Rainbow	O
in	O
the	O
Belly	O
so	O
mortally	O
that	O
he	O
fell	O
;	O
saying	O
,	O
He	O
had	O
his	O
Deaths	O
Wound	O
;	O
at	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
seemed	O
to	O
rejoyce	O
;	O
saying	O
,	O
so	O
much	O
the	O
better	O
,	O
he	O
owed	O
him	O
something	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
speak	O
no	O
English	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
had	O
an	O
Interpreter	O
,	O
as	O
likewise	O
a	O
Jury	O
for	O
the	O
purpose	O
being	O
half	O
English	O
and	O
half	O
French	O
,	O
who	O
upon	O
hearing	O
the	O
Evidence	O
on	O
both	O
parts	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
A	O
Fellow	B-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
a	O
House	O
at	O
Acton	B-place
,	O
taking	O
thence	O
Pewter	O
and	O
Brass	O
,	O
and	O
such	O
like	O
Household	O
Goods	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
he	O
dropped	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
Close	O
adjoyning	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
done	O
in	O
the	O
Day	O
time	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Tenant	I-pers
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Stealing	O
500	O
Weight	O
of	O
Tabacco	O
,	O
valued	O
at	O
eighteen	O
pound	O
,	O
from	O
Dice	B-place
Key	I-place
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Harrington	I-pers
,	O
which	O
Felony	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
against	O
the	O
former	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Roger	B-pers
Swinney	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Studded	O
Watch	O
,	O
valued	O
at	O
three	O
pounds	O
from	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
which	O
upon	O
search	O
was	O
found	O
pawned	O
at	O
a	O
Goldsmiths	O
in	O
Holborn	O
for	O
about	O
40	O
shillings	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
another	O
party	O
,	O
that	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
now	O
produced	O
:	O
but	O
by	O
what	O
was	O
gathered	O
from	O
his	O
Confession	O
and	O
the	O
Evidences	O
own	O
Knowledg	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
;	O
having	O
been	O
once	O
before	O
condemn	O
'd	O
for	O
Murder	O
and	O
Pardoned	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Barbara	B-pers
Orchard	I-pers
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
pocket	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Chesmess	I-pers
a	O
French	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
Strand-Lane	B-place
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
picking	O
him	O
up	O
;	O
from	O
whom	O
she	O
took	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
a	O
Tobacco-box	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
money	O
:	O
But	O
it	O
being	O
committed	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
not	O
apprehended	O
till	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Stanly	I-pers
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Camsel	I-pers
were	O
tryd	O
for	O
stealing	O
about	O
5	O
pounds	O
worth	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
23	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
proved	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
some	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Lodging	O
of	O
the	O
latter	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Country	O
fellow	O
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Horse	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Edmunds	I-pers
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
valued	O
at	O
50	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
acknowledged	O
,	O
he	O
only	O
borrowed	O
to	O
lend	O
to	O
a	O
Friend	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
perswaded	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
ingenious	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
:	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
which	O
Plea	O
,	O
't	O
was	O
adjudged	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
was	O
tryd	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Ring	O
from	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Horn	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
in	O
Woodstreet	B-place
,	O
the	O
which	O
being	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
when	O
apprehended	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Toms	I-pers
was	O
try	O
'd	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Watch	O
Aug.	O
22	O
.	O
from	O
W.	B-pers
Yong	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Leonards	I-place
Foster	I-place
,	O
the	O
which	O
was	O
afterwards	O
stop	O
'd	O
at	O
a	O
Brokers	O
in	O
Hosier	O
lane	O
.	O
But	O
upon	O
hearing	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
it	O
prov	O
'd	O
That	O
another	O
whom	O
he	O
pretended	O
sent	O
him	O
to	O
pawn	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Brokers	O
shop	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
staid	O
it	O
:	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
party	O
having	O
made	O
his	O
Escape	O
.	O
Clifford	B-pers
Glasium	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Tunk	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Circumstances	O
according	O
to	O
Evidence	O
were	O
these	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
keeping	O
a	O
Cooks-Shop	O
near	O
Clarken-Well-Green	O
,	O
receiving	O
some	O
small	O
Affront	O
from	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
Constable	O
to	O
apprehend	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
following	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
pretended	O
,	O
so	O
secure	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
insisting	O
to	O
be	O
gon	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
fell	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
by	O
throwing	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
broke	O
his	O
Leg	O
short	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
content	O
with	O
that	O
,	O
continued	O
beating	O
him	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
:	O
of	O
which	O
beating	O
,	O
And	O
by	O
reason	O
of	O
the	O
Gangreening	O
of	O
his	O
leg	O
in	O
Eight	O
dayes	O
time	O
he	O
dyed	O
:	O
yet	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
no	O
small	O
Wonder	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Wats	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
a	O
Fellony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
committed	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepny	B-place
,	O
in	O
July	O
last	O
on	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Grescom	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
several	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
40	O
shilli	O
gs	O
,	O
which	O
upon	O
pursuit	O
were	O
found	O
dropped	O
in	O
a	O
Court	O
before	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
Pleading	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
a	O
Boat	O
(	O
the	O
Yard	O
facing	O
the	O
water-side	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Witness	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Drew	I-pers
received	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
White-Chappel	B-place
Stole	O
two	O
Kettles	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Crackpit	I-pers
,	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
Ten	O
Pence	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
Court	O
had	O
sate	O
about	O
two	O
hours	O
,	O
four	O
Petitions	O
were	O
humbly	O
offered	O
to	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Judges	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
sitting	O
upon	O
Commission	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
Goal-delivery	O
&	O
c.	O
viz	O
.	O
That	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Earl	B-pers
of	I-pers
Shaftsbury	I-pers
,	O
that	O
of	O
my	O
Lord	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	I-pers
Barron	I-pers
of	I-pers
Escreek	I-pers
,	O
that	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wilmore	I-pers
,	O
and	O
that	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Whittaker	I-pers
,	O
all	O
remaining	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
the	O
Tower	O
,	O
as	O
charge	O
with	O
High-Treason	O
:	O
Their	O
Prayers	O
by	O
their	O
Petitions	O
(	O
which	O
th	O
Court	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
read	O
)	O
were	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
Committed	O
Prisoners	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
continued	O
a	O
considerable	O
tim	O
without	O
any	O
prosecution	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
might	O
be	O
brought	O
by	O
Habeas	O
Corpus	O
and	O
proceeded	O
against	O
,	O
or	O
Bail	O
'd	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Act	O
made	O
and	O
provided	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
securing	O
the	O
Liberty	O
of	O
the	O
Subject	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
my	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
returned	O
answer	O
,	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Opinion	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Judges	O
,	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
done	O
,	O
the	O
Tower	O
of	O
London	O
not	O
being	O
within	O
the	O
Jurisdiction	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
they	O
must	O
referr	O
themselves	O
to	O
the	O
High-Courts	O
at	O
Westminster	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Kings-Bench	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
there	O
,	O
if	O
no	O
Prosecution	O
was	O
made	O
,	O
they	O
might	O
be	O
releived	O
by	O
Bail	O
,	O
or	O
words	O
to	O
that	O
effect	O
.	O
Three	O
Bills	O
for	O
Subornation	O
being	O
drawn	O
up	O
against	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Macnamarra	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Hayns	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
be	O
sworn	O
to	O
before	O
the	O
Grand	O
Jury	O
,	O
were	O
offered	O
to	O
the	O
consideration	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
who	O
after	O
some	O
Debate	O
ordered	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
read	O
,	O
the	O
purport	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
suborned	O
against	O
the	O
Earl	B-pers
of	I-pers
Shaftsbury	I-pers
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Council	O
in	O
the	O
Cause	O
for	O
the	O
Plaintiff	O
being	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Court	O
would	O
by	O
no	O
means	O
allow	O
they	O
should	O
be	O
presented	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
they	O
were	O
drawn	O
up	O
without	O
the	O
knowledge	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Attorney	O
General	O
,	O
saying	O
:	O
That	O
if	O
such	O
practises	O
were	O
once	O
allowed	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
prevent	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
the	O
Law	O
,	O
and	O
render	O
invalid	O
all	O
manner	O
of	O
Evidence	O
.	O
This	O
being	O
over-ruled	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Sheriff	O
Bethel	O
stood	O
up	O
and	O
acquainted	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
lately	O
received	O
an	O
Information	O
,	O
that	O
some	O
persons	O
had	O
a	O
Design	O
aginst	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
offered	O
to	O
lay	O
Wagers	O
of	O
accomplishing	O
the	O
Design	O
by	O
Christmas	O
next	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
wait	O
upon	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
Information	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
Lordship	O
was	O
pleased	O
to	O
answer	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
admit	O
of	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
in	O
private	O
,	O
for	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
in	O
that	O
nature	O
must	O
be	O
done	O
in	O
open	O
Court	O
,	O
directing	O
him	O
to	O
attend	O
upon	O
Mr.	O
Attorney	O
General	O
with	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
A	O
while	O
after	O
the	O
Grand-Jury	O
for	O
London	O
,	O
presented	O
Joanna	B-pers
Broom	I-pers
,	O
for	O
publishing	O
the	O
Weekly	O
Pamphlet	O
,	O
Intituled	O
The	O
Observator	O
,	O
and	O
Benjamen	B-pers
Took	I-pers
,	O
for	O
publishing	O
a	O
Pamphlet	O
,	O
Intituled	O
,	O
Heraclitus	O
Ridens	O
,	O
as	O
likewise	O
Mr.	O
Thomsons	O
Loyal	O
Protestant	O
Domestic	O
Intelligence	O
,	O
as	O
Pamphlets	O
designed	O
to	O
divide	O
his	O
Majesties	O
true	O
Protestant	O
Subjects	O
,	O
and	O
much	O
Reflecting	O
upon	O
the	O
Magistracy	O
of	O
this	O
Honourable	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
delivered	O
in	O
a	O
Paper	O
,	O
Expressing	O
their	O
unfeined	O
thanks	O
to	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Patience	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
Knight	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Right	O
Worshipful	O
Slingsby	B-pers
Bethel	I-pers
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Cornish	I-pers
Esqrs	O
Sheriffs	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
good	O
service	O
they	O
had	O
done	O
the	O
City	O
in	O
the	O
Execution	O
of	O
their	O
Offices	O
,	O
and	O
discharging	O
their	O
great	O
Trusts	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Loyalus	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
,	I-pers
Munson	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
Jesuits	O
that	O
have	O
lain	O
so	O
long	O
under	O
Conviction	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
having	O
obtained	O
his	O
Majesties	O
Gracious	O
Pardon	O
,	O
but	O
with	O
condition	O
to	O
depart	O
the	O
Land	O
in	O
14	O
days	O
,	O
Pleaded	O
the	O
same	O
upon	O
his	O
Knees	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
it	O
allowed	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
called	O
upon	O
to	O
give	O
Gloves	O
as	O
is	O
usual	O
in	O
such	O
Cases	O
,	O
he	O
Pleaded	O
Poverty	O
,	O
but	O
notwithstanding	O
was	O
not	O
discharged	O
out	O
of	O
Custody	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
security	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
same	O
performed	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hetherington	I-pers
having	O
been	O
Bailed	O
out	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
made	O
his	O
Prayer	O
,	O
That	O
seeing	O
no	O
Prosecution	O
was	O
made	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
fully	O
Discharged	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
done	O
by	O
Proclamation	O
.	O
At	O
this	O
Sessions	O
7	O
persons	O
received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
,	O
Roger	B-pers
Swinny	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
;	O
Ten	O
burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
Two	O
ordered	O
for	O
Transportation	O
,	O
and	O
Three	O
to	O
be	O
Whipt	O
.	O
And	O
so	O
concluded	O
this	O
remarkable	O
Sessions	O
.	O
