TOKEN	NE
THE	O
TRYALS	O
Of	O
several	O
Notorious	O
MALEFACTORS	O
.	O
TOGETHER	O
With	O
the	O
other	O
most	O
Remarkable	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Quarter-Sessions	O
OF	O
GOALE-DELIVERY	O
,	O
Holden	O
at	O
the	O
Sessions-House	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
Which	O
began	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
December	O
7	O
.	O
1681.	O
and	O
ended	O
on	O
Thursday	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Instant	O
.	O
Giving	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Proceedings	O
against	O
the	O
Earl	O
of	O
Powis	O
,	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Lady	O
Yates	O
and	O
others	O
.	O
But	O
more	O
especially	O
the	O
Proceedings	O
in	O
the	O
Case	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Harvy	O
who	O
was	O
Committed	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
.	O
Together	O
with	O
the	O
Names	O
of	O
the	O
Persons	O
Condemned	O
to	O
Dye	O
,	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
Transported	O
and	O
Whipt	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Woodbridge	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Rape	O
,	O
committed	O
on	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Paine	I-pers
,	O
who	O
lived	O
with	O
his	O
Mother	O
in	O
quality	O
of	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
the	O
Circumstances	O
as	O
they	O
appeared	O
in	O
Court	O
upon	O
Evidence	O
were	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lying	O
in	O
a	O
Chamber	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
,	O
the	O
person	O
Prosecuted	O
likewise	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
Floor	O
,	O
crept	O
through	O
a	O
Hole	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
formerly	O
made	O
in	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
and	O
surprising	O
her	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
by	O
Violence	O
obtained	O
his	O
Will	O
on	O
her	O
;	O
She	O
being	O
asked	O
,	O
Why	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
cry	O
out	O
?	O
replyed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
stopt	O
her	O
mouth	O
,	O
and	O
threatned	O
to	O
knock	O
her	O
Brains	O
out	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
by	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
,	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
rather	O
a	O
Design	O
to	O
get	O
Mony	O
,	O
then	O
otherwise	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Horatius	B-pers
Sellwood	I-pers
(	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pancras	I-place
,	O
)	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Husbands	I-pers
,	O
living	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
aforesaidon	O
the	O
29	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
both	O
Linnen	O
and	O
Woolen	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Books	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
considerable	O
value	O
,	O
having	O
formerly	O
been	O
a	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
House	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
he	O
met	O
him	O
that	O
morning	O
with	O
them	O
under	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
long	O
after	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Books	O
being	O
found	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
disposed	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
Book-seller	O
in	O
More-fields	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
give	O
a	O
satisfactory	O
Account	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
and	O
Conversation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Hood	I-pers
being	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Scarlet	O
Ribon	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
20	O
shillings	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Petty	O
Larceny	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
being	O
Indicted	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
,	O
The	O
first	O
,	O
for	O
Stealing	O
two	O
Hogs	O
from	O
Emanuel	B-pers
Clansy	I-pers
,	O
and	O
eight	O
from	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Witherell	I-pers
of	O
Hornzy	B-place
,	O
they	O
Pleaded	O
Guilty	O
to	O
those	O
and	O
all	O
others	O
within	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
the	O
Clergy	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
being	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Bowl	O
,	O
Cups	O
,	O
Pottingers	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
pieces	O
of	O
Plate	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
value	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pauls	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
;	O
it	O
was	O
long	O
before	O
he	O
would	O
Plead	O
to	O
his	O
Indictment	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
,	O
being	O
ordered	O
to	O
the	O
Press	O
,	O
he	O
Pleaded	O
Guilty	O
to	O
that	O
and	O
all	O
others	O
within	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
the	O
Clergy	O
.	O
Joan	B-pers
Low	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Stockings	O
from	O
Mris	B-pers
.	I-pers
Sellenger	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Tower	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
near	O
eight	O
years	O
since	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
supposing	O
it	O
a	O
vexatious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
Jury	O
had	O
acquitted	O
her	O
,	O
granted	O
her	O
a	O
Coppy	O
of	O
her	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
on	O
the	O
22	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
from	O
Walter	B-pers
Cotton	I-pers
;	O
the	O
circumstances	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
Sworn	O
to	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
being	O
thus	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
to	O
Drink	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
brought	O
him	O
,	O
threw	O
down	O
the	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
watching	O
his	O
opportunity	O
,	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
upon	O
this	O
Evidence	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
being	O
Indicted	O
as	O
Principals	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
her	O
Jane	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wills	I-pers
,	O
Grace	B-pers
Wills	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
as	O
Accessaries	O
before	O
and	O
after	O
to	O
a	O
Robbery	O
committed	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Minson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
;	O
from	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
in	O
Plate	O
,	O
Money	O
and	O
Cloths	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
30	O
l.	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Houses	O
of	O
those	O
that	O
wore	O
Indicted	O
as	O
Accessaries	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
being	O
proved	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
either	O
privy	O
to	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
or	O
knew	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
stole	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
only	O
the	O
Principal	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
having	O
an	O
Indictment	O
preferred	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
Robbing	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Gardiner	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
several	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
and	O
other	O
pieces	O
of	O
Plate	O
,	O
Pleaded	O
Guilty	O
to	O
his	O
Indictment	O
.	O
As	O
likewise	O
John	B-pers
Stoaks	I-pers
upon	O
an	O
Indictment	O
for	O
Stealing	O
4	O
pair	O
ofGloves	O
from	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Pursh	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
Pleaded	O
Guilty	O
to	O
that	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
within	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
his	O
Clergy	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Snowden	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
for	O
Fellony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
the	O
Circumstances	O
thus	O
,	O
he	O
in	O
the	O
Company	O
of	O
3	O
other	O
on	O
the	O
19	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
came	O
to	O
Old-Ford	B-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Parish	I-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
where	O
watching	O
their	O
opportunity	O
,	O
two	O
Houses	O
only	O
standing	O
alone	O
,	O
they	O
rushed	O
into	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
when	O
they	O
had	O
broke	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
House	O
open	O
,	O
brought	O
the	O
People	O
into	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
binding	O
them	O
altogether	O
,	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
Cole-hole	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
rifled	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Linnen	O
,	O
Plate	O
,	O
Cloths	O
,	O
Moneys	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
50	O
l.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
Swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
brought	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
other	O
House	O
to	O
be	O
bound	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
make	O
Proof	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
as	O
likewise	O
several	O
parcels	O
of	O
Goods	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Possession	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
upon	O
both	O
the	O
Indictments	O
:	O
Another	O
Indictment	O
was	O
likewise	O
exhibited	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Pauls	O
Shadwell	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
obstinately	O
refusing	O
to	O
Plead	O
,	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
the	O
Press	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Dawkins	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
in	O
Cheapside	B-place
on	O
the	O
19	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
her	O
Plea	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
her	O
Company	O
when	O
she	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
prove	O
her	O
Marriage	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Sims	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
in	O
the	O
year	O
1678	O
,	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bickering	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
took	O
away	O
several	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
Gowns	O
and	O
other	O
Cloaths	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
value	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
Convicted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Squire	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Gun	O
from	O
a	O
Gun-Smith	O
,	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Pauls	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
which	O
was	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
by	O
many	O
shrewd	O
circumstances	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	B-pers
not	O
being	O
able	O
positively	O
to	O
fix	O
it	O
home	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
took	O
her	O
Tryal	O
for	O
Robbing	O
a	O
Gentleman	B-pers
at	O
Holborn-Bars	B-place
of	O
thirteen	O
pounds	O
and	O
a	O
Ring	O
,	O
valued	O
at	O
20	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Turn	O
keys	O
of	O
the	O
Marshalsea	O
's	O
,	O
her	O
Husband	O
being	O
in	O
that	O
Prison	O
,	O
under	O
Conviction	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
upon	O
full	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
having	O
been	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Lydia	B-pers
Arlington	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Girl	O
of	O
about	O
ten	O
years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
with	O
three	B-pers
more	I-pers
supposed	O
to	O
be	O
her	O
Accomplices	O
,	O
for	O
picking	O
two	O
several	O
Pockets	O
,	O
and	O
Stealing	O
Mony	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
six	O
pounds	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
former	O
taking	O
it	O
upon	O
her	O
Self	O
having	O
(	O
past	O
doubt	O
)	O
received	O
her	O
Instructions	O
in	O
Newgate	O
)	O
she	O
was	O
only	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
acquitted	O
.	O
At	O
this	O
Sessions	O
a	O
Grand	O
Jury	O
was	O
Impanelled	O
and	O
Sworn	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
and	O
served	O
there	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Grand	O
Juries	O
of	O
London	O
were	O
wont	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
a	O
thing	O
that	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
known	O
these	O
many	O
years	O
it	O
being	O
Composed	O
of	O
17	O
substantial	O
Freeholders	O
,	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
being	O
Foreman	O
,	O
who	O
after	O
the	O
finding	O
of	O
several	O
Bills	O
for	O
Fellony	O
,	O
Burglary	O
,	O
Trespasses	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
like	O
,	O
found	O
a	O
Bill	O
against	O
Earl	B-pers
Powis	I-pers
,	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Lady	O
Yates	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
for	O
Recusancy	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
persons	O
who	O
prefered	O
the	O
Bills	O
,	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
considered	O
for	O
their	O
care	O
in	O
that	O
particular	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Harvy	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
Accused	O
of	O
HIGH-TREASON	O
by	O
one	O
Alexander	B-pers
Younger	I-pers
,	O
who	O
gave	O
Information	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
heard	O
him	O
Speak	O
many	O
Treasonable	O
Words	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
Information	O
he	O
being	O
Committed	O
to	O
the	O
County	O
Goal	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
he	O
Petitioned	O
the	O
Court	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
his	O
being	O
Bail	O
'd	O
,	O
if	O
no	O
Prosecution	O
was	O
made	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
the	O
Court	O
was	O
pleased	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
They	O
took	O
Notice	O
of	O
his	O
Petition	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
,	O
sent	O
to	O
know	O
,	O
Whether	O
Mr	O
Attorny	O
General	O
designed	O
to	O
make	O
any	O
Prosecution	O
?	O
upon	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Ward	B-pers
Clerk	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Crown	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
Acquainted	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Attorny	O
was	O
Content	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
Released	O
from	O
his	O
Confinement	O
upon	O
goodsubstantial	O
Bail	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
Intended	O
to	O
prosecute	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Kings-Bench-Bar	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
Term	O
.	O
Proclamation	O
was	O
made	O
in	O
open	O
Court	O
for	O
about	O
fifty	O
persons	O
,	O
who	O
stood	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Recusancy	O
,	O
to	O
deliver	O
up	O
their	O
Bodies	O
to	O
the	O
Custody	O
of	O
the	O
Sheriff	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
,	O
Process	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
out	O
against	O
their	O
Lands	O
and	O
Tenements	O
,	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
Act	O
against	O
Recusancy	O
is	O
more	O
fully	O
expressed	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Challenor	I-pers
,	O
who	O
last	O
Sessions	O
pleaded	O
his	O
Pardon	O
for	O
Killing	O
a	O
Coachman	O
in	O
Salisbury	O
Court	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
some	O
defect	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
returned	O
to	O
pass	O
the	O
Seal	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
done	O
,	O
he	O
Pleaded	O
it	O
this	O
Sessions	O
upon	O
his	O
Knees	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
Prosecution	O
against	O
Mr.	O
Harvy	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Inlarged	O
upon	O
his	O
giving	O
in	O
Bail	O
to	O
appear	O
the	O
first	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
Term	O
,	O
himself	O
being	O
bound	O
in	O
a	O
thousand	O
pound	O
Bond	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
four	O
Security	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sands	I-pers
,	O
Guidian	B-pers
Harvy	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Parry	I-pers
,	O
bound	O
severally	O
in	O
Obligations	O
of	O
five	O
hundred	O
pound	O
a	O
peice	O
.	O
This	O
Sessions	O
a	O
general	O
Pardon	O
was	O
Pleaded	O
,	O
their	O
being	O
about	O
46	O
Persons	O
,	O
Men	O
and	O
Women	O
,	O
Included	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Six	O
persons	O
received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Sims	I-pers
,	O
Horatius	O
Cellwood	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Snowden	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
,	O
as	O
likewise	O
Mary	O
Clark	O
,	O
Reprieved	O
before	O
Judgment	O
.	O
Eight	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Two	O
to	O
be	O
Whipt	O
.	O
And	O
so	O
Concluded	O
this	O
Remarkable	O
Sessions	O
.	O
