TOKEN	NE
THE	O
True	O
Relation	O
OF	O
THE	O
TRYALS	O
At	O
the	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
Held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
and	O
Goale	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
which	O
began	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
January	O
,	O
and	O
ended	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
As	O
particularly	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wigenton	I-pers
FOR	O
Whipping	O
a	O
Girl	O
to	O
Death	O
at	O
Ratcliffe	O
.	O
And	O
John	B-pers
Peetly	I-pers
,	O
for	O
shooting	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
Queen-street	O
.	O
Also	O
the	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Proceedings	O
with	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Bully	I-pers
a	O
Popish	O
Priest	O
.	O
The	O
Number	O
of	O
the	O
Condemned	O
,	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
be	O
Whipped	O
,	O
with	O
many	O
other	O
material	O
Tryals	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
began	O
at	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
,	O
on	O
Monday	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
January	O
,	O
(	O
being	O
put	O
off	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
before	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
of	O
the	O
sitting	O
at	O
Guildhal	O
)	O
where	O
were	O
these	O
following	O
proceedings	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wigenton	I-pers
of	O
Ratcliff	B-place
Parish	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
a	O
Girl	B-pers
about	O
Thirteen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
her	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
the	O
manner	O
of	O
the	O
Murder	O
being	O
thus	O
:	O
She	O
being	O
by	O
Trade	O
a	O
Coat-maker	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
set	O
the	O
Girl	O
upon	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Work	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
done	O
it	O
so	O
well	O
as	O
she	O
required	O
,	O
whereupon	O
,	O
she	O
beat	O
her	O
grievously	O
,	O
the	O
which	O
not	O
sufficing	O
her	O
cruel	O
rage	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
bundle	O
of	O
rods	O
,	O
(	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
to	O
hold	O
her	O
)	O
with	O
which	O
,	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
bound	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
whiped	O
her	O
so	O
unmercifully	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
blood	O
ran	O
down	O
like	O
rain	O
;	O
yet	O
could	O
she	O
not	O
be	O
perswaded	O
to	O
desist	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
Girl	O
fainted	O
away	O
with	O
crying	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
her	O
unmerciful	O
usage	O
in	O
a	O
short	O
time	O
dyed	O
.	O
Upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
she	O
pleaded	O
little	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
defence	O
,	O
onely	O
saying	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
to	O
kill	O
her	O
.	O
So	O
that	O
it	O
being	O
proved	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
cruel	O
Woman	O
by	O
all	O
her	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
wilful	O
Murther	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Katherine	B-pers
Neale	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
about	O
Twenty	O
yards	O
of	O
Persian	O
Silk	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Mercer	B-pers
s	O
shop	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
taken	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Yong	I-pers
was	O
like	O
wise	O
found	O
guilty	O
for	O
stealing	O
Linnen	O
from	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	B-pers
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
nine	O
shillings	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
,	O
a	O
notorious	O
Shop-lift	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Will	B-pers
.	I-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Botolfes	B-place
without	I-place
Bishops-gate	I-place
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
eight	O
shillings	O
and	O
six	O
pence	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Telcoat	I-pers
received	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
being	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
an	O
aged	O
woman	B-pers
;	O
but	O
upon	O
Evidence	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
woman	O
being	O
troubled	O
with	O
Fits	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
hit	O
her	O
head	O
upon	O
an	O
Iron	O
,	O
which	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
wound	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
dyed	O
:	O
so	O
that	O
his	O
being	O
there	O
,	O
caused	O
this	O
Indictment	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
proof	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
near	O
her	O
when	O
she	O
fell	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Peetly	I-pers
Victualler	O
,	O
living	O
in	O
Whetstones-park	B-place
was	O
Arrained	O
and	O
Tryed	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Gerard	I-pers
,	O
Nephew	O
,	O
as	O
't	O
is	O
said	O
,	O
to	O
my	O
Lord	O
Gerard	O
;	O
the	O
circumstances	O
of	O
which	O
,	O
were	O
these	O
:	O
The	O
Party	O
killed	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
other	O
young	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
being	O
late	O
abroad	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
tenth	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
took	O
it	O
in	O
their	O
way	O
to	O
come	O
through	O
Whetstones	O
park	O
,	O
where	O
spying	O
Lights	O
in	O
Peetly	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
they	O
knocked	O
hard	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
open	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
which	O
he	O
refusing	O
,	O
one	O
or	O
more	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
began	O
to	O
break	O
the	O
windows	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
Linkmen	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
threw	O
up	O
lighted	O
Links	O
,	O
the	O
which	O
,	O
as	O
Peetly	O
said	O
,	O
did	O
set	O
fire	O
to	O
some	O
Linnen	O
in	O
a	O
Closet	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
he	O
being	O
Allarumed	O
,	O
got	O
his	O
Carbine	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
charged	O
with	O
small	O
Bullets	O
,	O
and	O
pursued	O
them	O
up	O
great	B-place
Queen-street	I-place
,	O
till	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
upper	O
end	O
o	O
n't	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
standing	O
Watch	O
had	O
stayed	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
caused	O
them	O
to	O
deliver	O
their	O
Swords	O
,	O
whenas	O
Peetly	O
thrusting	O
among	O
the	O
croud	O
,	O
was	O
pushed	O
by	O
a	O
Watchman	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
his	O
piece	O
went	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
shot	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
the	O
Thigh	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Wound	O
he	O
shortly	O
dyed	O
:	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pleading	O
that	O
the	O
Gun	O
went	O
off	O
without	O
his	O
knowledge	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Ditcher	I-pers
,	O
received	O
her	O
Tryal	O
for	O
stealing	O
forty	O
yards	O
of	O
Serge	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Campaigne	O
Coat	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Hatton	I-pers
in	O
Drury-lane	B-place
;	O
the	O
Discovery	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
by	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
,	O
who	O
being	O
taken	O
upon	O
suspition	O
for	O
hankering	O
about	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
confessed	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
where	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
carry	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
sold	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
being	O
at	O
a	O
Brokers	O
in	O
Southwark	O
.	O
The	O
Broaker	O
being	O
questioned	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
brought	O
out	O
the	O
woman	O
.	O
Upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
she	O
pleaded	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
produced	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
;	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
drawing	O
up	O
the	O
Latch	O
,	O
entred	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
one	O
Magdalen	B-pers
Wooff	I-pers
,	O
and	O
coming	O
to	O
her	O
bed-side	O
,	O
took	O
away	O
her	O
purse	O
with	O
eleven	O
shillings	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
departed	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
daring	O
to	O
hinder	O
her	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
her	O
life	O
;	O
they	O
gave	O
very	O
bad	O
Characters	O
of	O
each	O
other	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
railed	O
at	O
a	O
high	O
rate	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
fine	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Boys	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
a	O
Cravat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
;	O
the	O
which	O
being	O
confessed	O
by	O
him	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stollen	O
from	O
one	O
Edward	B-pers
Steevens	I-pers
of	O
Hounslow	B-place
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
ten	O
pence	O
.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Mathews	I-pers
,	O
an	O
old	O
Shop-lift	O
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
about	O
a	O
pound	O
and	O
half	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
and	O
near	O
sixty	O
yards	O
of	O
Taffeta	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
and	O
Ferrit	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Waite	I-pers
in	O
Holborn	B-place
.	O
She	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
onely	O
a	O
little	O
Girl	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
demanded	O
where	O
her	O
Mistress	O
was	O
?	O
who	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
into	O
London	O
;	O
whereupon	O
,	O
she	O
desired	O
to	O
see	O
some	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Girl	O
shewed	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
would	O
please	O
,	O
till	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
box	O
of	O
Ribbon	O
set	O
before	O
her	O
,	O
whenas	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
Accomplices	O
coming	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
desiring	O
to	O
see	O
some	O
likewise	O
,	O
held	O
the	O
Girl	O
busie	O
,	O
till	O
she	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
aforesaid	O
;	O
but	O
ere	O
she	O
could	O
make	O
her	O
escape	O
,	O
being	O
apprehended	O
and	O
carried	O
before	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
about	O
her	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
proof	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Convicted	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Cockman	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
as	O
being	O
accessary	O
to	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
Smith	B-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
shot	O
by	O
one	O
Orme	O
,	O
since	O
flead	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
a	O
Watch	O
which	O
appertained	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
custody	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
alleadging	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
pocket	O
of	O
the	O
dead	O
man	O
,	O
whose	O
breeches	O
she	O
had	O
to	O
wash	O
,	O
delivered	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
his	O
friends	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Jobe	B-pers
Laud	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Mare	O
,	O
appertaining	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Gun	I-pers
,	O
the	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
afterwards	O
sold	O
to	O
one	O
Church	O
,	O
the	O
bargain	O
being	O
made	O
at	O
the	O
George	O
in	O
Leather-lane	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Church	O
being	O
taken	O
upon	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
riding	O
into	O
the	O
Countrey	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
this	O
Tryal	O
,	O
the	O
party	O
from	O
whom	O
she	O
was	O
stole	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Fellony	O
.	O
Frances	B-pers
Emington	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
about	O
600	O
weight	O
of	O
Red-wood	O
from	O
the	O
Royal	B-pers
African	I-pers
Company	I-pers
,	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
Lighter	O
,	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
River	O
of	O
Thames	B-place
,	O
the	O
Hatches	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Lighter	O
being	O
broken	O
open	O
in	O
the	O
absence	O
of	O
the	O
Waiters	O
.	O
The	O
wood	O
being	O
taken	O
about	O
a	O
Month	O
after	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
conveying	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
Porters	O
into	O
Thames	O
street	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
pretended	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
dry	O
Salter	O
;	O
and	O
did	O
so	O
far	O
impose	O
upon	O
his	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
lodge	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
gone	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
Fellony	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
Blanch	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
a	O
servant-wench	O
was	O
Tryed	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
,	O
for	O
Robbing	O
her	O
Master	O
William	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
fields	I-place
,	O
of	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
Ten	O
pounds	O
,	O
which	O
his	O
Wife	O
had	O
hid	O
between	O
the	O
Mat	O
and	O
the	O
bed	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
making	O
the	O
bed	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
converted	O
about	O
three	O
pounds	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
own	O
use	O
,	O
before	O
they	O
missed	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
being	O
apprehended	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
delivered	O
the	O
other	O
moiety	O
.	O
Her	O
plea	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
imagined	O
it	O
was	O
lawfully	O
hers	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
weak	O
excuse	O
did	O
not	O
serve	O
her	O
turn	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Underthorp	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
having	O
Two	O
Wives	O
,	O
vix	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Toogood	I-pers
,	O
whom	O
he	O
Marryed	O
at	O
Dukes-place	O
;	O
and	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
which	O
he	O
since	O
Marryed	O
in	O
Worcestershire	O
,	O
with	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
competent	O
Portion	O
.	O
Both	O
the	O
Marriages	O
were	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
by	O
several	O
persons	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
by	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
gave	O
him	O
in	O
Marriage	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
several	O
others	O
,	O
the	O
latter	O
by	O
the	O
Woman	O
herself	O
,	O
who	O
appeared	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
proof	O
she	O
was	O
alive	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Convicted	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
two	O
Chair-men	O
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Washborn	I-pers
,	O
whom	O
they	O
killed	O
with	O
excessive	O
beating	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
second	O
of	O
December	O
;	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
quarrel	O
was	O
their	O
rushing	O
him	O
with	O
their	O
empty	O
Chair	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
rails	O
of	O
Northumberland-house	O
;	O
near	O
Charing-cross	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
striking	O
them	O
with	O
his	O
Cane	O
,	O
they	O
fell	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
so	O
many	O
bruises	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
dyed	O
within	O
twelve	O
days	O
after	O
:	O
wherefore	O
they	O
were	O
Convicted	O
of	O
Man-slaughter	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
proof	O
that	O
he	O
struck	O
them	O
first	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Oliver	I-pers
,	O
a	O
French-man	O
,	O
who	O
could	O
speak	O
no	O
English	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
into	O
a	O
Chamber	O
,	O
at	O
Man	O
's	O
Coffee-house	O
at	O
Charing-cross	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Ring	O
,	O
some	O
Lace	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
small	O
matters	O
:	O
he	O
pretended	O
,	O
as	O
his	O
Interpreters	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
there	O
only	O
to	O
sleep	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
searched	O
,	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
the	O
Constables	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
not	O
guilty	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
none	O
gave	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
or	O
saw	O
the	O
things	O
taken	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bully	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Popish	O
Priest	O
,	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Barr	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Indictment	O
read	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
Tried	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Fact	O
at	O
Lancaster	O
,	O
in	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
ought	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
Tryed	O
twice	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
But	O
in	O
that	O
the	O
Opinion	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
over-ruled	O
him	O
,	O
intimating	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
Indictment	O
being	O
laid	O
for	O
his	O
being	O
a	O
Priest	O
,	O
in	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
since	O
the	O
former	O
have	O
taken	O
Orders	O
from	O
the	O
See	O
of	O
Rome	O
.	O
Whereupon	O
he	O
had	O
directionto	O
get	O
Council	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
in	O
his	O
Plea	O
,	O
and	O
Time	O
allowed	O
him	O
for	O
that	O
purpose	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
long	O
Apology	O
,	O
alleadged	O
as	O
before	O
:	O
So	O
that	O
at	O
his	O
humble	O
Request	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
thought	O
sit	O
to	O
continue	O
him	O
untried	O
till	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
The	O
Countess	O
of	O
Portland	O
being	O
brought	O
into	O
Court	O
in	O
her	O
Sedan	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
sick	O
,	O
desired	O
to	O
Traverse	O
her	O
Indictment	O
for	O
Recusancy	O
,	O
the	O
which	O
was	O
allowed	O
.	O
At	O
this	O
Sessions	O
there	O
were	O
Nine	O
Persons	O
that	O
received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
;	O
viz	O
.	O
Katharine	O
Nevil	O
,	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Wiginton	I-pers
,	O
Anne	B-pers
Dicher	I-pers
,	O
Anne	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Mathews	I-pers
,	O
Blanch	O
Thomas	O
,	O
Philip	B-pers
Demerry	I-pers
,	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Wicks	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
.	O
Ten	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
And	O
Five	O
to	O
be	O
Whipped	O
.	O
