TOKEN	NE
THE	O
TRYALS	O
OF	O
THE	O
PRISONERS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions-House	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
,	O
Which	O
began	O
there	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
September	O
,	O
and	O
ended	O
on	O
Thursday	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
But	O
more	O
remarkably	O
of	O
the	O
Pewterer	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Killing	O
the	O
Boy	O
in	O
Walbrook	O
.	O
Together	O
with	O
the	O
Bailiffs	O
Tryals	O
for	O
Killing	O
a	O
Man	O
upon	O
an	O
Arrest	O
.	O
As	O
likewise	O
the	O
Account	O
of	O
those	O
Condemned	O
,	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
be	O
Whipt	O
;	O
with	O
many	O
other	O
Remarkable	O
Passages	O
.	O
September	O
6	O
.	O
This	O
Day	O
the	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
London	O
and	O
Middlesex	O
began	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
these	O
sequent	O
.	O
ANN	B-pers
Parkinson	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Sarah	B-pers
Puzny	I-pers
of	O
several	O
pieces	O
of	O
Plate	O
,	O
a	O
Mantua	O
Gown	O
,	O
pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
considerable	O
quantity	O
of	O
Silver	O
Coin	O
,	O
all	O
amounting	O
to	O
upwards	O
of	O
50	O
pounds	O
;	O
a	O
great	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Custody	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
such	O
places	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
evident	O
thet	O
she	O
Confessed	O
the	O
Robbery	O
since	O
her	O
Imprisonment	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
though	O
she	O
pleaded	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
given	O
her	O
to	O
sell	O
by	O
a	O
Woman	O
that	O
owed	O
her	O
Money	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Clifford	I-pers
received	O
his	O
Tryal	O
for	O
taking	O
a	O
Queen	O
Elizabeth	O
Piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Paine	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Person	O
who	O
came	O
to	O
lodg	O
at	O
an	O
Inn	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
under-Ostler	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
disposed	O
of	O
to	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
for	O
25	O
Shillings	O
,	O
at	O
first	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
said	O
hefound	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
availed	O
him	O
nothing	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Trebarford	I-pers
upon	O
his	O
Arraignment	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Tankard	O
,	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
at	O
10	O
l.	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
an	O
old	O
,	O
Offender	O
,	O
once	O
burnt	O
in	O
the	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
once	O
pardoned	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Hodges	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Sares	I-pers
at	O
Elin	B-place
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
Linnen	O
and	O
Woollen	O
,	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
Puter	O
,	O
Curtains	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
of	O
worth	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
being	O
pursued	O
on	O
their	O
way	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
overtaken	O
,	O
one	O
with	O
the	O
bundle	O
upon	O
his	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
accompanying	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
asked	O
what	O
they	O
could	O
say	O
for	O
themselves	O
,	O
Rogers	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
accidentally	O
overtook	O
the	O
other	O
not	O
knowing	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
said	O
that	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
him	O
by	O
a	O
strange	O
man	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
Brainford	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
6	O
d.	O
but	O
being	O
both	O
trapp	O
'd	O
in	O
their	O
Tails	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
Convicted	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Martin	B-pers
Aubery	I-pers
being	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
Arraigned	O
,	O
robbing	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
Napkins	O
,	O
Curtains	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
ingeniously	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Neve	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Horse	O
and	O
Mare	O
from	O
two	O
Persons	O
at	O
Beudly	B-place
in	I-place
Glocestershire	I-place
,	O
which	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
another	O
Person	O
who	O
is	O
since	O
dead	O
in	O
Prison	O
,	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Black-Lyon	O
Inn	O
in	O
Water-Lane	O
,	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Ostler	B-pers
owned	O
the	O
Horse	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
,	O
though	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
he	O
absolutely	O
denyed	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
travelling	O
for	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Person	O
deceased	O
overtook	O
him	O
near	O
Henly	O
,	O
riding	O
on	O
the	O
Mare	O
,	O
and	O
leading	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
for	O
two	O
Shillings	O
bargained	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
ride	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
would	O
not	O
believe	O
his	O
apology	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Jeffrey	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
robbing	O
John	B-pers
Fann	I-pers
of	O
Hornzey	B-place
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
Iron	O
and	O
Cloath	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
confessed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
whole	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Dakins	I-pers
,	I-pers
Alias	I-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
having	O
two	O
Husbands	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Wilson	B-pers
,	O
and	O
Hambleton	B-pers
,	O
the	O
former	O
being	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
latter	O
not	O
appearing	O
to	O
Wilson	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
declared	O
she	O
was	O
first	O
Married	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
about	O
7	O
years	O
since	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
to	O
the	O
latter	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
Married	O
above	O
a	O
year	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
being	O
asked	O
what	O
she	O
could	O
say	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
utterly	O
disowned	O
the	O
latter	O
Marriage	O
,	O
saying	O
her	O
Husband	O
prosecuted	O
maliciously	O
on	O
purpose	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
her	O
Life	O
to	O
espouse	O
one	O
he	O
loved	O
better	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
other-side	O
produced	O
her	O
Examination	O
,	O
taken	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
of	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
confessed	O
both	O
Marriages	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
utterly	O
denied	O
it	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
Jury	O
upon	O
hearing	O
both	O
Parties	O
,	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Simon	B-pers
Beale	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
picking	O
two	O
pockets	O
on	O
Ship-board	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
of	O
one	O
shilling	O
nine	O
pence	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
pleaded	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Mony	O
upon	O
the	O
Deck	O
,	O
but	O
appearing	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
business	O
on	O
Board	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
he	O
fled	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
Soo	O
Cony	O
Skins	O
from	O
Andrew	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
on	O
the	O
16	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Andrew	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
absence	O
ticed	O
a	O
youth	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
intrusted	O
there	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
come	O
in	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
at	O
first	O
refused	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
tempted	O
with	O
some	O
Mony	O
she	O
gave	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
at	O
last	O
consented	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
dusk	O
of	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
she	O
packed	O
up	O
the	O
skins	O
in	O
a	O
Bag	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
several	O
of	O
her	O
Neighbours	O
likewise	O
gave	O
testimony	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
naughty	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
inticed	O
Children	O
oft	O
to	O
Rob	O
their	O
Parents	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
utterly	O
denying	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
she	O
stood	O
Indicted	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
proof	O
but	O
the	O
Youths	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
in	O
all	O
likelyhood	O
her	O
Confederate	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gascone	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
for	O
stealing	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
of	O
considerable	O
value	O
on	O
the	O
second	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
several	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
alledged	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
nor	O
prove	O
of	O
whom	O
he	O
bought	O
'um	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
upon	O
consideration	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
circumstances	O
and	O
positive	O
evidence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
How	I-pers
being	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
of	O
good	O
worth	O
,	O
upon	O
his	O
being	O
ordered	O
to	O
plead	O
to	O
his	O
Indictment	O
,	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
two	O
Lytermen	O
,	O
were	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
as	O
much	O
silk	O
as	O
came	O
to	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Bale	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
stowing	O
in	O
their	O
Lyter	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
they	O
returned	O
answer	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
no	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
upon	O
turning	O
the	O
Bale	O
,	O
it	O
dropped	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
their	O
Breeches	O
only	O
to	O
secure	O
it	O
whilst	O
they	O
had	O
done	O
work	O
,	O
intending	O
then	O
to	O
return	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
apparent	O
that	O
they	O
concealed	O
it	O
upon	O
inquiry	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
convicted	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Anbry	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
Silks	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
to	O
a	O
great	O
worth	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
sold	O
in	O
Long-lane	O
,	O
&	O
;	O
other	O
places	O
,	O
&	O
being	O
known	O
a	O
notorious	O
Shoplift	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
A	O
Woman	B-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Marrying	O
a	O
second	B-pers
Husband	I-pers
during	O
the	O
Life	O
of	O
her	O
first	B-pers
,	O
but	O
only	O
the	O
first	O
Marriage	O
appearing	O
on	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
neither	O
Minister	O
nor	O
Sexton	O
being	O
there	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
second	O
,	O
although	O
it	O
was	O
alledged	O
to	O
be	O
contracted	O
at	O
St.	O
Catherines	O
Church	O
by	O
the	O
Tower	O
,	O
she	O
denying	O
any	O
Husband	O
but	O
he	O
that	O
prosecuted	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
being	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
valued	O
at	O
3	O
pounds	O
,	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
;	O
there	O
also	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Indictment	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Lacy	I-pers
,	O
but	O
upon	O
his	O
pleading	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
unknown	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
going	O
down	O
stairs	O
to	O
have	O
it	O
filled	O
again	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Fardinando	B-pers
Hews	I-pers
,	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ways	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Clipping	O
of	O
the	O
Lawful	O
and	O
currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
it	O
appearing	O
upon	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
latter	O
had	O
often	O
dealt	O
with	O
the	O
Witness	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Saltars	O
Man	O
)	O
for	O
broad	O
Monies	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
in	O
Exchange	O
21	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
of	O
Clipped	O
Money	O
for	O
20	O
s.	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
but	O
a	O
single	O
evidence	O
,	O
which	O
in	O
case	O
of	O
Treason	O
can	O
not	O
attaint	O
any	O
person	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stocdale	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
and	O
found	O
Guilty	O
for	O
taking	O
a	O
Box	O
of	O
Cloaths	O
from	O
a	O
Boy	B-pers
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bartholomew	I-place
the	I-place
Great	I-place
,	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
helping	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Felony	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ralph	B-pers
Saunderson	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Tankard	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Wheatly	I-pers
in	O
Holbourn	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
coming	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
took	O
his	O
opportunity	O
to	O
set	O
down	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Tankard	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
the	O
Silver	O
one	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
being	O
taken	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
his	O
Tryal	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Finamo	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Pancas	I-pers
,	I-pers
and	I-pers
Mary	I-pers
his	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	O
his	O
Wife	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Fenn	I-pers
,	O
whom	O
for	O
being	O
a	O
Marshals	O
Officer	O
,	O
having	O
arrested	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
seeming	O
unwilling	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
all	O
fell	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
throwing	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
bruised	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
for	O
several	O
weeks	O
he	O
spit	O
blood	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
upon	O
the	O
Tryal	O
Pancas	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
,	O
&	O
Finamo	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Farrel	I-pers
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Hunly	I-pers
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Murthering	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Price	I-pers
a	O
Brickmaker	O
at	O
Hammersmith	O
about	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
Month	O
,	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
this	O
,	O
The	O
two	O
Persons	O
Tryed	O
came	O
into	O
a	O
Victualling	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
a	O
pack	O
of	O
Cards	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
latter	O
was	O
refused	O
them	O
,	O
whereupon	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
pack	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
next	O
Room	O
,	O
where	O
several	O
Persons	O
were	O
drinking	O
,	O
and	O
invited	O
them	O
to	O
play	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
invitation	O
some	O
accepted	O
of	O
,	O
which	O
number	O
the	O
party	O
killed	O
was	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
some	O
time	O
playing	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Countrymen	O
told	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
they	O
wereCheats	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
the	O
Cards	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
themselves	O
,	O
which	O
so	O
iracitated	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
drew	O
their	O
Swords	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
several	O
passes	O
,	O
amongst	O
which	O
one	O
made	O
by	O
Farrel	O
entered	O
10	O
Inches	O
into	O
the	O
body	O
of	O
Price	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
wound	O
he	O
then	O
and	O
there	O
instantly	O
died	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
excuse	O
themselves	O
by	O
laying	O
it	O
upon	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
pleading	O
no	O
Malice	O
,	O
fore	O
thought	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
attended	O
with	O
such	O
evil	O
circumstances	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
them	O
in	O
both	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Wilful	O
Murther	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
White	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Hull	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Clemants	O
Danes	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
away	O
Puter	O
,	O
Brass	O
,	O
and	O
such	O
like	O
Houshold	O
Goods	O
to	O
a	O
good	O
value	O
,	O
many	O
of	O
them	O
as	O
by	O
Evidence	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
being	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
,	O
or	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
disposed	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Catharine	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Finch	B-pers
her	O
Brother-in-Law	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
things	O
of	O
great	O
value	O
specified	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
only	O
two	O
Puter	O
Porringers	O
being	O
proved	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Custody	O
,	O
and	O
those	O
she	O
alledged	O
her	O
Sister	O
in	O
her	O
life	O
time	O
gave	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
bringing	O
proof	O
of	O
her	O
reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Jaxson	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
robbing	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
St.	O
Dunstans	O
in	O
the	O
East	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
away	O
Gowns	O
,	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
pieces	O
of	O
Plate	O
,	O
Spoons	O
,	O
Porrengers	O
,	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
doing	O
the	O
Robbery	O
in	O
her	O
Masters	O
absence	O
.	O
Ralph	B-pers
.	I-pers
Bentum	I-pers
the	O
Pewterer	O
in	O
Walbrook	O
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
killing	O
Andrew	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
a	O
Joyners	O
Boy	O
,	O
the	O
substance	O
of	O
the	O
Tryal	O
as	O
the	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Lad	O
in	O
the	O
company	O
of	O
some	O
others	O
came	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
the	O
wood	O
designed	O
for	O
a	O
Bonfire	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
Assaulting	O
those	O
that	O
kept	O
it	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Bentum	O
came	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
Staff	O
,	O
and	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
disperse	O
them	O
,	O
when	O
amongst	O
the	O
rest	O
he	O
struck	O
this	O
Williams	O
over	O
the	O
head	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
two	O
wounds	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
wounds	O
being	O
heal	O
'd	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
returning	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
fell	O
sick	O
of	O
a	O
malignant	O
Feavour	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
on	O
the	O
28	O
of	O
August	O
he	O
died	O
,	O
several	O
able	O
Physicians	O
and	O
Chyrurgions	O
were	O
examined	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
affirmed	O
that	O
the	O
Feavour	O
was	O
occasioned	O
by	O
the	O
wounds	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
each	O
producing	O
the	O
reasons	O
that	O
induced	O
them	O
to	O
such	O
their	O
belief	O
,	O
when	O
as	O
the	O
Jury	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
upon	O
their	O
return	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Poltney	I-pers
pleaded	O
his	O
Pardon	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
it	O
allowed	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
Tryed	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
for	O
killing	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Howard	O
in	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
Square	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
Tryal	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
it	O
in	O
se	O
defendendo	O
.	O
A	O
Motion	O
was	O
made	O
by	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
Richard	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
Prisoner	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
for	O
being	O
Active	O
in	O
the	O
late	O
Scotch	O
Rebellion	O
,	O
might	O
not	O
be	O
tryed	O
at	O
this	O
Sessions	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
intended	O
that	O
he	O
shall	O
be	O
sent	O
for	O
Scotland	O
,	O
there	O
to	O
be	O
tryed	O
.	O
At	O
this	O
Sessions	O
were	O
nine	O
Persons	O
who	O
received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Farrel	I-pers
,	O
Rob	B-pers
.	I-pers
Hurling	I-pers
,	O
Pet	B-pers
.	I-pers
Hodges	I-pers
,	O
Rob	B-pers
.	I-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Wolley	I-pers
,	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Stocdale	I-pers
,	O
Hester	O
Vareright	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Pancus	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Parkason	I-pers
;	O
10	O
burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
4	O
to	O
be	O
Whipp	O
'd	O
.	O
And	O
so	O
ended	O
the	O
Sessions	O
.	O
