TOKEN	NE
AT	O
THE	O
SESSIONS	O
That	O
Begun	O
at	O
the	O
Sessions-house	O
IN	O
THE	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
,	O
On	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
Ended	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
Take	O
the	O
Account	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Stealing	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
9	O
Shillings	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Ashton	I-pers
in	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
April	O
which	O
were	O
afterwards	O
found	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
he	O
utterly	O
denyed	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
affirming	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
at	O
that	O
place	O
,	O
nor	O
knew	O
not	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
party	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
sold	O
them	O
,	O
attesting	O
that	O
he	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
received	O
Money	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Welling	I-pers
a	O
stripling	O
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	B-pers
in	O
Hony-Lane	B-place
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
proved	O
thus	O
,	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
lost	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
being	O
upon	O
search	O
of	O
the	O
Thief	O
,	O
a	O
woman	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
her	O
pocket	O
was	O
not	O
Pickt	O
,	O
telling	O
her	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
such	O
a	O
Boy	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
:	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
Boy	O
being	O
apprehended	O
,	O
declared	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
2	O
Boys	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
his	O
Company	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
which	O
he	O
likewise	O
urged	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
plain	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Sims	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Jameses	I-place
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
taking	O
thence	O
Sheets	O
,	O
Table-Linnen	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
12	O
pounds	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
sold	O
at	O
a	O
Brokers	O
in	O
Long-Acre	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
there	O
being	O
positive	O
proof	O
made	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Hanison	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
a	O
Shop	O
in	O
Leaden-Hall-Street	B-place
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
Ribons	O
,	O
Gloves	O
,	O
and	O
Linnen	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
value	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
things	O
not	O
being	O
found	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
as	O
't	O
is	O
supposed	O
,	O
having	O
conveyed	O
them	O
away	O
by	O
a	O
second	O
Person	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
not	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Spittle	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Tryer	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Jameses	I-place
Clarkenwell	I-place
on	O
the	O
20	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
Grates	O
,	O
Kettles	O
,	O
Pots	O
,	O
and	O
Pewter	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
proved	O
thus	O
,	O
That	O
a	O
Drayman	O
coming	O
over	O
Clarkenwell-green	O
,	O
perceiving	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Fellows	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
some	O
what	O
suspicious	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
Fellows	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
refusing	O
to	O
assist	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
meeting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Grates	O
upon	O
his	O
back	O
,	O
stopp	O
'd	O
him	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
the	O
custody	O
of	O
a	O
Constable	O
;	O
but	O
in	O
Court	O
he	O
pleaded	O
that	O
the	O
Grates	O
were	O
delivered	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
within	O
Forty	O
yards	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
that	O
was	O
broken	O
open	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Hinx	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Kingborne	I-pers
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
not	O
Guilty	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Evidence	O
were	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
first	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
Wife	O
to	O
the	O
party	O
in	O
whose	O
name	O
the	O
Indictment	O
was	O
laid	O
,	O
Swore	O
that	O
whilst	O
she	O
was	O
absent	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
tookthe	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
House	O
:	O
but	O
the	O
Constable	O
being	O
produced	O
that	O
went	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
Swore	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
formerly	O
taken	O
them	O
by	O
her	O
order	O
to	O
secure	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
Seisure	O
of	O
the	O
Landlord	O
:	O
So	O
that	O
it	O
being	O
Evident	O
that	O
the	O
Case	O
had	O
been	O
depending	O
above	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
looked	O
upon	O
as	O
a	O
Malitious	O
Persecution	O
,	O
thereupon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
cleared	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Cuerton	I-pers
was	O
brought	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
for	O
an	O
Accessary	O
to	O
a	O
Robbery	O
Committed	O
by	O
one	O
Ann	B-pers
Stubs	I-pers
Convicted	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
;	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
bought	O
Goods	O
of	O
her	O
that	O
were	O
stollen	O
from	O
Captain	B-pers
Faisby	I-pers
,	O
she	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
:	O
but	O
she	O
pleading	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
positive	O
proof	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Tobacco-box	O
and	O
Watch	O
from	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Vox	I-pers
,	O
taking	O
it	O
privily	O
from	O
his	O
Person	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
tampering	O
in	O
the	O
Case	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
positive	O
proof	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Suetor	I-pers
was	O
brought	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Cralling	I-pers
Living	O
in	O
Drury	O
Lane	O
of	O
49	O
pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
several	O
Rings	O
,	O
half	O
shirts	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
hilted	O
Sword	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
conveyed	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Lodging	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
formerly	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Earl	O
of	O
Argloss	O
,	O
with	O
whom	O
likewise	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
Lived	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
denyed	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
although	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
confessed	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
not	O
only	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
but	O
likewise	O
in	O
Prison	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
urged	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
to	O
tell	O
the	O
Truth	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
no	O
longer	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
declared	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Inticed	O
to	O
consent	O
to	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
aiding	O
and	O
abetting	O
therein	O
:	O
but	O
denyed	O
he	O
either	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
or	O
carryed	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
owned	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
share	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
the	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Fellony	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hermitage	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
the	O
Lady	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
by	O
entring	O
her	O
House	O
at	O
a	O
back	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
Feather-beds	O
,	O
Carpets	O
,	O
Curtains	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
like	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
discovered	O
in	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
conveyed	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
thought	O
it	O
not	O
convenient	O
to	O
put	O
the	O
Court	O
to	O
farther	O
trouble	O
,	O
but	O
confessed	O
he	O
was	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Catharine	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
several	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
from	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Jason	I-pers
in	O
Fetterlane	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
a	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
them	O
under	O
her	O
charge	O
:	O
But	O
she	O
Pleaded	O
that	O
she	O
never	O
had	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
verily	O
believe	O
that	O
a	O
Woman	O
who	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
ask	O
for	O
a	O
Person	O
,	O
took	O
them	O
:	O
but	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
alledged	O
that	O
she	O
promised	O
to	O
pay	O
her	O
share	O
towards	O
them	O
:	O
but	O
she	O
producing	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
support	O
her	O
Credit	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
Testimony	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
behaved	O
her	O
self	O
very	O
well	O
in	O
many	O
places	O
in	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
had	O
great	O
charges	O
of	O
Plate	O
and	O
Money	O
in	O
her	O
Custody	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
by	O
reason	O
no	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
were	O
produced	O
,	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Liddia	B-pers
Letsworth	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
upon	O
an	O
Indictment	O
Exhibited	O
against	O
her	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
living	O
with	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Thead	I-pers
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
Criplegate	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
several	O
opportunities	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
a	O
Closet	O
where	O
several	O
parcels	O
of	O
Money	O
lay	O
in	O
a	O
Cabinet	O
,	O
the	O
which	O
she	O
took	O
out	O
,	O
it	O
amounting	O
in	O
Gold	O
and	O
Silver	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
13	O
pounds	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
carried	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
acquaintance	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
keep	O
it	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
whether	O
through	O
fear	O
or	O
an	O
honest	O
principle	O
,	O
is	O
uncertain	O
,	O
she	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
restored	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
At	O
first	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
but	O
a	O
young	O
Thief	O
could	O
not	O
long	O
out-face	O
it	O
,	O
whereupon	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Fellony	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Bland	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Picking	O
a	O
Market-womans	O
Pocket	O
of	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
shillings	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
Hony	O
Lane	O
Market	O
,	O
taking	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Pocket	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
woman	O
well	O
noting	O
her	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
short	O
time	O
found	O
her	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
stifly	O
denyed	O
the	O
Robbery	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
the	O
positive	O
Oaths	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
it	O
appearing	O
in	O
Court	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
usual	O
practice	O
to	O
haunt	O
Markets	O
and	O
other	O
places	O
of	O
resort	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Cotton	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
a	O
woman	O
in	O
White-Chappel	O
of	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
Thirty	O
shillings	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
Iron-work	O
from	O
on	O
Ship-board	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Yemans	I-pers
,	O
being	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
very	O
Fact	O
,	O
yet	O
he	O
denyed	O
it	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
till	O
at	O
last	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
some	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
accidentally	O
drop	O
'd	O
into	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
so	O
impose	O
upon	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
a	O
Witch	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
sometime	O
past	O
had	O
bewitched	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Chamble	I-pers
the	O
Daughter	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Chamble	I-pers
on	O
Mile-End-Green	O
,	O
as	O
likewise	O
his	O
Wife	O
;	O
he	O
first	O
gave	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
Court	O
a	O
long	O
story	O
of	O
two	O
Sows	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
bewitched	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
trust	O
Jane	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
for	O
two	O
Pigs	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
bespoke	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
killed	O
any	O
Pigs	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
send	O
to	O
ask	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
killed	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Pigs	O
she	O
bespoke	O
:	O
and	O
farther	O
,	O
that	O
after	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
his	O
Swine	O
,	O
his	O
Daughter	O
fell	O
sick	O
and	O
dyed	O
in	O
a	O
strange	O
Manner	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Wife	O
falling	O
sick	O
likewise	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Doctor	O
in	O
Spittlefields	O
,	O
who	O
advised	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
Medicine	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
said	O
took	O
off	O
the	O
Spell	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
into	O
such	O
pain	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
howling	O
to	O
his	O
door	O
,	O
although	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
,	O
being	O
charged	O
to	O
keep	O
the	O
door	O
shut	O
.	O
A	O
woman	O
likewise	O
swore	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
an	O
unusual	O
Tet	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
strange	O
marks	O
:	O
But	O
Evidence	O
being	O
given	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
laborious	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
frequented	O
Religious	O
Assemblies	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Stafford	I-pers
one	O
of	O
the	O
Life-guard	O
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
killing	O
one	O
Roundvaith	B-pers
near	O
Hide-Park	O
in	O
fighting	O
;	O
the	O
Defendant	O
having	O
received	O
several	O
Wounds	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pleading	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
se	O
Defendendo	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Deceased	O
drew	O
,	O
he	O
retreated	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
;	O
And	O
there	O
appearing	O
no	O
former	O
grudge	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
gave	O
their	O
Verdict	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Chamber	O
of	O
Esq	O
;	O
Turner	B-pers
of	O
the	O
Temple	O
,	O
on	O
Sunday	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
this	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
Picklock	O
Keys	O
,	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
but	O
finding	O
it	O
bolted	O
,	O
he	O
with	O
a	O
Betty	O
forced	O
it	O
open	O
,	O
but	O
entring	O
found	O
the	O
Landress	O
there	O
,	O
whereat	O
he	O
cryed	O
he	O
was	O
betrayed	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
drawing	O
a	O
Pistol	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
Swore	O
that	O
unless	O
she	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
depart	O
without	O
making	O
any	O
discovery	O
he	O
would	O
Pistol	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
for	O
fear	O
she	O
promised	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
no	O
sooner	O
gone	O
but	O
she	O
shut	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
cryed	O
Thieves	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
upon	O
Evidence	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
A	O
Person	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
the	O
Chamber	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Hoile	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Temple	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
Silk	O
Curtains	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
worth	O
of	O
20	O
pounds	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Wife	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
pawn	O
them	O
at	O
a	O
Brokers	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
confessed	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Several	O
Presentments	O
were	O
made	O
this	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Recusants	O
,	O
many	O
of	O
them	O
being	O
of	O
note	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
4	O
Condemned	O
,	O
3	O
women	O
and	O
one	O
man	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Welling	I-pers
,	O
Liddia	B-pers
Littlewoth	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Blane	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
6	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
2	O
to	O
be	O
Whipt	O
,	O
one	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
Fined	O
20	O
Pounds	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
ended	O
the	O
Sessions	O
.	O
