TOKEN	NE
THE	O
TRUE	O
NARRATIVE	O
OF	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
The	O
Sessions-House	O
IN	O
THE	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
Which	O
began	O
on	O
Monday	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
January	O
and	O
ended	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
17th	O
following	O
.	O
Giving	O
an	O
,	O
account	O
of	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
Remarkable	O
Trials	O
there	O
,	O
viz	O
,	O
For	O
Murder	O
,	O
Fellonies	O
and	O
Burglaries	O
&	O
c.	O
with	O
a	O
particular	O
Relation	O
of	O
their	O
Names	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
places	O
of	O
their	O
committing	O
their	O
Facts	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
those	O
Condemned	O
to	O
die	O
;	O
burn	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
Transported	O
and	O
to	O
be	O
whipt	O
.	O
At	O
this	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
began	O
and	O
ended	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
the	O
most	O
remarkable	O
Tryals	O
and	O
proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Rowland	B-pers
St.	I-pers
Johns	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Murthering	O
John	B-pers
Stiles	I-pers
Esquire	O
,	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
of	O
Lincolns	O
Inn	O
,	O
the	O
which	O
upon	O
Evidence	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
thus	O
.	O
The	O
party	O
deceased	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
intimate	O
Acquaintance	O
and	O
often	O
keeping	O
Company	O
together	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
happened	O
to	O
meet	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
having	O
been	O
at	O
several	O
Taverns	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
came	O
to	O
Richards	O
Coffe-House	O
near	O
Temple-Bar	O
,	O
where	O
laying	O
a	O
trivial	O
wager	O
about	O
measuring	O
two	O
Dishes	O
of	O
Chockalet	O
,	O
they	O
afterwards	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
St.	O
Johns	O
H	O
Chancery-Lane	O
,	O
to	O
drink	O
it	O
,	O
where	O
falling	O
at	O
some	O
difference	O
about	O
paying	O
their	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
the	O
Kings-Head	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
not	O
well	O
agreeing	O
,	O
from	O
thence	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
three	B-place
Cranes	I-place
;	O
and	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
Company	O
of	O
some	O
Gentlemen	O
that	O
kept	O
a	O
Club	O
there	O
;	O
they	O
offered	O
to	O
refer	O
their	O
differences	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
finding	O
them	O
both	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
some	O
words	O
had	O
passed	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
all	O
but	O
one	O
Gentleman	O
left	O
them	O
,	O
when	O
after	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
hasty	O
words	O
passing	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
deceased	O
laid	O
his	O
hand	O
upon	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
which	O
occasioned	O
the	O
other	O
to	O
draw	O
and	O
whilst	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
that	O
went	O
in	O
their	O
Company	O
,	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
call	O
for	O
help	O
to	O
part	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
run	O
the	O
deceased	O
in	O
two	O
Inches	O
under	O
the	O
Left	O
Pap	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
in	O
three	O
days	O
he	O
dyed	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
former	O
Grudg	O
nor	O
premeditated	O
Malice	O
proved	O
,	O
notwithstanding	O
three	O
Indictments	O
were	O
laid	O
,	O
one	O
for	O
wilful	O
Murder	O
,	O
one	O
upon	O
the	O
Corroners	O
Inquest	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
upon	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
Stabbing	O
,	O
yet	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
only	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
and	O
Joyce	B-pers
Cove	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
as	O
principle	O
,	O
for	O
Robing	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Crook	I-pers
in	O
Soho	B-place
Fields	I-place
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
:	O
of	O
Ribon	O
,	O
Silk-Stockings	O
,	O
Gloves	O
,	O
Silks	O
,	O
Laces	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
value	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
last	O
as	O
Accessaries	O
in	O
receiving	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
principle	O
having	O
confessed	O
,	O
not	O
only	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
another	O
Robery	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
search	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Houses	O
of	O
the	O
accessaries	O
;	O
whereupon	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
as	O
likewise	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Sims	I-pers
,	O
another	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Gang	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
Bands	O
,	O
Hoods	O
and	O
Table-Linnen	O
,	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Gresham	I-pers
on	O
the	O
1st	O
instant	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
killing	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Willer	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Life-Guardman	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
on	O
this	O
side	O
Chelsey	O
,	O
the	O
manner	O
according	O
to	O
Evidence	O
thus	O
,	O
the	O
deceased	O
drinking	O
at	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Foot-Soldier	O
coming	O
by	O
,	O
called	O
him	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
wrestling	O
,	O
which	O
occasioned	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
withdrew	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
staying	O
there	O
some	O
time	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
as	O
he	O
alleaged	O
to	O
have	O
gon	O
his	O
ways	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
deceased	O
following	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
drawn	O
,	O
and	O
giving	O
him	O
several	O
Cuts	O
,	O
he	O
drew	O
likewise	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
the	O
deceased	O
in	O
in	O
two	O
places	O
of	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
instantly	O
dy	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
was	O
in	O
defence	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
Life	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
only	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Morley	I-pers
a	O
notorious	O
Offendor	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
brought	O
from	O
the	O
Marshalsea	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
burnt	O
in	O
the	O
hand	O
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Guilty	O
for	O
stealing	O
several	O
parcels	O
of	O
Linnen	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
Samuel	B-pers
Banfield	I-pers
in	O
Holbourn	B-place
.	O
Humphry	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
for	O
Robing	O
William	B-pers
Sellwood	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
Cravat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
upon	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
second	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
,	O
the	O
Cravat	O
being	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Breeches	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Ashurst	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
killing	O
Lucy	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
with	O
a	O
Cart	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
deposing	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
crossing	O
of	O
the	O
Horses	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
struck	O
her	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
the	O
wheeler	O
went	O
over	O
her	O
Head	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
wound	O
she	O
Instantly	O
dyed	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
adjudged	O
Chance	O
Medly	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
acquitted	O
,	O
yet	O
received	O
a	O
severe	O
Repremand	O
from	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
for	O
their	O
carelesness	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Cockhill	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Leather	O
out	O
of	O
Leaden-Hall	B-place
,	O
which	O
being	O
taken	O
upon	O
him	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fellony	O
,	O
saying	O
a	O
Cobler	O
set	O
him	O
on	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
shilling	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Carpet	O
,	O
Cupboard	O
Linnen	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
December	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Pordy	I-pers
of	O
Stepny	B-place
;	O
but	O
the	O
things	O
being	O
thrown	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
swear	O
they	O
see	O
him	O
take	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Clavel	B-pers
Cordwel	I-pers
had	O
an	O
Indictment	O
preferred	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
Marrying	O
a	O
second	B-pers
Wife	I-pers
,	O
the	O
first	B-pers
being	O
yet	O
alive	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
Witness	O
swearing	O
in	O
Court	O
to	O
both	O
the	O
Marriages	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Katherine	B-pers
Tobie	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
several	O
pieces	O
of	O
Ribon	O
,	O
Lutestring	O
Hoods	O
,	O
Scarves	O
,	O
Peticoats	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
from	O
one	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Gullet	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
January	O
of	O
which	O
upon	O
the	O
Testimony	O
of	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Hester	B-pers
Lemar	I-pers
:	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
the	O
Chamber	O
of	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Becks	I-pers
in	O
St.	B-place
Pauls	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
two	O
silver	O
,	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
a	O
Pearl	O
Necklace	O
,	O
Spoons	O
,	O
Silver	O
Plates	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
fifty	O
pounds	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
by	O
reason	O
of	O
several	O
French	O
Protestants	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
Evidence	O
of	O
her	O
former	O
Life	O
and	O
Conversation	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
one	O
of	O
those	O
that	O
fled	O
the	O
Persecution	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Harison	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robing	O
John	B-pers
Wise	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
of	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
Hoods	O
and	O
Linnen	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
value	O
her	O
Plea	O
was	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
bring	O
them	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
excused	O
her	O
not	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Huckle	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
Trial	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Jane	B-pers
Rand	I-pers
,	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Bethel	I-pers
in	O
Cornhil	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
Robed	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Bethel	O
of	O
three	O
Diamond	O
Rings	O
,	O
two	O
Silver	O
Tankards	O
,	O
six	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
ten	O
pieces	O
of	O
old	O
Gold	O
,	O
eighty	O
Guinies	O
,	O
and	O
such	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
value	O
,	O
as	O
amounted	O
to	O
300	O
pounds	O
,	O
The	O
Maid	O
confessed	O
the	O
Robery	O
,	O
and	O
accused	O
the	O
said	O
Huckle	O
,	O
who	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
give	O
any	O
good	O
Account	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wollman	I-pers
of	O
St.	O
Martins	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
killing	O
John	B-pers
Bret	I-pers
her	O
Husbands	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
the	O
manner	O
of	O
the	O
Murther	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
sworn	O
to	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
being	O
thus	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
at	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
that	O
joyned	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
deceased	O
playing	O
with	O
her	O
Son	O
,	O
and	O
throwing	O
an	O
empty	O
bag	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
missing	O
him	O
,	O
How	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
dore	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
being	O
over	O
powered	O
with	O
Drink	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
home	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Rage	O
,	O
and	O
getting	O
up	O
a	O
Broom-stick	O
,	O
fell	O
upon	O
the	O
Youth	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
from	O
her	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
after	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
small	O
Carying	O
Chizel	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
Brest	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
she	O
knew	O
she	O
should	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
for	O
him	O
one	O
time	O
or	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
seemed	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
sorry	O
for	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
but	O
rather	O
rejoyced	O
,	O
being	O
so	O
far	O
transported	O
with	O
Rage	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
threw	O
another	O
Chizel	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
upon	O
this	O
wound	O
received	O
,	O
the	O
Youth	O
got	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
next	O
house	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
instantly	O
dyed	O
!	O
She	O
pleaded	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
sawcy	O
Language	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
not	O
appearing	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
wilful	O
Murther	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Plate	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
30	O
pounds	O
on	O
the	O
10	O
of	O
December	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
Comissary	I-pers
of	O
Algare-Parish	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
evidently	O
proper	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
taken	O
with	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
Lap	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
ded	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
served	O
not	O
her	O
turn	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Emerton	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
from	O
the	O
three	O
Black-Birds	O
in	O
Warwick	O
Lane	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
positively	O
sworn	O
to	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Younger	I-pers
,	O
being	O
Indicted	O
upon	O
a	O
Trespass	O
,	O
for	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Spencer	O
in	O
Great	O
St.	O
Bartholomews	O
,	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
searching	O
for	O
Prohibited	O
Goods	O
,	O
took	O
thence	O
two	O
silver	O
Hilts	O
of	O
Swords	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
fined	O
ten	O
Mark	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
continue	O
in	O
Prison	O
till	O
next	O
Sessions	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
till	O
the	O
Fine	O
be	O
paid	O
.	O
Paul	B-pers
Rutter	I-pers
;	O
a	O
French	O
Chirurgion	O
,	O
or	O
Doctor	O
had	O
an	O
Indictment	O
of	O
Murther	O
preferred	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
poysoning	O
Robert	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
of	O
St.	O
Martins	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
Latter	O
end	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
which	O
appeared	O
in	O
Court	O
to	O
be	O
thus	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
keeping	O
the	O
deceaseds	O
wife	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
using	O
her	O
at	O
his	O
Will	O
,	O
the	O
deceased	O
one	O
Morning	O
meeting	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
drink	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
treat	O
about	O
a	O
Reconciliation	O
,	O
but	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
drank	O
two	O
pots	O
deceased	O
before	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
home	O
finding	O
himself	O
extream	O
ill	O
,	O
concluded	O
he	O
was	O
poysoned	O
and	O
to	O
his	O
last	O
exclaimed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Doctor	O
had	O
poysoned	O
him	O
for	O
his	O
wife	O
for	O
Estate	O
;	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
being	O
opened	O
,	O
several	O
symptoms	O
of	O
poison	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Stomack	O
,	O
yet	O
the	O
Jury	O
being	O
English	O
and	O
French	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Murther	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
Court	O
had	O
been	O
set	O
a	O
considerable	O
time	O
,	O
Council	O
moved	O
for	O
an	O
Order	O
to	O
warrant	O
the	O
Sheriffs	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
Middlesex	O
for	O
the	O
delivery	O
of	O
the	O
Jesuites	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
who	O
are	O
Ordered	O
by	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
Council	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Scilly	O
Islands	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Court	O
returned	O
for	O
Answer	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
could	O
grant	O
no	O
Order	O
,	O
the	O
matter	O
not	O
being	O
before	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
Majesties	O
Pleasure	O
to	O
Reprieve	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
dispose	O
of	O
them	O
as	O
he	O
thought	O
fit	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Sheriffs	O
must	O
deliver	O
them	O
.	O
In	O
Reply	O
to	O
which	O
the	O
Council	O
cited	O
a	O
President	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
used	O
upon	O
the	O
like	O
occasion	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Sheriffs	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
be	O
rid	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
might	O
be	O
saved	O
harmless	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
conclusion	O
my	O
Lord	O
Chief-Justice	O
utterly	O
refused	O
to	O
grant	O
any	O
Order	O
.	O
Seven	O
or	O
eight	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Recusancy	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
in	O
all	O
seven	O
persons	O
Condemned	O
in	O
dye	O
,	O
viz	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
Maratha	B-pers
Huckle	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
,	O
Joyce	B-pers
Cove	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Crossman	I-pers
,	O
Eight	O
burn	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
Five	O
to	O
be	O
whiped	O
and	O
three	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
.	O
