TOKEN	NE
THE	O
TRUE	O
NARRATIVE	O
OF	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
The	O
Sessions	O
House	O
IN	O
THE	O
OLD	O
BAYLY	O
which	O
began	O
on	O
Fryday	O
the	O
23th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
February	O
and	O
ended	O
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
24th	O
following	O
.	O
Giving	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
Remarkable	O
Trials	O
there	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
For	O
Murder	O
Fellonies	O
and	O
Burglaries	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
with	O
a	O
particular	O
Relation	O
of	O
their	O
Names	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
places	O
of	O
their	O
commiting	O
their	O
Facts	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
those	O
Condemed	O
to	O
die	O
,	O
Burn	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
Transported	O
and	O
to	O
be	O
whipt	O
.	O
AT	O
the	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
that	O
began	O
at	O
the	O
Old-Baly	O
,	O
on	O
Friday	O
the	O
23	O
of	O
February	O
and	O
ended	O
the	O
24	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
proceedings	O
were	O
these	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Whithead	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gelding	O
valued	O
five	O
pounds	O
,	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Trendal	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Magdelen	I-place
Bermonsy	I-place
the	O
Circumstances	O
were	O
these	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
taking	O
his	O
oportunity	O
entur	O
'd	O
into	O
the	O
prosecuters	O
stable	O
on	O
the	O
second	O
Instant	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
the	O
Gelding	O
sadled	O
slipped	O
a	O
Bridle	O
upon	O
him	O
and	O
rid	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Friday	O
following	O
was	O
apprehended	O
with	O
the	O
said	O
Gelding	O
at	O
the	O
Hernes	O
Inn	O
in	O
West-Smithfield	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
then	O
sold	O
and	O
received	O
one	O
Shilling	O
in	O
part	O
of	O
payment	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
this	O
accusation	O
being	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
demanded	O
what	O
he	O
could	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
defence	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
fact	O
only	O
desiring	O
that	O
his	O
sentence	O
might	O
be	O
Transportation	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Bigs	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Killing	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Benning	I-pers
in	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
Parish	I-place
;	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
which	O
in	O
Circumstance	O
appeared	O
thus	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
in	O
,	O
the	O
deceased	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
Cake	O
he	O
promised	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
refusing	O
to	O
give	O
,	O
words	O
arose	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
struck	O
a	O
paper	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
deceased	O
's	O
hands	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
slung	O
a	O
Coal	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
still	O
Augmenting	O
the	O
quarrel	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
threw	O
the	O
deceased	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
him	O
twice	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
upon	O
his	O
death-bed	O
alledged	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
his	O
death	O
:	O
but	O
there	O
having	O
been	O
a	O
Law-suit	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
offers	O
of	O
Agreement	O
proposed	O
by	O
the	O
Friend	O
of	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
and	O
further	O
,	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
infirm	O
man	O
,	O
Bigs	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
Tryal	O
for	O
that	O
He	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Neal	I-pers
a	O
Puterer	O
near	O
Aldgate	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
thence	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
servants	O
absence	O
,	O
29	O
Peuter-plates	O
unfinished	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
attempting	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
,	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
he	O
at	O
first	O
pleaded	O
innocence	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
having	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
no	O
ways	O
able	O
to	O
prove	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
the	O
Fellony	O
and	O
was	O
thereupon	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Slater	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robing	O
Amy	B-pers
Sarjeant	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Bartholomews	I-place
the	I-place
Great	I-place
,	O
which	O
uPon	O
Evidence	O
appeared	O
thus	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lived	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecuter	O
in	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
a	O
Servant	O
for	O
several	O
Months	O
,	O
when	O
missing	O
a	O
Crape-Gown	O
,	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Ribon	O
,	O
pieces	O
of	O
Stuff	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
like	O
;	O
She	O
began	O
to	O
suspect	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
getting	O
her	O
Keys	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
opening	O
her	O
Trunk	O
;	O
found	O
the	O
goods	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
layed	O
there	O
by	O
some	O
person	O
on	O
purpose	O
to	O
defame	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
their	O
being	O
there	O
,	O
yet	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
possitive	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
her	O
Allegations	O
availed	O
not	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
was	O
so	O
favourable	O
to	O
find	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
nine	O
Shillings	O
and	O
Eleven-pence	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
picking	O
a	O
young	B-pers
womans	I-pers
pocket	O
near	O
Criple-gate	B-place
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Box	O
and	O
fourteen	O
pence	O
in	O
mony	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Court	O
taking	O
pity	O
of	O
his	O
youth	O
,	O
gave	O
such	O
directions	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
within	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
Pettelarcenary	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
under	O
twelve	O
pence	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Whitnie	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
thirty	O
yards	O
of	O
Baiys	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
Joseph	B-pers
Gibals	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
which	O
according	O
to	O
Evidence	O
was	O
sugested	O
thus	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drinking	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecuters	O
house	O
watched	O
his	O
opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
the	O
Bays	O
and	O
make	O
his	O
escape	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Bays	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
none	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
them	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Howel	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robing	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Mountacut	I-pers
,	O
the	O
manner	O
as	O
in	O
appeared	O
upon	O
Evidence	O
thus	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
living	O
with	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Tisler	O
where	O
the	O
prosecuter	O
lodged	O
,	O
having	O
opportunity	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Chamber	O
found	O
means	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
Closet	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
his	O
absence	O
took	O
out	O
money	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
computed	O
in	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
twelve	O
pounds	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
being	O
detected	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
like	O
sum	O
of	O
mony	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Trunk	O
,	O
she	O
pleaded	O
she	O
earn	O
'd	O
it	O
part	O
in	O
service	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
another	O
part	O
was	O
left	O
her	O
by	O
her	O
mother	O
,	O
but	O
amongst	O
the	O
rest	O
were	O
found	O
one	O
Remarkable	O
Sixpence	O
and	O
a	O
Bag	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecuter	O
swore	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
Jury	O
only	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
ten	O
pounds	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mr.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Billip	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
being	O
aiding	O
and	O
abetting	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Leshly	O
in	O
Killing	O
Mr.	B-pers
Glower	I-pers
in	O
Convent-Garden	B-place
on	O
the	O
6th	O
day	O
ofSeptember	O
last	O
,	O
against	O
whom	O
it	O
was	O
sworn	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
put	O
a	O
Sword	O
into	O
Leshly	O
's	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
hinder	O
his	O
being	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
walking	O
in	O
the	O
Garden	O
before	O
the	O
duel	O
began	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
first	O
he	O
pleaded	O
that	O
being	O
struck	O
by	O
those	O
that	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
apprehend	O
Mr.	O
Leshly	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
maze	O
Mr.	O
Leshly	O
took	O
his	O
Sword	O
from	O
his	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
only	O
went	O
to	O
save	O
him	O
from	O
being	O
Knockt	O
on	O
the	O
head	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
second	O
he	O
brought	O
several	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
just	O
came	O
from	O
home	O
as	O
the	O
duel	O
happened	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
there	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
farther	O
alledged	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
any	O
acquaintance	O
witheither	O
of	O
the	O
parties	O
,	O
and	O
Consequently	O
could	O
have	O
no	O
Malice	O
against	O
the	O
party	O
deceased	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
upon	O
leaving	O
the	O
whole	O
Evidence	O
on	O
either	O
side	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Benson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Axly	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
a	O
Bastard-Child	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
custody	O
of	O
the	O
former	O
locked	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Box	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
of	O
which	O
as	O
it	O
appeared	O
upon	O
Evidence	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
delivered	O
some	O
days	O
before	O
,	O
her	O
plea	O
was	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
still-born	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
avoid	O
the	O
Penalty	O
of	O
the	O
Act	O
of	O
the	O
13	O
of	O
King	O
James	O
,	O
alledged	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
Married	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Axly	O
was	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
likewise	O
owned	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
a	O
Fellow	O
to	O
witness	O
they	O
were	O
Married	O
an	O
Tavern	O
,	O
so	O
,	O
that	O
by	O
that	O
means	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Joshua	B-pers
Bowes	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
upon	O
the	O
Libel	O
not	O
long	O
since	O
brought	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Dubots	O
by	O
a	O
then	O
unknown	O
hand	O
much	O
reflecting	O
upon	O
the	O
Government	O
,	O
tending	O
to	O
Sedition	O
and	O
Tumult	O
which	O
upon	O
the	O
reading	O
the	O
Indictment	O
and	O
offer	O
of	O
Proof	O
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
and	O
was	O
thereupon	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Peten	I-pers
,	O
and	O
one	O
Taylor	B-pers
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
of	O
Chamblet	O
and	O
Tapestrie-Hangings	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
value	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
Hangings	O
were	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
search	O
,	O
in	O
Petens	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
pleaded	O
they	O
were	O
left	O
there	O
by	O
one	O
Knowles	O
,	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
being	O
his	O
brothers	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
neither	O
bought	O
them	O
,	O
lent	O
money	O
ou	O
them	O
,	O
nor	O
knew	O
they	O
were	O
stole	O
,	O
as	O
for	O
the	O
other	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
witness	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
only	O
a	O
Suspition	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
taken	O
in	O
Pittens	O
House	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
in	O
Fine	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Martine	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Horse	O
of	O
five	O
pound	O
price	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
Daniel	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
of	O
Ware	B-place
,	O
which	O
was	O
afterwards	O
sold	O
by	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
person	O
in	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
him	O
to	O
others	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
upon	O
discoverie	O
that	O
the	O
Horse	O
was	O
stole	O
,	O
the	O
buyers	O
Prosecuted	O
and	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
deny	O
the	O
Fellony	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harsnet	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
29	O
Yards	O
of	O
Grey-Cloath	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Shop	O
in	O
Long-Lane	B-place
,	O
which	O
being	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
custody	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
give	O
any	O
satisfactory	O
account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
convicted	O
of	O
the	O
Fellony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tanner	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
proof	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
only	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Company	O
of	O
two	O
persons	O
who	O
were	O
drinking	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
balance	O
it	O
,	O
being	O
proved	O
that	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
standing	O
upon	O
the	O
Table	O
when	O
he	O
left	O
the	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
all	O
Circumstances	O
waighedhe	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Warder	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Bucannan	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murthering	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Sexton	I-pers
in	O
Grayes-Inn	B-place
Lane	I-place
on	O
the	O
Eleventh	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
February	O
but	O
the	O
latter	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
Circumstances	O
that	O
attended	O
the	O
Tryal	O
of	O
the	O
former	O
,	O
were	O
these	O
,	O
Sexton	O
being	O
abroadon	O
the	O
Evening	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
aforesaid	O
;	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
past	O
Eight	O
,	O
met	O
four	O
men	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
struck	O
him	O
over	O
the	O
head	O
with	O
his	O
Stick	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
offering	O
to	O
defend	O
himself	O
and	O
asking	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
reason	O
of	O
such	O
an	O
abuse	O
;	O
another	O
of	O
the	O
Company	O
steped	O
in	O
and	O
ran	O
him	O
through	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
wound	O
he	O
died	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
hours	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
suspition	O
had	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
was	O
grounded	O
upon	O
this	O
reason	O
;	O
that	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
the	O
Murther	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
observed	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
a	O
dishonest	O
house	O
,	O
with	O
three	O
hectoring	O
Blades	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
upon	O
the	O
death	O
of	O
Soxton	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
absented	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
only	O
,	O
presumption	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
possitive	O
proof	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Archer	I-pers
a	O
French-woman	O
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pearl-Necklaces	O
12	O
silver-spoons	O
and	O
other	O
pieces	O
of	O
plate	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
value	O
;	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
goods	O
being	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
custody	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
not	O
well	O
denying	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Arthur	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robing	O
John	B-pers
Almtac	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
taking	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Cart	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
suger	O
,	O
stuffs	O
,	O
and	O
parchments	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
ten	O
pound	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
custody	O
of	O
Edward	O
Arthur	O
,	O
upon	O
proof	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Quarles	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robing	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
S.	B-place
Martains	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
,	O
5	O
Yards	O
of	O
Fustain	O
,	O
2	O
Yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Cloath	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
of	O
considerable	O
value	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Gulty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Haris	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
Edward	B-pers
Sharp	I-pers
s	O
house	O
near	O
Bishops-gate	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
taking	O
thence	O
Coats	O
,	O
Table	O
,	O
and	O
Bed	O
Linnen	O
Peuter	O
Dishes	O
stocking	O
and	O
the	O
like	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
ten	O
pounds	O
and	O
afterwards	O
attemping	O
a	O
second	O
Robery	O
,	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
dropped	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
upon	O
proof	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Norman	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Daniel	B-pers
Fry	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
and	O
found	O
Guilty	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
scarfe	O
,	O
linnen	O
and	O
other	O
goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
thirty	O
pounds	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Lawson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
upon	O
the	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
Riot	O
of	O
Apprentices	O
in	O
Cheap	B-place
side	I-place
,	O
but	O
none	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
he	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
This	O
Sessions	O
three	O
persons	O
received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
Viz	O
.	O
William	O
Witehead	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Martine	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Atcher	I-pers
:	O
Six	O
burnt	O
in	O
the	O
hand	O
,	O
Viz	O
.	O
Robert	O
Quarless	O
,	O
John	O
Haris	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	O
Harsot	O
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Slaughter	I-pers
,	O
&	O
c.	O
seven	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
,	O
Viz	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Bigs	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Fry	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Norman	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Haris	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Arthur	I-pers
,	O
&	O
c	O
and	O
two	O
to	O
be	O
whipt	O
,	O
Viz	O
.	O
John	O
Bennet	O
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Howel	I-pers
,	O
and	O
thus	O
the	O
Sessions	O
ended	O
