TOKEN	NE
The	O
TRUE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
OF	O
THE	O
SESSIONS	O
,	O
Begun	O
at	O
the	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
18th	O
.	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
1683	O
.	O
Giving	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
several	O
Tryals	O
(	O
viz	O
.	O
)	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
Murders	O
,	O
Felonies	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
with	O
the	O
Condemnation	O
of	O
those	O
Convicted	O
.	O
Printed	O
by	O
Authority	O
.	O
THe	O
First	O
Arraigned	O
was	O
Richard	B-pers
Mackrel	I-pers
,	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
valued	O
at	O
3	O
l.	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Speed	I-pers
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
Pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
One	O
Hull	B-pers
was	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Canvas	O
Bag	O
and	O
50	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
from	O
a	O
Gold-Smith	B-pers
in	O
London	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
his	O
said	O
Arraignment	O
Pleaded	O
Guilty	O
to	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
things	O
within	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
the	O
Clergy	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Riggs	I-pers
,	O
Hugh	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Third	B-pers
Person	I-pers
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
one	O
Terry	O
a	O
Country-man	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
out	O
there	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
l.	O
which	O
being	O
taken	O
upon	O
Riggs	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Whitehand	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Whitehand	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Andrew	B-pers
Whitehand	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Coining	O
and	O
putting	O
off	O
Counterfeit	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
for	O
Clipping	O
of	O
other	O
good	O
Money	O
which	O
was	O
of	O
the	O
Lawful	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
:	O
The	O
two	O
Men	O
fled	O
upon	O
some	O
Alarum	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
be	O
seized	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
said	O
Elizabeth	O
was	O
Tryed	O
and	O
Acquitted	O
;	O
for	O
that	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
not	O
clear	O
against	O
her	O
paricularly	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Frances	B-pers
the	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Richard	I-pers
Hemming	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Silver	O
Box	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
6	O
s.	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
passing	O
from	O
Leaden-hall-market	B-place
near	I-place
Cree-Church	I-place
;	O
she	O
made	O
Oath	O
positively	O
the	O
Box	O
was	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Market	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
but	O
snatching	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
running	O
away	O
;	O
upon	O
her	O
Out-cry	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
yet	O
no	O
Box	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
of	O
that	O
sort	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
abetting	O
,	O
procuring	O
,	O
or	O
Counsilling	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Frogmorton	I-pers
,	O
(	O
on	O
or	O
about	O
the	O
29	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
)	O
by	O
incouraging	O
or	O
desiring	O
Mr.	O
David	B-pers
Stanyer	I-pers
to	O
revenge	O
some	O
affront	O
Sir	O
William	O
had	O
offered	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
Stanyer	O
did	O
soon	O
after	O
kill	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Frogmorton	I-pers
,	O
(	O
viz	O
.	O
in	O
June	O
last	O
)	O
and	O
being	O
fled	O
,	O
stands	O
Convicted	O
by	O
Out-lawry	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Fellony	O
and	O
Murder	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
the	O
Tryal	O
,	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
whereas	O
about	O
that	O
time	O
the	O
said	O
Sir	O
William	O
came	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Clarkes	O
House	O
much	O
in	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
some	O
slight	O
occasion	O
pull	O
'd	O
her	O
Head-cloathes	O
off	O
;	O
yet	O
to	O
avoid	O
difference	O
,	O
she	O
withdrew	O
to	O
another	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
also	O
quarrelling	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Stanyer	O
;	O
some	O
challenge	O
hapned	O
between	O
them	O
without	O
her	O
contributing	O
any	O
thing	O
thereto	O
;	O
as	O
also	O
a	O
full	O
Testimony	O
of	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
coming	O
in	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
lived	O
peaceably	O
and	O
in	O
good	O
repute	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
thereof	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Infant	O
of	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
year	O
Old	O
,	O
the	O
manner	O
thus	O
:	O
The	O
Mother	O
of	O
Hill	O
kept	O
a	O
publick	O
House	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
Parish	I-place
,	O
where	O
of	O
a	O
Sunday	O
night	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
Moneth	O
,	O
Johnson	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
drink	O
Brandy	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
one	O
Quartern	O
would	O
have	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
drink	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
private	O
Room	O
with	O
one	O
he	O
called	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Landlady	O
refusing	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
threatned	O
revenge	O
before	O
Saturday	O
following	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
after	O
about	O
eight	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
came	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
rude	O
manner	O
,	O
and	O
breaking	O
her	O
Windows	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
abuses	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
yet	O
revenge	O
enough	O
,	O
the	O
Woman	O
running	O
to	O
strike	O
him	O
,	O
or	O
defend	O
her	O
Goods	O
with	O
the	O
Child	O
in	O
her	O
Arms	O
,	O
he	O
struck	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
with	O
his	O
stick	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
blow	O
it	O
dyed	O
about	O
seven	O
hours	O
after	O
.	O
Yet	O
the	O
Jury	O
being	O
of	O
Opinion	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
premediated	O
Malice	O
to	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
accidentally	O
in	O
the	O
Womans	O
Arms	O
whom	O
he	O
might	O
strike	O
at	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
it	O
Man	O
Slaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ralph	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
(	O
or	O
Capt	O
.	O
Philips	O
)	O
Indicted	O
for	O
killing	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Herne	I-pers
in	O
a	O
Duel	O
at	O
Katherine-street	B-place
near	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
;	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
and	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
that	O
whereas	O
Mr.	O
Philips	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Gentlemanwere	O
of	O
a	O
Company	O
drinking	O
in	O
a	O
Tavern	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Herne	O
being	O
of	O
another	O
Company	O
came	O
into	O
theirs	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
abusive	O
:	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Philips	O
did	O
all	O
that	O
was	O
possible	O
to	O
avoid	O
a	O
quarrel	O
,	O
and	O
yet	O
not	O
with	O
standing	O
,	O
when	O
each	O
Company	O
were	O
parted	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Herne	O
privately	O
followed	O
Mr.	O
Philips	O
,	O
and	O
drew	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
and	O
other	O
great	O
likelyhoods	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Philips	O
had	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
evade	O
that	O
Duel	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Man	O
Slaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
Centinel	O
at	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Gates	O
at	O
the	O
Tower	O
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
upon	O
an	O
Indictment	O
of	O
Murder	O
,	O
the	O
manner	O
thus	O
:	O
When	O
the	O
said	O
Savage	O
was	O
Centinel	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
one	O
Philip	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
and	O
another	O
Person	O
,	O
both	O
likewise	O
Soldier	O
s	O
upon	O
some	O
other	O
Duty	O
coming	O
by	O
the	O
Centinel	O
,	O
each	O
having	O
a	O
Musquet	O
on	O
his	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
Russel	O
as	O
they	O
past	O
by	O
said	O
,	O
how	O
now	O
Rogue	O
,	O
art	O
thou	O
here	O
,	O
lets	O
kill	O
him	O
,	O
meaning	O
the	O
Centinel	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
Savage	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
call	O
me	O
Rogue	O
,	O
I'le	O
kill	O
you	O
first	O
;	O
immediately	O
Fired	O
his	O
Musquet	O
and	O
shot	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
Bullet	O
passing	O
quite	O
through	O
his	O
Body	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
Guts	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
dyed	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
three	O
hours	O
.	O
Savage	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
nothing	O
but	O
his	O
Duty	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
done	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
been	O
kill	O
'd	O
himself	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
but	O
Russel	O
had	O
a	O
design	O
to	O
take	O
the	B-place
Tower	I-place
,	O
or	O
such	O
like	O
excuses	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
other	O
Soldier	O
who	O
was	O
passing	O
with	O
Russel	O
,	O
witnessed	O
that	O
Russel	O
laughed	O
when	O
he	O
spoke	O
of	O
killing	O
the	O
Centinel	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
only	O
in	O
Jest	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
never	O
pulled	O
their	O
Musquets	O
from	O
their	O
Shoulders	O
,	O
or	O
made	O
any	O
the	O
least	O
offer	O
against	O
the	O
Centinel	O
,	O
but	O
passed	O
on	O
in	O
the	O
common	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
gone	O
beyond	O
the	O
Centinel	O
before	O
he	O
Fired	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
therefore	O
brought	O
it	O
in	O
Willful	O
Murder	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lental	I-pers
a	O
Brazier	O
,	O
or	O
such	O
like	O
Tradesman	O
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
several	O
Brass	O
Pots	O
,	O
Kettles	O
,	O
or	O
Skillets	O
,	O
(	O
or	O
some	O
of	O
each	O
)	O
also	O
several	O
Pewter-dishes	O
,	O
Plates	O
,	O
Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
Frying-pan	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
House	O
or	O
Yard	O
near	O
the	O
Artillery	B-place
Wall	I-place
by	I-place
Bun-hill-fields	I-place
;	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
he	O
only	O
had	O
bought	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
endevoured	O
to	O
find	O
,	O
or	O
found	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
Thief	O
being	O
one	O
Jones	O
,	O
against	O
which	O
Person	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
Lental	O
was	O
ready	O
to	O
give	O
Evidence	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
circumstances	O
in	O
his	O
Vindication	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Indictment	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
against	O
Jones	O
for	O
that	O
Fact	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Piner	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Scurvil	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
conspiring	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Arrowsmith	I-pers
to	O
kill	O
and	O
murder	O
Thomas	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
but	O
were	O
all	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cary	I-pers
or	I-pers
Cariff	I-pers
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
himself	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Lewis	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
an	O
old	O
Man	O
of	O
above	O
Fourscore	O
years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
for	O
Stealing	O
22	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
Katherine	B-pers
Steel	I-pers
,	O
Roger	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
and	O
several	O
others	O
which	O
here	O
is	O
not	O
room	O
to	O
insert	O
,	O
were	O
likewise	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felonies	O
to	O
a	O
small	O
value	O
;	O
six	O
or	O
eight	O
more	O
not	O
named	O
,	O
Tryed	O
for	O
like	O
Felonies	O
and	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Littleton	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Batts	I-pers
,	O
known	O
by	O
the	O
Title	O
of	O
Gransir	O
to	O
the	O
Pick-Pockets	O
,	O
(	O
although	O
a	O
Boy	O
of	O
about	O
Fourteen-years	O
Old	O
)	O
Tryed	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
pass	O
'd	O
through	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
eight	O
or	O
ten	O
pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
some	O
Silver	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
clear	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
Single	O
Woman	O
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
black	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
things	O
from	O
Allin	B-pers
Culler	I-pers
of	O
Black-fryars	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
thereof	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Simms	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
publick	O
House	O
at	O
Westminster	O
,	O
(	O
viz	O
.	O
from	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
)	O
and	O
albeit	O
he	O
produced	O
another	O
Person	O
to	O
own	O
the	O
Stealing	O
it	O
and	O
excuse	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
used	O
such	O
Interest	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Evidence	O
for	O
a	O
considerable	O
time	O
would	O
not	O
swear	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Man	O
;	O
yet	O
upon	O
a	O
strict	O
Examination	O
thereof	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
discovered	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Person	O
and	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cherry	I-pers
for	O
Stealing	O
two	O
Silk	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Bayly	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Mantua	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Scarf	O
,	O
some	O
Laces	O
,	O
Forehead-cloaths	O
,	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lambourne	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Gelding	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Marsh	O
near	O
Hampton-Court	O
,	O
valued	O
to	O
the	O
worth	O
20	O
l.	O
but	O
by	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
who	O
owned	O
him	O
at	O
50	O
l.	O
which	O
Gelding	O
Lambourne	O
Sold	O
at	O
Tame	O
in	O
Oxford-shire	O
for	O
50	O
l	O
pretending	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
said	O
Gelding	O
of	O
one	O
he	O
met	O
in	O
the	O
Road	O
near	O
Hounslow	O
for	O
34	O
s.	O
but	O
having	O
no	O
witness	O
to	O
prove	O
how	O
he	O
lived	O
,	O
or	O
of	O
his	O
said	O
buying	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
alledging	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Seller	O
by	O
chance	O
,	O
having	O
no	O
knowledge	O
whence	O
,	O
or	O
who	O
he	O
was	O
;	O
Lambourne	O
was	O
threfore	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Conway	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
Ensignes	O
,	O
who	O
lately	O
fought	O
the	O
Duel	O
behind	O
Southampton	O
Buildings	O
near	O
Tatnam	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
therein	O
kill	O
'd	O
Mr.	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Man	O
Slaughter	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Rossington	I-pers
,	O
who	O
that	O
Evening	O
kill	O
'd	O
Stephen	B-pers
Know	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
being	O
Tryed	O
,	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
agreeing	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
know	O
did	O
give	O
the	O
first	O
Provocation	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
also	O
found	O
Man	O
Slaughter	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
,	O
who	O
refused	O
to	O
Plead	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
being	O
again	O
Araigned	O
on	O
Thursday	O
,	O
continued	O
obstinate	O
till	O
the	O
Sentence	O
against	O
a	O
Mute	O
was	O
read	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Executioner	O
ordered	O
to	O
tye	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
who	O
beginning	O
to	O
take	O
hold	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
,	O
he	O
yielded	O
to	O
Plead	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
his	O
Brother	O
,	O
Pleaded	O
Guilty	O
of	O
that	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
within	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
the	O
Clergy	O
.	O
After	O
which	O
William	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Stealing	O
the	O
Beaver	O
Hat	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
five	O
more	O
coming	O
into	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
not	O
far	O
from	O
the	O
Haymarket	O
,	O
about	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
drank	O
about	O
13	O
d.	O
and	O
paid	O
it	O
,	O
called	O
for	O
some	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Landlord	O
one	O
Richard	B-pers
Groom	I-pers
going	O
to	O
draw	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
tumbled	O
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
Servant	O
after	O
him	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
using	O
them	O
barbarously	O
,	O
and	O
Robbing	O
the	O
House	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
100	O
l.	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
,	O
two	O
young	O
Fellows	O
(	O
but	O
yet	O
well	O
known	O
at	O
Newgate	O
)	O
being	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Beaver	O
Hat	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
both	O
refused	O
to	O
Plead	O
positively	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
a	O
dilatory	O
way	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
knew	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
than	O
the	O
Child	O
unborn	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
like	O
;	O
persisting	O
in	O
that	O
stubborn	O
humour	O
,	O
the	O
Executioner	O
was	O
called	O
to	O
tye	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
that	O
the	O
Sentence	O
for	O
Pressing	O
should	O
be	O
read	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
at	O
that	O
Instant	O
no	O
more	O
Indictments	O
ready	O
in	O
London	O
to	O
proceed	O
upon	O
,	O
they	O
hapned	O
to	O
be	O
set	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
called	O
to	O
try	O
these	O
following	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
then	O
Indicted	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
In	O
Conclusion	O
,	O
6	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
W.	O
Riggs	O
,	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Cary	I-pers
or	O
Carriff	O
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
Sam	O
Lambourne	O
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Cherry	I-pers
.	O
As	O
many	O
Received	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
the	O
Clergy	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Conway	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Philips	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Rossington	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Lewis	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Katherine	B-pers
Steel	I-pers
.	O
8	O
or	O
more	O
obtained	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
,	O
Edw	B-pers
.	I-pers
Mackrel	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Hull	I-pers
,	O
W.	O
Griffith	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
,	O
W	B-pers
.	I-pers
Simths	O
,	O
Philip	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Walker	O
.	O
And	O
5	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
to	O
be	O
Whipt	O
.	O
Besides	O
the	O
Fellons	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
also	O
Indicted	O
at	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
,	O
some	O
Persons	O
for	O
Writing	O
and	O
Printing	O
of	O
a	O
Scandalous	O
Pamphlet	O
or	O
Libel	O
.	O
The	O
Oaths	O
of	O
Allegiance	O
and	O
Supremacy	O
,	O
were	O
again	O
tendred	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bampfield	O
and	O
Mr	O
Griffith	O
,	O
two	O
Dissenting	O
Ministers	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
them	O
refused	O
.	O
Some	O
Presentments	O
hath	O
been	O
made	O
by	O
the	O
Grand	O
Jury	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
relating	O
to	O
the	O
putting	O
the	O
Laws	O
in	O
Execution	O
against	O
Popish	O
Recusants	O
,	O
and	O
unlawful	O
Conventicles	O
.	O
We	O
hear	O
that	O
the	O
Quarter	O
Sessions	O
was	O
also	O
this	O
Week	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Surrey	O
,	O
where	O
Mr.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Vincent	I-pers
was	O
again	O
brought	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
Council	O
heard	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
,	O
his	O
Case	O
(	O
as	O
its	O
reported	O
)	O
was	O
referred	O
to	O
be	O
desided	O
at	O
the	O
Kings-Bench-Bar	O
.	O
