TOKEN	NE
AN	O
ACCOUNT	O
OF	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
Of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
,	O
And	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
HELD	O
FOR	O
THE	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
AT	O
Justice-Hall	O
,	O
IN	O
THE	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
.	O
The	O
12	O
,	O
13	O
,	O
and	O
14th	O
.	O
Days	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
1683	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
35th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Reign	O
.	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
Morning	O
the	O
Court	O
being	O
set	O
,	O
consisting	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Henry	B-pers
Tulse	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
George	B-pers
Jeffreys	I-pers
Knight	O
and	O
Barronet	O
,	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Court	O
of	O
King's-Bench	O
,	O
and	O
One	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
most	O
Honourable	O
Privy-Council	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Worshipful	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jenner	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
One	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Councellors	O
at	O
Law	O
;	O
and	O
other	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
City	O
,	O
Proclamation	O
was	O
made	O
for	O
silence	O
whilst	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Majesties	O
Commissions	O
should	O
be	O
in	O
Reading	O
:	O
Thereupon	O
the	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Commission	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
were	O
openly	O
Read	O
;	O
After	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
petty	O
Jury	O
was	O
Impannelled	O
and	O
Sworn	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
consisting	O
of	O
very	O
Honest	O
and	O
Loyal	O
Men	O
;	O
And	O
divers	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
called	O
to	O
Plead	O
to	O
their	O
Indictments	O
:	O
And	O
first	O
,	O
Rawley	B-pers
Ratford	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Tide-Surveyour	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Custom-house	O
,	O
being	O
Indicted	O
for	O
killing	O
Charles	B-pers
Augustin	I-pers
Duranda	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Outlandish	O
man	O
;	O
Edward	B-pers
Clements	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Raymond	I-pers
,	O
two	O
Watermen	O
,	O
also	O
Indicted	O
as	O
accessaries	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
;	O
It	O
did	O
appear	O
,	O
after	O
a	O
very	O
long	O
Trial	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
said	O
Augustin	O
did	O
Die	O
of	O
some	O
Blow	O
given	O
him	O
:	O
But	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
occasioned	O
by	O
a	O
refusal	O
to	O
let	O
the	O
said	O
Tide-Surveyor	O
Search	O
a	O
Boat	O
for	O
smuggled	O
Goods	O
;	O
which	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
demanded	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Companions	O
,	O
drew	O
their	O
Swords	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
refusing	O
any	O
Obedience	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
of	O
Englands	O
Authority	O
;	O
saying	O
,	O
They	O
were	O
the	O
Subjects	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
of	O
Poland	O
;	O
giving	O
likewise	O
many	O
other	O
great	O
provocations	O
:	O
So	O
that	O
Ratford	O
apprehended	O
his	O
own	O
Life	O
in	O
danger	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
conclusion	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Rawley	O
Ratford	O
being	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Officers	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
his	O
Commission	O
,	O
being	O
opposed	O
by	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
kill	O
'd	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
defence	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
Indicted	O
as	O
Accessaries	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elenor	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Murthering	O
her	O
Bastard	O
Child	O
.	O
A	O
Waterman	O
and	O
his	O
Boy	O
gave	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
day	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
instant	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
her	O
in	O
at	O
Brandford	O
,	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
Queenhithe	B-place
,	O
where	O
,	O
albeit	O
she	O
pretended	O
a	O
further	O
Journey	O
,	O
yet	O
staied	O
by	O
her	O
self	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
Landed	O
a	O
Male	O
Infant	O
was	O
found	O
dead	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
that	O
goes	O
to	O
the	O
common	O
Vaults	O
;	O
which	O
Child	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
she	O
confest	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
hers	O
.	O
She	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
alledged	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
and	O
her	O
Father-in-law	O
having	O
lodged	O
about	O
six	O
Months	O
at	O
Brandford	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
known	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
they	O
forced	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
;	O
that	O
with	O
cold	O
,	O
and	O
want	O
of	O
conveniencies	O
,	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
still	O
born	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
delivered	O
in	O
the	O
Boat	O
,	O
tho	O
concealed	O
from	O
the	O
Watermen	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Husband	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
Sea	O
.	O
Her	O
Father-in-law	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
give	O
some	O
Evidence	O
in	O
her	O
favour	O
,	O
did	O
it	O
so	O
as	O
that	O
just	O
suspition	O
was	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
the	O
Father	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Bastard	O
;	O
which	O
suspition	O
was	O
confirmed	O
by	O
evidence	O
of	O
his	O
extraordinary	O
kindness	O
to	O
his	O
Daughter	O
more	O
than	O
to	O
his	O
Wife	O
;	O
with	O
other	O
circumstances	O
.	O
And	O
no	O
proof	O
being	O
of	O
her	O
Marriage	O
,	O
more	O
than	O
her	O
saying	O
so	O
,	O
the	O
Statute	O
was	O
Read	O
in	O
that	O
case	O
:	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Murder	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Christopher	B-pers
Ashley	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
;	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
to	O
that	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
Offences	O
within	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
his	O
Clergy	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
having	O
two	O
Wives	O
now	O
living	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hargrave	I-pers
,	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
was	O
Married	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
25th	O
Year	O
of	O
this	O
King	O
,	O
at	O
Trinity	O
Minories	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
also	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
Married	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Shipman	I-pers
,	O
at	O
Lambeth	B-place
:	O
The	O
latter	O
being	O
the	O
Daughter	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Minister	O
well	O
known	O
.	O
Collins	O
owned	O
his	O
last	O
Marriage	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
first	O
was	O
so	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Twelve	O
Sacks	O
,	O
and	O
Eight	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Mault	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Lighter	O
at	O
Queenhith	B-place
,	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Shelton	I-pers
his	O
Master	O
.	O
Also	O
,	O
Henry	B-pers
English	I-pers
,	O
another	O
of	O
Shelton	O
's	O
Servant	O
s	O
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
the	O
like	O
quantity	O
of	O
Malt	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Sacks	O
,	O
from	O
Joshua	B-pers
Niblin	I-pers
.	O
And	O
the	O
said	O
Shelton	O
himself	O
likewise	O
Indicted	O
as	O
accessary	O
to	O
the	O
Theft	O
of	O
Joshua	B-pers
English	I-pers
.	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
appeared	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
to	O
be	O
Revengeful	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
Indicted	O
to	O
take	O
off	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
Councel	O
were	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
heard	O
;	O
and	O
great	O
suspition	O
discovered	O
that	O
Shelton	O
had	O
been	O
too	O
well	O
acquainted	O
with	O
these	O
actions	O
of	O
his	O
Servants	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
Gibson	O
and	O
English	O
Guilty	O
each	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
Ten	O
Pence	O
:	O
and	O
by	O
reason	O
they	O
found	O
so	O
low	O
,	O
the	O
Accessary	O
Acquitted	O
in	O
course	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Thurman	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Page	O
to	O
a	O
Noble	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
Joan	B-pers
Witherington	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Maid-servant	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Family	O
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
another	O
of	O
their	O
fellow-servant	O
s	O
,	O
for	O
taking	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Lodging-room	O
,	O
a	O
Book	O
valued	O
at	O
15	O
Shillings	O
,	O
Five	O
Guineys	O
,	O
and	O
Five	O
and	O
twenty	O
Pounds	O
in	O
Silver	O
;	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
malltious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Coney	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Denis	B-pers
Obrian	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Terruit	I-pers
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Evidence	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
these	O
Three	O
,	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Dean	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
-	O
being	O
all	O
met	O
at	O
the	O
St.	O
Albans-Tavern	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Albans-street	O
,	O
upon	O
a	O
former	O
difference	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
St.	B-place
James's-Square	I-place
and	O
Fought	O
Three	O
against	O
Three	O
;	O
Foster	O
and	O
Terruit	O
were	O
kill	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
spot	O
;	O
Deane	O
and	O
-	O
made	O
their	O
escape	O
;	O
Coney	O
and	O
Obrian	O
,	O
being	O
wounded	O
,	O
were	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
very	O
plain	O
against	O
Coney	O
;	O
who	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
two	O
Gentlemen	O
were	O
kill	O
'd	O
,	O
fled	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Tavern	O
,	O
desiring	O
they	O
would	O
hide	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
Swearing	O
Terruit	O
was	O
kill	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
.	O
Obrian	O
was	O
likewise	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Six	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
assisting	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Murther	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
wilful	O
Murder	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Edmonton	B-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Mantle	O
from	O
Ann	B-pers
Gadsbey	I-pers
;	O
no	O
good	O
Proof	O
being	O
made	O
thereof	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Tretheague	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
private-House	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	B-place
,	O
being	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joyce	B-pers
Mosse	I-pers
;	O
he	O
came	O
upon	O
a	O
Visit	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
his	O
going	O
away	O
took	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
carrying	O
the	O
Tankard	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
He	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
pretended	O
she	O
lent	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
being	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
wanting	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
Sold	O
it	O
;	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
strong	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Trason	I-pers
,	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Canvas	O
Sheets	O
from	O
Margery	B-pers
Pye	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
Haydon-yard	B-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Minories	I-place
:	O
The	O
said	O
Sheets	O
having	O
been	O
by	O
her	O
hung	O
upon	O
a	O
Line	O
to	O
dry	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Yard	O
:	O
And	O
Trason	O
confessing	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
when	O
first	O
apprehended	O
,	O
as	O
appeared	O
by	O
an	O
Examination	O
taken	O
and	O
signed	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Stout	I-pers
,	O
being	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
;	O
Francis	B-pers
Head	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
as	O
Accessories	O
thereto	O
:	O
it	O
appeared	O
the	O
said	O
Persons	O
were	O
in	O
Maskerade	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Sutton	O
was	O
a	O
Fidler	O
,	O
who	O
refusing	O
to	O
play	O
before	O
them	O
so	O
long	O
as	O
they	O
required	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
drew	O
their	O
Swords	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
Killed	O
Him	O
.	O
Mary	O
James	O
was	O
acquitted	O
:	O
But	O
Richard	B-pers
Stout	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Francis	B-pers
Head	I-pers
,	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Man-slaughter	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Stephen	B-pers
Bumsted	I-pers
,	O
Tried	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Grey	O
Gelding	O
,	O
valued	O
at	O
Six	O
and	O
forty	O
Shillings	O
,	O
from	O
a	O
person	O
unknown	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
very	O
little	O
Defence	O
;	O
only	O
pretended	O
the	O
said	O
Gelding	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
lent	O
him	O
by	O
some	O
Friend	O
near	O
Ipswich	O
;	O
but	O
producing	O
no	O
Proof	O
thereof	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Wyne	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Wheatly	I-pers
,	O
for	O
Stealing	O
as	O
much	O
Speckled	O
Wood	O
,	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
as	O
amounted	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
Sixty	O
Pounds	O
;	O
were	O
thereof	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edmund	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
valued	O
at	O
Five	O
Pounds	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Catherine	B-pers
Long	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
suspition	O
by	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
proffered	O
to	O
Sell	O
the	O
Lid	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Tankard	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
Search	O
,	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
it	O
being	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
;	O
It	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
malitious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Howel	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Child	O
of	O
about	O
Ten	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
some	O
Childrens	O
Clothes	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
when	O
first	O
Examined	O
,	O
having	O
confest	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
pence	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Patience	I-pers
,	O
having	O
been	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Ratcliff	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Oil-man	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	B-place
,	O
and	O
being	O
removed	O
from	O
her	O
said	O
Service	O
,	O
to	O
Lodge	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Widow	O
,	O
in	O
Southwark	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
Steal	O
several	O
pieces	O
of	O
Cloth	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
smal	O
Linen	O
,	O
from	O
her	O
said	O
Service	O
;	O
which	O
upon	O
Search	O
being	O
found	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
as	O
principals	O
.	O
Mary	O
Patience	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
Ten	O
Pence	O
;	O
And	O
Elizabeth	O
Hall	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Robbery	O
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
committed	O
upon	O
Thomas	B-pers
Field	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Road	O
beyond	O
Maribone	B-place
;	O
Field	O
Swore	O
positively	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
with	O
Two	O
others	O
Robbed	O
him	O
of	O
Ten	O
Shillings	O
and	O
Nine	O
Pence	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
small	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
drawing	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
Field	O
,	O
left	O
him	O
Bound	O
:	O
That	O
this	O
was	O
done	O
about	O
Sun-set	O
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mayors	O
Day	O
:	O
Against	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
produced	O
Four	O
or	O
Five	O
credible	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
That	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Read	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
Merchant	O
,	O
in	O
Aldermanbury	O
;	O
And	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
being	O
also	O
called	O
,	O
that	O
spoke	O
much	O
of	O
Price	O
's	O
good	O
Reputation	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
therefore	O
acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Clipping	O
Eight	O
half-Crowns	O
,	O
and	O
Six	O
Shillings	O
.	O
Several	O
were	O
produced	O
from	O
whom	O
he	O
frequently	O
obtained	O
broad	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
upon	O
his	O
re-payments	O
of	O
any	O
Sum	O
,	O
much	O
of	O
it	O
Clipt	O
.	O
Also	O
one	O
Nickson	O
,	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Companion	O
of	O
his	O
in	O
those	O
Practices	O
,	O
Swore	O
positively	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
often	O
seen	O
him	O
Clip	O
the	O
Currant	O
Mony	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
.	O
In	O
conclusion	O
,	O
upon	O
a	O
clear	O
Evidence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
High	O
Treason	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Gowen	B-pers
Harden	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Killing	O
John	B-pers
Sexton	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Grays-Inn-lane	B-place
,	O
was	O
thereof	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Rastal	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Killing	O
Richard	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
by	O
Blows	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
Fighting	O
,	O
(	O
being	O
Youth	O
s	O
)	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Roger	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
several	O
Good	O
,	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
for	O
Stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
but	O
Acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
going	O
into	O
a	O
Shop	O
in	O
Shoreditch	B-place
,	O
and	O
Stealing	O
from	O
thence	O
a	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
Twelve	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Philip	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Ravishing	O
Jane	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Girl	O
of	O
Twelve	O
Years	O
Old	O
.	O
The	O
Girl	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
also	O
her	O
Mother	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Midwife	O
gave	O
some	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
either	O
their	O
over-much	O
modesty	O
,	O
or	O
for	O
some	O
other	O
reason	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
favourable	O
,	O
that	O
no	O
positive	O
Proof	O
being	O
thereof	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
having	O
been	O
Seven	O
weeks	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
some	O
Ale-House-keeper	O
in	O
Moor-lane	B-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
she	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
some	O
Cravats	O
,	O
or	O
other	O
small	O
Linen	O
,	O
from	O
her	O
said	O
Master	B-pers
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
Six	O
Pence	O
only	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
that	O
having	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
24th	O
Year	O
of	O
this	O
King	O
,	O
been	O
Married	O
to	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Moor	I-pers
;	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
was	O
likewise	O
Married	O
to	O
Amy	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
:	O
The	O
former	O
being	O
a	O
live	O
;	O
but	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
coming	O
in	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
One	O
to	O
Prosecute	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Margery	B-pers
Yoel	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Feltom	B-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
a	O
poor	O
ancient	O
Man	O
that	O
lived	O
alone	O
;	O
and	O
with	O
another	O
Woman	O
in	O
her	O
Company	O
(	O
both	O
disguised	O
in	O
Mens	O
Clothes	O
)	O
Rob	O
'd	O
him	O
of	O
a	O
Grey	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
new	O
Shooes	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Breeches	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
and	O
indeed	O
,	O
all	O
of	O
value	O
the	O
poor	O
Man	O
had	O
;	O
threatning	O
to	O
Kill	O
him	O
,	O
unless	O
he	O
would	O
produce	O
them	O
some	O
Mony	O
:	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Hartshorn	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Starkey	I-pers
,	O
(	O
formerly	O
'Servant	O
s	O
to	O
Goodenough	O
and	O
Aaron	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
)	O
Indicted	O
for	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Lord	I-pers
Pagett	I-pers
,	O
at	O
West-Drayden	B-place
,	O
demanding	O
Entrance	O
at	O
Three	O
or	O
Four	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
with	O
Pistols	O
and	O
drawn	O
Swords	O
in	O
their	O
hands	O
,	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
Searching	O
for	O
Traytors	O
,	O
offering	O
great	O
Rudeness	O
and	O
Violence	O
,	O
forcing	O
all	O
the	O
Servants	O
(	O
one	O
excepted	O
)	O
into	O
the	O
Hall	O
,	O
set	O
a	O
Guard	O
over	O
them	O
,	O
then	O
making	O
the	O
Steward	O
shew	O
them	O
all	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
likewise	O
confined	O
him	O
amongst	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Servants	O
,	O
whilst	O
for	O
an	O
hour	O
or	O
two	O
they	O
Ransack	O
'd	O
about	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
running	O
their	O
Swords	O
through	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Beds	O
:	O
And	O
other	O
like	O
Misdemeanours	O
.	O
In	O
their	O
Defence	O
they	O
produced	O
Warrants	O
Impowering	O
them	O
to	O
Search	O
for	O
certain	O
Traitors	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Instructions	O
to	O
Search	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
that	O
Honourable	O
Peer	O
:	O
Therefore	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
a	O
Trespass	O
and	O
Assault	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
How	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Ring	O
,	O
a	O
Razor	O
,	O
two	O
Silk	O
Purses	O
,	O
and	O
Three	O
Pounds	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Latham	I-pers
;	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Knowles	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hanson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wedge	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Richard	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
Stole	O
two	O
Cows	O
;	O
One	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Bilson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
other	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Windmill	I-pers
.	O
Wedge	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Roger	B-pers
Wixley	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Goldsmith	B-pers
s	O
Glass	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shop	O
;	O
wherein	O
was	O
48	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
several	O
Necklaces	O
,	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
of	O
value	O
;	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Delawn	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Zacharias	B-pers
Ralphson	I-pers
,	O
being	O
Indicted	O
as	O
the	O
Authors	O
of	O
Seditious	O
Libels	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
said	O
Bills	O
found	O
,	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
Pleaded	O
thereto	O
not	O
Guilty	O
;	O
Praying	O
Coppies	O
of	O
their	O
Indictments	O
,	O
and	O
time	O
till	O
next	O
Sessions	O
to	O
try	O
them	O
:	O
Which	O
were	O
both	O
granted	O
.	O
Langly	B-pers
Curtis	I-pers
likewise	O
Pleaded	O
not	O
Guilty	O
to	O
an	O
Indictment	O
,	O
for	O
Publishing	O
the	O
Libel	O
Entituled	O
,	O
The	O
Night	O
Walker	O
of	O
Bloomsbury	O
:	O
He	O
praying	O
time	O
till	O
next	O
Sessions	O
;	O
offering	O
Bail	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
sufficient	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
taking	O
notice	O
of	O
him	O
for	O
an	O
Old	O
Offendor	O
,	O
Committed	O
him	O
to	O
Newgate	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
also	O
;	O
at	O
Hicks's-Hall	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Hawkers	O
that	O
Sold	O
this	O
Pamphlet	O
,	O
The	O
Night-Walker	O
of	O
Bloomsbury	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
The	O
Lord	O
Russel	O
's	O
Ghost	O
:	O
Ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Whipt	O
round	O
the	O
Market-place	O
at	O
Bloomsbury	O
.	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
ended	O
,	O
Judgment	O
was	O
given	O
,	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Six	O
Persons	O
received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
Viz	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Coney	I-pers
,	O
Dennis	B-pers
Obrian	I-pers
,	O
Stephen	B-pers
Bumsted	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
Elenor	O
Adams	O
,	O
and	O
Margery	B-pers
Toel	I-pers
:	O
Amongst	O
which	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
to	O
be	O
Drawn	O
on	O
a	O
Hurdle	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
of	O
Execution	O
.	O
Three	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
Thomas	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Trethague	I-pers
.	O
Richard	O
Stout	O
,	O
and	O
Francis	B-pers
Heait	I-pers
,	O
who	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
,	O
beg	O
'd	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
their	O
Clergy	O
:	O
But	O
by	O
reason	O
some	O
Persons	O
who	O
Assisted	O
at	O
the	O
taking	O
them	O
,	O
lie	O
dangerously	O
sick	O
of	O
Wounds	O
then	O
received	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
thought	O
fit	O
to	O
suspend	O
their	O
Judgment	O
till	O
another	O
Sessions	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
indicted	O
as	O
Accessary	O
with	O
the	O
said	O
Stout	O
and	O
Head	O
,	O
though	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
yet	O
is	O
for	O
the	O
like	O
,	O
or	O
other	O
reason	O
,	O
continued	O
in	O
Goal	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
Twelve	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
:	O
Patrick	B-pers
May	I-pers
,	O
John	O
Hockins	O
,	O
Christopher	O
Ashler	O
,	O
Henry	O
Wyne	O
,	O
Robert	O
Wheatly	O
,	O
Roger	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
John	O
Howard	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Danson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
How	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Roger	O
Wicksly	O
.	O
Five	O
to	O
be	O
Whipt	O
:	O
Henry	B-pers
English	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Howel	O
,	O
William	O
Gibson	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Trason	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Patience	I-pers
:	O
Sentenc	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
Whipt	O
from	O
Newgate	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
several	O
Places	O
where	O
their	O
respective	O
Facts	O
were	O
committed	O
.	O
Nathaniel	O
Hartshorn	O
,	O
and	O
Samuel	O
Starkey	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Trespass	O
and	O
Assault	O
;	O
upon	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
set	O
a	O
fine	O
of	O
a	O
hundred	O
pounds	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bampfield	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Greffith	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Nonconformist	O
Ministers	O
,	O
are	O
yet	O
continued	O
in	O
Newgate	O
.	O
Six	O
Scotchmen	O
lately	O
commited	O
for	O
refusal	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Oathes	O
of	O
Allegiance	O
and	O
Supremacy	O
being	O
all	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
five	O
of	O
them	O
continued	O
in	O
their	O
obstinate	O
refusal	O
,	O
and	O
are	O
recommitted	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
took	O
the	O
said	O
Oaths	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
entring	O
into	O
a	O
Recognizance	O
of	O
200	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Draper	O
of	O
this	O
City	O
for	O
him	O
in	O
100	O
l.	O
for	O
his	O
being	O
of	O
the	O
good	O
behaviour	O
till	O
the	O
Quarter	O
Sessions	O
,	O
which	O
shall	O
be	O
after	O
Michaelmas	O
next	O
he	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
