TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
Of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
,	O
And	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
HELD	O
FOR	O
THE	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
AT	O
Justice-Hall	O
,	O
IN	O
THE	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
.	O
The	O
3d	O
.	O
4th	O
.	O
and	O
5th	O
.	O
Days	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
1684	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
36th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
being	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bayly	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
the	O
3d	O
.	O
4th	O
.	O
and	O
5th	O
.	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
1684.	O
before	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Henry	B-pers
Tulse	I-pers
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jenner	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Majesties	O
Serjeants	O
at	O
Law	O
,	O
and	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
other	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Tuly	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Dandridge	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Juxon	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Bradley	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Leak	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
Roger	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
,	O
Edm	B-pers
.	I-pers
Jackson	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Baxter	I-pers
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Bateman	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Supple	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Leeson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Parkinson	I-pers
,	O
Stephen	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hardy	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Boyce	I-pers
,	O
Zachariah	B-pers
Grant	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
William	B-pers
Peirce	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bay	O
Gelding	O
price	O
5	O
l.	O
from	O
Edmond	B-pers
Prideaux	I-pers
,	O
at	O
Hornsey	B-place
.	O
The	O
Matter	O
against	O
him	O
appear	O
'd	O
;	O
That	O
William	B-pers
Peirce	I-pers
rode	O
upon	O
this	O
Gelding	O
to	O
Gravesend	O
,	O
where	O
setting	O
him	O
up	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
White-Hart	O
,	O
be	O
agreed	O
with	O
the	O
Inn	O
keeper	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
him	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
Month	O
afterwards	O
the	O
Gelding	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
Gazette	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Reward	O
of	O
20	O
s.	O
proposed	O
to	O
such	O
as	O
should	O
discover	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
:	O
hereupon	O
,	O
Peirce	O
thinking	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
Reward	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
the	O
Gelding	O
comes	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Prideaux	O
,	O
and	O
informed	O
him	O
that	O
the	O
Horse	O
was	O
at	O
Gravesend	O
aforesaid	O
:	O
where	O
Prideaux	O
enquiring	O
after	O
it	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Master	O
of	O
the	O
Inn	O
producing	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
Peirce	O
,	O
Pierce	O
was	O
soon	O
after	O
apprehended	O
.	O
All	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
hired	O
this	O
Horse	O
of	O
one	O
Traverse	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
lately	O
hanged	O
for	O
a	O
Robbery	O
committed	O
in	O
Hornsey	O
,	O
which	O
Traverse	O
's	O
Wife	O
swore	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
believing	O
her	O
,	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
and	O
Martin	B-pers
Stevenson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Murdering	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
Servant	O
to	O
Sr.	O
George	B-pers
Downing	I-pers
at	O
Knightsbridge	B-place
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Tryal	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
this	O
William	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
about	O
Ten	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
of	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
with	O
one	O
Athis	O
,	O
about	O
nailing	O
up	O
a	O
door	O
that	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
said	O
R.	O
Burton	O
and	O
Martin	B-pers
Stevenson	I-pers
(	O
being	O
a	O
Constable	O
and	O
a	O
Beadle	O
)	O
by	O
chance	O
then	O
coming	O
by	O
,	O
commanded	O
the	O
Peace	O
;	O
which	O
Fletcher	O
not	O
observing	O
,	O
they	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
bruised	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
as	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
said	O
Persons	O
being	O
upon	O
their	O
Duty	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
positively	O
proved	O
that	O
he	O
died	O
of	O
those	O
Wounds	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Wheate	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Paddington	B-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
dark	O
Brown	O
Gelding	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
:	O
the	O
matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
against	O
him	O
being	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Gelding	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Possession	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Wheate	O
.	O
But	O
Wheate	O
produced	O
his	O
Witness	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
said	O
Horse	O
at	O
Blockamore	O
Fair	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Gelding	O
in	O
dispute	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
he	O
there	O
bought	O
:	O
whereupon	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
not	O
Guilty	O
William	B-pers
Dier	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bag	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
containing	O
forty	O
pounds	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Edward	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
Esquire	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Tryal	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Hackney-Coachman	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
taken	O
up	O
Esq	O
;	O
Howard	O
in	O
Bow-street	O
in	O
Covent-Garden	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
Norfolk-street	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
and	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Coach	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drove	O
away	O
without	O
taking	O
his	O
Hire	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Money	O
lying	O
upon	O
the	O
Seat	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
observed	O
to	O
turn	O
and	O
tumble	O
about	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
producing	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
his	O
Honesty	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Body	O
swearing	O
positive	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Long	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tumbler	O
,	O
Val	O
.	O
35	O
s.	O
being	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Clough	I-pers
,	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Lanceve	I-pers
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lord	I-pers
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
31th	O
.	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
Assault	O
upon	O
one	O
Robert	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
High-way	O
rob	O
him	O
of	O
a	O
Watch	O
with	O
two	O
Silver	O
Cases	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Harvey	O
coming	O
late	O
at	O
Night	O
by	O
a	O
Tavern	O
near	O
Shoe-lane	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
and	O
going	O
in	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
said	O
two	O
Persons	O
,	O
with	O
whom	O
he	O
sat	O
a	O
while	O
drinking	O
;	O
That	O
at	O
his	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
they	O
made	O
an	O
Assault	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
That	O
Sam	B-pers
.	I-pers
Lord	I-pers
held	O
him	O
whilst	O
Lanceve	O
took	O
his	O
said	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
pleaded	O
,	O
Harvey	O
went	O
away	O
refusing	O
to	O
pay	O
a	O
Shilling	O
for	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
following	O
him	O
down	O
Stairs	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
he	O
delivered	O
them	O
his	O
Watch	O
to	O
clear	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
But	O
by	O
reason	O
Lanecve	O
fled	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
pawned	O
the	O
said	O
Watch	O
for	O
30	O
s.	O
that	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
when	O
called	O
,	O
found	O
Harvey	O
to	O
be	O
bloody	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Band	O
to	O
be	O
torn	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
aggravating	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
Lanceve	O
and	O
Lord	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Robbery	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
three	O
Pair	O
of	O
laced	O
Sleeves	O
one	O
laced	O
Cravat	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Stockings	O
,	O
five	O
Pair	O
of	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Vickers	I-pers
.	O
The	O
said	O
Smith	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
Company	O
,	O
came	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Cooks	O
at	O
the	O
Sun	B-place
Tavern	I-place
behind	I-place
the	I-place
Royal	I-place
Exchange	I-place
to	O
drink	O
Wine	O
;	O
and	O
taking	O
his	O
Opportunity	O
,	O
went	O
up	O
another	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
breaking	O
open	O
a	O
Trunk	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
stole	O
away	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
.	O
All	O
his	O
Companions	O
slipt	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
stop	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
as	O
paying	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Ratcliff	I-pers
,	O
hired	O
Servant	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
set	O
with	O
nine	O
Diamond	O
Stones	O
value	O
20	O
or	O
30	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
from	O
her	O
said	O
Master	O
;	O
which	O
Ring	O
she	O
had	O
Pawned	O
for	O
but	O
5	O
s.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
length	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
saying	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
ill	O
thing	O
she	O
ever	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
seemed	O
to	O
beg	O
for	O
Mercy	O
:	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Gerrard	B-pers
Trent	I-pers
and	O
Lewis	B-pers
Conoway	I-pers
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
kill	O
'd	O
one	O
Richard	B-pers
Mowbray	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Butcher	O
,	O
whom	O
they	O
met	O
in	O
Drury	B-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
late	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
One	O
Witness	O
proved	O
he	O
saw	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
pass	O
at	O
the	O
Butcher	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
him	O
thereupon	O
fall	O
;	O
another	O
said	O
that	O
seeing	O
the	O
Man	O
lye	O
dead	O
,	O
Trent	O
was	O
next	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
a	O
third	O
Witness	O
was	O
so	O
near	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
run	O
him	O
through	O
the	O
Sleeve	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
produced	O
some	O
to	O
say	O
they	O
heard	O
a	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
Streets	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
Will	O
you	O
rob	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
their	O
Wiggs	O
and	O
Hats	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
suggest	O
the	O
Butcher	O
would	O
have	O
robbed	O
them	O
:	O
The	O
Witnesses	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
seemed	O
to	O
bring	O
it	O
very	O
home	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
had	O
before	O
abused	O
some	O
Gentlewomen	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
the	O
Watch	O
.	O
In	O
conclusion	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
as	O
to	O
Murder	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
of	O
Man	O
slaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
One	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
18	O
Yards	O
of	O
Flowered	O
Silk	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Bantlin	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
taking	O
two	O
Iron	O
Locks	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
d.	O
being	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
Mark	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Gale	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
in	O
Clipping	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
forty	O
Pieces	O
called	O
Queen	O
Elizabeth	O
Shillings	O
,	O
forty	O
other	O
Pieces	O
called	O
King	O
James	O
Shillings	O
,	O
forty	O
other	O
Pieces	O
called	O
King	O
Charles	O
the	O
First	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
forty	O
Pieces	O
called	O
King	O
Charles	O
the	O
First	O
Half	O
Crowns	O
;	O
clipping	O
and	O
diminishing	O
from	O
each	O
of	O
the	O
Shillings	O
,	O
Silver	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
from	O
each	O
of	O
the	O
Half-Crowns	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
d.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Tryal	O
was	O
only	O
proved	O
,	O
that	O
Foster	O
had	O
frequently	O
Changed	O
Guinea	O
's	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
20	O
,	O
30	O
,	O
or	O
40	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
,	O
for	O
Silver	O
;	O
with	O
other	O
like	O
Circumstances	O
:	O
and	O
against	O
Gale	O
,	O
that	O
in	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
7	O
l.	O
16	O
s.	O
of	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
33	O
clip	O
'd	O
Shillings	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Instruments	O
to	O
Clip	O
with	O
being	O
found	O
,	O
nor	O
Proof	O
that	O
any	O
see	O
them	O
Clip	O
Money	O
.	O
Likewise	O
Gale	O
producing	O
near	O
twenty	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
therefore	O
Acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Christian	B-pers
Bromfeild	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Jorden	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Maid	O
Servant	O
to	O
Geo	B-pers
.	I-pers
Bromfeild	I-pers
of	O
Wood-street	B-place
,	O
London	O
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
one	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
,	O
Value	O
35	O
s.	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
Value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
Value	O
30	O
s.	O
two	O
Suits	O
of	O
laced	O
Child	O
bed	O
Linnen	O
,	O
Value	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
four	O
other	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
Value	O
30	O
s.	O
two	O
laced	O
Cravats	O
,	O
one	O
long	O
Scarf	O
,	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
Pounds	O
in	O
Money	O
;	O
being	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
her	O
said	O
Master	O
,	O
from	O
whom	O
with	O
she	O
said	O
Goods	O
she	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
at	O
Newcastle	O
upon	O
Tyne	O
.	O
She	O
confess	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Tryal	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
led	O
away	O
by	O
ill	O
Company	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
said	O
Things	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
So	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Todd	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Gelding	O
coloured	O
Gray	O
,	O
price	O
4	O
l.	O
from	O
Jonas	B-pers
Rigden	I-pers
living	O
at	O
Throwley	B-place
in	I-place
Kent	I-place
.	O
The	O
said	O
Rigdin	O
missing	O
his	O
Horse	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
Man	O
riding	O
him	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
challenged	O
to	O
have	O
stol'n	O
his	O
Horse	O
:	O
The	O
said	O
Person	O
produced	O
Todd	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
the	O
said	O
Horse	O
of	O
;	O
the	O
said	O
Todd	O
was	O
therefore	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hyde	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Minister	O
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
having	O
married	O
a	O
second	O
Wife	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
being	O
yet	O
alive	O
,	O
and	O
proved	O
he	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
.	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
29th	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
Married	O
to	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
11th	O
.	O
of	O
November	O
in	O
the	O
35th	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
to	O
one	O
-	B-pers
Richins	I-pers
;	O
that	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
he	O
had	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Children	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Mr.	O
Hyde	O
upon	O
the	O
Tryal	O
denied	O
he	O
even	O
saw	O
the	O
last	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
very	O
strange	O
of	O
them	O
both	O
;	O
but	O
was	O
however	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Bonner	I-pers
,	O
Widdow	O
,	O
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Herne	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
,	O
Widdow	O
,	O
living	O
about	O
Basing-hall-street	B-place
,	O
London	O
.	O
After	O
Examination	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Herne	I-pers
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
pawned	O
the	O
Cup	O
for	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
said	O
Ann	B-pers
Bonner	I-pers
had	O
half	O
the	O
Money	O
:	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
each	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Cruffe	I-pers
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
.	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
he	O
made	O
an	O
Assault	O
upon	O
William	B-pers
Culliford	I-pers
,	O
Esquire	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
passing	O
from	O
the	O
Custom-House	O
,	O
London	O
,	O
through	O
Water-lane	B-place
,	O
shooting	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Back	O
with	O
a	O
Brace	O
of	O
Bullets	O
,	O
with	O
Intent	O
to	O
kill	O
and	O
murder	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
at	O
first	O
evaded	O
Pleading	O
;	O
but	O
at	O
length	O
said	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Culliford	O
had	O
put	O
a	O
Clog	O
upon	O
his	O
Conscience	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
Reason	O
he	O
resolved	O
to	O
put	O
one	O
upon	O
his	O
Body	O
(	O
or	O
upon	O
his	O
Heart	O
)	O
confessing	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Caskey	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Scotch-man	O
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Teagle	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Watch-man	O
,	O
at	O
Rosemary-lane	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
.	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
Upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
thus	O
;	O
viz	O
.	O
This	O
Geo	O
.	O
Caskey	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Francis	B-pers
Pevanson	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Peverson	I-pers
,	O
a	O
French-man	O
,	O
and	O
Daniel	B-pers
Ballantine	I-pers
an	O
Italian	O
having	O
been	O
drinking	O
at	O
a	O
Musick	O
House	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
coming	O
away	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
another	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Wine	O
;	O
which	O
the	O
Master	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
refused	O
:	O
at	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
highly	O
offended	O
,	O
broke	O
the	O
Windows	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
abused	O
the	O
Woman	O
:	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
Master	O
going	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
just	O
against	O
his	O
Door	O
,	O
told	O
the	O
Watch	O
of	O
the	O
Disturbance	O
made	O
by	O
these	O
Gentlemen	O
.	O
Whereupon	O
,	O
Teagle	O
the	O
Watch-man	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
kill	O
'd	O
,	O
ran	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
meeting	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Parties	O
,	O
bid	O
him	O
come	O
over	O
to	O
the	O
Constable	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
at	O
first	O
refusing	O
,	O
whether	O
the	O
said	O
Teagle	O
struck	O
him	O
or	O
laid	O
Hands	O
on	O
him	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
Proof	O
,	O
but	O
thereupon	O
he	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Breast	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Wound	O
he	O
died	O
.	O
Several	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
produced	O
who	O
proved	O
positively	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
kill	O
'd	O
the	O
Watch-man	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
of	O
a	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
their	O
Swords	O
severally	O
drawn	O
.	O
This	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
for	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
brought	O
several	O
Persons	O
of	O
Quality	O
who	O
testified	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
Honesty	O
and	O
Reputation	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
rarely	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
given	O
to	O
Quarrel	O
:	O
besides	O
,	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
spoke	O
disgracefully	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
It	O
was	O
no	O
better	O
than	O
a	O
Bawdy-House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
several	O
People	O
had	O
come	O
to	O
Damage	O
by	O
resorting	O
thither	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
with	O
Ballantine	O
the	O
Italian	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
before	O
the	O
French-man	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
Mischief	O
had	O
befell	O
the	O
Watch-man	O
;	O
but	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
make	O
of	O
and	O
escape	O
the	O
Round-house	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
followed	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
:	O
The	O
Party	O
that	O
did	O
the	O
Murder	O
made	O
his	O
way	O
towards	O
Well-Close	O
:	O
but	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
Evidence	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Accessary	O
in	O
Murder	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
legally	O
Convicted	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
thereof	O
.	O
In	O
like	O
manner	O
,	O
Pevanson	O
and	O
Ballantine	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Murder	O
,	O
tryed	O
by	O
a	O
Party	O
Jury	O
,	O
half	O
English	O
and	O
half	O
Foreigners	O
;	O
and	O
both	O
also	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Murder	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Cowley	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Coach-man	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
London	O
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
driving	O
his	O
Coach	O
,	O
drawn	O
with	O
two	O
Horses	O
,	O
over	O
the	O
Head	O
of	O
Edith	B-pers
Isham	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Child	O
of	O
three	O
Years	O
old	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
very	O
strong	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
That	O
two	O
Children	O
playing	O
together	O
in	O
Chiswel-street	B-place
,	O
upon	O
the	O
turning	O
of	O
the	O
Corner	O
,	O
being	O
upon	O
his	O
full	O
Trot	O
,	O
he	O
beat	O
down	O
both	O
the	O
Children	O
;	O
Edith	B-pers
Isham	I-pers
was	O
run	O
over	O
and	O
slain	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
under	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
escaped	O
:	O
after	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
drove	O
away	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
;	O
and	O
tho	O
often	O
called	O
unto	O
to	O
stop	O
the	O
said	O
Coach	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
hearken	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
Shoreditch	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
forc	O
'd	O
to	O
alight	O
;	O
and	O
was	O
thereupon	O
secured	O
.	O
What	O
he	O
offered	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
said	O
Children	O
,	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
at	O
that	O
Instant	O
calling	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
drive	O
on	O
and	O
he	O
stooping	O
to	O
hear	O
what	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
happened	O
to	O
commit	O
this	O
unfortunate	O
Accident	O
:	O
The	O
reason	O
why	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
when	O
called	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
the	O
Party	O
calling	O
him	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Man	O
slaughter	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Dethwick	I-pers
and	I-pers
Ann	I-pers
and	O
Ann	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
of	O
White-lyon-street	B-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Parish	I-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
for	O
Coyning	O
and	O
washing	O
several	O
false	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Money	O
;	O
viz	O
.	O
thirty	O
Pieces	O
in	O
Imitation	O
of	O
King	O
Charles	O
the	O
First	O
Half	O
Crowns	O
,	O
forty	O
Pieces	O
in	O
Imitation	O
of	O
Queen	O
Elizabeth	O
's	O
Shillings	O
.	O
The	O
Witnesses	O
against	O
them	O
proved	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
disposed	O
of	O
several	O
of	O
these	O
Counterfeit	O
Pieces	O
in	O
Bartholomew-Fair	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
William	B-pers
Dethwick	I-pers
would	O
particularly	O
have	O
sold	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Pieces	O
to	O
them	O
:	O
however	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Tue	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Graves	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
William	B-pers
Graves	I-pers
being	O
a	O
Bayliffs	O
Follower	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
the	O
Bayliff	O
and	O
three	O
others	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	O
Tue	O
,	O
who	O
kept	O
an	O
Ale	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
for	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
supplied	O
them	O
;	O
when	O
as	O
is	O
supposed	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
suspecting	O
them	O
for	O
Bayliffs	O
,	O
passed	O
by	O
the	O
Door	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
drinking	O
,	O
and	O
makes	O
towards	O
his	O
Kitchin	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
armed	O
himself	O
with	O
a	O
Halbard	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
following	O
him	O
,	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
the	O
Writ	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Word	O
of	O
the	O
Arrest	O
:	O
but	O
not	O
having	O
laid	O
hands	O
on	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Word	O
was	O
not	O
sufficient	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
yet	O
touched	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
come	O
near	O
him	O
at	O
their	O
Peril	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Followers	O
being	O
more	O
resolute	O
than	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
received	O
two	O
Wounds	O
one	O
through	O
his	O
Hand	O
the	O
other	O
in	O
his	O
Arm	O
;	O
but	O
with	O
the	O
Advantage	O
of	O
his	O
Weapon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drove	O
them	O
all	O
clear	O
of	O
his	O
Kitchin	O
,	O
and	O
shut	O
the	O
Door	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
resolving	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
,	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
said	O
Kitchin	O
door	O
and	O
enter	O
'd	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
upon	O
him	O
:	O
Graves	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
was	O
kill	O
'd	O
)	O
whilst	O
Tue	O
was	O
opposing	O
his	O
Companions	O
,	O
gets	O
in	O
at	O
a	O
Back-door	O
;	O
which	O
Tue	O
espying	O
turns	O
suddenly	O
about	O
darts	O
his	O
Holbard	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
wounds	O
him	O
under	O
the	O
left	O
Pap	O
;	O
of	O
which	O
,	O
without	O
speaking	O
one	O
Word	O
,	O
he	O
died	O
:	O
upon	O
whose	O
Death	O
he	O
was	O
secured	O
.	O
Tue	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
brought	O
several	O
of	O
his	O
Neighbours	O
to	O
prove	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
strove	O
to	O
possess	O
the	O
Court	O
that	O
they	O
never	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Word	O
of	O
Arrest	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
same	O
being	O
proved	O
by	O
all	O
the	O
four	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Writ	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
willful	O
Murder	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
observable	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
Action	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
that	O
,	O
likewise	O
upon	O
Dispute	O
between	O
Him	O
and	O
the	O
Plantiff	O
,	O
yet	O
was	O
he	O
so	O
desperate	O
to	O
attempt	O
this	O
fatal	O
and	O
execrable	O
Action	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Tinker	O
,	O
living	O
at	O
Killingham	B-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
killing	O
his	O
Wife	O
Martha	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Neighbours	O
who	O
came	O
as	O
Witnesses	O
proved	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
threw	O
her	O
violently	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
kick	O
'd	O
and	O
beat	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
Neck	O
,	O
Stomach	O
,	O
and	O
Belly	O
;	O
of	O
which	O
Blows	O
and	O
Bruises	O
she	O
languished	O
from	O
the	O
said	O
22th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
and	O
Languishing	O
died	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
August	O
following	O
.	O
The	O
Sister	O
of	O
his	O
wife	O
proved	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
,	O
on	O
her	O
Death-Bed	O
,	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
her	O
Death	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
Died	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
revenged	O
by	O
her	O
said	O
Sister	O
.	O
All	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
Positively	O
Swore	O
,	O
That	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
Womans	O
Languishing	O
,	O
she	O
still	O
laid	O
her	O
Death	O
at	O
her	O
Husbands	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
never	O
be	O
induced	O
to	O
Pardon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Day	O
after	O
her	O
Beating	O
,	O
she	O
spit	O
Blood	O
Extreamly	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
her	O
Beating	O
,	O
she	O
Bled	O
at	O
least	O
a	O
Pint	O
and	O
a	O
Half	O
:	O
which	O
as	O
was	O
given	O
in	O
Evidence	O
,	O
she	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
Wash	O
and	O
scrape	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
were	O
the	O
same	O
was	O
Shed	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
out	O
the	O
Marks	O
thereof	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
no	O
material	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
his	O
Wife	O
was	O
Drunk	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
she	O
pretended	O
she	O
was	O
Beaten	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
fell	O
Down	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
Swore	O
positively	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
see	O
him	O
drag	O
her	O
along	O
the	O
Street	O
by	O
the	O
Heels	O
,	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
laid	O
her	O
Head	O
over	O
the	O
Threshold	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
turn	O
'd	O
her	O
Heels	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
shutting	O
the	O
Door	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
This	O
Fact	O
was	O
the	O
more	O
Barbarous	O
in	O
that	O
the	O
Woman	O
that	O
was	O
thus	O
Kill	O
'd	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
Young	O
Woman	O
,	O
not	O
above	O
25	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
be	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
and	O
Honest	O
Life	O
and	O
Carriage	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
50	O
or	O
upwards	O
:	O
and	O
that	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
thus	O
Beaten	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
took	O
the	O
least	O
Care	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
thereby	O
done	O
her	O
Business	O
,	O
she	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
some	O
other	O
time	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
further	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
Fellow	O
was	O
supposed	O
to	O
have	O
Murthered	O
his	O
former	O
Wife	O
;	O
for	O
that	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
Testified	O
she	O
had	O
Died	O
Suddenly	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
under	O
the	O
Bed	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
her	O
Hair	O
about	O
her	O
Ears	O
.	O
The	O
Fellow	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
ill	O
Look	O
and	O
Character	O
;	O
by	O
all	O
that	O
appeared	O
against	O
him	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
Evidence	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
Plain	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Willful	O
Murder	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jeffes	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Stephen	I-place
Coleman-street	I-place
,	O
by	O
keeping	O
a	O
dangerous	O
Dog	O
who	O
used	O
to	O
fly	O
upon	O
and	O
bite	O
People	O
:	O
and	O
albeit	O
he	O
had	O
several	O
times	O
been	O
warned	O
to	O
hang	O
the	O
Dog	O
,	O
yet	O
refused	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
23th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
the	O
said	O
Dog	O
bit	O
Martin	O
so	O
as	O
he	O
died	O
thereof	O
:	O
Jeffes	O
was	O
however	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Selly	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
in	O
Coyning	O
and	O
Washing	O
twenty	O
false	O
Guinea	O
's	O
forty	O
Half	O
Crowns	O
in	O
Imitation	O
of	O
King	O
Charles	O
the	O
First	O
Half	O
Crowns	O
,	O
fifty	O
Pieces	O
in	O
Imitation	O
of	O
King	O
James	O
's	O
Shillings	O
forty	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Queen	O
Elizabeth	O
Shillings	O
.	O
Three	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
produced	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
had	O
put	O
off	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Guinea	O
's	O
for	O
him	O
:	O
yet	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
no	O
positive	O
Proof	O
of	O
the	O
Coining	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Tredeech	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Tredeech	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Hair	O
Camblet	O
Coat	O
,	O
Value	O
40	O
s.	O
one	O
Silk	O
Faringdon	O
Mantua	O
Gown	O
,	O
Value	O
12	O
s.	O
one	O
Flaxen	O
Shirt	O
,	O
Value	O
4	O
s.	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Egleton	I-pers
,	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Payne	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Book	O
called	O
Cuckolds	O
Folly	O
,	O
Value	O
13	O
s.	O
another	O
called	O
Hookers	O
Policy	O
,	O
Value	O
14	O
s.	O
with	O
several	O
other	O
Books	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Lombard-street	B-place
,	O
London	O
.	O
Also	O
Samuel	B-pers
Foreman	I-pers
Indicted	O
,	O
as	O
accessary	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Felony	O
,	O
in	O
receiving	O
the	O
said	O
stol'n	O
Goods	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
both	O
accordingly	O
found	O
guilty	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
the	O
latter	O
as	O
accessary	O
thereto	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Rickets	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Goffe	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
Crape	O
Shrowds	O
,	O
Value	O
10	O
s.	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
.	O
The	O
Witnesses	O
against	O
them	O
swore	O
that	O
Goffe	O
brought	O
the	O
Crape	O
to	O
them	O
to	O
scour	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Stains	O
which	O
were	O
upon	O
it	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
Purging	O
of	O
dead	O
Bodies	O
;	O
therefore	O
concluded	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
some	O
Graves	O
.	O
But	O
Rickets	O
produced	O
several	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Shrowds	O
were	O
stained	O
in	O
a	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
by	O
Rats	O
or	O
other	O
Vermine	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
such	O
other	O
Defence	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Ditcher	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Fuller	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
forty	O
pieces	O
of	O
Guinea	O
Gold	O
,	O
Value	O
,	O
every	O
one	O
,	O
21	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
.	O
The	O
most	O
material	O
Witness	O
was	O
a	O
Boy	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
Ditcher	O
being	O
his	O
Uncle	O
,	O
demanded	O
of	O
him	O
where	O
his	O
Grandfather	O
's	O
Gold	O
was	O
?	O
The	O
Boy	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Waste	O
band	O
of	O
his	O
Breeches	O
:	O
It	O
was	O
also	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
old	O
Man	O
had	O
this	O
Gold	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Ditchers	O
House	O
to	O
lodge	O
,	O
where	O
in	O
a	O
short	O
time	O
he	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
said	O
Persons	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
Indicted	O
upon	O
the	O
Statute	O
for	O
having	O
two	O
Wives	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
the	O
first	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Grays-Inn	O
Chappel	O
,	O
the	O
27th	O
.	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
18th	O
.	O
Year	O
of	O
this	O
King	O
;	O
and	O
to	O
Alice	B-pers
Pope	I-pers
,	O
the	O
second	O
,	O
at	O
St.	B-place
Pancras	I-place
Church	I-place
the	O
27th	O
.	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
the	O
35th	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
he	O
ever	O
was	O
Married	O
to	O
Margaret	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
,	O
only	O
had	O
kept	O
her	O
Company	O
:	O
but	O
the	O
Clerk	O
of	O
Grays-Inn	O
Chappel	O
proved	O
their	O
Marriage	O
and	O
a	O
Certificate	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Other	O
Witnesses	O
of	O
their	O
living	O
together	O
as	O
Man	O
and	O
Wife	O
many	O
Years	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
Children	O
by	O
her	O
:	O
both	O
the	O
said	O
Wives	O
were	O
in	O
Court	O
:	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Levet	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Levet	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
green	O
Ring	O
,	O
Value	O
9	O
s.	O
one	O
linnen	O
Packing	O
Sheet	O
,	O
Value	O
11	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
;	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Morret	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
one	O
Flaxen	O
Sheet	O
,	O
Value	O
8	O
s.	O
two	O
Silk	O
Scarfs	O
Value	O
18	O
s.	O
six	O
Towels	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
s.	O
four	O
Holland	O
Aprons	O
,	O
Value	O
10	O
s	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Deborah	B-pers
Poultee	I-pers
.	O
It	O
was	O
proved	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Poultee	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
July	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
some	O
other	O
Women	O
waited	O
near	O
at	O
hand	O
,	O
were	O
seen	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
with	O
their	O
Aprons	O
full	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
9	O
s.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Philip	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
forty	O
Yards	O
of	O
Kenting	O
Cloath	O
,	O
Value	O
50	O
s.	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Sherman	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
.	O
The	O
said	O
Cloath	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
sware	O
he	O
broke	O
a	O
Hatch	O
open	O
to	O
get	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Vosse	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
broad	O
Piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
Value	O
25	O
s.	O
another	O
Piece	O
,	O
Value	O
12	O
s.	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
Value	O
10	O
s.	O
three	O
Holland	O
Aprons	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
striped	O
Morning	O
Gown	O
.	O
Value	O
50	O
s.	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
London	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Turner	O
,	O
broke	O
open	O
a	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Orlando	B-pers
Bolston	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
an	O
Alamode	O
Scarf	O
of	O
the	O
price	O
of	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
of	O
the	O
price	O
of	O
7	O
l.	O
from	O
Timothy	B-pers
Torton	I-pers
.	O
He	O
confessed	O
the	O
Indictment	O
before	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Clarkenwel	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
20	O
Ewe	O
Sheep	O
,	O
Price	O
12	O
s.	O
a	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
six	O
Lambs	O
at	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
piece	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Allen	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Tryal	O
Parsons	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
overtook	O
two	O
Men	O
upon	O
the	O
Road	O
by	O
White-Chappel	O
,	O
of	O
whom	O
he	O
enquired	O
after	O
his	O
Sheep	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
acquainted	O
him	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
hired	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Middleton	O
to	O
drive	O
such	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Sheep	O
to	O
Pancras	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
Clarkenwel	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
left	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Custody	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
,	O
who	O
declared	O
he	O
intended	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
same	O
in	O
Southwark	O
.	O
But	O
Parsons	O
strictly	O
enquiring	O
after	O
found	O
them	O
sold	O
by	O
Middleton	O
in	O
White-Chappel	O
;	O
of	O
which	O
some	O
were	O
kill	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
returned	O
.	O
The	O
Matter	O
being	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
thereupon	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Temple	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
of	O
15	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
from	O
Sarah	B-pers
Welsh	I-pers
,	O
Widdow	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Temple	I-pers
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
but	O
Butler	O
being	O
Tryed	O
,	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Welsh	O
keeps	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
both	O
the	O
said	O
Parties	O
coming	O
in	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
she	O
served	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
put	O
into	O
a	O
Room	O
where	O
the	O
Money	O
aforesaid	O
lay	O
in	O
a	O
Cup	O
board	O
,	O
upon	O
Mrs.	O
Welshes	O
turning	O
her	O
Back	O
,	O
they	O
got	O
the	O
same	O
thence	O
.	O
After	O
which	O
,	O
they	O
paid	O
their	O
Reckoning	O
and	O
desired	O
the	O
Woman	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
her	O
Tankard	O
,	O
who	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
them	O
as	O
very	O
honest	O
Guest	O
,	O
till	O
she	O
see	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
care	O
of	O
her	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
conveyed	O
the	O
same	O
away	O
.	O
Upon	O
full	O
Evidence	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
of	O
St	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Hempen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
Val	O
.	O
8	O
s.	O
one	O
Looking	O
glass	O
,	O
Val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
being	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Wetherby	I-pers
.	O
The	O
said	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Glannister	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Mantua-Gown	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
to	O
a	O
small	O
Value	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
Joseph	B-pers
Fenton	I-pers
,	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Vickers	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Indicted	O
together	O
with	O
John	B-pers
James	I-pers
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
20	O
Yards	O
of	O
green	O
Broad-Cloth	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
l.	O
from	O
a	O
Tenter	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Farmer	I-pers
.	O
Upon	O
Proof	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
that	O
Vickers	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
for	O
55	O
s.	O
to	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Bath	O
a	O
Pawn	O
broker	O
.	O
The	O
said	O
Proof	O
being	O
manifest	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
Person	O
Indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
for	O
stealing	O
36	O
Yards	O
of	O
Poppinger	O
Green	O
Weish	O
Cotton	O
,	O
Value	O
30	O
s.	O
being	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
;	O
which	O
were	O
taken	O
about	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
His	O
Excuse	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
by	O
Anna	O
St.	O
Clare	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
believing	O
him	O
,	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Patrick	B-pers
Tuffe	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Flower	O
,	O
Value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Sack	O
,	O
Value	O
3	O
s.	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Muston	I-pers
,	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
to	O
Munston	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
much	O
deny	O
it	O
at	O
his	O
Tryal	O
;	O
but	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Bourne	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
Spinster	O
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Flowered	O
Sattin	O
Gown	O
Value	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Crape	O
Gown	O
Value	O
23	O
s.	O
a	O
Crape	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
Value	O
7	O
s.	O
a	O
Flanders	O
lac	O
'd	O
Cornet	O
,	O
Value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
gold	O
laced	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
embroydered	O
Stayes	O
,	O
a	O
Flowered	O
Sattin	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
things	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Clutton	I-pers
.	O
Also	O
Ann	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Bagnal	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
.	O
Indicted	O
as	O
accessary	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Felony	O
,	O
with	O
Jane	O
Bourne	O
;	O
the	O
same	O
being	O
proved	O
by	O
full	O
Evidence	O
,	O
also	O
by	O
their	O
own	O
Confessions	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Bourne	I-pers
was	O
therefore	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
in	O
accessary	O
thereto	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Denton	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
of	O
some	O
Child-bed	O
Linnen	O
from	O
Christopher	B-pers
Shepheard	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Fire	O
in	O
York	B-place
Buildings	I-place
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
them	O
about	O
him	O
:	O
he	O
alledged	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Susan	B-pers
Heydon	I-pers
,	O
Widdow	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Yards	O
of	O
Callicoe	O
,	O
Val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
five	O
Rugs	O
,	O
Val	O
.	O
40	O
s.	O
Curtains	O
,	O
Valense	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
being	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Everard	I-pers
;	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Lodging	O
:	O
but	O
pleading	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
same	O
from	O
Everards	O
Apprentice	O
who	O
was	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
contradictory	O
Proof	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Presby	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White-Chappel	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
Val	O
5	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
being	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Mild	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proof	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
nor	O
would	O
he	O
much	O
deny	O
the	O
same	O
in	O
Court	O
;	O
therefore	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Amye	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
of	O
Covent-Garden	B-place
,	O
Indicted	O
with	O
one	O
Katherine	B-pers
Bouser	I-pers
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
laced	O
Cravat	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
s.	O
with	O
other	O
Goods	O
from	O
Luellin	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
who	O
keeps	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
:	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
same	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Pot	O
where	O
they	O
stood	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchin	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
proved	O
she	O
sold	O
the	O
Cravat	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
to	O
one	O
who	O
testified	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Dennet	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Savoy	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
two	O
Yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
black	O
Silk	O
Lace	O
,	O
Val	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
of	O
small	O
Value	O
,	O
from	O
Margaret	B-pers
Forgee	I-pers
,	O
nothing	O
was	O
proved	O
effectually	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Ludbrooke	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
Val	O
.	O
21	O
l.	O
being	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
come	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Chissel	O
,	O
Value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
but	O
no	O
Proof	O
being	O
thereof	O
,	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Katherine	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Common	O
Harlot	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
same	O
Person	O
that	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
Bed	O
with	O
Francis	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
Pewter	B-place
Platter	I-place
in	I-place
Soper-lane	I-place
the	O
Night	O
he	O
died	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Hargate	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
entertaining	O
and	O
receiving	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Jones	O
,	O
alias	O
Smith	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
formerly	O
convicted	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Sherland	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Chamberlain	I-pers
being	O
Indicted	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
some	O
small	O
Cheats	O
,	O
are	O
Fined	O
each	O
20	O
Nobles	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
each	O
twice	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
the	O
Judgment	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
upon	O
the	O
several	O
Offenders	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
12	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
:	O
viz	O
.	O
Geo	B-pers
.	I-pers
Caskey	I-pers
,	O
Fran	O
.	O
Pevanson	O
,	O
and	O
Daniel	B-pers
Ballantine	I-pers
,	O
for	O
Murdering	O
John	O
Teagle	O
,	O
Watch-man	O
:	O
John	B-pers
Tue	I-pers
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murdering	O
of	O
William	O
Granves	O
John	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
for	O
Murder	O
of	O
his	O
Wife	O
:	O
Christian	B-pers
Bromfeild	I-pers
,	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Ratcliff	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Vosse	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Pierce	I-pers
,	O
Tho	O
Vickers	O
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Bourne	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
Fourteen	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
:	O
viz	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
John	O
Davies	O
,	O
Will	O
.	O
Hide	O
,	O
Philip	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
Will	O
.	O
Jones	O
,	O
Edward	O
Long	O
Mary	B-pers
Tredeech	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Merret	I-pers
,	O
Gerrard	O
Trent	O
,	O
Lewis	O
Conneway	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Middleton	I-pers
,	O
Orlando	O
Bolston	O
,	O
Sam	B-pers
.	I-pers
Freshy	I-pers
.	O
Four	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
:	O
viz	O
Will	O
.	O
Temple	O
,	O
Will	O
.	O
Butler	O
Edward	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
,	O
Sam	O
Freeman	O
.	O
Six	O
to	O
be	O
Whip	O
'd	O
:	O
viz	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Bonner	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Herne	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Glarmister	I-pers
,	O
Patrick	B-pers
Tusse	I-pers
,	O
Amye	O
Scot	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Crusse	I-pers
,	O
for	O
Shooting	O
Mr.	O
Culliford	O
,	O
was	O
Fined	O
500	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
at	O
the	O
Custom-house	O
,	O
Exchange	O
,	O
and	O
Temple-bar	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Inscription	O
over	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
his	O
Crime	O
;	O
also	O
to	O
find	O
Sureties	O
for	O
his	O
Good	O
Behaviour	O
seven	O
Years	O
.	O
Katherine	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
to	O
be	O
sent	O
to	O
Bridewel	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
remain	O
till	O
next	O
Sessions	O
;	O
which	O
will	O
begin	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
8th	O
.	O
of	O
October	O
next	O
.	O
Three	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
set	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
Judgment	O
not	O
given	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
