TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
Of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
HELD	O
FOR	O
THE	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
,	O
IN	O
THE	O
OLD	O
BAYLY	O
.	O
The	O
10th	O
11th	O
12th	O
and	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
1684	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
36th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
being	O
held	O
at	O
Justice	O
hall	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Fryday	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
the	O
10th	O
11th	O
12th	O
and	O
13th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
1684	O
before	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jenner	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Serjeants	O
at	O
Law	O
,	O
and	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
City	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
other	O
Justices	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Box	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Mayer	I-pers
,	O
Walter	B-pers
Coventry	I-pers
,	O
Jacob	B-pers
David	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
Ralph	B-pers
Izzard	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Easton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Forster	I-pers
,	O
Roger	B-pers
Astley	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Drinkwater	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Sharp	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Elton	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bliset	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Aubury	I-pers
Zacariah	B-pers
Grant	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
,	O
Aubury	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Berk	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Fern	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Jaxon	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Oating	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
&	O
c.	O
were	O
these	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Thoroughgood	I-pers
,	O
being	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Eight	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
valued	O
at	O
8s	O
.	O
from	O
a	O
Person	O
in	O
Coleman-street	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
upon	O
his	O
Arraignment	O
Pleaded	O
Guilty	O
,	O
owning	O
himself	O
to	O
have	O
Committed	O
the	O
said	O
Fellony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Fell	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Mare	O
,	O
valued	O
at	O
4l	O
.	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
November	O
1684	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
upon	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
Fell	O
had	O
the	O
Mare	O
in	O
his	O
possession	O
,	O
and	O
conveyed	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Dolphin	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Buttolph	O
without	O
Bishopsgate	O
,	O
publickly	O
owning	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
her	O
being	O
seized	O
,	O
he	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
execute	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
alledging	O
he	O
bought	O
her	O
of	O
one	O
Francis	B-pers
Gooding	I-pers
,	O
but	O
no	O
proof	O
being	O
made	O
of	O
any	O
such	O
bargain	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Fuller	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
7l	O
.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Osburn	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
his	O
taking	O
the	O
said	O
Gelding	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
Osburn	O
to	O
borrow	O
a	O
Horse	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
but	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
spare	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
those	O
that	O
were	O
at	O
grass	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
up	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
Fuller	O
going	O
away	O
somewhat	O
dissatisfied	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
the	O
Gelding	O
being	O
missed	O
,	O
upon	O
diligent	O
inquiry	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
a	O
Porter	O
in	O
West-Smithfield	O
,	O
which	O
Porter	O
produced	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
delivered	O
him	O
into	O
his	O
possession	O
,	O
all	O
which	O
appearing	O
upon	O
Oath	O
,	O
Fuller	O
made	O
divers	O
trivial	O
excuses	O
,	O
alledging	O
he	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
lane	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
plain	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Mug	O
,	O
valued	O
at	O
3l	O
.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Head	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Woolnoth	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
Eight	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
upon	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
Mr	O
.	O
Heads	O
glass	O
standing	O
in	O
the	O
fore	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Mug	O
taken	O
thence	O
by	O
Morgan	O
,	O
who	O
upon	O
pursuit	O
dropt	O
it	O
,	O
when	O
in	O
vindication	O
of	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
pleaded	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
not	O
;	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
pursuit	O
,	O
whilst	O
he	O
was	O
looking	O
about	O
him	O
a	O
Person	O
came	O
running	O
by	O
and	O
dropped	O
it	O
at	O
his	O
feet	O
,	O
which	O
slender	O
shift	O
not	O
weighing	O
with	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
the	O
proof	O
being	O
full	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Eden	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
valued	O
5l	O
.	O
15s	O
.	O
as	O
likewise	O
,	O
Linnen	O
,	O
Lace	O
and	O
other	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
considerable	O
value	O
,	O
from	O
Matthias	B-pers
Bligis	I-pers
,	O
with	O
whom	O
she	O
had	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
a	O
Servant	O
about	O
three	O
days	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
she	O
taking	O
the	O
opportunity	O
of	O
her	O
Master	O
s	O
being	O
busie	O
about	O
his	O
Affairs	O
,	O
rifled	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
made	O
her	O
escape	O
,	O
but	O
shortly	O
after	O
apprehended	O
,	O
she	O
confessed	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
adding	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
or	O
pawned	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Rose	O
in	O
Field-lane	O
,	O
yet	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
she	O
denyed	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
plainly	O
appearing	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Killing	O
Giles	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
by	O
wounding	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
right	O
Eye	O
with	O
a	O
Tobacco	O
pipe	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
playing	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
ed	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
return	O
the	O
like	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
which	O
,	O
running	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
unfortunately	O
happened	O
that	O
Williams	O
struck	O
the	O
Pipe	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
his	O
Eye	O
,	O
which	O
breaking	O
in	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
inches	O
pierced	O
his	O
Brian	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
remaining	O
in	O
much	O
torture	O
till	O
the	O
10th	O
following	O
,	O
he	O
then	O
dyed	O
,	O
the	O
Chirurgeons	O
having	O
in	O
vain	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
draw	O
forth	O
the	O
Pipe	O
in	O
his	O
life	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Malice	O
appearing	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
shewing	O
a	O
sense	O
of	O
sorrow	O
for	O
so	O
unfortunate	O
a	O
disaster	O
,	O
and	O
alledging	O
the	O
deceased	O
run	O
upon	O
the	O
Pipe	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
man-slaughter	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Wooden	O
Box	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
and	O
half	O
of	O
,	O
value	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
Person	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Cripplegate	B-place
,	O
upon	O
his	O
Arraignment	O
Pleaded	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Montgomery	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Walter	B-pers
Norman	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
is	O
Tryal	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
second	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Montgomery	O
coming	O
the	O
Rainbow	O
Coffee-house	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
the	O
Deceased	O
there	O
,	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
to	O
Fight	O
,	O
Notwithstanding	O
which	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
of	O
some	O
Persons	O
to	O
procure	O
a	O
reconcilement	O
they	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
unhappily	O
met	O
behind	O
the	O
Middle	O
Temple	O
Hall	O
,	O
and	O
drawing	O
upon	O
each	O
other	O
e	O
're	O
any	O
came	O
to	O
prevent	O
it	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Norman	O
received	O
three	O
Wounds	O
one	O
through	O
the	O
Arm	O
,	O
another	O
through	O
the	O
Thigh	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
slight	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
hand	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
dyed	O
the	O
16th	O
following	O
,	O
whereupon	O
it	O
appearing	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
continued	O
malice	O
or	O
irreconcilable	O
hatred	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
their	O
meeting	O
was	O
rather	O
appointment	O
than	O
accident	O
,	O
though	O
Mr.	O
Montgomery	O
laboured	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
latter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
wilful	O
Murther	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Cadry	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
valued	O
at	O
20l	O
.	O
from	O
James	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Strand	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
proof	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
having	O
taken	O
opportunity	O
,	O
conveyed	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
absconded	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
though	O
upon	O
search	O
the	O
Goods	O
or	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
found	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
Pleaded	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
her	O
Sister	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
capable	O
to	O
produce	O
her	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
one	O
to	O
testifie	O
for	O
her	O
life	O
and	O
conversation	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Rug	O
of	O
small	O
value	O
,	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Bradford	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Pauls	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
the	O
fact	O
plainly	O
appearing	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Pettelarcary	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joan	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
30	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Moneys	O
numbered	O
,	O
from	O
Cornelius	B-pers
Key	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Clarkenwell	I-place
,	O
of	O
the	O
1st	O
October	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
against	O
her	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
upon	O
her	O
being	O
apprehended	O
,	O
owned	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
before	O
Sir	O
Clements	O
Armiger	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
she	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
excuse	O
or	O
deny	O
her	O
former	O
confession	O
,	O
alledgeing	O
she	O
remembered	O
no	O
such	O
confession	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
clerk	O
being	O
present	O
,	O
and	O
testifying	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Killing	O
Sir	O
James	B-pers
Hacket	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
October	O
,	O
the	O
circumstances	O
appearing	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
were	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
at	O
Dukes	O
Theatre	O
,	O
the	O
Play	O
ended	O
,	O
a	O
croud	O
happened	O
upon	O
their	O
coming	O
out	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
supposing	O
himself	O
to	O
be	O
jostled	O
,	O
or	O
brushed	O
by	O
the	O
deceased	O
(	O
who	O
had	O
a	O
Cane	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
)	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
without	O
further	O
consideration	O
run	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
left	O
Thigh	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
weapon	O
appeared	O
both	O
ways	O
,	O
cutting	O
likewise	O
his	O
Fingers	O
,	O
whilst	O
he	O
struggled	O
to	O
draw	O
it	O
forth	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
recovered	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
the	O
deceased	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
sinking	O
down	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
no	O
further	O
opportunity	O
,	O
ere	O
it	O
was	O
seized	O
by	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
present	O
,	O
whereat	O
he	O
expressed	O
much	O
indignation	O
,	O
and	O
getting	O
it	O
once	O
more	O
at	O
M	O
stood	O
upon	O
his	O
Guard	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
seized	O
one	O
already	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
deserved	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
that	O
effect	O
,	O
yet	O
the	O
deceased	O
after	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
received	O
went	O
home	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
and	O
lived	O
until	O
the	O
26th	O
following	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
dyed	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Martins	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
the	O
defence	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
a	O
push	O
in	O
the	O
Mouth	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
verily	O
believed	O
from	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
that	O
means	O
came	O
so	O
rashly	O
unfortunate	O
,	O
adding	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
fell	O
through	O
his	O
occasion	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
could	O
have	O
premeditated	O
malice	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
returning	O
their	O
Verdict	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Man-slaughter	O
only	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
statute	O
of	O
stabbing	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
statute	O
he	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
a	O
second	O
indictment	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
murdering	O
and	O
Robbing	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Fairbank	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Martins	B-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Fairbank	O
being	O
found	O
Murthered	O
in	O
her	O
Celler	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Barbarous	O
manner	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
her	O
Neck	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
in	O
divers	O
parts	O
greatly	O
bruised	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
that	O
Night	O
in	O
the	O
company	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wise	I-pers
,	O
convicted	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Murther	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Tooly	I-pers
sometime	O
since	O
deceased	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
upon	O
the	O
discovery	O
of	O
the	O
Murther	O
,	O
fled	O
beyond	O
the	O
Seas	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
surely	O
dye	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
further	O
proved	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
disposed	O
of	O
a	O
Hair	O
Ring	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
left	O
with	O
the	O
Party	O
Murthered	O
in	O
pledge	O
for	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
she	O
was	O
Murthered	O
,	O
her	O
Trunks	O
and	O
Boxes	O
being	O
then	O
broken	O
up	O
and	O
rifled	O
,	O
which	O
Ring	O
being	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
sworn	O
to	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
that	O
several	O
other	O
things	O
described	O
to	O
be	O
Fairbanks	O
,	O
were	O
seen	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
since	O
had	O
made	O
away	O
,	O
himself	O
being	O
formerly	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
hand	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
Perriwigs	O
,	O
and	O
making	O
a	O
slender	O
defence	O
,	O
not	O
being	O
capable	O
of	O
producing	O
any	O
Testimony	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
Murther	O
Committed	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Murther	O
and	O
Fellony	O
,	O
as	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
St.	I-pers
Johns	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
Edmund	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Murdering	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Hescot	I-pers
Knight	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	B-place
Tavern	I-place
in	I-place
Fleet-street	I-place
,	O
as	O
likewise	O
upon	O
the	O
statute	O
of	O
stabbing	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
upon	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
Esq	O
;	O
St.	O
John	O
together	O
with	O
Edward	O
Webb	O
,	O
Sir	O
William	O
Hescot	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
persons	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
Globe	O
Tavern	O
,	O
somewhat	O
late	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
Drinking	O
several	O
Bottles	O
of	O
Claret	O
,	O
a	O
discourse	O
arose	O
in	O
the	O
Company	O
about	O
leaping	O
horses	O
,	O
being	O
first	O
started	O
between	O
Esq	O
;	O
St.	O
Johns	O
and	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Stonehouse	O
,	O
but	O
long	O
it	O
lasted	O
not	O
,	O
e	O
're	O
upon	O
that	O
occasion	O
St.	O
William	O
Hescot	O
urged	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
unfair	O
since	O
Esq	O
;	O
St	O
John	O
had	O
Twenty	O
Horse	O
in	O
his	O
Stable	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Stonehouse	O
's	O
but	O
a	O
few	O
,	O
which	O
causing	O
further	O
Argument	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
St.	O
John	O
's	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
all	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
above	O
six	O
were	O
Asses	O
&	O
c.	O
Whereupon	O
the	O
word	O
Fool	O
being	O
returned	O
,	O
a	O
Bottle	O
was	O
thrown	O
by	O
Esquire	O
St.	O
Johns	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
pursuing	O
the	O
throw	O
drew	O
his	O
sword	O
,	O
which	O
Sir	O
William	O
observing	O
made	O
his	O
retreat	O
,	O
but	O
soon	O
after	O
being	O
Wounded	O
,	O
he	O
fell	O
upon	O
which	O
Esq	O
;	O
St.	O
Johns	O
struck	O
him	O
several	O
blows	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
o	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
Language	O
,	O
bid	O
him	O
beg	O
his	O
pardon	O
,	O
or	O
ask	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
likewise	O
sworn	O
,	O
that	O
upon	O
Esq	O
;	O
St	O
Johns	O
rising	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Webb	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
having	O
his	O
sword	O
likewise	O
drawn	O
,	O
the	O
which	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
his	O
cravat	O
was	O
afterwards	O
found	O
Bloody	O
and	O
that	O
notwithstanding	O
,	O
the	O
endeavour	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
Persons	O
present	O
,	O
so	O
sudden	O
was	O
the	O
mischief	O
,	O
that	O
Sir	O
William	O
having	O
received	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
in	O
his	O
Belly	O
;	O
as	O
likewise	O
,	O
three	O
others	O
in	O
his	O
Groin	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
hand	O
much	O
cut	O
,	O
he	O
instantly	O
dyed	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
his	O
Sword	O
was	O
drawn	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
it	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
Window	O
in	O
the	O
Scabboard	O
,	O
although	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
prove	O
their	O
Innocence	O
,	O
or	O
at	O
least	O
strong	O
provocations	O
,	O
yet	O
the	O
contrary	O
being	O
evident	O
by	O
many	O
Witnesses	O
present	O
,	O
before	O
,	O
at	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
the	O
unhappy	O
misfortune	O
,	O
as	O
likewise	O
the	O
Chirurgeon	O
that	O
searched	O
the	O
body	O
,	O
declaring	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Wounds	O
were	O
given	O
with	O
different	O
Swords	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
his	O
Skill	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
those	O
in	O
the	O
Groin	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
Belly	O
were	O
Mortal	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Murther	O
at	O
Common	O
Law	O
,	O
as	O
Likewise	O
upon	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
stabbing	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
the	O
other	O
Persons	O
,	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Company	O
were	O
discharged	O
upon	O
Proclamation	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Hutchins	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Sturt	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Murdering	O
John	B-pers
Sparks	I-pers
a	O
Waterman	O
in	O
Fleet-street	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
December	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
upon	O
their	O
Tryal	O
,	O
that	O
Sparks	O
with	O
two	O
of	O
his	O
Companions	O
,	O
coming	O
from	O
a	O
place	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
about	O
business	O
,	O
met	O
two	O
Women	O
,	O
which	O
as	O
Sparks	O
stroaked	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
Belly	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
of	O
jest	O
,	O
which	O
so	O
far	O
incited	O
Hutchins	O
to	O
revenge	O
,	O
they	O
being	O
of	O
his	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
the	O
Party	O
Tryed	O
with	O
him	O
as	O
Accessary	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
first	O
striking	O
him	O
over	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
afterwards	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
right	O
Thigh	O
,	O
whereof	O
he	O
instantly	O
dyed	O
,	O
which	O
Fact	O
he	O
Pleaded	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
ignorant	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
plainly	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
without	O
the	O
least	O
Provocation	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
wilful	O
Murder	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
that	O
Sturt	O
was	O
adding	O
or	O
abetting	O
,	O
but	O
on	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
consequently	O
insensible	O
of	O
what	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Charly	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
as	O
Principal	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Abigail	B-pers
Maloray	I-pers
as	O
Accessaries	O
;	O
the	O
former	O
together	O
with	O
Charles	B-pers
Charly	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Pilkington	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Simms	I-pers
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
270	O
yards	O
of	O
Stuff	O
and	O
Cloath	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
great	O
value	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Ware-house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Loveday	I-pers
,	O
Scituate	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
22th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
three	O
latter	O
,	O
for	O
comforting	O
,	O
harbouring	O
,	O
aiding	O
,	O
abetting	O
and	O
Maintaining	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
had	O
been	O
found	O
in	O
divers	O
places	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
disposed	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
particularly	O
at	O
Elizabeth	O
Lewis	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
where	O
likewise	O
several	O
Pick-pockets	O
were	O
found	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
proof	O
positive	O
against	O
the	O
Principal	O
,	O
both	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
Accessaries	O
,	O
through	O
the	O
Inadvertancy	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Sally	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Tuck	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Aldridge	I-pers
near	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
with	O
whom	O
she	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
a	O
servant	O
,	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
Linnen	O
and	O
Woollen	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
,	O
or	O
otherways	O
disposed	O
of	O
them	O
at	O
places	O
distant	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
confessed	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
upon	O
not	O
being	O
capable	O
of	O
making	O
defence	O
,	O
and	O
ed	O
as	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
9s	O
.	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Gladman	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Killing	O
Mary	B-pers
Patrick	I-pers
,	O
by	O
driving	O
a	O
Cart	O
over	O
her	O
in	O
Maiden-lane	B-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Ward	I-place
of	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
on	O
the	O
23th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
driving	O
a	O
Cart	O
Loaden	O
with	O
Dung	O
,	O
his	O
Horses	O
rushed	O
against	O
a	O
Brasiers	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
and	O
beating	O
down	O
a	O
Copper	O
,	O
that	O
stood	O
there	O
,	O
knock	O
down	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
who	O
stood	O
close	O
to	O
avoid	O
the	O
danger	O
of	O
the	O
Cart	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
said	O
Gladman	O
used	O
some	O
endeavours	O
to	O
stop	O
his	O
Horses	O
upon	O
the	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
gave	O
in	O
their	O
Verdict	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
happened	O
by	O
misfortune	O
,	O
acquitting	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
for	O
Murder	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
of	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
Man-slaughter	O
.	O
Soloman	B-pers
Morrice	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Killing	O
James	B-pers
Belcher	I-pers
his	O
fellow	O
Soldier	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
after	O
having	O
been	O
upon	O
the	O
Guard	O
,	O
went	O
together	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
drank	O
and	O
eat	O
plentifully	O
,	O
during	O
which	O
some	O
words	O
passing	O
,	O
Morrice	O
finding	O
himself	O
aggrieved	O
because	O
his	O
Manhood	O
was	O
called	O
into	O
question	O
,	O
told	O
Belcher	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
soon	O
see	O
what	O
a	O
man	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
yet	O
the	O
beat	O
seemingly	O
being	O
pacified	O
by	O
others	O
of	O
their	O
Company	O
,	O
they	O
left	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
were	O
so	O
unhappy	O
as	O
to	O
meet	O
,	O
and	O
fight	O
near	O
the	O
Guard	O
at	O
Whitehall	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
encounter	O
,	O
Belcher	O
receiving	O
a	O
Wound	O
Six	O
inches	O
deep	O
into	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
he	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
23th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
dyed	O
,	O
to	O
this	O
charge	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Pleaded	O
he	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
obliged	O
him	O
to	O
fight	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
not	O
well	O
appearing	O
,	O
yet	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
done	O
ere	O
they	O
cooled	O
upon	O
the	O
quarrel	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Man-slaughter	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
and	O
George	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
their	O
Son	O
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Clipping	O
and	O
Fileing	O
the	O
lawful	O
Coine	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Six	O
of	O
King	O
Charles	O
the	O
First	O
'	O
Half	O
Crowns	O
,	O
and	O
Twenty	O
Shillings	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
King	O
's	O
Coin	O
it	O
was	O
sworn	O
by	O
one	O
D'Cain	O
a	O
Frenchman	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
coming	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
through	O
a	O
Key-hole	O
,	O
saw	O
George	O
Clark	O
the	O
Elder	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Lee	O
Clipping	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
promised	O
to	O
put	O
away	O
divers	O
counterfeit	O
Guinneys	O
for	O
a	O
Friend	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
blaming	O
him	O
for	O
making	O
the	O
Trade	O
so	O
publick	O
,	O
by	O
communicating	O
the	O
secret	O
to	O
many	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
said	O
D'Cain	O
making	O
a	O
discovery	O
,	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Clark	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
entrance	O
,	O
Mary	O
Clark	O
hid	O
divers	O
Clippings	O
,	O
and	O
filings	O
together	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
powder	O
to	O
rub	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Coals	O
,	O
the	O
which	O
discovered	O
,	O
she	O
fell	O
down	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
secure	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
further	O
search	O
,	O
Scales	O
,	O
Weights	O
,	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Clipping	O
implements	O
were	O
found	O
so	O
,	O
that	O
Clark	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
being	O
Committed	O
,	O
when	O
their	O
Goods	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
removed	O
,	O
upon	O
seizure	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
a	O
File	O
with	O
Silver	O
dust	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Bed-straw	O
,	O
it	O
likewise	O
appeared	O
upon	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Clark	O
the	O
younger	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
going	O
to	O
his	O
Grand-fathers	O
,	O
living	O
in	O
or	O
about	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
dropped	O
Paper	O
of	O
Clipping	O
,	O
which	O
together	O
with	O
what	O
are	O
before	O
mentioned	O
,	O
being	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
notwithstanding	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Pleading	O
ignorance	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
former	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
latter	O
being	O
but	O
a	O
Youth	O
under	O
the	O
Tutorage	O
of	O
his	O
Parents	O
,	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Perin	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
22l	O
.	O
3s	O
.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Farthing	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
Perin	O
being	O
a	O
Joyner	O
had	O
done	O
work	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
abovementioned	O
,	O
which	O
sum	O
being	O
agreed	O
to	O
be	O
paid	O
,	O
Farthing	O
desired	O
a	O
release	O
,	O
as	O
likewise	O
,	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
Bill	O
scrutinized	O
by	O
other	O
Workmen	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
tender	O
taking	O
up	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
refusing	O
to	O
sign	O
to	O
what	O
was	O
proposed	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
was	O
made	O
,	O
which	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
Malicious	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
Felony	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Law	O
Perin	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Farthing	O
checked	O
for	O
bringing	O
an	O
Indictment	O
on	O
such	O
a	O
frivolous	O
occasion	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bosham	I-pers
a	O
Negro	O
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Six	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Silver	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
31th	O
of	O
October	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pauls	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
upon	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
offering	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
said	O
Silver	O
,	O
being	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
broken	O
Chafing	O
dish	O
,	O
was	O
stopped	O
by	O
the	O
Goldsmith	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
place	O
of	O
his	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
enquired	O
into	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
refused	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
end	O
believing	O
,	O
found	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
Esq	O
,	O
Russel	O
,	O
the	O
Justice	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
before	O
whom	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
,	O
Committed	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
denying	O
that	O
fact	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Master	O
not	O
Prosecuting	O
,	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Fellony	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Pot	O
value	O
12	O
pence	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Boyce	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
November	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
brought	O
a	O
Pot	O
marked	O
with	O
the	O
said	O
Boyces	O
mark	O
to	O
a	O
Pewterers	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
it	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
denying	O
the	O
Fact	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
stealing	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Prosecution	O
made	O
by	O
the	O
owner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Faulks	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
More	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
12s	O
.	O
and	O
8	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
from	O
George	B-pers
Gay	I-pers
of	O
White-Chappel	B-place
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
pawned	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Faulks	O
,	O
for	O
4s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
owned	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
pawning	O
she	O
denyed	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
Pleaded	O
it	O
was	O
given	O
her	O
by	O
a	O
sea	O
man	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
then	O
produce	O
,	O
as	O
for	O
More	O
,	O
the	O
Pewter	O
was	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
lap	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
confessing	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
possession	O
,	O
she	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
excuse	O
it	O
upon	O
one	O
Phillip	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
whom	O
she	O
said	O
was	O
her	O
Brother	O
in-law	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
was	O
about	O
to	O
furnish	O
,	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
her	O
6d	O
.	O
for	O
so	O
doing	O
,	O
but	O
neither	O
of	O
them	O
proving	O
what	O
they	O
Pleaded	O
to	O
be	O
true	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
severally	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
9s	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
On	O
the	O
12th	O
Instant	O
Mr.	O
John	O
Forster	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
John	O
Coley	O
,	O
being	O
sworn	O
upon	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
of	O
Mr	O
.	O
Box	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Astley	O
(	O
who	O
were	O
excused	O
by	O
reason	O
of	O
their	O
indisposition	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
,	O
viz	O
,	O
Barbara	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cradock	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
Aug	O
.	O
last	O
,	O
with	O
whom	O
,	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
she	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
a	O
servant	O
,	O
of	O
Plate	O
,	O
Linnen	O
and	O
Woollen	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
Sugar	O
,	O
Pewter	O
,	O
Brass	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
to	O
a	O
great	O
value	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fellony	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
considerable	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
the	O
Brokers	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Persons	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
and	O
embezzled	O
them	O
,	O
whereupon	O
she	O
having	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
herself	O
,	O
especially	O
to	O
the	O
purpose	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Guinneys	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
Mary	I-place
Woolnoth	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
Octob	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
fellow	O
servant	O
with	O
the	O
said	O
Harris	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
frequent	O
access	O
to	O
his	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
day	O
,	O
leaving	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
Chamber	O
when	O
his	O
Trunk	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
he	O
soon	O
after	O
missed	O
his	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
therewith	O
;	O
who	O
denyed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
not	O
being	O
manifest	O
by	O
any	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Guinies	O
Charged	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
40	O
yards	O
of	O
fleize	O
,	O
Holland	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Se	I-pers
ing	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
little	B-place
St.	I-place
All	I-place
Hallows	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
Sept	O
.	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
found	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
disposed	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
as	O
likewise	O
a	O
Pick-lock	O
key	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Chizel	O
taken	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
9s	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Goff	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Keech	I-pers
,	O
as	O
likewise	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquistion	O
for	O
Man	O
slaughter	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
being	O
Prisoners	O
together	O
in	O
the	O
Poultry	B-place
Counter	I-place
,	O
upon	O
a	O
scuffle	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
Goff	O
having	O
a	O
Tobacco-pipe	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
struck	O
Keech	O
on	O
the	O
Face	O
twice	O
,	O
when	O
upon	O
the	O
second	O
stroak	O
or	O
push	O
,	O
the	O
Pipe	O
entred	O
his	O
right	O
Eye	O
,	O
and	O
breaking	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
languished	O
from	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
November	O
to	O
the	O
16th	O
and	O
then	O
dyed	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
former	O
malice	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
it	O
only	O
Man-slaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Walter	B-pers
Corbet	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Annes	I-place
Black-fryers	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Clipping	O
6	O
of	O
K	O
Charles	O
the	O
First	O
's	O
Half-crowns	O
,	O
20	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Shillings	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Witness	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Wife	O
had	O
payed	O
a	O
party	O
3l	O
.	O
or	O
thereabouts	O
,	O
in	O
Money	O
newly	O
Clipped	O
,	O
amongst	O
which	O
,	O
remained	O
a	O
considerable	O
quantity	O
of	O
File	O
dust	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
several	O
Clipping	O
sheres	O
were	O
found	O
near	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
balance	O
the	O
Evidence	O
testimony	O
being	O
given	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
and	O
Conversation	O
,	O
as	O
likewise	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Wife	O
received	O
that	O
Money	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
saw	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
ground	O
of	O
the	O
suspicion	O
was	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
of	O
a	O
Servant	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
who	O
confessed	O
she	O
had	O
belyed	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Treason	O
layed	O
to	O
his	O
charge	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Botly	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
16s	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Pedle	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Peters	I-place
the	I-place
Poor	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
6	O
of	O
Dec	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
a	O
Char-woman	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Pedle	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
found	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Money	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
confessing	O
poverty	O
had	O
inforced	O
her	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Court	O
commiserating	O
the	O
wretched	O
condition	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
her	O
Fellony	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
9s	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Yeomans	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Pike	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
5l	O
.	O
10s	O
.	O
from	O
Hester	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
near	O
Pauls-wharf	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
coming	O
to	O
drink	O
(	O
the	O
House	O
being	O
publick	O
,	O
)	O
had	O
a	O
Tankard	O
brought	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
which	O
soon	O
after	O
their	O
departure	O
,	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
bringing	O
proof	O
of	O
their	O
candid	O
reputations	O
,	O
and	O
alledging	O
,	O
they	O
left	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
the	O
Mistriss	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Silver	O
Cups	O
,	O
value	O
4l	O
.	O
from	O
Henry	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Woolnoth	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
the	O
proof	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Cups	O
were	O
stole	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
another	O
of	O
the	O
Gang	O
were	O
seen	O
hankering	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Cup	O
found	O
likewise	O
,	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
dropt	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
little	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
charging	O
it	O
home	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Willson	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Towels	O
,	O
3	O
Napkins	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Table-cloath	O
,	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Willson	I-pers
of	O
Great	B-place
All-hallows	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
Nov	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
in	O
for	O
a	O
Jill	O
of	O
Sack	O
,	O
whilst	O
Willson	O
,	O
who	O
keeps	O
a	O
Tavern	O
was	O
drawing	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
slipped	O
the	O
Linnen	O
under	O
her	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
presently	O
missed	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
pursued	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
her	O
upon	O
which	O
undeniable	O
proof	O
,	O
although	O
she	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
excuse	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Hodian	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
skirt	O
of	O
a	O
Cloath	O
Gown	O
,	O
from	O
George	B-pers
Gay	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Skirt	O
upon	O
search	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
pawn	O
broker	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
lost	O
goods	O
to	O
a	O
great	O
value	O
,	O
his	O
House	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
being	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
urging	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
matter	O
being	O
of	O
a	O
light	O
value	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Gardener	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
defrauding	O
Isaiah	B-pers
Laurel	I-pers
a	O
Mercer	O
in	O
Pater-noster-row	B-place
,	O
of	O
Silks	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
8l	O
.	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
meeting	O
the	O
Son	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Mercer	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Silk	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
took	O
acquaintance	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
some	O
discourse	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
of	O
an	O
Errand	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Coffin	O
in	O
Cannon	O
street	O
,	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
Bundle	O
of	O
Silks	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
hold	O
the	O
Silk	O
he	O
had	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
the	O
mean	O
while	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
the	O
Youth	O
not	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
exc	O
14	O
years	O
of	O
Age	O
consented	O
,	O
but	O
while	O
he	O
search	O
of	O
the	O
place	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
,	O
she	O
pa	O
with	O
the	O
Silk	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Fact	O
,	O
she	O
Pleaded	O
Ignor	O
but	O
being	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
notorious	O
cheat	O
and	O
shoplift	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Trespass	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
together	O
with	O
Elizabeth	O
Po	O
,	O
coming	O
upon	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
in	O
Exchange-alley	B-place
,	O
and	O
she	O
cheapening	O
Lace	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
Octob	O
.	O
Last	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
amounted	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
5l	O
.	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
when	O
the	O
Lace	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Marshals	O
Men	O
being	O
implored	O
to	O
find	O
her	O
out	O
,	O
she	O
confessed	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
her	O
confederate	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
accordingly	O
did	O
,	O
for	O
about	O
17s	O
.	O
where	O
upon	O
being	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
in	O
unlawful	O
practices	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
9s	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hayes	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Ward	O
of	O
the	O
Vintrie	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
Nov	O
about	O
10	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
by	O
opening	O
the	O
Door	O
with	O
Pick	O
lock	O
Keys	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Door	O
being	O
forced	O
open	O
by	O
Hayes	O
's	O
sudden	O
coming	O
home	O
he	O
fled	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
end	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
of	O
Pick	O
locks	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
yet	O
he	O
Pleaded	O
Innocence	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
but	O
the	O
Proof	O
being	O
he	O
was	O
Convicted	O
of	O
the	O
Trespass	O
it	O
not	O
amounting	O
to	O
Fellony	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
had	O
time	O
to	O
remove	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bay	O
Gelding	O
,	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harvy	I-pers
valued	O
at	O
7l	O
.	O
which	O
being	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
possession	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
he	O
upon	O
his	O
Arraignment	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fellony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Matthew	B-pers
Harlow	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
30s	O
.	O
and	O
understanding	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
upon	O
his	O
Arraignment	O
Pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Trespass	O
&	O
c.	O
it	O
appeared	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
by	O
two	O
credible	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
in	O
Drury-lane	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
23th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
fell	O
into	O
many	O
extravagant	O
,	O
scandalous	O
,	O
and	O
seditious	O
expressions	O
,	O
casting	O
reflections	O
upon	O
his	O
Royal	O
Highness	O
,	O
as	O
likewise	O
,	O
many	O
dangerous	O
words	O
against	O
the	O
Government	O
,	O
relating	O
to	O
raise	O
up	O
and	O
stir	O
up	O
Sedition	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
upon	O
proof	O
of	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
Pleaded	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
but	O
expressed	O
those	O
words	O
in	O
his	O
mad	O
extravagancy	O
,	O
yet	O
that	O
not	O
being	O
a	O
sufficient	O
excuse	O
for	O
such	O
Insolency	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Trespass	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Phillip	B-pers
Wallis	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
speaking	O
many	O
dangerous	O
and	O
seditious	O
words	O
,	O
bordering	O
upon	O
,	O
if	O
not	O
altogether	O
Treasonous	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
reproved	O
for	O
such	O
extravagancies	O
,	O
he	O
seemed	O
much	O
displeased	O
,	O
and	O
Challenged	O
one	O
of	O
those	O
that	O
reproved	O
him	O
to	O
fight	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
another	O
time	O
attempted	O
to	O
stab	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
refusing	O
to	O
drink	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Monmouth	O
's	O
Health	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
and	O
divers	O
expressions	O
,	O
not	O
fitting	O
to	O
be	O
mentioned	O
in	O
this	O
Pages	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Trespass	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Daniel	B-pers
D'Coiner	I-pers
and	O
Catherine	B-pers
D'Coiner	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
both	O
French	O
People	O
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Clipping	O
40	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Shillings	O
,	O
as	O
likewise	O
,	O
divers	O
Half-crowns	O
of	O
K.	O
Charles	O
the	O
First	O
's	O
Coine	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
Coining	O
false	O
Guinneys	O
,	O
half	O
Guinneys	O
,	O
Mill	O
'd	O
Half-Crowns	O
,	O
and	O
Crowns	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
proved	O
against	O
Daniel	O
D'Coiner	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
Coined	O
divers	O
Guinneys	O
,	O
and	O
new	O
pieces	O
of	O
silver	O
,	O
offering	O
the	O
Guinneys	O
at	O
10s	O
a	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
false	O
silver	O
at	O
25s	O
.	O
to	O
the	O
pound	O
,	O
whereupon	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
being	O
searched	O
,	O
several	O
counterfeit	O
Guinneys	O
and	O
pieces	O
imitating	O
Crowns	O
Half-crowns	O
were	O
found	O
with	O
almost	O
all	O
manner	O
of	O
Coining	O
Instruments	O
,	O
and	O
pieces	O
of	O
Metal	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Pleaded	O
Innocence	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
as	O
to	O
Coining	O
being	O
plain	O
against	O
the	O
Husband	O
,	O
both	O
by	O
his	O
own	O
confession	O
and	O
demonstrable	O
proofs	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Witnesses	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
hand	O
in	O
the	O
design	O
,	O
or	O
was	O
assisting	O
her	O
Husband	O
in	O
his	O
unlawful	O
practices	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Barnwell	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Brian	B-pers
O	I-pers
Cane	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gelding	O
price	O
10l	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
14	O
of	O
Oct.	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Winlow	I-pers
,	O
the	O
proof	O
was	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Winlow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16	O
of	O
Sept.	O
last	O
,	O
was	O
Robbed	O
near	O
Sto	O
Church	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
returning	O
from	O
Ailesbury	O
fair	O
,	O
buy	O
3	O
Men	O
,	O
2	O
on	O
Horseback	O
and	O
one	O
on	O
Foot	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
the	O
Gelding	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
as	O
likewise	O
,	O
Scarfes	O
,	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Necklace	O
of	O
Beads	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
soon	O
after	O
finding	O
his	O
Saddle	O
at	O
a	O
private	O
house	O
upon	O
the	O
Road	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
left	O
it	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
direction	O
to	O
send	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Bell	O
Inn	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
he	O
taking	O
the	O
advice	O
of	O
Capt	O
.	O
Richardson	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
applied	O
himself	O
,	O
carryed	O
the	O
Saddle	O
accordingly	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
directed	O
to	O
the	O
Tapster	O
,	O
desiring	O
him	O
to	O
stop	O
any	O
Person	O
that	O
should	O
come	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
when	O
soon	O
after	O
,	O
Brian	O
O	O
Cane	O
came	O
to	O
demand	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
his	O
Master	O
James	O
Watts	O
,	O
who	O
being	O
accordingly	O
stayed	O
,	O
gave	O
directions	O
how	O
to	O
find	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
who	O
in	O
fine	O
,	O
was	O
taken	O
together	O
,	O
with	O
Peter	O
Barnwell	O
,	O
after	O
some	O
resistance	O
at	O
Chelsey	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
gelding	O
found	O
at	O
the	O
Bell-Inn	O
in	O
Westminster	O
,	O
Watts	O
owning	O
the	O
Saddle	O
and	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
Barnwell	O
having	O
about	O
him	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
and	O
Necklace	O
,	O
taken	O
from	O
Winlows	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Watts	O
Chamber	O
a	O
broken	O
Ring	O
found	O
,	O
being	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Winlow	O
,	O
the	O
trivial	O
excuses	O
they	O
made	O
of	O
Innocence	O
,	O
they	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
bring	O
any	O
proof	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
Committed	O
,	O
Watts	O
and	O
Barnwell	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Fellony	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Horse	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
it	O
was	O
Committed	O
in	O
another	O
County	O
,	O
and	O
Brian	O
O	O
Cane	O
acquitted	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
proof	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Willmore	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
8	O
ounces	O
of	O
Silver	O
Wire	O
,	O
value	O
3l	O
.	O
from	O
Philis	B-pers
D'Mott	I-pers
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
plate	O
Wire	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
soon	O
after	O
,	O
had	O
sold	O
a	O
like	O
parcel	O
at	O
an	O
under	O
rate	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
verily	O
believed	O
was	O
hers	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
Willmore	O
Pleaded	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
one	O
Benison	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
considerable	O
quantity	O
of	O
Nectrils	O
,	O
Peach-trees	O
and	O
Cherry	O
stocks	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28	O
of	O
Nov	O
last	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Theophilus	B-pers
Stacy	I-pers
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
such	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Trees	O
being	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Custody	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
in	O
the	O
Stocks-market	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
seized	O
,	O
whereupon	O
Brown	O
consented	O
to	O
claim	O
them	O
as	O
his	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
likewise	O
did	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
,	O
alledging	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
Gardener	O
in	O
Southwark	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
plain	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
hand	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Garden	O
at	O
Hackney	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
layed	O
in	O
the	O
ground	O
to	O
be	O
preserved	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Christopher	B-pers
Cain	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
wounding	O
Mr.	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
and	O
Mr.	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
Hawkins	O
imploying	O
Griffin	O
to	O
Arrest	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
with	O
Hawkins	O
and	O
divers	O
others	O
entring	O
his	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
passing	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
he	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
and	O
kept	O
the	O
passage	O
of	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
where	O
Griffin	O
and	O
Hawkins	O
were	O
both	O
wounded	O
by	O
C	O
,	O
one	O
deep	O
in	O
the	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
in	O
the	O
shoulder	O
,	O
which	O
Wounds	O
,	O
he	O
alledged	O
he	O
gave	O
them	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
defence	O
,	O
as	O
not	O
knowing	O
their	O
design	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
breach	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
being	O
apparent	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
a	O
contempt	O
of	O
the	O
Kings	O
Writs	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Trespass	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
and	I-pers
Francis	I-pers
Rock	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
11	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
5	O
silk	O
Pettecoats	O
,	O
a	O
Brass	O
Mortar	O
,	O
a	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
parcels	O
of	O
Linnen	O
from	O
Jane	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
house	O
in	O
Bunhill	B-place
fields	I-place
,	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
positive	O
proof	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
who	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
laborious	O
People	O
in	O
an	O
honest	O
employ	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Shirly	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
embezzling	O
&	O
c	O
making	O
away	O
2500	O
Bricks	O
,	O
contrary	O
to	O
the	O
knowledge	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
and	O
Mr.	B-pers
Steel	I-pers
,	O
who	O
imployed	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
to	O
Albemarle	O
Buildings	O
,	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hargate	I-pers
,	O
had	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
another	O
work	O
in	O
Dog-fields	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
received	O
Money	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
at	O
an	O
under	O
rate	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
converted	O
to	O
their	O
own	O
use	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
value	O
not	O
being	O
40s	O
,	O
it	O
amounted	O
not	O
to	O
a	O
Fellony	O
upon	O
the	O
Statute	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
Indicted	O
,	O
wherefore	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Stockdale	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
being	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
a	O
Sealed	O
bag	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
James	B-pers
Hern	I-pers
his	O
Master	O
had	O
Instrusted	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
converting	O
30l	O
15s	O
.	O
10d	O
.	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
use	O
,	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
30	O
Yards	O
of	O
Fustian	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
considerable	O
parcel	O
of	O
dyed	O
Calco	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Plasto	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
18	O
of	O
Oct.	O
it	O
was	O
sworn	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
whilst	O
Plasto	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Back-room	O
,	O
and	O
under	O
the	O
shelter	O
of	O
the	O
Night	O
make	O
his	O
escape	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Fellony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wix	I-pers
of	O
White-Chappel	B-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Broughton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
Dec.	O
no	O
Inhabitant	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Bolster	O
and	O
Stuff	O
Vallance	O
,	O
valued	O
at	O
5s	O
.	O
which	O
things	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
and	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Cheshire	I-pers
,	O
being	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
goods	O
from	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Prosecution	O
made	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Leech	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
shirts	O
and	O
2	O
Nec	O
cloaths	O
from	O
William	B-pers
East	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22	O
of	O
Octob	O
.	O
Yet	O
upon	O
Evidence	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
shirts	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloath	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Doublet	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Dockle	I-pers
of	O
Cripplegate	B-place
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Chamber	O
,	O
when	O
his	O
Chest	O
was	O
open	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
upon	O
his	O
departure	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
himself	O
confessing	O
the	O
taking	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
stealing	O
a	O
P	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
from	O
Francis	B-pers
Kerals	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10	O
Octob	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
Person	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Kerals	O
,	O
the	O
Coat	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
in	O
jest	O
than	O
otherwise	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
restored	O
again	O
some	O
days	O
before	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
insomuch	O
that	O
it	O
being	O
apprehended	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
O	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
10	O
Laced	O
Co	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
from	O
Hannah	B-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
Nov.	O
Widow	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Proof	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
Convict	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Susanna	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
40s	O
.	O
from	O
Catherine	B-pers
[	I-pers
Text	I-pers
unreadable	I-pers
in	I-pers
original	I-pers
.	I-pers
]	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
8	O
of	O
Octob	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
with	O
whom	O
she	O
had	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
after	O
having	O
stayed	O
there	O
a	O
while	O
,	O
upon	O
her	O
leave	O
,	O
upon	O
whose	O
departure	O
the	O
Cup	O
that	O
stood	O
upon	O
the	O
Bar	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
alledging	O
her	O
innocency	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
proof	O
to	O
the	O
purpose	O
being	O
made	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Willson	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
18	O
dozen	O
of	O
Sissers	O
,	O
from	O
Anthony	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Minories	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
6	O
of	O
Dec.	O
he	O
confessed	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Sessers	O
;	O
and	O
disposed	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
one	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
stole	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
most	O
of	O
them	O
into	O
his	O
and	O
one	O
David	O
's	O
possession	O
,	O
which	O
Ingenious	O
Confession	O
,	O
caused	O
the	O
Jury	O
so	O
far	O
to	O
convict	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Martha	B-pers
Michel	I-pers
of	O
Hendon	B-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
from	O
Susanna	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22	O
of	O
Nov.	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
the	O
party	O
whose	O
goods	O
were	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
being	O
frivolous	O
and	O
vexatious	O
,	O
the	O
Indictment	O
was	O
thrown	O
aside	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Catherines	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Plate	O
,	O
Ring	O
,	O
Corral	O
,	O
Laced	O
Linnen	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
of	O
value	O
from	O
Henry	B-pers
Barrow	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8	O
of	O
Aug.	O
and	O
the	O
goods	O
partly	O
found	O
,	O
as	O
likewise	O
his	O
words	O
being	O
given	O
in	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Fellony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Trelage	I-pers
,	O
Roger	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Penelope	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4	O
of	O
Nov.	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
Linnen	O
and	O
Silks	O
,	O
made	O
into	O
Sempstry	O
ware	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
12l	O
.	O
which	O
goods	O
sometime	O
after	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Lodging	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
Constable	O
that	O
was	O
searching	O
for	O
other	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
notice	O
,	O
that	O
such	O
goods	O
were	O
found	O
,	O
soon	O
owned	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
Chest	O
,	O
standing	O
in	O
an	O
empty	O
Chamber	O
,	O
adjacent	O
to	O
their	O
Lodging	O
,	O
they	O
disowned	O
all	O
claim	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
alledging	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
chest	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Trelages	I-pers
,	O
Husband	O
to	O
Mary	O
Trelage	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
fled	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
contrary	O
being	O
proved	O
,	O
Adams	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Fellony	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Women	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Zachariah	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
dozen	O
of	O
Links	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
4d	O
.	O
being	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Linly	I-pers
of	O
Stoke	B-place
Newington	I-place
,	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
evident	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Law	O
Suit	O
about	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
A	O
Bill	O
of	O
Indictment	O
for	O
the	O
wilful	O
perjury	O
,	O
being	O
found	O
against	O
Titus	B-pers
Oates	I-pers
,	O
by	O
the	O
Grand	O
Jury	O
sworn	O
,	O
to	O
inquire	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
from	O
the	O
King's-Bench	O
on	O
Fryday	O
Morning	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Marshals	O
Officers	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
to	O
Plead	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
indictment	O
,	O
which	O
in	O
open	O
Court	O
was	O
accordingly	O
Read	O
,	O
the	O
substance	O
being	O
to	O
this	O
effect	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
that	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
Titus	O
Oates	O
,	O
had	O
sworn	O
at	O
the	O
Tryals	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Ireland	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pickering	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Grove	I-pers
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
Consult	O
of	O
the	O
Fathers	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
White-horse	O
Tavern	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
a	O
resolution	O
to	O
Kill	O
the	O
K.	O
and	O
then	O
separated	O
into	O
divers	O
Companies	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
Titus	O
Oates	O
,	O
did	O
carry	O
the	O
said	O
resolution	O
from	O
place	O
to	O
place	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
Signed	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
,	O
he	O
Pleaded	O
not	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
a	O
Cortierars	O
might	O
be	O
allowed	O
him	O
to	O
remove	O
it	O
,	O
seeing	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
upon	O
another	O
Tryal	O
above	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
an	O
order	O
would	O
be	O
granted	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Friends	O
might	O
have	O
free	O
Access	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
wherein	O
he	O
should	O
reside	O
,	O
which	O
not	O
being	O
denyed	O
upon	O
his	O
request	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
remanded	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
from	O
whence	O
he	O
came	O
.	O
The	O
Pavements	O
and	O
cleaning	O
the	O
Streets	O
,	O
being	O
recommended	O
to	O
the	O
Grand	O
Jury	O
for	O
London	O
,	O
they	O
presented	O
,	O
that	O
no	O
expedient	O
way	O
could	O
be	O
found	O
,	O
for	O
keeping	O
the	O
Streets	O
clean	O
and	O
in	O
good	O
order	O
,	O
than	O
the	O
City	O
's	O
disencumbering	O
it	O
self	O
of	O
hiring	O
Rakers	O
,	O
and	O
sufering	O
each	O
Parish	O
or	O
Preccinct	O
to	O
agree	O
with	O
the	O
Rakers	O
themselves	O
,	O
which	O
presentment	O
was	O
favourably	O
accepted	O
.	O
An	O
Appeal	O
against	O
George	O
Porter	O
being	O
allowed	O
he	O
was	O
Barr	O
'd	O
his	O
Clergy	O
,	O
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Voss	I-pers
,	O
who	O
formerly	O
pleading	O
her	O
Belly	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
continued	O
in	O
Prison	O
,	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Executed	O
upon	O
her	O
former	O
Sentence	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
calling	O
over	O
the	O
Gaol	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
Adjourned	O
,	O
appointing	O
the	O
next	O
Sessions	O
to	O
be	O
held	O
there	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16	O
of	O
January	O
next	O
insuing	O
.	O
11	O
Persons	O
were	O
burnt	O
in	O
the	O
hand	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Goff	O
,	O
James	O
Stockdale	O
,	O
John	O
Cooper	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Williams	O
,	O
John	O
Johnson	O
,	O
Hannah	O
Faulks	O
,	O
Mary	O
More	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Wix	O
,	O
Anne	O
Knot	O
,	O
Dorothy	O
Botly	O
,	O
and	O
Jane	O
Sally	O
5	O
.	O
Persons	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Transportation	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
John	O
Thoroughgood	O
,	O
John	O
Morgan	O
,	O
Sylvarius	O
Morrice	O
,	O
Matthew	O
Harlo	O
,	O
Roger	O
Adams	O
18	O
Persons	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
William	O
Thomas	O
,	O
John	O
Fell	O
,	O
John	O
Fuller	O
,	O
Sarah	O
carter	O
,	O
John	O
Hutchins	O
,	O
Barbara	O
Williams	O
,	O
Francis	O
Knight	O
,	O
Henry	O
St.	O
Johns	O
,	O
Edmund	O
Webb	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Mongomery	O
,	O
Mary	O
Cade	O
,	O
John	O
Johnson	O
,	O
Richard	O
Jones	O
,	O
George	O
Clark	O
,	O
Mary	O
Clark	O
,	O
Daniel	O
O'Connor	O
,	O
James	O
Watts	O
,	O
and	O
Peter	O
Barnwell	O
.	O
6	O
Persons	O
Sentenced	O
to	O
be	O
Whipt	O
.	O
Viz	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Willson	O
,	O
Edward	O
Brown	O
,	O
John	O
Richardson	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Leech	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Hall	O
,	O
and	O
Nicholas	O
Willson	O
5	O
Persons	O
Fined	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Anne	O
Gardiner	O
10l	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
in	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
John	O
Smith	O
alias	O
Alemet	O
s.	O
Christopher	O
Cain	O
5l	O
.	O
and	O
to	O
be	O
of	O
the	O
good	O
behaviour	O
3	O
Months	O
,	O
John	O
Ward	O
and	O
Philip	O
Wallis	O
10l	O
.	O
each	O
and	O
to	O
be	O
of	O
the	O
good	O
behaviour	O
for	O
the	O
space	O
of	O
a	O
Year	O
.	O
An	O
Appeal	O
against	O
George	O
Porter	O
being	O
allowed	O
he	O
was	O
Barr	O
'd	O
his	O
Clergy	O
,	O
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Voss	I-pers
,	O
who	O
formerly	O
pleading	O
her	O
Belly	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
continued	O
in	O
Prison	O
,	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Executed	O
upon	O
her	O
former	O
Sentence	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
calling	O
over	O
the	O
Gaol	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
Adjourned	O
,	O
appointing	O
the	O
next	O
Sessions	O
to	O
be	O
held	O
there	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16	O
of	O
January	O
next	O
insuing	O
.	O
