TOKEN	NE
AN	O
ACCOUNT	O
OF	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
Of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
,	O
And	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
HELD	O
FOR	O
THE	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
AT	O
Justice-Hall	O
,	O
IN	O
THE	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
.	O
The	O
15th	O
and	O
16th	O
Days	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
1684	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
36th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
being	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bayly	O
,	O
London	O
,	O
on	O
Thursday	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
the	O
15th	O
.	O
and	O
16th	O
.	O
Days	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
1684	O
before	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Henry	B-pers
Tulse	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Wythens	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Levins	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Gregory	O
,	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jenner	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Majesties	O
Serjeants	O
at	O
Law	O
,	O
and	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
other	O
Judges	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Tryed	O
before	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
Judgment	O
given	O
thereon	O
,	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Sarah	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Lewis	B-pers
Gradue	I-pers
,	O
a	O
French-man	O
,	O
of	O
eleven	O
pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Coin	O
of	O
the	O
Kingdom	O
of	O
France	O
,	O
each	O
of	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
17	O
s.	O
English	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
and	O
another	O
of	O
her	O
Companions	O
,	O
had	O
pick	O
'd	O
up	O
Monsieur	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Play-House	O
,	O
begging	O
of	O
him	O
to	O
make	O
them	O
drink	O
;	O
but	O
soon	O
after	O
they	O
got	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
Chamber	O
,	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
Women	O
and	O
his	O
Money	O
being	O
of	O
a	O
sudden	O
all	O
vanish	O
'd	O
,	O
(	O
as	O
he	O
called	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
But	O
this	O
Sarah	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
alledging	O
she	O
only	O
kindled	O
a	O
Fire	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
him	O
Kissing	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Evidence	O
being	O
produced	O
but	O
himself	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
eleven	O
Razors	O
,	O
tip	O
'd	O
with	O
Silver	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Richrd	B-pers
Plat	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Barber	O
,	O
living	O
in	O
Barbycane	B-place
;	O
seven	O
of	O
which	O
Razors	O
were	O
sold	O
to	O
one	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Peacocke	I-pers
who	O
kept	O
a	O
Brokers	O
Shop	O
:	O
but	O
no	O
positive	O
Proof	O
being	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Polit	I-pers
,	O
(	O
or	O
such	O
Name	O
)	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
21	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Silver	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Flawyer	I-pers
,	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Frances	B-pers
Hutchinson	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
entising	O
the	O
Servant	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Beby	I-pers
to	O
imbesle	O
or	O
steal	O
his	O
Goods	O
and	O
selling	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
small	O
Value	O
,	O
was	O
thereof	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Blaney	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Blaney	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Riccabie	I-pers
.	O
The	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Blaney	I-pers
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
Wife	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
Perjury	O
,	O
by	O
Swearing	O
falsly	O
in	O
a	O
Cause	O
before	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
the	O
Exchequer	O
,	O
at	O
Westm	O
.	O
taking	O
two	O
Guineys	O
in	O
Earnest	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
have	O
them	O
made	O
up	O
forty	O
Guineys	O
if	O
the	O
Cause	O
succeeded	O
to	O
their	O
Mind	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
sworn	O
to	O
be	O
by	O
him	O
confess	O
'd	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
thereof	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
some	O
Gold	O
Lace	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Mushee	I-pers
,	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Crape-Gown	O
,	O
Value	O
18	O
s.	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
Value	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
silk	O
Hood	O
,	O
Value	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Stomacher	O
,	O
a	O
Girdle	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Isacke	I-pers
:	O
They	O
were	O
stol'n	O
from	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
some	O
Place	O
in	O
Southwark	B-place
,	O
but	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
passing	O
through	O
Thames-street	O
,	O
London	O
:	O
Yet	O
she	O
alledged	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
to	O
havebought	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
Broker	O
in	O
Houndsditch	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
Gown	O
might	O
be	O
like	O
another	O
.	O
But	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Swearing	O
positively	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Gown	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Isacke	I-pers
,	O
the	O
said	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Hall	I-pers
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
but	O
of	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
9	O
s.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mark	B-pers
Hambleton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Quondam	O
Servant	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Dangerfield	O
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
in	O
Clipping	O
the	O
Currant-Coyn	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
twenty	O
Pieces	O
called	O
King	O
Charles	O
the	O
First	O
Half-Crowns	O
,	O
and	O
twenty	O
other	O
Pieces	O
called	O
King	O
Charles	O
the	O
Second	O
Half	O
Crowns	O
.	O
The	O
City-Marshal	O
produced	O
a	O
Paper	O
of	O
Quick-silver	O
,	O
or	O
such-like	O
Trade	O
,	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Hambleton	O
's	O
Trunk	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
any	O
Brass	O
or	O
Copper	O
Piece	O
might	O
be	O
made	O
as	O
bright	O
and	O
to	O
look	O
like	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
Experiment	O
thereof	O
being	O
tryed	O
in	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Jury	O
:	O
besides	O
which	O
,	O
no	O
other	O
Evidence	O
,	O
except	O
his	O
buying	O
of	O
ten	O
Guineys	O
in	O
Lumbard-street	O
,	O
and	O
offering	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
them	O
with	O
Money	O
great	O
part	O
whereof	O
was	O
Clip	O
'd	O
.	O
He	O
owned	O
himself	O
to	O
have	O
formerly	O
been	O
Dangerfield	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
but	O
produced	O
several	O
to	O
witness	O
his	O
being	O
the	O
Son	O
of	O
an	O
Honest	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Ill	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
,	O
in	O
conclusion	O
,	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Stanes	I-pers
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
Great	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
certain	O
Male	O
Infant	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
.	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Male	O
Infant	O
by	O
the	O
Providence	O
of	O
God	O
did	O
bring	O
forth	O
alive	O
:	O
which	O
said	O
Male	O
infant	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Laws	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
being	O
a	O
Bastard-Child	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
said	O
Bastard-Child	O
so	O
alive	O
,	O
feloniously	O
,	O
malicitously	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
her	O
Malice	O
afore-thought	O
;	O
she	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
Assault	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
said	O
Child	O
between	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Blankets	O
did	O
put	O
,	O
and	O
thrust	O
,	O
with	O
Intent	O
to	O
smother	O
and	O
strangle	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Choaking	O
,	O
Smothering	O
,	O
and	O
Strangling	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Child	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
sick	O
,	O
pretended	O
to	O
her	O
Mistress	O
to	O
be	O
troubled	O
with	O
the	O
Wind-Cholick	O
,	O
or	O
Gravel	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
that	O
Pretence	O
kept	O
them	O
without	O
Suspicion	O
;	O
but	O
before	O
she	O
recovered	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
out	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
Delivered	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
put	O
the	O
Child	O
in	O
a	O
Box	O
:	O
How	O
be	O
it	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
speaking	O
very	O
favourably	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	B-pers
Stanes	I-pers
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Knightly	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Corporal	O
of	O
Foot	O
in	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Guards	O
.	O
Knightly	O
is	O
a	O
Youth	O
who	O
keeps	O
very	O
ill	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
at	O
a	O
House	O
together	O
with	O
other	O
such	O
Youths	O
,	O
they	O
fell	O
out	O
one	O
among	O
another	O
about	O
a	O
Cap	O
taken	O
off	O
from	O
one	O
of	O
their	O
Heads	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
said	O
Cap	O
afterwards	O
being	O
taken	O
from	O
them	O
,	O
by	O
Richardson	O
;	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
hapned	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
Knightly	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
several	O
Passes	O
killed	O
Richardson	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
have	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Man-slaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Mustard-Pot	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
;	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hannuay	I-pers
:	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Jane	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
having	O
lately	O
gone	O
in	O
Mans	O
Cloaths	O
as	O
a	O
Youth	O
to	O
wait	O
upon	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
as	O
such	O
entertained	O
into	O
the	O
Service	O
of	O
Mr.	O
William	B-pers
Hanuay	I-pers
,	O
waiting	O
upon	O
him	O
as	O
his	O
Boy	O
untill	O
she	O
had	O
gotten	O
a	O
new	O
Suit	O
of	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
with	O
the	O
said	O
Plate	O
run	O
away	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
nine	O
Shillings	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Billingsley	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Sheet	O
,	O
a	O
Dimity	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
two	O
Holland	O
Aprons	O
,	O
a	O
Callicoe	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
from	O
Sarah	B-pers
Cocker	I-pers
,	O
Widdow	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
committed	O
the	O
6th	O
.	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
the	O
33th	O
.	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
in	O
Clipping	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
twenty	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Silver	O
called	O
Queen	O
Elizabeths	O
Shillings	O
,	O
twenty	O
other	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Silver	O
called	O
King	O
Charles	O
the	O
First	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
twenty	O
other	O
Pieces	O
called	O
King	O
Charles	O
the	O
First	O
Half	O
Crowns	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Tryal	O
it	O
did	O
appear	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Jackson	O
was	O
a	O
kind	O
of	O
a	O
Merchant	O
,	O
and	O
lived	O
in	O
very	O
great	O
Credit	O
in	O
Bow-lane	B-place
,	O
London	O
:	O
The	O
Proof	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
by	O
one	O
Nicheson	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
and	O
others	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
which	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
divers	O
times	O
seen	O
Mr.	O
Jackson	O
Clip	O
Money	O
:	O
A	O
second	O
likewise	O
was	O
positive	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
thing	O
:	O
A	O
third	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
imployed	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Jackson	O
to	O
melt	O
down	O
Clippings	O
.	O
and	O
particularly	O
named	O
one	O
Day	O
wherein	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
melt	O
a	O
great	O
Quantity	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Room	O
being	O
inconvenient	O
,	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
finish	O
it	O
in	O
one	O
day	O
;	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Jackson	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
again	O
the	O
melted	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
Clippings	O
unmelted	O
;	O
That	O
some	O
Days	O
after	O
they	O
met	O
in	O
another	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
melted	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
A	O
Goldsmith	O
who	O
lives	O
at	O
Chelmesford	O
was	O
also	O
produced	O
,	O
who	O
bought	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
melted	O
Silver	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Jackson	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
Six	O
Pounds	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
another	O
Parcel	O
which	O
came	O
to	O
Ten	O
Pounds	O
.	O
A	O
Goldsmith	O
in	O
Cheap-side	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
about	O
forty	O
Ounces	O
of	O
melted	O
Silver	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
refused	O
to	O
do	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Stranger	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
plainly	O
,	O
he	O
suspected	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
Clippings	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
replyed	O
,	O
All	O
your	O
Neighbours	O
know	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
immediately	O
called	O
to	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Draper	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
Jackson	O
produced	O
above	O
twenty	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
all	O
or	O
most	O
of	O
which	O
spoke	O
of	O
his	O
great	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
great	O
Sums	O
which	O
they	O
had	O
received	O
from	O
time	O
to	O
time	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
upon	O
account	O
of	O
several	O
Matters	O
of	O
Merchandizing	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
all	O
those	O
Payments	O
they	O
found	O
very	O
good	O
Money	O
.	O
In	O
conclusion	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
High-Treason	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Crosse	I-pers
,	I-pers
(	I-pers
or	I-pers
Gosse	I-pers
)	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Murdering	O
her	O
Bastard-Child	O
,	O
by	O
throwing	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
of	O
Easement	O
,	O
filled	O
with	O
Urine	O
and	O
other	O
Excrements	O
;	O
which	O
Child	O
hapning	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
before	O
quite	O
Dead	O
,	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
lived	O
12	O
Dayes	O
in	O
a	O
Languishing	O
Condition	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Searchers	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Women	O
,	O
declaring	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
their	O
Opinion	O
,	O
the	O
putting	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Easement	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
its	O
Death	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
it	O
thrived	O
very	O
well	O
four	O
Dayes	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
at	O
length	O
Died	O
of	O
a	O
Convulsion	O
.	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
alleadging	O
that	O
it	O
fell	O
into	O
the	O
said	O
Place	O
againsther	O
Will	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
endeavoured	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
reach	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
therefore	O
acquitted	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Hubbart	I-pers
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
one	O
Ann	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Girl	O
of	O
12	O
Years	O
old	O
,	O
was	O
carrying	O
a	O
Box	O
wherein	O
was	O
Sarsnet	O
Hoods	O
,	O
gray	O
Lace	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
24	O
s.	O
through	O
Lumbard	B-place
street	I-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
of	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
March	O
;	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
Hubbart	O
snach	O
'd	O
the	O
Box	O
;	O
but	O
running	O
away	O
,	O
being	O
hastily	O
Pursued	O
,	O
drop	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Christian	B-pers
Tompson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
30	O
Yards	O
of	O
Mohair	O
Silk	O
,	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Audley	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
;	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Silk	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
or	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
drop	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Procecutor	O
only	O
Swearing	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
like	O
his	O
Silk	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
Positive	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
therefore	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
53	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
Edward	B-pers
Hynton	I-pers
:	O
the	O
manner	O
thus	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Hynton	O
being	O
to	O
pay	O
15	O
Pound	O
at	O
the	B-place
Roe-Buck	I-place
in	I-place
Fleet-street	I-place
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
telling	O
out	O
his	O
Money	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
this	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
coming	O
by	O
,	O
clap	O
'd	O
his	O
Hand	O
upon	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
a	O
Handful	O
;	O
but	O
Hynton	O
Pursuing	O
him	O
immediately	O
,	O
he	O
drop	O
'd	O
most	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
was	O
Seised	O
:	O
He	O
is	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Slath	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
Committed	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Seth	B-pers
Lamb	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Minister	O
of	O
Elin	B-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
:	O
The	O
said	O
Margaret	B-pers
Slath	I-pers
was	O
his	O
Maid-Servant	O
,	O
when	O
four	O
Men	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dead	O
of	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
broke	O
in	O
and	O
Rifled	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
ill	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
he	O
greatly	O
Suspected	O
she	O
let	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Thieves	O
,	O
or	O
left	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
he	O
Indicted	O
one	O
that	O
was	O
her	O
Sweet-Heart	O
as	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Burglary	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
then	O
Acquitted	O
;	O
as	O
likewise	O
was	O
now	O
the	O
said	O
Margaret	O
Slath	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gower	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Journey-man	O
Coach-maker	O
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Murdering	O
his	O
Wife	B-pers
,	O
it	O
being	O
the	O
same	O
Woman	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
.	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
was	O
found	O
dead	O
at	O
Green-Berry	B-place
Hill	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Parish	I-place
of	I-place
Hampsted	I-place
,	O
having	O
been	O
shot	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
with	O
a	O
Pistol	O
Bullet	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
,	O
first	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
led	O
a	O
very	O
ill	O
Life	O
,	O
having	O
married	O
another	O
Woman	O
;	O
That	O
his	O
first	O
Wife	O
having	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
he	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Month	O
of	O
March	O
sent	O
for	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
caused	O
her	O
to	O
lodge	O
several	O
Days	O
at	O
a	O
House	O
near	O
Knights-Bridge	O
;	O
That	O
about	O
the	O
Time	O
she	O
was	O
Murdered	O
he	O
was	O
known	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
never	O
more	O
seen	O
alive	O
by	O
any	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
also	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
old	O
Grudge	O
between	O
them	O
;	O
for	O
he	O
upon	O
the	O
Discourse	O
of	O
sending	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
came	O
together	O
there	O
would	O
be	O
Murder	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
5	O
l.	O
to	O
one	O
Young	O
Fellow	O
to	O
prevail	O
to	O
lye	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
a	O
Pretence	O
for	O
a	O
Divorce	O
.	O
Many	O
other	O
very	O
strong	O
Circumstances	O
were	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
himself	O
making	O
little	O
or	O
no	O
Defence	O
;	O
Pretending	O
,	O
if	O
his	O
Tryal	O
might	O
be	O
put	O
off	O
till	O
the	O
Morrow	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
produce	O
more	O
Witnesses	O
:	O
but	O
he	O
having	O
had	O
a	O
considerable	O
time	O
to	O
prove	O
them	O
,	O
as	O
being	O
brought	O
to	O
Newgate	O
before	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
only	O
an	O
Excuse	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Felony	O
and	O
Murther	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
two	O
Silver	O
Tankards	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
.	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
valued	O
at	O
14	O
l.	O
being	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Boone	I-pers
a	O
Cook	O
,	O
living	O
behind	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
London	O
.	O
The	O
said	O
Boone	O
made	O
Oath	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
going	O
from	O
Home	O
about	O
4	O
that	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
left	O
his	O
Tanckards	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
returning	O
at	O
Six	O
in	O
the	O
Even	O
,	O
found	O
them	O
gone	O
;	O
that	O
either	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
or	O
soon	O
after	O
,	O
two	O
Men	O
came	O
to	O
desire	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
into	O
Salisbury-Court	O
,	O
to	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
who	O
would	O
tell	O
him	O
what	O
was	O
become	O
of	O
his	O
Tanckards	O
;	O
that	O
going	O
accordingly	O
to	O
the	O
Swan	O
in	O
Salisbury-Court	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
Fletcher	O
there	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
one	O
Francis	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
had	O
Stole	O
his	O
Tanckards	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
stod	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
while	O
Robinson	O
fetched	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
Barr	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Tanckards	O
were	O
Sold	O
and	O
Melted	O
Down	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
he	O
having	O
Shop	O
'd	O
some	O
Women	O
,	O
this	O
Robinson	O
came	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
Privately	O
ask	O
him	O
what	O
the	O
said	O
Tankards	O
were	O
Worth	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
satisfaction	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
both	O
denied	O
all	O
they	O
had	O
formerly	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
other	O
Concurring	O
Evidence	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Fletcher	O
:	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Scot	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
Pillow-Beres	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
Silk	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Yowle	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
Ann	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
had	O
been	O
a	O
Maid-Servant	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Yowle	I-pers
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
at	O
the	B-place
Castle	I-place
and	I-place
Falcon	I-place
Inn	I-place
without	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
.	O
Her	O
Mistress	O
alledged	O
she	O
had	O
Missed	O
several	O
Things	O
during	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
her	O
Service	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Two	O
Broad	O
pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
some	O
Linnen	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Pillow-Beres	O
and	O
Ribbon	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
Ribbon	O
in	O
her	O
Maids	O
Trunk	O
;	O
with	O
many	O
other	O
Aggravations	O
;	O
rendring	O
the	O
said	O
Ann	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
Common	O
Thief	O
.	O
But	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
Hand	O
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
Produced	O
her	O
former	O
Master	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
Intrusted	O
her	O
with	O
all	O
his	O
Goods	O
;	O
his	O
wife	O
Sickning	O
and	O
Dying	O
whilest	O
this	O
Maid	O
lived	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
Lost	O
or	O
Missed	O
any	O
thing	O
whilst	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Several	O
other	O
Winesses	O
speaking	O
much	O
of	O
the	O
Maids	O
Honesty	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Yowle	O
never	O
Charged	O
her	O
as	O
a	O
Thief	O
untill	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
Demand	O
her	O
Wages	O
:	O
And	O
the	O
said	O
Mrs.	O
Yowel	O
discovring	O
her	O
Self	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
Passionate	O
angry	O
Woman	O
,	O
even	O
before	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Ann	O
Wood	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
by	O
Vertue	O
of	O
an	O
Inquisition	O
,	O
taken	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
Coroner	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Cap	B-pers
.	I-pers
Blackston	I-pers
,	O
as	O
Accessary	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Edward	B-pers
Hubbard	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Charles	O
Rowlinson	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Cap	O
.	O
Blackston	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
.	O
of	O
Aprill	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Back	O
Back	B-place
Temple-Gate	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
White-Fryers	I-place
:	O
For	O
Proof	O
of	O
which	O
,	O
were	O
these	O
Circumstances	O
Following	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
said	O
Edward	B-pers
Hubbard	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Rowlinson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
BurbridgeChurch	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Blow	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
,	O
were	O
that	O
Night	O
all	O
Drinking	O
at	O
the	O
George	O
Tavern	O
in	O
White-Fryers	O
;	O
going	O
from	O
the	O
said	O
Tavern	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
parted	O
at	O
the	O
Doore	O
.	O
Hubbard	O
,	O
Rawlinson	O
,	O
and	O
Williams	O
,	O
turning	O
down	O
the	O
Fryers	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
rest	O
turned	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Fleet-street	O
;	O
that	O
immediately	O
,	O
Cap	O
.	O
Blackston	O
was	O
Killed	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Back-Gate	O
of	O
the	O
Temple	O
:	O
also	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
Cap	O
.	O
Blackston	O
,	O
was	O
then	O
come	O
from	O
an	O
Eating-House	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
through	O
Salisbury-Court	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
pass	O
that	O
way	O
to	O
his	O
Lodging	O
.	O
A	O
Gentleman	O
of	O
the	O
Temple	O
,	O
whose	O
Chamber	O
is	O
over	O
the	O
Gate	O
,	O
heard	O
the	O
Clashing	O
of	O
Swords	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
going	O
away	O
of	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Persons	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
of	O
Hubbard	O
's	O
confessing	O
to	O
a	O
Chirurgeon	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
wounded	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
White-Fryers	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
of	O
Night	O
;	O
also	O
the	O
Sword	O
of	O
Williams	O
being	O
sworn	O
to	O
be	O
bloody	O
when	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Blackston	O
,	O
upon	O
Inquisition	O
,	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
wounded	O
in	O
three	O
Places	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
several	O
Swords	O
:	O
Hubbard	O
and	O
Rawlinson	O
fled	O
from	O
Justice	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Albeit	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Murder	O
,	O
yet	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Man-slaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
Killing	O
George	B-pers
Bowes	I-pers
,	O
Esquire	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21th	O
.	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Robinson	O
was	O
a	O
Lieutenant	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Bowes	O
a	O
Captain	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
lately	O
from	O
Tangier	O
in	O
the	O
Ship	O
called	O
the	O
English	O
Tyger	O
;	O
and	O
about	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
after	O
they	O
came	O
a	O
Shore	O
,	O
hapned	O
to	O
Fight	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
near	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
(	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
time	O
)	O
and	O
making	O
several	O
Passes	O
at	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
both	O
went	O
off	O
dangerously	O
wounded	O
;	O
and	O
some	O
Spectators	O
were	O
of	O
Opinion	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Robinson	O
had	O
his	O
Deaths	O
Wound	O
by	O
his	O
Staggering	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
those	O
of	O
Capt	O
.	O
Bowes	O
proved	O
only	O
mortal	O
,	O
he	O
dying	O
thereof	O
about	O
three	O
Days	O
after	O
.	O
A	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
was	O
given	O
in	O
Court	O
by	O
Persons	O
of	O
Quality	O
,	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Robinson	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
that	O
Captain	O
Bowes	O
in	O
his	O
Life-time	O
was	O
generally	O
quarrelsome	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
therefore	O
acquitted	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Indictment	O
of	O
Murther	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Man-slaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
herein	O
before	O
mentioned	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Stealing	O
two	O
Silver	O
Tankards	O
from	O
Hen	O
.	O
Boone	O
,	O
was	O
also	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Burglary	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
and	O
two	O
others	O
coming	O
to	O
drink	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Elenor	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
Widdow	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
,	O
took	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
break	O
open	O
her	O
Lodging	O
Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
from	O
them	O
120	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
besides	O
Rings	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Value	O
;	O
which	O
they	O
so	O
concealed	O
about	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
unsuspected	O
,	O
bidding	O
the	O
Maid	O
look	O
after	O
her	O
Tankard	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Burglary	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Measures	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Campaign	O
Coats	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
George	B-pers
Freed	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
left	O
him	O
in	O
trust	O
with	O
his	O
House	O
whilst	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Sturbidge	O
Fair	O
;	O
but	O
at	O
his	O
Return	O
,	O
Measures	O
was	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
stol'n	O
several	O
Things	O
from	O
him	O
:	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Ashburneham	I-pers
,	O
a	O
notorious	O
Highway-man	O
,	O
whose	O
Name	O
hath	O
been	O
in	O
a	O
Proclamation	O
and	O
several	O
Gazettes	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
his	O
being	O
Apprehended	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Page	I-pers
a	O
Headborough	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
The	O
said	O
Smith	O
and	O
other	O
Highway-men	O
having	O
committed	O
several	O
Robberies	O
on	O
the	O
Road	O
near	O
Stoke	O
Newington	O
,	O
in	O
July	O
was	O
a	O
Twelve-month	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
said	O
Page	O
with	O
Watchmen	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
being	O
in	O
Pursuit	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
shot	O
at	O
the	O
Watch-men	O
and	O
kill	O
'd	O
the	O
Hedborough	O
in	O
Execution	O
of	O
his	O
Office	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
Gang	O
,	O
who	O
pretends	O
to	O
be	O
reformed	O
,	O
swore	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
other	O
concurring	O
Evidence	O
was	O
so	O
plain	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
willful	O
Murder	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Hutton	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Bodies	O
,	O
four	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
three	O
Pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Thread	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
from	O
her	O
Master	O
Richard	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
:	O
but	O
the	O
said	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Hutton	I-pers
so	O
defended	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
as	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
thought	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
mistaken	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Peacocke	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
seven	O
Razors	O
tip	O
'd	O
with	O
Silver	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Plat	I-pers
in	O
Barbycane	B-place
:	O
but	O
she	O
made	O
it	O
appear	O
,	O
to	O
have	O
bought	O
them	O
fairly	O
in	O
her	O
Shop	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
Broker	O
s	O
Shop	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Which	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
,	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Five	O
received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
for	O
the	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
drawn	O
and	O
hanged	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Gower	I-pers
for	O
killing	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Hubbard	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Ashburneham	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
Hanged	O
.	O
Seven	O
were	O
burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
Sam	B-pers
.	I-pers
Knightley	O
,	O
Nich	O
.	O
Polit	O
(	O
or	O
such	O
a	O
name	O
,	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Measures	I-pers
,	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Hall	O
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
.	O
Two	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
.	O
Two	O
to	O
be	O
Whip	O
'd	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Billingsley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Blaney	I-pers
.	O
One	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Jonathan	O
Hall	O
.	O
