TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
Of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
,	O
And	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
Held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
,	O
The	O
29th	O
.	O
30th	O
.	O
Days	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
as	O
also	O
May	O
1	O
.	O
1685	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Reign	O
.	O
THe	O
Sessions	O
of	O
PEACE	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
and	O
Gaol-delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
being	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
the	O
29th	O
.	O
and	O
30th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
on	O
Friday	O
,	O
May	O
1	O
.	O
1685	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jenner	I-pers
Kt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Serjeants	O
at	O
Law	O
,	O
and	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
City	O
;	O
together	O
with	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
Humphrey	B-pers
Thornberry	I-pers
John	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Mitchell	I-pers
John	B-pers
Reginolds	I-pers
John	B-pers
Rolls	I-pers
John	B-pers
Hedgabout	I-pers
John	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
James	B-pers
Reddish	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Law	I-pers
Alexander	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
Francis	O
Boyton	O
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Nehemiah	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
John	B-pers
Anger	I-pers
John	B-pers
Kirk	I-pers
John	B-pers
Vigars	I-pers
John	B-pers
Howlett	I-pers
Mark	B-pers
Lawne	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Burch	I-pers
Abraham	B-pers
Harrisson	I-pers
James	B-pers
Cunningham	I-pers
Edmund	B-pers
Yeoman	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Bromfeild	I-pers
.	O
The	O
London	O
Jury	O
after	O
some	O
few	O
Tryals	O
(	O
upon	O
some	O
Exceptions	O
)	O
were	O
Dismist	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
their	O
stead	O
these	O
following	O
Empannell	O
'd	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Cotton	I-pers
Peter	B-pers
Floyer	I-pers
Laurence	B-pers
Coale	I-pers
John	B-pers
Ballard	I-pers
John	B-pers
Richley	I-pers
Philip	B-pers
Stubbs	I-pers
William	B-pers
Pye	I-pers
John	B-pers
Pott	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Larnar	I-pers
Nicholas	B-pers
Heyward	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Cooke	I-pers
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
from	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Allum	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
said	O
Browne	O
being	O
taken	O
on	O
suspicion	O
and	O
carried	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
she	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
saying	O
,	O
That	O
her	O
Husband	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
knock	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
unless	O
she	O
would	O
steal	O
something	O
from	O
the	O
said	O
Allum	O
.	O
Which	O
being	O
fully	O
and	O
positively	O
proved	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
Nine	O
shillings	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Dye	I-pers
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Sinclo	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
taking	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
White-bone	O
Lace	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
40	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
Widow	O
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
said	O
Walker	O
meeting	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
the	O
Butcher-Rowe	B-place
without	I-place
Temple-Bar	I-place
,	O
about	O
Three	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Walker	O
,	O
forcing	O
her	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
and	O
then	O
got	O
her	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
robbing	O
her	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Lace	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
prove	O
them	O
selves	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
them	O
both	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
them	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Robbery	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Davies	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
divers	O
pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
and	O
a	O
Farendine	O
Mantua	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
in	O
all	O
of	O
60	O
l.	O
from	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
affirm	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
said	O
Davies	O
lodged	O
in	O
Hunter	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
being	O
from	O
home	O
,	O
Davies	O
went	O
into	O
their	O
Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
carried	O
away	O
a	O
Trunk	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
said	O
Gold	O
,	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
lay	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
clearly	O
proved	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ralph	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Maiden	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Kensington	B-place
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
James	B-pers
Burden	I-pers
,	O
who	O
hath	O
already	O
confessed	O
the	O
Indictment	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
did	O
break	O
open	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
Earl	B-pers
of	I-pers
Nottingham	I-pers
,	O
stealing	O
from	O
thence	O
divers	O
parcels	O
of	O
Cloaths	O
of	O
the	O
proper	O
Goods	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Carpenter	I-pers
,	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Earl	O
of	O
Nottingham	O
;	O
to	O
wit	O
,	O
one	O
black	O
Suit	O
,	O
one	O
stuff	O
Coat	O
,	O
three	O
Swords	O
,	O
one	O
flower	O
'd	O
Sattin	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
two	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
parcels	O
of	O
Linnen	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
of	O
considerable	O
value	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
being	O
very	O
plain	O
and	O
full	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Cloaths	O
being	O
found	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
swore	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Carpenter	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
being	O
fully	O
satisfied	O
therewith	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
said	O
Watson	O
and	O
Maiden	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Buckler	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Dorcas	B-pers
Taverner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
White	O
bone	O
Lace	O
,	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
fully	O
appearing	O
only	O
against	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
both	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Davies	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Canvas	O
Bagg	O
and	O
five	O
Pounds	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
Margaret	B-pers
Dransfeild	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Davies	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Dransfeild	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
having	O
a	O
Bagg	O
of	O
Money	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Davies	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
and	O
run	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
said	O
Dransfeild	O
cried	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
on	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
Seized	O
by	O
three	O
Men	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Dransfeilds	O
Shop	O
door	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
still	O
denied	O
the	O
having	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
going	O
to	O
search	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
loose	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Hands	O
,	O
and	O
thrust	O
it	O
under	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
the	O
Bagg	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
drops	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
takes	O
it	O
up	O
again	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
the	O
Money	O
you	O
tax	O
me	O
with	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Persons	O
present	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
to	O
the	O
Owner	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Excuse	O
of	O
himself	O
pretended	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
not	O
,	O
till	O
they	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
by	O
chance	O
step	O
'd	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
full	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
West	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
from	O
Gideon	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
;	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Mills	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Buttery	O
after	O
the	O
Maid	O
Servant	O
of	O
the	O
Mr.	O
Mills	O
as	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
draw	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Brandy	O
Stole	O
away	O
the	O
said	O
Tankard	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
plain	O
against	O
her	O
besides	O
her	O
own	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
of	O
Peace	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
but	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
Poverty	O
compelled	O
her	O
so	O
to	O
do	O
;	O
which	O
Confession	O
was	O
proved	O
by	O
the	O
Justice	O
of	O
Peace	O
his	O
Clerk	O
,	O
yet	O
she	O
denying	O
the	O
matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Banfeild	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Zachariah	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Thompson	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
the	O
fourth	O
day	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
Eleven	O
and	O
Twelve	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
,	O
did	O
Break	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Butlin	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Stole	O
form	O
thence	O
one	O
Drabdebury	O
Stuff	O
Suit	O
,	O
one	O
Gray	O
Cloth	O
Suit	O
,	O
one	O
Hair	O
Camlet	O
Coat	O
,	O
one	O
Mohair	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
Clothes	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
five	O
Pound	O
;	O
but	O
altho	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
seemed	O
to	O
appear	O
very	O
Circumstantial	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
them	O
in	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Elton	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
from	O
Samuel	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
one	O
Knife	O
one	O
silver	O
Tobacco-stopper	O
one	O
bundle	O
of	O
Keys	O
,	O
18	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
one	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
one	O
Hanger	O
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
that	O
the	O
Sixteenth	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
about	O
two	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
a	O
Cellar-window	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Smiths	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
the	O
things	O
aforesaid	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
not	O
getting	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
again	O
the	O
man	O
finding	O
himself	O
robbed	O
when	O
he	O
arose	O
,	O
acquainted	O
his	O
Wife	O
therewith	O
and	O
she	O
presently	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
the	O
Thief	O
found	O
the	O
said	O
Elton	O
under	O
a	O
Basket	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
very	O
strong	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ambrose	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Carpenter	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Ann	B-pers
Buller	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
thence	O
one	O
Feather-Bed	O
,	O
four	O
Blankets	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Ann	O
Buller	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
only	O
against	O
Morris	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
and	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
rest	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
taking	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
one	O
Isaac	B-pers
Blunt	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
very	O
plain	O
her	O
hand	O
being	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Blunt	O
's	O
pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
vindication	O
of	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
Ten	O
pence	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Lippy	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Wetherington	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Martha	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Diaper	O
Table	O
Cloths	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Flaxen	O
sheet	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
Jeptha	B-pers
Gridley	I-pers
of	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
20	O
s.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Gridley	O
's	O
Wife	O
finding	O
the	O
said	O
Linnen	O
wanting	O
,	O
she	O
left	O
word	O
with	O
all	O
the	O
Pawn-Brokers	O
thereabout	O
,	O
acquainting	O
them	O
with	O
the	O
marks	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Linnen	O
and	O
thereby	O
she	O
got	O
News	O
thereof	O
,	O
being	O
offered	O
to	O
pawn	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
to	O
wit	O
Ann	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
;	O
but	O
she	O
confessing	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
the	O
said	O
Sarah	O
in	O
vindication	O
of	O
her	O
self	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
found	O
,	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
full	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Lippy	O
,	O
only	O
the	O
said	O
Lippy	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Burglary	O
and	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
said	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
rest	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Bell	O
:	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Lippy	O
:	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
W.	B-pers
Cosenes	I-pers
,	O
T.	B-pers
Barnett	I-pers
,	O
together	O
with	O
Matthew	B-pers
Chamlett	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
Cows	O
each	O
of	O
the	O
price	O
of	O
4	O
l.	O
from	O
Joseph	B-pers
Chamlett	I-pers
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
between	O
the	O
said	O
Matthew	B-pers
Chamlett	I-pers
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Chamlett	I-pers
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
Joseph	O
and	O
his	O
Sollicitor	O
were	O
Committed	O
for	O
a	O
Conspiracy	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
Order	O
of	O
Court	O
,	O
to	O
answer	O
to	O
an	O
Information	O
in	O
the	O
Kings	O
Bench	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
next	O
Term	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Langley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mildred	I-place
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
parcels	O
of	O
Cloaths	O
and	O
Linnen	O
,	O
from	O
Jane	B-pers
Rochester	I-pers
Widow	O
:	O
That	O
on	O
Saturday	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
9	O
or	O
10	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Langley	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Chamber	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Mrs.	O
Rochester	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
what	O
he	O
made	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
He	O
thought	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Coffee-house	O
.	O
The	O
proof	O
against	O
him	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
Cup	O
,	O
was	O
very	O
plain	O
and	O
full	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Linnen	O
and	O
Clothes	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
Chamber	O
in	O
a	O
heap	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
as	O
was	O
supposed	O
,	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
opportunity	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Coach	O
glasses	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Livery	O
Cloak	O
,	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
Nelson	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
the	O
Coachman	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Nelson	O
finding	O
the	O
said	O
Glasses	O
stolen	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
inquiry	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Frames	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Glasses	O
at	O
one	O
Johnson	O
's	O
house	O
in	O
Cow-lane	O
,	O
and	O
inquiring	O
of	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
frames	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
said	O
Price	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
where	O
Price	O
was	O
in	O
prison	O
,	O
he	O
confest	O
to	O
the	O
Coachman	O
where	O
the	O
Glasses	O
were	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Christopher	B-pers
Orchard	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margarets	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Yard	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
thence	O
a	O
Pepper-box	O
,	O
Mustard	O
box	O
,	O
three	O
Spoons	O
,	O
two	O
Saltsellers	O
,	O
all	O
silver	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
proper	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Robert	O
Yard	O
.	O
The	O
Witnesses	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
were	O
,	O
that	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
they	O
finding	O
the	O
House	O
robbed	O
of	O
the	O
Plate	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
acquainting	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
thereof	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
said	O
Orchard	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
who	O
fell	O
into	O
a	O
laughter	O
which	O
caused	O
them	O
to	O
suspect	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
Theft	O
,	O
and	O
searching	O
his	O
Pocket	O
found	O
the	O
said	O
Plate	O
,	O
The	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Minshall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
for	O
murdering	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Battle	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Witnesses	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
swore	O
,	O
They	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
Brandy-shop	O
near	O
Charing-cross	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Minshall	O
and	O
Battle	O
were	O
at	O
which	O
time	O
Battle	O
gave	O
Minshall	O
very	O
reproachful	O
language	O
,	O
threatning	O
to	O
fight	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
Minshall	O
refused	O
;	O
but	O
afterwards	O
taking	O
his	O
leave	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
homeward	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Battle	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
swearing	O
,	O
God	O
damn	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
fight	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
run	O
him	O
through	O
.	O
Upon	O
that	O
they	O
fought	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
parted	O
;	O
but	O
Battle	O
still	O
pursuing	O
him	O
,	O
fighting	O
again	O
,	O
Minshall	O
run	O
him	O
through	O
by	O
which	O
wound	O
he	O
suddenly	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
James	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Wilsdon	B-place
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
ten	O
Weather	O
sheep	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
Ram	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
grounds	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Winfeild	I-pers
,	O
who	O
making	O
inquiry	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
had	O
an	O
Account	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
driven	O
to	O
Limehouse	O
;	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
seek	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
James	O
's	O
Custody	O
,	O
four	O
alive	O
,	O
and	O
seven	O
Skins	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
one	O
Goose	O
of	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
but	O
a	O
slight	O
Excuse	O
,	O
the	O
matter	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
David	B-pers
Anthonyck	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Paddington	B-place
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
taking	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Poynton	I-pers
three	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
buttons	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
mushing	O
Crevat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
9	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
a	O
Whip	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
near	O
Hide-park	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
February	O
about	O
7	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
affirm	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
said	O
Poynton	O
being	O
robbed	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Whitwood	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
make	O
search	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
accordingly	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
searching	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Mrs.	O
Hill	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
suspected	O
place	O
for	O
harbouring	O
of	O
Rogues	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
said	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
her	O
house	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Buttons	O
.	O
AnotherWitness	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
affirm	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
said	O
Gardner	O
and	O
Anthony	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
others	O
,	O
not	O
as	O
yet	O
apprehended	O
,	O
robbed	O
the	O
said	O
Poyston	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
very	O
clear	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
several	O
Goods	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Showell	I-pers
.	O
The	O
said	O
Charles	O
Middleton	O
,	O
upon	O
his	O
Arraignment	O
,	O
confessed	O
the	O
Felony	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Julian	B-pers
Penn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Bason	O
from	O
Katharine	B-pers
Lady	I-pers
Walgrave	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
offered	O
it	O
to	O
Sale	O
to	O
several	O
Goldsmiths	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
selling	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
in	O
Fleetstreet	O
for	O
9	O
l.	O
and	O
upwards	O
,	O
as	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Goldsmith	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Proof	O
being	O
full	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Saterthite	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pauls	I-place
Shadwel	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Tan	O
'd	O
Hydes	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Herring	I-pers
,	O
on	O
Febr	O
.	O
17	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
s	O
inquiry	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
custody	O
of	O
a	O
Cobler	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Satherthite	O
,	O
who	O
owning	O
the	O
sale	O
thereof	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Aufrey	B-pers
King	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
taking	O
two	O
musling	O
Night-rayls	O
,	O
12	O
pair	O
of	O
Kids	O
leather	O
Gloves	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Sleeves	O
,	O
several	O
pieces	O
of	O
Lace	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
parcels	O
of	O
Linnen	O
from	O
Heneage	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
carrying	O
away	O
several	O
Goods	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
conceal	O
and	O
keep	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
producing	O
several	O
persons	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
honesty	O
of	O
her	O
Life	O
and	O
Conversation	O
,	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Gown	O
,	O
one	O
Peticoat	O
,	O
one	O
flannel	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Cloaths	O
from	O
Johanna	B-pers
Lucraft	I-pers
;	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Wilson	O
lay	O
at	O
Lucraft	O
's	O
house	O
for	O
about	O
five	O
weeks	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
said	O
Cloaths	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
30s	O
.	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Cockerim	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proof	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
very	O
full	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
made	O
appear	O
by	O
a	O
Note	O
under	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Blancher	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Parcel	I-pers
Goldsmith	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
positive	O
Proof	O
made	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lynister	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
24	O
Shoes	O
from	O
Stephen	B-pers
Dangerfeild	I-pers
.	O
A	O
second	O
Indictment	O
against	O
them	O
for	O
stealing	O
12	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
appearing	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Doyley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
from	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
;	O
which	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hillard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michaels	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6s	O
.	O
in	O
money	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
Lowry	B-pers
Lindsey	I-pers
.	O
The	O
fact	O
being	O
punctually	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
several	O
Goods	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Showell	I-pers
;	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
positive	O
Proof	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Newberry	I-pers
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
a	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
.	O
The	O
stealing	O
of	O
the	O
Tankard	O
being	O
only	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gelding	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Upton	I-pers
;	O
but	O
there	O
appearing	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Burden	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
9	O
yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Velvet	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Lord	O
John	B-pers
Oselton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Peddington	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
flying	O
from	O
his	O
Colours	O
.	O
The	O
Witnesses	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
proving	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Regiment	O
under	O
the	O
Command	O
of	O
Capt	O
.	O
Kirk	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
deserted	O
his	O
Colours	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Blank	I-pers
five	O
times	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Horses	O
and	O
two	O
Mares	O
,	O
with	O
Bridle	O
and	O
Saddle	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
Holden	B-pers
,	O
Dermin	B-pers
,	O
Row	B-pers
,	O
and	O
others	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
very	O
clear	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
in	O
all	O
the	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Peter	B-pers
Roach	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Tomlyn	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
of	O
one	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
Buttons	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
;	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
Indicted	O
as	O
Accessary	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Robbery	O
.	O
The	O
Witnesses	O
made	O
it	O
appear	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Tomlyn	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Bow	O
,	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
said	O
Roach	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
others	O
,	O
who	O
carried	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
bound	O
him	O
,	O
then	O
robbed	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
aforesaid	O
:	O
which	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
quitted	O
Elizabeth	O
Hill	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samuel	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Stretton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
stealing	O
two	O
Suits	O
of	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
being	O
clear	O
only	O
against	O
Smith	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
Stretton	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Katharine	B-pers
Masey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
Hackney	B-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Clock	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
30l	O
.	O
two	O
Gold	O
Laces	O
,	O
and	O
30l	O
.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mann	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Masey	O
being	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Mann	O
,	O
he	O
going	O
from	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
intrusting	O
her	O
with	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
returning	O
home	O
again	O
,	O
found	O
wanting	O
the	O
things	O
and	O
money	O
aforementioned	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Proof	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
clear	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
though	O
fit	O
to	O
acquit	O
her	O
.	O
Patrick	B-pers
Purcell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Precincts	B-place
of	I-place
the	I-place
Savoy	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
murthering	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Crompton	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Witnesses	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
said	O
Purcell	O
and	O
Crompton	O
drinking	O
in	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
together	O
,	O
where	O
words	O
did	O
arise	O
between	O
them	O
about	O
paying	O
of	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
alledging	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
to	O
pay	O
it	O
,	O
whereupon	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
did	O
ensue	O
,	O
which	O
occasion	O
'd	O
the	O
mischief	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
not	O
fully	O
appearing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
only	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Man-slaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Lionel	B-pers
Fenninck	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Pistols	O
from	O
James	B-pers
Meryweather	I-pers
,	O
and	O
another	O
person	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
very	O
strong	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Gabriel	B-pers
Sheires	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Horse	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Sheires	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
,	O
meeting	O
with	O
Watson	O
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
near	O
Battersey	O
,	O
Sheires	O
and	O
his	O
Companions	O
stopped	O
him	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
riding	O
along	O
,	O
took	O
him	O
off	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
carried	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
Field	O
,	O
robbed	O
him	O
of	O
13s	O
.	O
taking	O
away	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
leaving	O
him	O
bound	O
hand	O
and	O
foot	O
.	O
The	O
matter	O
being	O
strongly	O
proved	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Peter	B-pers
Roach	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Halsey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
of	O
one	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Handerson	I-pers
.	O
They	O
were	O
likewise	O
Indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
for	O
robbing	O
Alexander	B-pers
Handerson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
said	O
Roach	O
and	O
Halsey	O
,	O
with	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
others	O
,	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Handerson	O
,	O
and	O
robbed	O
him	O
of	O
three	O
gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
silver	O
Cup	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
strongly	O
proved	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Robbery	O
both	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Bridge	B-pers
Collens	I-pers
and	O
Judith	B-pers
Viner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
China	O
Cup	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Pemberton	I-pers
:	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Pemberton	O
's	O
house	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
only	O
a	O
Servant	O
Maid	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
several	O
Goods	O
for	O
my	O
Lady	O
Banks	O
:	O
but	O
that	O
proving	O
a	O
Falsity	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
bound	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
ten	O
pence	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Farlowe	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
Coach	O
Glasses	O
from	O
Roger	B-pers
Whitley	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
being	O
strong	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
themselves	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
them	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Price	I-pers
being	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
several	O
Coach-Glasses	O
from	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Blathwaite	I-pers
;	O
it	O
being	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Coale	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Razors	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Scissors	O
,	O
one	O
Water	O
pot	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
;	O
which	O
being	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
Ten	O
pence	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Peters	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Curtains	O
from	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
,	O
and	O
being	O
clearly	O
Convicted	O
thereof	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
Ten	O
pence	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
Richard	B-pers
Woolley	I-pers
,	O
but	O
there	O
appearing	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Miscall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
White-Chappel	B-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Hay	O
from	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Cox	O
having	O
missed	O
some	O
Hay	O
,	O
suspected	O
the	O
said	O
Miscall	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
made	O
a	O
search	O
in	O
Miscalls	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
as	O
they	O
verily	O
believed	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
Hay	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
examining	O
the	O
said	O
Miscall	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
that	O
Hay	O
,	O
in	O
excuse	O
of	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
thereupon	O
took	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
Loft	O
.	O
The	O
matter	O
being	O
but	O
of	O
small	O
Value	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
Ten	O
pence	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Hackney	B-place
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Iron	O
Grate	O
,	O
one	O
Lock	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
le-Butt	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
Ten	O
pence	O
.	O
Nowel	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
11	O
s.	O
from	O
one	O
Joan	B-pers
Isaac	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
Excuse	O
of	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Katharine	B-pers
Mathews	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
14	O
Yards	O
of	O
Fustin	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
one	O
Francis	B-pers
Firchild	I-pers
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
full	O
Proof	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Oakely	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
with	O
two	O
others	O
,	O
did	O
Break	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mrs	O
Ann	B-pers
Buller	I-pers
Widdow	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
one	O
Feather	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
Blankets	O
:	O
But	O
giving	O
a	O
good	O
Account	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
and	O
Conversation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Katharine	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
Spoon	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
Brock	I-pers
Vintner	O
.	O
Which	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
Ten	O
pence	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Bartlett	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
yards	O
of	O
Bone-lace	O
from	O
Cary	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
value	O
35	O
s.	O
which	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
John	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Baker	O
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Peal	O
,	O
one	O
shovel	O
,	O
one	O
brass	O
skillet	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
one	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Steele	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
vindication	O
of	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
stuff	O
Crape	O
Gown	O
from	O
one	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bawden	I-pers
:	O
That	O
the	O
said	O
Roberts	O
came	O
to	O
Bawden	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
tarrying	O
there	O
some	O
short	O
time	O
,	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
with	O
him	O
the	O
said	O
Gown	O
,	O
which	O
afterwards	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
custody	O
:	O
The	O
Theft	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
William	B-pers
Cottle	I-pers
.	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
one	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Prince	I-pers
,	O
stealing	O
divers	O
great	O
quantities	O
of	O
Linnen	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Chattels	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Prince	O
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
Prince	O
suspecting	O
the	O
said	O
Cottle	O
to	O
have	O
robbed	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
had	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
fully	O
and	O
clearly	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Elthorpe	I-pers
,	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
several	O
Pots	O
from	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Havery	I-pers
Vintner	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
Elthorpe	O
drinking	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
at	O
Havery	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
went	O
away	O
without	O
paying	O
for	O
his	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
away	O
with	O
him	O
several	O
Pots	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Havery	O
's	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Andrew	B-pers
Poultney	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Horse	O
from	O
one	O
Robert	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
;	O
but	O
there	O
appearing	O
no	O
positive	O
Proof	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Batchellor	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Clerken-well	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Curtains	O
from	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
,	O
but	O
there	O
appearing	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Wall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Precincts	B-place
of	I-place
the	I-place
Savoy	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
speaking	O
seditious	O
Words	O
against	O
the	O
Government	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
producing	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
Life	O
and	O
Conversation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Beazil	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
Goldsmith	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
buying	O
stolen	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
razing	O
out	O
the	O
marks	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
thereupon	O
fined	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
5	O
l.	O
also	O
ordered	O
to	O
make	O
restitution	O
for	O
all	O
the	O
Goods	O
he	O
so	O
bought	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
find	O
Sureties	O
for	O
his	O
Good	O
Behaviour	O
.	O
Several	O
were	O
Indicted	O
,	O
to	O
wit	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Payne	I-pers
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Smitten	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
for	O
speaking	O
Words	O
against	O
the	O
Government	O
.	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
being	O
brought	O
from	O
the	O
Kings-Bench	O
by	O
Habeas	O
Corpus	O
,	O
pleaded	O
His	O
Majesties	O
most	O
Gracious	O
Pardon	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
,	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Fourteen	O
Ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Silk	I-pers
,	O
Elinor	B-pers
Michell	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Lippy	I-pers
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Orchard	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Cooke	I-pers
,	O
Lionel	B-pers
Feninck	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Farlowe	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Farlowe	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Davies	I-pers
,	O
Nowell	B-pers
Greene	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Langley	I-pers
.	O
Eight	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Botturnley	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Langley	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Satequake	I-pers
,	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
,	O
Patrick	B-pers
Purcell	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Elithorpe	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
.	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
passed	O
upon	O
Twenty	O
three	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Davies	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Elton	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Lachford	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Cottle	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Dye	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Sinclo	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Ellis	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
David	B-pers
Antholick	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Hill	O
,	O
Ralph	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Maiden	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Burden	I-pers
,	O
Julian	B-pers
Penn	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Peddington	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Roach	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Hallsey	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Blank	I-pers
,	O
Gabriel	B-pers
Seires	I-pers
.	O
Elinor	B-pers
Mitchell	I-pers
pleaded	O
her	O
Belly	O
.	O
Four	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Payn	I-pers
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Smitten	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith-Long	I-pers
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
being	O
brought	O
from	O
the	O
Kings-Bench	O
by	O
Habeas	O
Corpus	O
,	O
pleaded	O
His	O
Majesties	O
most	O
Gracious	O
Pardon	O
.	O
