TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
Of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
;	O
And	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
Held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
,	O
The	O
4th	O
.	O
and	O
5th	O
.	O
of	O
June	O
1685	O
,	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
First	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
PEACE	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
being	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
on	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
June	O
the	O
4th	O
and	O
5th	O
,	O
1685	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jenner	I-pers
Kt	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Serjeants	O
at	O
Law	O
,	O
and	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
City	O
:	O
Together	O
with	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
,	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Jeeckes	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Johane	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Chase	I-pers
William	B-pers
Skinner	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Blackway	I-pers
John	B-pers
Redwood	I-pers
John	B-pers
West	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Washington	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Steere	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Bolytha	I-pers
Arthur	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
John	B-pers
Lawford	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
John	B-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
Benjamin	B-pers
Dunn	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Fuller	I-pers
Stephen	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Bishopp	I-pers
John	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
William	B-pers
Baldwin	I-pers
William	B-pers
Wheatley	I-pers
John	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Redhill	I-pers
Lawrence	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Saltmarsh	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
London	O
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Black	O
and	O
Brown	O
Mare	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
Davidge	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
21	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
Davidge	O
lost	O
the	O
said	O
Mare	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Ground	O
in	O
Essex	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Davidge	O
,	O
went	O
from	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
being	O
Sick	O
,	O
about	O
Lady	O
Day	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
Davidge	O
making	O
inquiry	O
after	O
the	O
said	O
Mare	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sold	O
the	O
same	O
for	O
53	O
s.	O
which	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Odian	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Buff-Coat	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Crew	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
Crew	O
did	O
put	O
his	O
Coat	O
to	O
be	O
Scowred	O
to	O
another	O
Person	O
,	O
who	O
lost	O
the	O
said	O
Coat	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
8th	O
.	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
made	O
Inquiry	O
after	O
his	O
Coat	O
at	O
Odian	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
Pawn	O
Broker	O
,	O
and	O
inquired	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
such	O
Coat	O
pawned	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
at	O
first	O
denied	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
If	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
35	O
s.	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
the	O
Coat	O
again	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Man	O
telling	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
poor	O
,	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
the	O
said	O
Coat	O
without	O
money	O
,	O
which	O
Odian	O
refused	O
to	O
do	O
;	O
thereupon	O
Crew	O
had	O
a	O
Warrant	O
from	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
to	O
search	O
Odian	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
said	O
Coat	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
not	O
being	O
positive	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
producing	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
pawn	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
by	O
a	O
Stranger	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
his	O
Name	O
was	O
Smith	O
,	O
for	O
35	O
s.	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
London	O
,	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
silk	O
Mantles	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
Blanket	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
on	O
April	O
30.	O
from	O
George	B-pers
Morisson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
formerly	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Morisson	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
had	O
one	O
S.	O
Chapman	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
the	O
said	O
Chapman	O
did	O
at	O
Night-times	O
lead	O
Ann	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
into	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Morisson	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
unknown	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
by	O
some	O
means	O
or	O
other	O
understanding	O
thereof	O
,	O
and	O
missing	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
accused	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
the	O
taking	O
away	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Proof	O
against	O
her	O
not	O
being	O
punctual	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
-	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
Amy	B-pers
Hurst	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Gay	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Hurst	O
,	O
the	O
11th	O
.	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Tankard	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
staid	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
about	O
two	O
Hours	O
,	O
tarrying	O
for	O
one	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
pretended	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
said	O
Tankard	O
,	O
without	O
paying	O
his	O
Reckoning	O
;	O
And	O
afterwards	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
Apprehended	O
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
Sold	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Floyer	O
,	O
for	O
5	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
Which	O
being	O
very	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Woodwin	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Edmunds	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Breaking	O
open	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
thence	O
several	O
Goods	O
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
one	O
other	O
Person	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Glover	O
the	O
16th	O
.	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
Nine	O
or	O
Ten	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Servant	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Glover	O
demanded	O
their	O
Business	O
,	O
they	O
told	O
him	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
Bill	O
of	O
Exchange	O
for	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
telling	O
them	O
that	O
his	O
Master	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
them	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
accept	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Bill	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
desired	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Glovers	O
Servant	O
to	O
lend	O
them	O
a	O
Pen	O
and	O
Ink	O
,	O
to	O
leave	O
their	O
Business	O
in	O
Writing	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
accordingly	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Companion	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
they	O
both	O
fell	O
upon	O
the	O
said	O
Servant	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Glovers	O
,	O
and	O
Strangled	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
Cravat	O
,	O
and	O
bound	O
him	O
Hand	O
and	O
Foot	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
unless	O
he	O
would	O
tell	O
where	O
his	O
Masters	O
Treasure	O
and	O
Money	O
lay	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
Murder	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Proof	O
being	O
very	O
Strong	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Clayton	I-pers
,	O
Hessins	B-pers
Hedge	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Liddall	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Cock	O
and	O
two	O
Hens	O
,	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Page	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
passing	O
by	O
a	O
Barn	O
near	O
a	O
Wood	O
,	O
they	O
looking	O
therein	O
,	O
found	O
all	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
the	O
said	O
Hens	O
and	O
Cock	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
themselves	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Timothy	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Murdering	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Betts	I-pers
;	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Smith	O
Riding	O
very	O
fast	O
through	O
a	O
narrow	O
Lane	O
,	O
called	O
South-Lane	B-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
the	I-place
Hay-Market	I-place
,	O
did	O
Ride	O
over	O
the	O
said	O
Ann	B-pers
Betts	I-pers
,	O
by	O
means	O
whereof	O
she	O
Died	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Man-slaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jenkin	B-pers
Cradock	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Saraden	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Murdering	O
one	O
Christian	B-pers
Eaires	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
said	O
Cradock	O
coming	O
by	O
the	O
door	O
where	O
Eaires	O
lived	O
,	O
had	O
some	O
words	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
passed	O
away	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
came	O
again	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
about	O
Nine	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
whereupon	O
Eaires	O
coming	O
to	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Candlestick	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
fell	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
her	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
took	O
the	O
Candlestick	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
by	O
which	O
Wounds	O
she	O
languished	O
,	O
and	O
died	O
;	O
Which	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
12	O
Ounces	O
of	O
sewing	O
Silk	O
,	O
valued	O
10	O
shillings	O
,	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
very	O
Clear	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Silk	O
being	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
seen	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
same	O
from	O
under	O
the	O
Grate	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Jones	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Harefield	B-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
Labourer	O
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
two	O
Lambs	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
;	O
which	O
appeared	O
very	O
fully	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
Examination	O
and	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
of	O
Peace	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
Read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Wilmot	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bennets	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
divers	O
pieces	O
of	O
Holland	O
from	O
Lydia	B-pers
Cantrell	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
,	O
with	O
another	O
woman	O
,	O
came	O
into	O
Cantrell	O
's	O
shop	O
to	O
cheapen	O
some	O
Hoods	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
time	O
she	O
lost	O
the	O
said	O
Linnen	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
positive	O
Proof	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
24.	O
l.	O
from	O
one	O
Robert	B-pers
King	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
King	O
and	O
Bennet	O
Lodged	O
both	O
in	O
one	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
on	O
Saturday	O
about	O
Nine	O
or	O
Ten	O
a	O
Clock	O
he	O
missed	O
the	O
said	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
being	O
in	O
his	O
Room	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
go	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
towards	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Bagg	O
of	O
Money	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
her	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
Swore	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Bagg	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
believed	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Excuse	O
of	O
her	O
self	O
pretended	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
House-of-Office	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
House-of-Office	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
Common	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
positive	O
Proof	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bedwell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Stevens	I-place
alias	I-place
Wright	I-place
,	O
indicted	O
for	O
1	O
gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
4	O
silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
2	O
silk	O
Gowns	O
,	O
1	O
Muff	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
from	O
Stephen	B-pers
Daught	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
being	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Daught	O
took	O
her	O
opportunity	O
in	O
the	O
night-time	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Goods	O
upon	O
which	O
her	O
Master	O
causing	O
search	O
after	O
her	O
had	O
her	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
of	O
Peace	O
;	O
before	O
whom	O
she	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
9	O
s.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
-	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Ellin	B-pers
Lyell	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
stealing	O
from	O
thence	O
divers	O
quantities	O
of	O
Goods	O
,	O
As	O
Gold	O
,	O
Silver	O
,	O
Clothes	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
thus	O
:	O
That	O
the	O
said	O
Lyell	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Sunday	O
,	O
left	O
Lachfield	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
upon	O
her	O
coming	O
home	O
she	O
found	O
her	O
Chamber-door	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Trunk	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
suspecting	O
Lachfield	O
to	O
be	O
concern	O
'd	O
,	O
who	O
,	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
following	O
,	O
removed	O
his	O
Lodging	O
,	O
she	O
caused	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
only	O
two	O
Irons	O
which	O
fitted	O
the	O
Locks	O
that	O
were	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
Afterwards	O
in	O
a	O
Cellar	O
,	O
not	O
far	O
distant	O
from	O
his	O
Lodging	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
a	O
bundle	O
of	O
Clothes	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
hers	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
affirmed	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
alledged	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
was	O
mallcious	O
,	O
and	O
procuring	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Mackroe	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mackroe	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Silver	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Silver	O
Standish	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
Robert	B-pers
Dowglas	I-pers
Esq	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
very	O
plain	O
and	O
full	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Elizabeth	O
pawned	O
the	O
Standish	O
in	O
Blackamore-street	O
,	O
and	O
Daniel	O
offered	O
the	O
Candlestick	O
to	O
pawn	O
at	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
;	O
having	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Daniel	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
-	I-pers
living	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
indicted	O
as	O
being	O
accessary	O
with	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
of	O
two	O
Coach-glasses	O
from	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Blethwaite	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
said	O
Glasses	O
of	O
Price	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
knowing	O
they	O
were	O
stole	O
,	O
and	O
giving	O
to	O
the	O
full	O
value	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Lewis	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bennets	I-place
Pauls	I-place
wharf	I-place
,	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Chamber	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Waller	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
thence	O
one	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
,	O
one	O
Gown	O
one	O
Hood	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
was	O
thus	O
:	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Waller	O
going	O
from	O
his	O
Chamber	O
in	O
Doctors	O
Commons	O
about	O
Eight	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
returning	O
about	O
Ten	O
or	O
Eleven	O
the	O
same	O
night	O
,	O
found	O
his	O
Chamber	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Goods	O
missing	O
.	O
Upon	O
inquiry	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
house	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
pleading	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
their	O
being	O
brought	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
producing	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
good	O
Fame	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Susan	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
silk	O
Mantles	O
&	O
c	O
from	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Morisson	I-pers
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
producing	O
divers	O
Witnesses	O
as	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Carey	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Davies	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Curtains	O
and	O
Vallins	O
,	O
one	O
Rug	O
,	O
two	O
Sheets	O
,	O
one	O
Looking-glass	O
,	O
one	O
Brass-pot	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
goods	O
from	O
one	O
Abel	B-pers
Blundel	I-pers
,	O
valued	O
32	O
s.	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Abel	B-pers
Blundel	I-pers
did	O
Lett	O
a	O
Room	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	O
Carey	O
Ready	O
furnished	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
Lodged	O
about	O
a	O
Month	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
all	O
the	O
said	O
goods	O
,	O
unknown	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Blundel	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
very	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
her	O
.	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Hitchcock	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
.	O
Upon	O
his	O
Arraignement	O
Pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Bedford	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Murthering	O
one	O
Humphry	B-pers
Garland	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Bedford	O
about	O
five	O
Years	O
since	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mr.	O
King	O
in	O
York-Buildings	B-place
,	O
where	O
he	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
said	O
Garland	O
,	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
the	O
said	O
Bedfords	O
Wife	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
time	O
,	O
there	O
arose	O
some	O
Words	O
between	O
the	O
said	O
Bedford	O
and	O
Garland	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
some	O
short	O
time	O
,	O
Bedfords	O
Wife	O
cried	O
out	O
Help	O
,	O
Help	O
:	O
Some	O
Persons	O
hearing	O
the	O
Noise	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
found	O
Garland	O
lying	O
Dead	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Wife	O
Weeping	O
over	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
demanded	O
who	O
Killed	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
not	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
own	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Coroner	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
Killed	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
only	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
both	O
their	O
swords	O
were	O
Drawn	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Flaggon	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Hatton	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
drink	O
at	O
Hattons	O
House	O
the	O
third	O
of	O
June	O
and	O
Stole	O
away	O
the	O
Pott	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
afterwards	O
offered	O
it	O
to	O
Sale	O
to	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
Vindication	O
of	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Pillborow	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchers	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Gray	O
Horse	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Reeve	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
very	O
Strong	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
Vindication	O
of	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Tims	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
third	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
Lodged	O
at	O
Middletons	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
Middleton	O
Wife	O
missing	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Cup	O
made	O
inquiry	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
whether	O
he	O
knew	O
what	O
was	O
become	O
of	O
the	O
Cup	O
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
and	O
offered	O
it	O
to	O
Sale	O
for	O
20	O
l.	O
But	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
little	O
less	O
than	O
a	O
Fool	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Hugh	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Edmunds	I-place
Lumbard	I-place
street	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
19	O
Yards	O
of	O
striped	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Young	I-pers
a	O
Mercer	O
in	O
Lumbard-street	B-place
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
May	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Youngs	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
Stole	O
away	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Proof	O
against	O
him	O
being	O
clear	O
;	O
for	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Eaires	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Caster	O
Hat	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
Mary	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
36th	O
Year	O
of	O
King	O
Charles	O
the	O
Second	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
appearing	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Newberry	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Enfield	B-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
3	O
Cows	O
,	O
value	O
each	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
8	O
in	O
the	O
36th	O
Year	O
of	O
King	O
Charles	O
the	O
Second	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
positive	O
Proof	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Blood	O
stone	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
shillings	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Beverley	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
being	O
clear	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Rapier	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
248	O
Yards	O
of	O
Crape	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
l.	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
of	O
considerable	O
value	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Sall	I-pers
,	O
Widdow	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
Excuse	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
very	O
full	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Alice	B-pers
Sayes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
indicted	O
for	O
19	O
Yards	O
of	O
Blue-Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
from	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Abaldiston	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
not	O
being	O
very	O
Positive	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
two	O
Bullocks	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Henry	B-pers
Pascall	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
very	O
Full	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Little	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Christian	B-pers
Lady	I-pers
Newport	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
thence	O
three	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
a	O
brass	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
clear	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
little	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Second	O
Indictment	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
Stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
one	O
Matthew	B-pers
Shannio	I-pers
,	O
which	O
was	O
likwise	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
6	O
l.	O
from	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Proctor	I-pers
the	O
18th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
upon	O
his	O
Arraignment	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Gorden	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Savoy	I-place
,	O
indicted	O
for	O
murdering	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Dyson	I-pers
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
Monday	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Dyson	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Savoy	B-place
,	O
late	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
hapning	O
to	O
drink	O
at	O
a	O
Victualling-house	O
with	O
one	O
Bowen	O
and	O
Higgins	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
said	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
Dyson	O
was	O
,	O
on	O
a	O
sudden	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
words	O
,	O
or	O
provocation	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
arose	O
from	O
where	O
he	O
sate	O
,	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
Dyson	O
through	O
the	O
Belly	O
,	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
God	O
Damn	O
me	O
I	O
have	O
done	O
thy	O
Business	O
:	O
All	O
the	O
words	O
which	O
Dyson	O
afterwards	O
said	O
,	O
were	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
have	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
instantly	O
expired	O
.	O
All	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
whereupon	O
on	O
they	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Wilful	O
Murder	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Minshall	I-pers
,	O
last	O
Sessions	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
,	O
Pleaded	O
his	O
Majesties	O
Most	O
Gracious	O
Pardon	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
,	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Four	O
Ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Mackrowe	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
,	O
Hugh	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
Nine	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Richard	O
-	O
Jenkin	O
Craddock	O
,	O
Timothy	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hitchcock	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Bedford	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bedwell	I-pers
.	O
Six	O
to	O
be	O
Whipt	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Clayton	I-pers
,	O
Hessins	O
Hodge	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Lydall	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
.	O
Seven	O
received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Saltmarsh	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Woodwin	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Cary	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Pilborow	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Little	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Rapyer	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Gorden	I-pers
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Cary	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Rapier	I-pers
pleaded	O
their	O
Bellies	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
found	O
by	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Women	O
to	O
be	O
Quick	O
with	O
Child	O
.	O
