TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
OF	O
PEACE	O
And	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
HELD	O
FOR	O
THE	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
,	O
IN	O
THE	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
,	O
The	O
25th	O
.	O
26th	O
.	O
and	O
27th	O
.	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
1685	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
First	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
being	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
the	O
25th	O
.	O
26th	O
.	O
and	O
27th	O
.	O
days	O
of	O
February	O
1684	O
Before	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
James	B-pers
Smyth	I-pers
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Justice	O
Jones	O
,	O
Baron	O
Gregory	O
,	O
Judge	O
Holloway	O
,	O
Judge	O
Levinze	O
,	O
Baron	O
Street	O
,	O
Sir	O
Job	B-pers
Charton	I-pers
,	O
Sir	O
Francis	B-pers
Withins	I-pers
,	O
Judge	O
Walcoat	O
,	O
Judge	O
Wright	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jenner	I-pers
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Majesties	O
Serjeants	O
at	O
Law	O
,	O
and	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
of	O
together	O
with	O
other	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Tryal	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Caborne	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
Clipping	O
several	O
pieces	O
of	O
money	O
.	O
She	O
very	O
obscurely	O
used	O
to	O
follow	O
this	O
too	O
fatal	O
Employ	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
supposed	O
the	O
secresie	O
of	O
a	O
dark	O
Night	O
was	O
her	O
chiefest	O
friend	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
often	O
,	O
to	O
supply	O
the	O
craying	O
importunities	O
of	O
sin	O
,	O
diminish	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Coin	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
no	O
small	O
acquaintance	O
of	O
that	O
bad	O
profession	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
very	O
often	O
pay	O
Debts	O
and	O
Rent	O
in	O
new	O
Clipt	O
money	O
,	O
her	O
Implements	O
for	O
such	O
occasions	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Apartments	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
new	O
pieces	O
of	O
money	O
Clipt	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
,	O
upon	O
so	O
plain	O
an	O
Evidence	O
as	O
appeared	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Treason	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
she	O
received	O
sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Law	O
in	O
such	O
Cases	O
awards	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Elton	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
felonious	O
taking	O
of	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
with	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
3	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
from	O
Samuel	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
whereinto	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
first	O
Crime	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
therefore	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
Bench	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Elfey	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
several	O
Cocks	O
and	O
Hens	O
from	O
Samuel	B-pers
Freebody	I-pers
:	O
To	O
his	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
;	O
owning	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
was	O
convicted	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Bowden	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
considerable	O
parcel	O
of	O
Red	O
Wool	O
;	O
but	O
by	O
many	O
Persons	O
it	O
being	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Trade	O
,	O
or	O
at	O
least	O
wise	O
such	O
Employment	O
,	O
as	O
for	O
no	O
small	O
thing	O
be	O
had	O
undertook	O
,	O
to	O
deal	O
in	O
such	O
Communities	O
,	O
as	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
Wool	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Archer	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Hackney	O
Coachman	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
murder	O
of	O
a	O
poor	O
old	B-pers
man	I-pers
,	O
upon	O
opening	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
it	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
thus	O
;	O
That	O
the	O
said	O
Andrew	O
driving	O
his	O
Coach	O
very	O
fast	O
from	O
Westminster	O
in	O
Hilary	O
Term	O
last	O
through	O
Westminster	B-place
Gate	I-place
,	O
there	O
hapned	O
to	O
be	O
some	O
Contention	O
betwixt	O
the	O
said	O
Andrew	O
and	O
a	O
Carman	O
,	O
for	O
getting	O
first	O
through	O
the	O
Gate	O
;	O
and	O
during	O
the	O
strife	O
,	O
the	O
old	O
man	O
aforesaid-cross	O
'd	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
laying	O
his	O
hand	O
upon	O
the	O
Gate	O
,	O
the	O
better	O
to	O
secure	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
Coach-wheel	O
crushed	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
pieces	O
,	O
whereof	O
in	O
ten	O
days	O
after	O
he	O
dyed	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
declaring	O
upon	O
his	O
Death-bed	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
misfortune	O
was	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
his	O
End	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
also	O
the	O
Chyrurgion	O
in	O
Court	O
declar	O
'd	O
upon	O
Oath	O
)	O
but	O
no	O
premeditated	O
malice	O
being	O
made	O
appear	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
only	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
Soldier	O
lately	O
in	O
the	O
Garison	O
of	O
Tangier	O
)	O
Indicted	O
for	O
two	O
several	O
Robberies	O
committed	O
near	O
Padington	O
(	O
about	O
Eight	O
of	O
the	O
clock	O
at	O
night	O
)	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
being	O
on	O
Foot	O
,	O
he	O
with	O
Two	O
more	O
of	O
his	O
Complices	O
,	O
seized	O
Two	O
honest	O
Countrey-Fellows	B-pers
,	O
bound	O
them	O
hand	O
and	O
foot	O
,	O
stript	O
them	O
of	O
their	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
what	O
money	O
they	O
had	O
about	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
made	O
appear	O
that	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
back	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
he	O
pretended	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
)	O
and	O
other	O
violent	O
circumstances	O
concurring	O
the	O
said	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Robbery	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Dorothy	B-pers
German	I-pers
had	O
Three	O
several	O
Indictments	O
presono	O
'd	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
First	O
,	O
for	O
wheedling	O
a	O
Line	O
draper	O
's	O
Prentice	O
,	O
causing	O
him	O
to	O
steal	O
imbezle	O
his	O
Master	B-pers
s	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
privately	O
(	O
without	O
his	O
Masters	O
knowledge	O
)	O
to	O
convey	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
who	O
received	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
employed	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
own	O
use	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
some	O
(	O
though	O
but	O
very	O
little	O
)	O
monies	O
for	O
his	O
pains	O
;	O
his	O
Master	O
finding	O
his	O
Goods	O
gone	O
without	O
his	O
knowledge	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
account	O
of	O
them	O
from	O
his	O
man	O
,	O
he	O
with	O
threats	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
ways	O
,	O
(	O
as	O
he	O
thought	O
fit	O
)	O
forc	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
discovery	O
of	O
her	O
flie	O
insinuating	O
Trick	O
and	O
afterwards	O
did	O
apprehend	O
her	O
.	O
Other	O
indictments	O
were	O
read	O
against	O
her	O
much	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
nature	O
,	O
whereunto	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
several	O
Asseverations	O
averred	O
her	O
innocence	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
being	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
prove	O
where	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
whom	O
she	O
got	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
expect	O
to	O
be	O
brought	O
in	O
otherwise	O
,	O
than	O
as	O
the	O
Jury	O
gave	O
in	O
their	O
Verdict	O
,	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Crime	O
alledged	O
in	O
her	O
Indictment	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
having	O
Wives	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Hoggi	I-pers
;	O
but	O
no	O
persons	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
prove	O
the	O
second	O
Marriage	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquited	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Bee	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
1	O
Casters	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
Haberdasher	O
l	O
ving	O
on	O
London-Bridge	O
;	O
he	O
sent	O
them	O
t	O
an	O
Inn	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	B-place
,	O
in	O
order	O
t	O
their	O
being	O
sent	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
stealing	O
both	O
Box	O
and	O
Hats	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
sell	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
Person	O
that	O
knew	O
their	O
Mark	O
,	O
by	O
whom	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
.	O
He	O
pleaded	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Holms	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Burglary	O
and	O
Felony	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Long	I-pers
near	O
Ludgate	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
several	O
silver-hafted	O
Knives	O
,	O
Razors	O
,	O
Scissers	O
,	O
and	O
Combs	O
,	O
amounting	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
Value	O
.	O
The	O
Witnesses	O
prov	O
'd	O
it	O
plainly	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
making	O
little	O
or	O
no	O
defence	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
;	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Emanuel	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
large	O
Winding-Jack	O
,	O
valued	O
at	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Owner	O
found	O
him	O
carrying	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
seized	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
pleaded	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Gate	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Hughs	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pewter-Pot	O
,	O
2	O
Coats	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Goose	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Coats	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
He	O
broke	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
seiz	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
through	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
having	O
broke	O
open	O
a	O
Trunk	O
,	O
whence	O
he	O
took	O
several	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
a	O
Chizel	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
very	O
plain	O
by	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
,	O
wherefore	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
both	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Benson	I-pers
,	O
Gerard	B-pers
Sanskel	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
taking	O
a	O
silver	O
Cup	O
out	O
of	O
an	O
,	O
Ale-house	O
in	O
Fetter-lane	B-place
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
drinking	O
.	O
The	O
Servant	O
swore	O
he	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
their	O
departure	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Another	O
proved	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
theirLodgings	O
,	O
where	O
,	O
upon	O
search	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
under	O
the	O
stairs	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
plain	O
and	O
full	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
wherefore	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Crime	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
valued	O
at	O
9	O
l.	O
17	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
he	O
could	O
produce	O
no	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
his	O
Civility	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
a	O
debauched	O
Character	O
;	O
and	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
prove	O
himself	O
(	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
stole	O
)	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
a	O
Tavern	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
he	O
called	O
several	O
persons	O
to	O
vouch	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
not	O
agreeing	O
in	O
what	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
were	O
disbelieved	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Congrile	I-pers
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
several	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
as	O
two	O
Coats	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
but	O
no	O
persons	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Isabel	B-pers
Roseby	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
young	O
Girl	O
about	O
Thirteen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
)	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
felonious	O
taking	O
of	O
Three	O
pounds	O
and	O
monies	O
from	O
a	O
person	B-pers
.	O
Upon	O
discussing	O
of	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
it	O
appearing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
kind	O
of	O
a	O
Nurse	O
or	O
a	O
Superintendent	O
upon	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
in	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
her	O
sickness	O
in	O
Childbed	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Prosecutor	O
sent	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
up	O
into	O
a	O
Chamber	O
,	O
to	O
fetch	O
some	O
Linen	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Trunk	O
,	O
wherein	O
was	O
laid	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Sum	O
(	O
as	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
alledged	O
)	O
but	O
no	O
positive	O
or	O
plain	O
Proof	O
being	O
made	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
a	O
presumption	O
or	O
suspicion	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fallofield	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
bloody	O
,	O
barbarous	O
and	O
cruel	O
murder	O
committed	O
upon	O
the	O
body	O
of	O
his	O
Cousin	O
Mary	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
Upon	O
opening	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
an	O
illiterate	O
,	O
rustick	O
Countrey	O
Fellow	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
up	O
to	O
London	O
to	O
get	O
Employment	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
visit	O
his	O
Cousin	O
Mary	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
(	O
who	O
having	O
also	O
a	O
Kinswoman	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
with	O
her	O
called	O
also	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
)	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
kindly	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
friendly	O
manner	O
entertained	O
both	O
with	O
meat	O
,	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
lodging	O
;	O
but	O
coming	O
in	O
one	O
Night	O
about	O
Nine	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
,	O
took	O
Occasion	O
to	O
quarrel	O
with	O
his	O
said	O
Kinswomen	O
,	O
assaulting	O
in	O
a	O
most	O
bloody	O
and	O
Furious	O
manner	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	B-pers
Hunts	I-pers
with	O
a	O
Rubbing-Brush	O
,	O
and	O
knockt	O
her	O
down	O
and	O
left	O
her	O
,	O
(	O
supposing	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
dead	O
)	O
and	O
presently	O
run	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
other	O
Mary	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
in	O
her	O
Bed	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
also	O
most	O
barbarously	O
assaulted	O
,	O
by	O
taking	O
up	O
a	O
Quart-pot	O
,	O
and	O
knocked	O
out	O
her	O
brains	O
,	O
whereof	O
she	O
presently	O
expired	O
:	O
The	O
Assassinate	O
flying	O
,	O
made	O
his	O
Escape	O
into	O
Oxfordshire	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
vengeance	O
of	O
God	O
pursuing	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
by	O
accident	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
up	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
where	O
his	O
poor	O
Cousin	O
whom	O
he	O
knocked	O
down	O
and	O
assaulted	O
below	O
stairs	O
,	O
made	O
the	O
matter	O
very	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
deservedly	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
inhumane	O
murder	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joel	B-pers
Gaischone	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
upon	O
suspicion	O
of	O
stealing	O
Forty	O
Gallions	O
of	O
Wine	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Cellar	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Rawley	I-pers
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
full	O
and	O
plain	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Felony	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Rawlinson	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
murdering	O
of	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Blackstone	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
upon	O
some	O
small	O
or	O
trivial	O
matter	O
,	O
fell	O
to	O
blows	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
gave	O
the	O
first	O
provocation	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
prepensed	O
or	O
forethought	O
malice	O
appearing	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Rawlinson	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
commit	O
the	O
said	O
murder	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
after	O
some	O
deliberation	O
,	O
found	O
it	O
only	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Johanna	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
,	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
of	O
3	O
l.	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
positively	O
swear	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
bringing	O
sufficient	O
Housholders	O
to	O
vouch	O
her	O
honest	O
course	O
of	O
life	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thought	O
fit	O
to	O
acquit	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Walter	I-pers
,	O
Committed	O
for	O
removing	O
several	O
pieces	O
of	O
Linnen	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
not	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
good	O
Witness	O
to	O
prove	O
his	O
honesty	O
,	O
was	O
allowed	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
his	O
Clergy	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Committed	O
and	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
valued	O
at	O
six	O
Pound	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
permitted	O
to	O
have	O
(	O
at	O
his	O
humble	O
request	O
of	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Court	O
)	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
his	O
Clergy	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Perkins	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
upon	O
suspiction	O
of	O
Committing	O
divers	O
Robberies	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
several	O
places	O
;	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
Dark-Lanthorn	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
bunch	O
of	O
Pick-lock	O
Keys	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Watch	O
about	O
him	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
suffered	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
priviledge	O
of	O
his	O
Clergy	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charity	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
Tryed	O
for	O
picking	O
thePocket	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Battin	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
six	O
silver	O
spoons	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
some	O
Company	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Luke	B-pers
Wine	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
19	O
sheep	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
grounds	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lockey	I-pers
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
Nine	O
pounds	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
his	O
first	O
Crime	O
(	O
as	O
he	O
said	O
)	O
he	O
desired	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
Bench	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Amis	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
being	O
a	O
common	O
and	O
notorious	O
Cheat	O
,	O
having	O
lately	O
cozened	O
16.	O
persons	O
of	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
200	O
l.	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Bennison	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
11	O
ounces	O
of	O
silver-twist	O
.	O
The	O
proof	O
not	O
being	O
full	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Mullins	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
black	O
Cloth	O
,	O
of	O
very	O
considerable	O
value	O
,	O
from	O
Abraham	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
thus	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
running	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
said	O
Cloth	O
,	O
was	O
observ	O
'd	O
afterwards	O
to	O
drop	O
it	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Money-box	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
small	O
money	O
i	O
n't	O
,	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Draper	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hays	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Linsey	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stevenson	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Banfeild	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Dennis	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
Both	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Rawson	I-pers
,	O
a	O
noted	O
Highway-man	O
,	O
who	O
riding	O
along	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
supposed	O
his	O
Fellow	O
Travellers	O
Horse	O
better	O
than	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
thereupon	O
borrow	O
'd	O
him	O
(	O
as	O
he	O
pleaded	O
)	O
and	O
some	O
monies	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
apprehended	O
with	O
the	O
Horse	O
in	O
his	O
custody	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
received	O
sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
.	O
Roger	B-pers
Marcy	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
,	O
had	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
his	O
Clergy	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
mall	O
Trunk	O
of	O
Linen	O
and	O
Woollen	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
afforded	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
his	O
Clergy	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Clinton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Clinton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Whitening	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Martha	B-pers
Marnes	I-pers
,	O
the	O
former	O
is	O
Accessary	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
latter	O
as	O
Principals	O
;	O
It	O
was	O
proved	O
against	O
John	B-pers
Clinton	I-pers
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
24	O
l.	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Possession	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
disposed	O
of	O
it	O
upon	O
sundry	O
occasions	O
;	O
he	O
not	O
having	O
before	O
any	O
Money	O
as	O
could	O
be	O
gathered	O
by	O
those	O
that	O
had	O
frequent	O
converse	O
with	O
him	O
upon	O
which	O
Evidence	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Last	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ralph	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
silver	O
Cups	O
,	O
several	O
Yards	O
of	O
black	O
Crape	O
and	O
divers	O
pieces	O
of	O
Childbed	O
Linnen	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Answorth	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
;	O
It	O
was	O
proved	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
entered	O
the	O
respective	O
Houses	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
thence	O
the	O
Goods	O
charged	O
in	O
the	O
two	O
Indictments	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
upon	O
search	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
their	O
Custody	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
they	O
making	O
a	O
slender	O
defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
Indictment	O
according	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
laid	O
which	O
was	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
second	O
tho	O
'	O
laid	O
as	O
the	O
former	O
,	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
,	I-pers
Steers	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
money	O
Box	O
,	O
3	O
Shillings	O
,	O
a	O
single	O
Penney	O
and	O
divers	O
Farthings	O
;	O
were	O
upon	O
full	O
Proof	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Malbrough	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Nine	O
half	O
Hundred	O
Weights	O
;	O
It	O
was	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
said	O
Weights	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
and	O
disposed	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
behoof	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
make	O
any	O
considerable	O
defence	O
though	O
he	O
pleaded	O
innocence	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Petty	O
Larcenary	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Amies	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Cheating	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Baily	I-pers
,	O
of	O
a	O
considerable	O
parcel	O
of	O
Butter	O
and	O
Cheese	O
under	O
a	O
pretext	O
of	O
barganing	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
and	O
behoof	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
,	O
a	O
Customer	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Baily	O
's	O
;	O
as	O
likewise	O
upon	O
a	O
second	O
Indictment	O
for	O
Cheating	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Morehead	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Ribon	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
23	O
l.	O
under	O
the	O
like	O
pretext	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
proved	O
and	O
he	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
make	O
any	O
considerable	O
defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Walter	B-pers
Butcher	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
an	O
intended	O
Rape	O
upon	O
a	O
Female	B-pers
Infant	I-pers
of	O
Five	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
;	O
Evidence	O
was	O
produced	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Attempt	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
bringing	O
divers	O
People	O
to	O
justifie	O
his	O
used	O
behaviour	O
and	O
modest	O
Carriage	O
all	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
no	O
ways	O
given	O
to	O
Lewdness	O
or	O
Debauchery	O
:	O
They	O
over	O
ballanced	O
the	O
Testemony	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
in	O
so	O
much	O
that	O
the	O
Jury	O
looking	O
upon	O
it	O
as	O
a	O
design	O
to	O
get	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
At	O
this	O
remarkable	O
Sessions	O
9	O
were	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Charles	O
Rowlandson	O
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Elton	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Elsey	I-pers
,	O
Richard	O
Bee	O
,	O
Lake	O
Win	O
,	O
Andrew	B-pers
Archor	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Banfield	I-pers
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Hodges	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
10	O
viz	O
John	O
Walker	O
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Perkins	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Holms	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	O
Smith	O
,	O
Roger	B-pers
Mercy	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	O
Stevenson	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Hays	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Williams	O
Clark	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Clinton	I-pers
.	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
passed	O
upon	O
11.	O
viz	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Coats	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Rawson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	O
Fallowfield	O
,	O
George	O
,	O
Saunders	O
,	O
George	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Buckler	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Mullins	I-pers
,	O
Henry	O
List	O
,	O
Ralph	O
Harrisod	O
,	O
Mary	O
Reaves	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Cabourn	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whip	O
'd	O
9.	O
viz	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Fletcher	O
John	O
Steers	O
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Malborough	I-pers
,	O
Joel	B-pers
Gascoign	I-pers
,	O
William	O
Gayer	O
,	O
William	O
Hudges	O
John	B-pers
Benson	I-pers
,	O
Gerard	B-pers
Salkel	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Emanuel	O
Hall	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Amins	O
Fined	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
.	O
And	O
so	O
ends	O
this	O
great	O
Sessions	O
.	O
