TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
And	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
,	O
The	O
8th	O
.	O
9th	O
.	O
10th	O
.	O
and	O
11th	O
.	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
1686	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
:	O
Held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bayly	O
;	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
the	O
8th	O
.	O
9th	O
.	O
10th	O
.	O
and	O
11th	O
.	O
Days	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
1686	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Peak	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Holt	I-pers
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
City	O
,	O
with	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
for	O
London	O
and	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
follow	O
,	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Canon	I-pers
Chististopher	B-pers
Kemble	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
Gilbert	B-pers
East	I-pers
Nathaniel	B-pers
Lawson	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
East	I-pers
George	B-pers
Waples	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
Nathaniel	B-pers
Huit	I-pers
Barthotomew	B-pers
Layton	I-pers
Hugh	B-pers
Grainger	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Gilbert	B-pers
Herring	I-pers
Humphrey	B-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
John	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
John	B-pers
Cash	I-pers
William	B-pers
Pickering	I-pers
John	B-pers
Merrick	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Parr	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Davison	I-pers
John	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
William	B-pers
Gardiner	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Lunt	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
follow	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Patience	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Little	B-place
Allhallows	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Killing	O
one	O
Joseph	B-pers
Holt	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Bruise	O
upon	O
the	O
Left	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
8th	O
.	O
of	O
November	O
and	O
then	O
dyed	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
happened	O
to	O
quarrel	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
chanced	O
to	O
fall	O
upon	O
the	O
Pavement	O
,	O
and	O
Received	O
the	O
afore-said	O
Bruise	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Doctor	O
and	O
Chyrurgeon	O
appearing	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
side	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Bruise	O
was	O
not	O
any	O
occasion	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
died	O
of	O
a	O
Natural	O
Disease	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Mallice	O
appearing	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolph	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
.	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
one	O
Linnen	O
Pettycoat	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
d.	O
one	O
Shirt	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
one	O
Apron	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Richard	B-pers
Fullam	I-pers
of	O
the	O
same	O
Parish	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Fullam	O
himself	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
through	O
the	O
Yard	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
material	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
so	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolphs	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Cloath	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
The	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Woolstone	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
day	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
December	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Woolstone	O
himself	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
abroad	O
and	O
his	O
Family	O
,	O
his	O
house	O
was	O
Robbed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
under	O
his	O
Bed	O
hiding	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
plain	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Olives	I-place
Jury	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
Porringer	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
Salt	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
twenty	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Coined	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Piece	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
.	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
proper	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sr.	O
Robert	B-pers
Walsh	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Sr.	O
Robert	O
himself	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
offer	O
himself	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
Sr.	O
Robert	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
his	O
house	O
for	O
some	O
few	O
days	O
,	O
to	O
entertain	O
him	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
an	O
opportunity	O
,	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Culverwell	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Black	O
Mare	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Hayward	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
past	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Mare	O
was	O
Sold	O
by	O
him	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
to	O
another	O
person	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
a	O
Horse-Courser	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
but	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
on	O
his	O
own	O
behalf	O
,	O
using	O
several	O
Evasions	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
found	O
in	O
several	O
Storys	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
being	O
so	O
clear	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anne	I-place
Agnes	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
Salt	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
17	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2	O
d.	O
day	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
past	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Wetherell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Iron	O
Keys	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
d.	O
and	O
30	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
.	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Osborne	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
Landress	O
to	O
the	O
abovesaid	O
Esq	O
;	O
had	O
the	O
opportunity	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
Desk	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Money	O
and	O
Keys	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
having	O
little	O
or	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
five	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Tapstrie	O
Hangings	O
value	O
12	O
l.	O
one	O
Counterpain	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Cauldron	I-pers
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Custody	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
deny	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
Tryal	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
no	O
Witness	O
on	O
his	O
side	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Redman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Harrow	B-place
on	I-place
the	I-place
Hill	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
two	O
pair	O
more	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Boalton	I-pers
,	O
two	O
Doulace	O
Smocks	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
Holland	O
Smock	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Oglestile	I-pers
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
Pleaded	O
Guilty	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Congrill	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
(	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Richard	B-pers
Hide	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
silver	O
Beakers	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
one	O
silver	O
Porringer	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
six	O
Ounces	O
of	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
31	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
past	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Shrimton	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
under	O
some	O
pretence	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Cake	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
possitive	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Bracelet	O
set	O
with	O
fifty	O
one	O
Diamonds	O
,	O
and	O
six	O
Camelion	O
Stones	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
l.	O
16	O
s.	O
and	O
40	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
.	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
Christopher	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
of	O
the	O
abovesaid	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
possitively	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Merriot	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Susannah	B-pers
Merriot	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anne	I-place
Black-Fryars	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Clipping	O
30	O
Pieces	O
of	O
silver	O
,	O
called	O
Half-Crowns	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
other	O
Pieces	O
called	O
Shillings	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
Piece	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
other	O
Pieces	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Piece	O
:	O
Did	O
Feloniously	O
and	O
Traiterously	O
Clip	O
and	O
deminish	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Richard	B-pers
Merriot	I-pers
,	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
Clip	O
Money	O
four	O
years	O
ago	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
swear	O
that	O
he	O
or	O
his	O
Wife	O
had	O
used	O
that	O
Art	O
of	O
late	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
denying	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Evidence	O
being	O
produced	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
fully	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Ryan	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Leech	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Henley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
.	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
one	O
Cloath	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
one	O
Hair-Camble	O
,	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
one	O
other	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
abovesaid	O
Goods	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
said	O
in	O
their	O
defence	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
drink	O
and	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
they	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
not	O
possitive	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Powis	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gartrey	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Christopher	B-pers
Hilliard	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
four	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
Robing	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
one	O
Daniel	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pancras	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
.	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
past	O
,	O
of	O
one	O
Gunn	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
Pound	O
of	O
Powder	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
in	O
a	O
rude	O
manner	O
,	O
asking	O
for	O
drink	O
(	O
he	O
keeping	O
a	O
Victualling	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Gun	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
by	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
:	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
intended	O
no	O
ill	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
And	O
being	O
found	O
in	O
false	O
stories	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
four	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
thirteen	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Coined	O
Gold	O
,	O
called	O
Guineas	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
.	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Jasper	B-pers
Stoaks	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
Indicted	O
,	O
four	O
several	O
Indictments	O
being	O
read	O
against	O
them	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
Robing	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
one	O
Giles	B-pers
Dumcombe	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
of	O
one	O
Cloath	O
Coat	O
with	O
Gold	O
Loops	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
one	O
other	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
five	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cloath	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
twenty	O
two	O
Napkins	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
two	O
suits	O
of	O
Childbed	O
Linnen	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
three	O
Stuff	O
Gowns	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
with	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
value	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Also	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
one	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
with	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
good	O
value	O
,	O
Also	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
one	O
Anne	B-pers
Gibbon	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
one	O
Allamode	O
Hood	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
one	O
Scarfe	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
one	O
Gause	O
Hood	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
small	O
Goods	O
.	O
Also	O
for	O
Robing	O
John	B-pers
Blundell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
one	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
Pettycoat	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
one	O
Cabinet	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
one	O
Piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
for	O
the	O
Kings	O
Evil	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
many	O
more	O
small	O
parcels	O
of	O
good	O
value	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
they	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Tops	O
of	O
the	O
Respective	O
houses	O
and	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Garret	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Lower	O
Rooms	O
and	O
got	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
all	O
which	O
Indictments	O
were	O
very	O
plainly	O
proved	O
against	O
Parsons	O
and	O
Powell	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
possitive	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
Stoaks	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
having	O
been	O
Old	O
Offenders	O
,	O
and	O
Branded	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
four	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Peter	B-pers
Minshaw	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
threescore	O
Yards	O
of	O
Shaloon	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Shudale	I-pers
,	O
the	O
2	O
d.	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
lurk	O
about	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
possitively	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Humsted	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Seapulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Cliping	O
ten	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Silver	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
Piece	O
and	O
20	O
other	O
Pieces	O
called	O
Half-Crowns	O
in	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
deminishing	O
from	O
each	O
Piece	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
2	O
d.	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
Clip	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
through	O
a	O
Key-hole	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
:	O
but	O
she	O
who	O
swore	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
person	O
of	O
no	O
good	O
Repute	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
no	O
other	O
Witness	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
denying	O
that	O
ever	O
she	O
was	O
any	O
ways	O
concerned	O
in	O
Clipping	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Gold	O
Chain	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
from	O
one	O
Rebeckah	B-pers
Playner	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Child	O
about	O
fourteen	O
years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
.	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
December	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
met	O
the	O
Girl	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
near	O
Temple	O
Bar	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
and	O
snatch	O
'd	O
the	O
Chain	O
off	O
her	O
Neck	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
Rose-Tavern	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
not	O
denying	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
drink	O
and	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Fyance	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
Blanket	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
2	O
d.	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Boddenham	I-pers
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
to	O
come	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
stopped	O
he	O
dropt	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
taken	O
afterwards	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Matter	O
being	O
so	O
plainly	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Nowell	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Cheat	O
,	O
in	O
Forging	O
and	O
Counterfeiting	O
a	O
False	O
Writing	O
or	O
Brief	O
,	O
to	O
Collect	O
Moneys	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Name	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
Sign	O
Manual	O
,	O
bearing	O
date	O
at	O
White	O
Hall	O
,	O
the	O
23	O
d.	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
witnessed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
Printed	O
several	O
Copys	O
of	O
the	O
Brief	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Kings	O
Arms	O
on	O
the	O
Top	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
by	O
the	O
Printer	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
gone	O
to	O
several	O
places	O
in	O
England	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
gathered	O
some	O
Moneys	O
,	O
by	O
virtue	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
particularly	O
at	O
Islington	O
,	O
near	O
London	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
Received	O
Eighteen	O
Shillings	O
three	O
Farthings	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
there	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
defence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
said	O
Writing	O
at	O
White-Hall	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Hands	O
of	O
another	O
Person	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
produce	O
any	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Deale	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
.	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
taking	O
thereout	O
,	O
three	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Crevats	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
one	O
other	O
pair	O
of	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
soe	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
Anne	B-pers
Hedger	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Winds	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
thirty	O
five	O
Yards	O
of	O
Colour	O
'd	O
Lute	O
String	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
10	O
s.on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
last	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
Witnessed	O
that	O
Baker	O
and	O
Winds	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
under	O
a	O
presence	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Crape	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Baker	O
and	O
Winds	O
,	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
deny	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
found	O
in	O
several	O
Storys	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
but	O
Anne	O
Hedger	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bethell	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Midlesex	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Set	O
of	O
strip	O
'd	O
Woolen	O
Curtains	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Vallens	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
one	O
Blanket	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
.	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
left	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
Chamber	O
behind	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
not	O
denying	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
Poverty	O
constrained	O
her	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
-	B-pers
J	I-pers
.	I-pers
-	I-pers
and	O
a	O
Boy	B-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Eldridge	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
silver	O
Tankards	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
l.	O
six	O
silver	O
Porringers	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
l.	O
one	O
silver	O
Salt	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
one	O
Necklace	O
of	O
Pearl	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
one	O
gold	O
Bodkin	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
one	O
gold	O
Locket	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
silk	O
Pettycoat	O
with	O
a	O
silver	O
Fringe	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
six	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Crevats	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
l.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
with	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
great	O
value	O
and	O
40	O
l.	O
in	O
Moneys	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
.	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
one	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Bowman	I-pers
,	O
who	O
Evidenced	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mayors	O
Day	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
absent	O
from	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
doors	O
being	O
open	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
search	O
being	O
made	O
,	O
the	O
Plate	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
J	O
.	O
Chamber	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Boy	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Robery	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
so	O
strong	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
in	O
that	O
some	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
in	O
a	O
Boat	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
coming	O
from	O
Graves	O
End	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Tankard	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
Eldridges	O
Coat	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Boy	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
upon	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
,	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
J.	O
and	O
Boy	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Eldridge	O
:	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
.	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
past	O
,	O
one	O
Caster	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
Sleeves	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Colcot	I-pers
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Hat	O
.	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
nothing	O
material	O
to	O
urge	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
Branded	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
before	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Glasborrow	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
.	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
swear	O
possitively	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Christ	B-place
Church	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
thirty	O
five	O
Allamode	O
Hoods	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
four	O
Yards	O
of	O
Bone	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
.	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Delap	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Newgate	B-place
street	I-place
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
possitive	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Hellens	I-place
the	I-place
Less	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
one	O
Pettycoat	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
one	O
Scarfe	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
Sleeves	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
with	O
other	O
goods	O
of	O
small	O
value	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Methall	I-pers
,	O
who	O
witnessed	O
that	O
Joseph	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
being	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
his	O
Brother	O
John	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
had	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
the	O
more	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
left	O
an	O
Knife	O
behind	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
Johns	O
Knife	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
several	O
Evidences	O
on	O
their	O
sides	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
another	O
place	O
when	O
the	O
Robery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Knife	O
was	O
none	O
of	O
theirs	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
all	O
which	O
Evidence	O
outweighing	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
E	B-pers
-	I-pers
S	I-pers
-	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Killing	O
one	O
J	B-pers
-	I-pers
B	I-pers
on	O
the	O
15th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
left	O
Arm	O
hole	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
three	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
dyed	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
after	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
happened	O
thus	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
(	O
with	O
some	O
others	O
in	O
Company	O
,	O
)	O
were	O
drinking	O
together	O
at	O
the	O
Tavern	O
pretty	O
late	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
words	O
arose	O
between	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
concerning	O
the	O
Rebellion	O
in	O
the	O
West	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
for	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Monmouth	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
after	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Company	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
they	O
grew	O
to	O
higher	O
words	O
,	O
but	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
pacified	O
before	O
they	O
went	O
down	O
Stairs	O
:	O
But	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
without	O
the	O
door	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Scuffle	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
received	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Wound	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
particular	O
Evidence	O
that	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
give	O
any	O
thrust	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
Sword	O
was	O
drawn	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
had	O
no	O
Sword	O
:	O
but	O
no	O
premeditared	O
Malice	O
appeared	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
between	O
them	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
argued	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
struck	O
him	O
twice	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
ground	O
in	O
a	O
violent	O
manner	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Sword	O
was	O
drawn	O
,	O
so	O
upon	O
a	O
fall	O
beating	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
only	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Annes	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
piece	O
of	O
Copper	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
22	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
.	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
two	O
men	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
owning	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
for	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Nicholson	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Danish	O
man	O
Born	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Killing	O
one	O
Richard	B-pers
Emmerson	I-pers
;	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
near	O
to	O
his	O
Navel	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
six	O
Inches	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
.	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
dyed	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
a	O
party	O
Jury	O
was	O
sworn	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
half	O
Danes	O
half	O
English	O
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
were	O
drinking	O
together	O
,	O
in	O
an	O
Ale	O
house	O
in	O
Bell	B-place
Yard	I-place
in	I-place
Kings-street	I-place
,	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
one	O
Stephenson	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
happened	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
about	O
being	O
together	O
at	O
Windsor	O
in	O
an	O
uncivil	O
house	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
between	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
one	O
Thomson	O
,	O
who	O
Lodged	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
being	O
parted	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Stephenson	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
went	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
in	O
the	O
dark	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
several	O
passes	O
at	O
the	O
deceased	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
the	O
deceased	O
returned	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
again	O
,	O
with	O
has	O
Hand	O
upon	O
his	O
Belly	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
done	O
his	O
business	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
by	O
his	O
Interpreter	O
)	O
could	O
say	O
but	O
little	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
unfortunately	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Widow	O
of	O
the	O
deceased	O
said	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
had	O
no	O
Mallice	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
called	O
several	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
draw	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
not	O
make	O
any	O
thrust	O
at	O
the	O
deceased	O
;	O
and	O
no	O
premeditated	O
mallice	O
appearing	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
upon	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
,	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
R	B-pers
-	I-pers
H	I-pers
-	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
and	O
three	O
Shillings	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
.	O
of	O
November	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Lot	B-pers
Heycock	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
house	O
privately	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Pick-Lock	O
Keys	O
being	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
urged	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
drink	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilt	O
the	O
of	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Holliland	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robing	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Kinn	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
.	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
of	O
three	O
gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
eight	O
silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
silver	O
Cups	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
,	O
one	O
Corral	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
half	O
Guineas	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
four	O
Pieces	O
more	O
of	O
gold	O
,	O
containing	O
each	O
20	O
s.	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
William	B-pers
Kinn	I-pers
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
house	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Chamber	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
goods	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Custody	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
James	I-pers
but	O
none	O
in	O
Hollilands	O
Custody	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
Woman	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Nineteen	O
Pieces	O
of	O
gold	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
20	O
l.	O
8	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Holding	I-pers
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Servant	O
in	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
therefore	O
suspect	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
positively	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
several	O
good	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
her	O
Life	O
and	O
Conversation	O
had	O
always	O
been	O
honest	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Adam	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Day	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sword	O
with	O
a	O
silver	O
Hilt	O
,	O
from	O
Mr.	O
William	B-pers
Story	I-pers
,	O
value	O
9	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
.	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Story	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
street	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
felt	O
his	O
Sword	O
suddenly	O
snatch	O
'd	O
from	O
his	O
side	O
.	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
possitively	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
discharged	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
John	B-pers
Pargiter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Hackney	B-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Samuel	B-pers
Bomet	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
.	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
one	O
Damask	O
Table-Cloath	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
Reverend	O
Father	O
in	O
God	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
of	I-pers
Litchfield	I-pers
and	I-pers
Coventry	I-pers
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Witnesses	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Evidenced	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Table-Cloath	O
off	O
from	O
a	O
Hedge	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
hanging	O
to	O
dry	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
pursued	O
he	O
drop	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
so	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Kensington	B-place
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Dowlace	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
two	O
Dowlace	O
Smocks	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
Holland	O
Pillowbear	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
.	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Thomas	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
Hedge	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
a	O
drying	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
pursued	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
Hedge	O
in	O
the	O
grounds	O
,	O
not	O
far	O
from	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
the	O
goods	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
his	O
things	O
again	O
:	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
so	O
clear	O
against	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Loe	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Frize	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
.	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
one	O
Cloatch	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
one	O
Perriwig	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Morris	B-pers
Gardener	I-pers
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
Loe	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Larence	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
to	O
defraud	O
her	O
Mistress	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
particularly	O
picking	O
her	O
Pocket	O
at	O
one	O
time	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
which	O
she	O
told	O
her	O
Mistress	O
upon	O
her	O
suspecting	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Jones	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
only	O
Indicted	O
as	O
Accessary	O
:	O
And	O
no	O
possitive	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
but	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Loe	I-pers
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
David	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Coach	O
Seat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
.	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
unknown	O
;	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
against	O
him	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Seat	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
in	O
Chancery	B-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
about	O
9	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
immediately	O
Catch	O
'd	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
several	O
false	O
Keys	O
and	O
Files	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
being	O
Noted	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Old	O
Offender	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Farmer	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shorditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Jenkin	I-pers
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
.	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
one	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
one	O
Pettycoat	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Serge	O
Breeches	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Fustian	O
Drawers	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Patshud	I-pers
,	O
but	O
no	O
possitive	O
proof	O
appearing	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
stoale	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Swetman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
that	O
the	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Anne	B-pers
Needham	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
.	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
two	O
Pettycoats	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
one	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
17	O
s.	O
one	O
Flanders	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Cornet	O
,	O
value	O
21	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
goods	O
of	O
small	O
value	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
swear	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
stole	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
rather	O
believed	O
it	O
was	O
Needham	O
.	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
A	O
Woman	B-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hester	I-pers
on	O
the	O
13th	O
.	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
of	O
twenty	O
one	O
Pieces	O
of	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
21	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
Pieces	O
more	O
of	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
7	O
s.	O
two	O
French	O
Pistols	O
,	O
value	O
22	O
s.	O
and	O
15	O
s.	O
in	O
moneys	O
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Hester	O
,	O
who	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
possitively	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
denying	O
the	O
Fast	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Garrell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Le-Bow	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Chesnut	O
Colour	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Eaere	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
.	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Witness	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Horse	O
into	O
the	O
Custody	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Horse	O
of	O
another	O
person	O
at	O
Cirenester	O
in	O
Glocestershire	O
.	O
As	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
his	O
Horse	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
with	O
him	O
falling	O
Lame	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
to	O
was	O
immediately	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Garrel	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
for	O
attempting	O
to	O
Kidnap	O
away	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
to	O
Maryland	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
with	O
two	O
other	O
persons	O
had	O
made	O
a	O
Contract	O
to	O
send	O
Persons	O
over	O
the	O
Seas	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Procurer	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
head	O
for	O
every	O
one	O
he	O
should	O
get	O
to	O
go	O
;	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
put	O
Matthews	O
on	O
Shipboard	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
send	O
him	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
fetch	O
'd	O
back	O
being	O
discovered	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
argued	O
long	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
desired	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Matthews	O
,	O
to	O
shew	O
him	O
the	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
hand	O
in	O
his	O
being	O
kidded	O
away	O
,	O
so	O
upon	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
he	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Lipsham	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
several	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
and	O
Plates	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
.	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
lost	O
one	O
of	O
Lincolns	O
Inn	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
swearing	O
possitively	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Esther	B-pers
Collingwood	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cambrick	O
Cloath	O
,	O
from	O
Mr.	O
William	B-pers
Oswatstone	I-pers
;	O
but	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
others	O
concerned	O
with	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Felony	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
(	O
viz	O
.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
gillingham	I-pers
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jasper	I-pers
and	O
Rebeckah	B-pers
Timson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
Witness	O
not	O
being	O
positive	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Cloath	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Peters	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Dutch-man	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Meres	I-pers
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
from	O
one	O
Oerrck	B-pers
on	O
the	O
9th	O
.	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
six	O
Lambskin	O
Pictures	O
value	O
each	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
entrusted	O
with	O
all	O
things	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
her	O
Husband	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
But	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
give	O
Evidence	O
of	O
his	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
lookt	O
upon	O
as	O
a	O
malicious	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Plaget	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Silk	O
Pettycoat	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
other	O
Pettycoat	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
with	O
some	O
other	O
small	O
goods	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
possitive	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
Sleeves	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Pinners	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
small	O
goods	O
valued	O
all	O
about	O
10	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
not	O
much	O
denying	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
known	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Gabriel	B-pers
Low	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
several	O
goods	O
from	O
one	O
Rihhard	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
value	O
about	O
3	O
l.	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appering	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Forging	O
and	O
Counterfeiting	O
a	O
false	O
Deputation	O
,	O
to	O
raise	O
Money	O
towards	O
Repairing	O
the	O
Losses	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
at	O
Wappen	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
Finchley	O
Churchwardens	O
,	O
and	O
Received	O
17	O
s.	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
4	O
l.	O
at	O
Edmonton	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
Receipts	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
by	O
the	O
two	O
abovesaid	O
Names	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
by	O
very	O
credible	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
but	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
one	O
Johnston	O
alias	O
Hudson	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
lately	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Countrey	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
seduced	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
aforesaid	O
Master	O
gave	O
him	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
day	O
to	O
Collect	O
the	O
Monies	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
knowing	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Deceit	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
sentence	O
as	O
follows	O
.	O
Order	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
9.	O
viz	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Boy	O
,	O
-	O
J	B-pers
.	I-pers
-	O
William	O
Mason	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Redman	I-pers
,	O
Frances	O
Henry	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Nicholson	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Summers	I-pers
.	O
Order	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
,	O
2.	O
viz	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Eldridge	I-pers
.	O
Order	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
Whip	O
'd	O
20.	O
viz	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Wetherel	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Ryan	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Leech	I-pers
,	O
Henry	O
Lewis	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Garrett	I-pers
,	O
Ri	O
.	O
Evans	O
,	O
Christen	O
Hylliard	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Fyance	I-pers
,	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Bethel	I-pers
,	O
Anne	O
Baker	O
,	O
Sarah	O
Wids	O
,	O
Ellen	O
Loe	O
,	O
Da	O
.	O
Roberts	O
,	O
James	O
Word	O
-	O
R	O
-	O
H	O
John	O
Pargiter	O
,	O
John	O
Atkins	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentenced	O
to	O
Death	O
;	O
viz	O
John	O
Culverwell	O
,	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
Tho	O
.	O
Powel	O
,	O
Nich	O
.	O
Jones	O
Eliz	O
James	O
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Deale	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Nowel	I-pers
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
pay	O
20	O
mark	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
on	O
the	O
Pillory	O
on	O
Monday	O
next	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Maypole	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
following	O
at	O
White	O
Chappel	O
Church	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
after	O
that	O
at	O
Chancery	O
Lane	O
End	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
with	O
an	O
Inscription	O
over	O
his	O
head	O
declaring	O
his	O
fault	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
There	O
were	O
also	O
two	O
other	O
Persons	O
Tried	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Judgment	O
of	O
them	O
being	O
deferr	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
sessions	O
,	O
we	O
shall	O
make	O
no	O
further	O
mention	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
his	O
Paper	O
.	O
One	O
Arrabella	O
Reeves	O
,	O
was	O
committed	O
till	O
next	O
Sessions	O
for	O
Clipping	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Coine	O
.	O
