TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
,	O
And	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
Held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
,	O
The	O
13th	O
.	O
15th	O
.	O
and	O
16th	O
.	O
days	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
1686	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
Tear	O
of	O
His	O
Majestys	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
;	O
Held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bayly	O
;	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Friday	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
the	O
13th	O
.	O
15th	O
.	O
and	O
16th	O
.	O
Days	O
of	O
October	O
1686	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Jefferies	I-pers
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Holt	I-pers
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
City	O
,	O
with	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
for	O
London	O
and	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
follow	O
,	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Burley	I-pers
James	B-pers
Murmosn	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Keebly	I-pers
John	B-pers
Amery	I-pers
George	B-pers
Downes	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Coale	I-pers
John	B-pers
Nibbs	I-pers
Maurice	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
Abraham	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
William	B-pers
Byng	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Nehemiah	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
John	B-pers
Green	I-pers
John	B-pers
Ainger	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Whitfield	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
William	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
James	B-pers
Fern	I-pers
John	B-pers
Vigures	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Peacock	I-pers
John	B-pers
Collett	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Burch	I-pers
William	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
follow	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Runing	O
from	O
his	O
Colours	O
;	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Souldier	O
under	O
Command	O
of	O
Captain	O
Berry	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
Entertained	O
by	O
him	O
at	O
Rochester	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Received	O
into	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Service	O
about	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
Received	O
his	O
Pay	O
as	O
did	O
others	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Company	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
not	O
being	O
Possitive	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
his	O
absenting	O
himself	O
:	O
And	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Pleading	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
never	O
Master	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Company	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Olander	B-pers
Boston	I-pers
,	O
Of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolphs	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
30	O
yards	O
of	O
Quilted	O
Callico	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
l.	O
80	O
yards	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
four	O
Callico	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
20	O
l.	O
of	O
Tea	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
Deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Ware-house	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
being	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
himself	O
making	O
but	O
a	O
weak	O
and	O
frivolous	O
defence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
W	B-pers
-	I-pers
Of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
twice	O
,	O
once	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Kynn	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
past	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
three	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
eight	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
two	O
silver	O
Cups	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
Corral	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
four	O
pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
call	O
'd	O
King	O
Charles	O
's	O
the	O
first	O
,	O
twenty	O
shilling	O
pieces	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
three	O
other	O
pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
another	O
piece	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
18	O
l.	O
in	O
Moneys	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
William	B-pers
Kynn	I-pers
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Who	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
others	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
House	O
to	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
abovesaid	O
Goods	O
and	O
Moneys	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
Room	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Trunk	O
or	O
Box	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
and	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
he	O
took	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
not	O
much	O
denying	O
the	O
matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
Indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
T	B-pers
-	I-pers
for	O
Feloniously	O
taking	O
away	O
from	O
Samuel	B-pers
Blackman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
6th	O
day	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
one	O
lac	O
'd	O
Scarfe	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
one	O
Allamode	O
Hood	O
12	O
s.	O
another	O
Allamode	O
Hood	O
6	O
s.	O
two	O
Gauze	O
Hoods	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
lac	O
'd	O
Cornet	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
Muff	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
Pettycoat	O
16	O
s.	O
one	O
Fustian	O
Wastcoat	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
value	O
16	O
d.	O
one	O
Caster	O
Hat	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
one	O
parcel	O
of	O
Ribboning	O
15	O
s.	O
one	O
Bible	O
8	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
Buckles	O
6	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Damask	O
Sleeves	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
l.	O
5	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
W	O
-	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
making	O
some	O
Enquiry	O
about	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
and	O
T	O
-	O
took	O
upon	O
himself	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Country	O
Farmer	O
,	O
who	O
waited	O
upon	O
W	O
-	O
and	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
missed	O
;	O
and	O
found	O
afterwards	O
in	O
the	O
Custody	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
having	O
but	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
themselves	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Matter	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
W	O
:	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
T	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Wilder	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
Buckles	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
9	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
unto	O
which	O
Indictment	O
upon	O
his	O
Arreignment	O
,	O
he	O
Pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Parsison	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Chyswick	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
together	O
with	O
another	O
Person	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
on	O
the	O
seaventh	O
day	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
steal	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Earle	I-pers
of	O
Burlington	O
,	O
one	O
set	O
of	O
white	O
Damask	O
Curtains	O
value	O
15	O
l	O
six	O
yellow	O
Curtains	O
fring	O
'd	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
one	O
other	O
fring	O
'd	O
Damask	O
Curtain	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
eight	O
yards	O
of	O
Stuff	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
one	O
green	O
Serge	O
Cover	O
for	O
a	O
Chair	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
good	O
value	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
about	O
two	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Goods	O
,	O
all	O
which	O
were	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
stolen	O
before	O
:	O
and	O
having	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
most	O
gracious	O
Pardon	O
heretofore	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
as	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Michael	B-pers
Wakeland	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Norgrave	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Cooley	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Wakeland	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
three	O
former	O
as	O
principals	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
latter	O
as	O
being	O
accessaries	O
,	O
)	O
for	O
Robing	O
the	O
Waggon	O
of	O
Matthew	B-pers
Bugbeard	I-pers
,	O
(	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
.	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
)	O
of	O
two	O
silver	O
Tankards	O
value	O
14	O
l.	O
6	O
silver	O
Caps	O
value	O
14	O
l.	O
12	O
dozen	O
of	O
silver	O
Thimbles	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
3	O
dozen	O
of	O
Bodkins	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
4	O
silver	O
Whistles	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
2	O
dozen	O
of	O
silver	O
Clasps	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
6	O
silver	O
Chains	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
12	O
Wooden	O
Cups	O
tipt	O
with	O
silver	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
24	O
Stone	O
Mugs	O
tipt	O
with	O
silver	O
value	O
34	O
s.	O
with	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
150	O
l.	O
The	O
proper	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Russell	I-pers
;	O
The	O
Evidence	O
againg	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Waggoner	O
driving	O
his	O
Waggon	O
along	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
beyond	O
Aston	O
,	O
(	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Uxbridge-Fair	O
)	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
set	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
bound	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Waggon	O
,	O
which	O
Goods	O
afterwards	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
having	O
but	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
themselves	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
found	O
in	O
several	O
Stories	O
they	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
the	O
Men	O
were	O
all	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Women	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
Parish	I-place
.	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
killing	O
Robert	B-pers
Shoarditch	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
.	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
October	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
moral	O
wound	O
a	O
little	O
above	O
the	O
right	O
Pap	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
four	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
wound	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
drinking	O
together	O
in	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
out	O
about	O
a	O
Trifle	O
,	O
(	O
viz	O
.	O
)	O
an	O
Oyster	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
snatching	O
the	O
Oyster	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
deceased	O
's	O
hand	O
,	O
the	O
deceased	O
fell	O
into	O
a	O
great	O
passion	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
by	O
no	O
means	O
be	O
pacified	O
,	O
notwithstanding	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
would	O
have	O
given	O
him	O
a	O
Penny	O
to	O
buy	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
continued	O
to	O
threaten	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
Revenge	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
deceased	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
going	O
homewards	O
towards	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
met	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
who	O
immediately	O
drew	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
draw	O
,	O
(	O
they	O
being	O
both	O
Souldier	O
s	O
,	O
)	O
the	O
deceased	O
made	O
several	O
Passes	O
at	O
him	O
before	O
he	O
drew	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
forc	O
'd	O
to	O
defend	O
himself	O
,	O
gave	O
the	O
wound	O
aforesaid	O
to	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
premeditated	O
malice	O
being	O
proved	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
not	O
Guilty	O
,	O
only	O
Se	O
Defendendo	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
John	B-pers
Redhead	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
.	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
for	O
Making	O
,	O
Counterfeiting	O
,	O
and	O
Stamping	O
of	O
half-Pence	O
,	O
made	O
of	O
Copper	O
,	O
Tyn	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
mixt	O
Mettals	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Tooles	O
and	O
Instruments	O
fit	O
for	O
the	O
work	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
bag	O
of	O
Coyn	O
'd	O
Half-pence	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
House	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Paper	O
Writing	O
containing	O
Articles	O
of	O
Agreement	O
,	O
between	O
him	O
and	O
his	O
two	O
Brothers	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
William	O
Redhead	O
and	O
Anthony	B-pers
Redhead	I-pers
,	O
all	O
which	O
Implements	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
the	O
Bag	O
of	O
Half-pence	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
Materiall	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
matter	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Redhead	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
11	O
l.	O
weight	O
of	O
Mettle	O
call	O
'd	O
Brokidge	O
pieces	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
8	O
d.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
working	O
at	O
Skinners-Hall	B-place
,	O
stole	O
the	O
Brokidge	O
,	O
pretending	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Hammer	O
,	O
which	O
Goods	O
being	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Trunk	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
defence	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
looked	O
upon	O
as	O
an	O
Assistant	O
to	O
his	O
Brother	O
John	B-pers
Redhead	I-pers
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
a	O
misdemeanour	O
also	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Redhall	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Boy	O
about	O
15	O
years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bartholomew	I-place
Exchange	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Killing	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Bridges	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Pistol	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
shooting	O
the	O
said	O
Bridges	O
into	O
the	O
hinder	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
six	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
wound	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
were	O
fellow	O
Apprentice	O
s	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
happening	O
to	O
play	O
with	O
a	O
Brace	O
of	O
Pistols	O
that	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
charged	O
with	O
a	O
Bullet	O
,	O
the	O
Pistol	O
in	O
the	O
hand	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
unhappily	O
gave	O
Fire	O
,	O
and	O
shot	O
the	O
deceased	O
into	O
the	O
Head	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
:	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
not	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
shoot	O
of	O
the	O
Pistol	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
sorry	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
loved	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
proof	O
of	O
any	O
malice	O
,	O
and	O
forasmuch	O
as	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
Pistol	O
was	O
Charged	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
,	O
only	O
did	O
it	O
per	O
Misfortunam	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
Agnes	I-place
&	O
c.	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
l.	O
one	O
silver	O
Porringer	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
eight	O
silver	O
Spoons	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
silver	O
Bowl	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Hampstead	B-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
High-Misdemeanour	O
,	O
in	O
pretending	O
himself	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Monmouth	O
,	O
intending	O
thereby	O
to	O
disturb	O
and	O
disquiet	O
the	O
Peace	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
;	O
did	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
day	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
presence	O
of	O
several	O
people	O
,	O
Say	O
,	O
Assert	O
,	O
Affirm	O
,	O
and	O
Declare	O
,	O
(	O
with	O
aloud	O
Voice	O
)	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Monmouth	O
,	O
and	O
Right	O
Heir	O
to	O
the	O
Crown	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
hoped	O
very	O
suddenly	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
would	O
restore	O
all	O
Losses	O
to	O
the	O
Subjects	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
an	O
Army	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sent	O
Three	O
Ships	O
into	O
Scotland	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
thither	O
himself	O
ere	O
long	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
to	O
all	O
which	O
,	O
upon	O
his	O
Arraignment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Hackney	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
l.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Wosted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
Holland	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
with	O
a	O
Bridle	O
and	O
Saddle	O
,	O
and	O
45	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
James	B-pers
Mayfield	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Mayfield	O
himself	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
met	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Kings	O
High-way	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
all	O
the	O
above	O
said	O
Goods	O
from	O
him	O
and	O
left	O
him	O
bound	O
in	O
the	O
Field	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
committing	O
another	O
Robery	O
upon	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Horse	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
used	O
several	O
Evasions	O
whereby	O
to	O
extenuate	O
the	O
Fault	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Horse	O
at	O
Bristol	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
being	O
so	O
apparent	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Newgent	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
a	O
Doctor	B-pers
of	I-pers
Physick	I-pers
,	O
one	O
Perriwig	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
Beaver	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
.	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Doctor	O
himself	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
street	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
snatch	O
'd	O
off	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Perriwig	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
:	O
but	O
pursuing	O
of	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
immediatly	O
taken	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
using	O
several	O
extenuating	O
Arguments	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
no	O
purpose	O
:	O
Being	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
an	O
Old	O
Offender	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Thistleworth	B-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Killing	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Patfield	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Aged	O
Person	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
.	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
in	O
the	O
Throat	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
Eight	O
Inches	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
three	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Wound	O
the	O
said	O
Patfield	O
instantly	O
dyed	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
who	O
gave	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
deceased	O
in	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
nor	O
far	O
from	O
his	O
own	O
dwelling	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
inhumanely	O
fell	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
cast	O
him	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
kneeling	O
upon	O
his	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
deceaseds	O
own	O
Knife	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
several	O
Cuts	O
in	O
the	O
Throat	O
,	O
and	O
jobb	O
'd	O
the	O
Knifedown	O
his	O
Throat	O
in	O
a	O
most	O
Barbarous	O
manner	O
:	O
The	O
Knife	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
all	O
besmeared	O
in	O
Blood	O
likewise	O
,	O
and	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
Knife	O
the	O
deceased	O
used	O
to	O
carry	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Sons	O
of	O
the	O
deceased	O
;	O
all	O
which	O
,	O
was	O
Corroborated	O
by	O
several	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
nothing	O
material	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
;	O
but	O
denying	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
after	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Wilful	O
Murther	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Bently	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Swithens	I-place
,	O
was	O
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
silver	O
Tankards	O
,	O
value	O
17	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Penryn	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
.	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidenceagainst	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
the	O
Tankards	O
were	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
sitting	O
near	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
Tankards	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
Ten	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
:	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
several	O
substantial	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
his	O
Life	O
and	O
Conversation	O
hath	O
always	O
been	O
honest	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Covey	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripple-gate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Bag	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Black	O
Shammy	O
Gloves	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Gilney	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Parish	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
time	O
that	O
the	O
Gloves	O
were	O
lost	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
she	O
actually	O
took	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
Ludgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
October	O
a	O
silver-hilted	O
Sword	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
standing	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
near	O
Ludgate	B-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
about	O
Eight	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
felt	O
his	O
Sword	O
suddenly	O
snatch	O
'd	O
from	O
his	O
side	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
possitively	O
that	O
the	O
person	O
did	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Harley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
Eight	O
other	O
Gold	O
pieces	O
,	O
being	O
half	O
Guinneys	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Summerkol	I-pers
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Brockhouse	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Braton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Nine	O
Yards	O
of	O
Flower	O
'd	O
Silk	O
Callico	O
,	O
wrought	O
with	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
7	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
.	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Coape	I-pers
and	I-pers
Partners	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
being	O
proved	O
how	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
,	O
under	O
pretence	O
to	O
fetch	O
some	O
Patterns	O
,	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Callico	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
being	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
deny	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
and	O
Agnes	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Holland	O
Sheet	O
,	O
value	O
,	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
Flaxen	O
Sheet	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
two	O
Blankets	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
Smoothing-Irons	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
Pewter	O
Dish	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
Table	O
Cloath	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
with	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
small	O
value	O
,	O
from	O
Christopher	B-pers
Gardener	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
.	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Witness	O
to	O
swear	O
possitively	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Minace	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
having	O
two	O
Wives	O
,	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
Anne	B-pers
Story	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
the	O
second	O
Frances	B-pers
Mansell	I-pers
;	O
it	O
appeared	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
drawn	O
in	O
by	O
a	O
sham	O
to	O
Marry	O
the	O
latter	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
proved	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Married	O
to	O
the	O
former	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
although	O
he	O
Married	O
the	O
second	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
another	O
Man	O
,	O
(	O
viz	O
.	O
)	O
one	O
Jeffery	O
Wakeland	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
drink	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
and	O
Edmond	B-pers
Anthony	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Matthew	B-pers
Pluck	I-pers
Esq	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
.	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
six	O
flowr	O
'd	O
damask	O
Curtains	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
four	O
Mohair	O
Curtains	O
40	O
s.	O
one	O
Quilt	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
Perriwig	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
Sarsnet	O
Quilt	O
10	O
s.	O
16	O
Diaper	O
Towels	O
2	O
s.	O
3	O
course	O
Napkins	O
10	O
d.	O
3	O
Diaper	O
Table	O
Cloths	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
Sheets	O
20	O
s.	O
3	O
pieces	O
of	O
Woollen	O
Cloth	O
11	O
s.	O
one	O
Muff	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
Cloth	O
Breeches	O
12	O
d.	O
one	O
silver	O
Hilted	O
Sword	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
lac	O
'd	O
Crevat	O
30	O
s.	O
with	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
good	O
value	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
whilst	O
the	O
Family	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
they	O
Robbed	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Goods	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
being	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
idle	O
Fellows	O
,	O
having	O
both	O
together	O
with	O
Thomas	O
Fann	O
broke	O
out	O
of	O
Newgate	O
lately	O
,	O
(	O
but	O
were	O
again	O
taken	O
)	O
and	O
being	O
found	O
in	O
several	O
Stories	O
and	O
Lyes	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
after	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
E.	B-pers
R	I-pers
.	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
Sugar	O
Castors	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
six	O
silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
two	O
silver	O
Forks	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
Dr.	O
of	O
Physick	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Spoons	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
a	O
Goldsmiths	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
sold	O
to	O
him	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
further	O
deposed	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
rest	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Spoons	O
being	O
proved	O
only	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Custody	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
no	O
Witness	O
on	O
his	O
side	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fann	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stoak-Newington	B-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bay	O
Mare	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Holton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Mare	O
at	O
a	O
place	O
called	O
Welton	O
in	O
Norhamptonshire	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
Mare	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
9	O
l.	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
paid	O
3	O
l.	O
in	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
rest	O
at	O
Michaelmas	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
owned	O
the	O
Mare	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
,	O
at	O
Welton	O
afore	O
said	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
Corroborated	O
by	O
others	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Mare	O
at	O
Bristol	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
having	O
no	O
witness	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
Criminals	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Those	O
afore-mentioned	O
,	O
who	O
broke	O
the	O
Goal	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Philmore	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
drowning	O
John	B-pers
Philmore	I-pers
her	O
Infant	O
Child	O
,	O
about	O
Nine	O
Weeks	O
old	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
,	O
day	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Pail	O
of	O
Water	O
:	O
The	O
Matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
happened	O
thus	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
very	O
Covetous	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
fearing	O
she	O
should	O
be	O
Poor	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
lost	O
a	O
small	O
parcel	O
of	O
Bottles	O
that	O
she	O
used	O
to	O
sell	O
Small-Beer	O
in	O
,	O
she	O
grew	O
into	O
an	O
ill	O
Humour	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
after	O
her	O
Husband	O
was	O
in	O
Bed	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
her	O
Children	O
,	O
she	O
put	O
the	O
Childs	O
Head	O
into	O
the	O
Pail	O
of	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
absented	O
her	O
self	O
till	O
Monday	O
,	O
But	O
withal	O
went	O
and	O
discovered	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Childs	O
Godmother	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
not	O
denying	O
it	O
at	O
her	O
Tryal	O
,	O
but	O
alledged	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
distracted	O
,	O
yet	O
that	O
not	O
prevailing	O
with	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Bag	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
Pillow-Bear	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
12	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
.	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
all	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Spratt	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
House	O
,	O
had	O
opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
W	B-pers
-	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Townley	I-pers
in	O
the	O
day	O
time	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
.	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
one	O
piece	O
of	O
Copper	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
very	O
plain	O
and	O
possitive	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
yet	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
breaking	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
Copper	O
being	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hensly	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Pocket	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
3	O
Iron	O
Keys	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
six	O
shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
.	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
past	O
from	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Newhall	I-pers
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Lumbard-street	B-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
met	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
pickt	O
her	O
Pocket	O
of	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Keys	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
swearing	O
possitively	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Rebekah	B-pers
Broxbey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
Ludgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
13	O
yards	O
of	O
black	O
Silk	O
Lute-string	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
Nine	O
yards	O
of	O
Norwich	O
Stuff	O
14	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
.	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
from	O
Henry	B-pers
Rapier	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Rapiers	O
Servant	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Maid	O
being	O
a	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
hid	O
them	O
for	O
a	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
made	O
her	O
self	O
Clothes	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
offered	O
them	O
to	O
Sale	O
at	O
a	O
Brokers	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
received	O
26	O
s.	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
not	O
much	O
denying	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Nath	B-pers
.	I-pers
Crowdon	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Robert	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
.	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
one	O
blue	O
Silk	O
Scarfe	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
Embroidered	O
Belt	O
40	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
wrought	O
Mug	O
30	O
s.	O
one	O
Watch	O
40	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
Spoon	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
30	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
,	O
day	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rowland	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
House	O
,	O
one	O
Eveningabout	O
Nine	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
Lodged	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
took	O
away	O
a	O
Tankard	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
Goods	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
won	O
the	O
Tankard	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
at	O
Cards	O
,	O
and	O
bringing	O
several	O
good	O
Evidence	O
on	O
his	O
side	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
a	O
good	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Skelton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Killing	O
Henry	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
divers	O
mortal	O
bruses	O
upon	O
the	O
Brest	O
.	O
Belly	O
and	O
Back	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
dyed	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
very	O
Numerous	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
very	O
concurring	O
in	O
their	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
Howard	O
,	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
a	O
Coffee-House	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
side	O
of	O
Ratcliff	O
High	O
way	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
Night	O
before	O
the	O
Murther	O
was	O
Committed	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
(	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Headborrow	O
in	O
that	O
Parish	O
,	O
)	O
who	O
would	O
have	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
Prison	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Money	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
for	O
that	O
Night	O
but	O
on	O
the	O
next	O
Evening	O
being	O
Saturday	O
,	O
the	O
deceased	O
happening	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
one	O
Mr	O
.	O
Staples	O
's	O
(	O
who	O
kept	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
thereabouts	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
a	O
Friend	O
of	O
the	O
deceaseds	O
.	O
)	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
Nine	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
very	O
much	O
indisposed	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Staples	O
was	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
Bed	O
,	O
but	O
on	O
a	O
sudden	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Hedborrow	O
knockt	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
Skelton	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
let	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
immediately	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
haled	O
the	O
deceased	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
Collar	O
,	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
Field	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
most	O
barbarous	O
and	O
inhumane	O
manner	O
,	O
crying	O
out	O
Murther	O
,	O
dragging	O
the	O
deceased	O
into	O
the	O
Grass	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
him	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
away	O
to	O
the	O
Watch	O
or	O
to	O
Prison	O
,	O
but	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
deceased	O
was	O
found	O
Dead	O
,	O
lying	O
against	O
a	O
Bank	O
in	O
a	O
Ditch	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Headborrow	O
argued	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
intended	O
to	O
do	O
nothing	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
his	O
Duty	O
to	O
do	O
;	O
he	O
confest	O
indeed	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Scuffle	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
deceased	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
his	O
Death	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
all	O
which	O
prevailed	O
nothing	O
on	O
his	O
account	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
wilfull	O
Murther	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Isaac	B-pers
Bosford	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
,	O
in	O
taking	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
23	O
s.	O
from	O
Jane	B-pers
Fich	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
.	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Prosecutor	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Robert	B-pers
Worsendel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shorditch	I-place
;	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
writing	O
and	O
publishing	O
Scandalous	O
,	O
False	O
,	O
and	O
Seditious	O
News-Letters	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
Peace	O
and	O
Quiet	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
to	O
which	O
indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Han	O
d	O
Four	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
T	O
-	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Mathews	I-pers
,	O
the	O
two	O
latter	O
of	O
which	O
,	O
were	O
last	O
Sessions	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Sentence	O
as	O
followeth	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Han	O
d	O
Four	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
T	O
-	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Mathews	I-pers
,	O
the	O
two	O
latter	O
of	O
which	O
,	O
were	O
last	O
Sessions	O
.	O
Ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
Two	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Wilder	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
Ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Whip	O
'd	O
Five	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
E.	O
R.	O
Olander	O
Boston	O
,	O
Rebeckah	O
Broxbey	O
Robert	B-pers
Worsendell	I-pers
,	O
to	O
be	O
Whipt	O
from	O
Newgate	O
to	O
Shorditch	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
pay	O
20	O
s.	O
as	O
a	O
Fine	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
,	O
to	O
be	O
whipt	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
next	O
from	O
Newgate	O
to	O
Tyburn	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
next	O
Wednesday	O
after	O
,	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pyllory	O
at	O
Charing	O
Cross	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
following	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
May	O
pole	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
John	B-pers
Redhead	I-pers
,	O
to	O
pay	O
a	O
Fine	O
of	O
200	O
Mark	O
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Redhead	I-pers
,	O
to	O
pay	O
a	O
Fine	O
of	O
100	O
Mark	O
,	O
and	O
both	O
to	O
stand	O
Committed	O
till	O
they	O
pay	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Elizabeth	O
Brackhouse	O
,	O
was	O
Reprieved	O
before	O
Judgment	O
passed	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Philmore	I-pers
,	O
Pleading	O
her	O
Belly	O
,	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Marrow	O
were	O
Empannell	O
'd	O
,	O
who	O
brought	O
in	O
their	O
Verdict	O
in	O
the	O
Negative	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
:	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
Fourteen	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hensley	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
W	O
-	O
Richard	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Edward	O
Newgate	O
,	O
Michael	B-pers
Wakeland	I-pers
,	O
Richard	O
Norgrave	O
John	B-pers
Cooley	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fann	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
Edward	O
Antony	O
,	O
Anne	O
,	O
Philmore	O
,	O
Richard	O
&	O
Richardson	O
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Skelton	I-pers
.	O
