TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
;	O
And	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
Held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
,	O
The	O
7th	O
.	O
and	O
8th	O
.	O
days	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
1686	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
2d	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
Held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bayly	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
and	O
Thursday	O
,	O
the	O
7th	O
.	O
and	O
8th	O
.	O
Days	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
1686	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Jefferies	I-pers
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Holt	I-pers
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
City	O
,	O
with	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
for	O
London	O
and	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
follow	O
,	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Gibbon	I-pers
Phillip	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
Phillip	B-pers
Stubbs	I-pers
Luke	B-pers
Field	I-pers
Stephen	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
Joon	B-pers
Parrot	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Speed	I-pers
Abraham	B-pers
Hemingway	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Larner	I-pers
William	B-pers
Hayward	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Peake	I-pers
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Glasbrook	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Boltbey	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Hempstead	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Edmonds	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Robbins	I-pers
John	B-pers
Langley	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Richmond	I-pers
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
Nicholas	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
John	B-pers
Tease	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Gizmon	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
follows	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Water-man	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
.	O
of	O
June	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Peters	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolph	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
were	O
Thomas	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
person	O
coming	O
to	O
drink	O
in	O
Peter	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Wife	O
filled	O
them	O
a	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
person	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Mackrel	O
to	O
Dress	O
;	O
and	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
occasion	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
left	O
stranger	O
alone	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
his	O
return	O
,	O
found	O
a	O
Pewter-pot	O
ing	O
upon	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
person	O
gone	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
they	O
seized	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
alledged	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
no	O
other	O
but	O
the	O
Pewter-pot	O
:	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
came	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
meer	O
stranger	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
carried	O
him	O
over	O
the	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
only	O
invited	O
him	O
to	O
Drink	O
.	O
And	O
besides	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
several	O
very	O
Credible	O
Witnesses	O
on	O
his	O
side	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
poor	O
labouring	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
great	O
pains	O
all	O
his	O
days	O
for	O
his	O
Lively-hood	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Boy	O
of	O
about	O
Twelve	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
fourteen	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Coffee-Berrys	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
.	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Kingwell	I-pers
,	O
one	O
white	O
Beaver-Hat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
One	O
Yard	O
and	O
a	O
Half	O
of	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
from	O
Joseph	B-pers
Sheriff	I-pers
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Sheriff	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
in	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Boy	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
him	O
upon	O
liking	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
sold	O
the	O
Coffee-Berrys	O
to	O
a	O
Drugster	O
in	O
Lumber-street	O
,	O
all	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
not	O
denying	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barret	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Barnell	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
a	O
Boy	O
Aged	O
about	O
Ten	O
Years	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
steal	O
Four	O
and	O
Twenty	O
Yards	O
of	O
Blew	O
and	O
White	O
Linnen	O
Cloath	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
from	O
one	O
David	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
David	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
come	O
by	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Cloath	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Collins	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
Confess	O
'd	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
:	O
But	O
he	O
denying	O
it	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
John	B-pers
Cane	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Cloath	O
Coats	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
One	O
Stuff	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
.	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
Paul	B-pers
St.	I-pers
John	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
without	O
any	O
Coats	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
his	O
return	O
,	O
brought	O
away	O
the	O
said	O
Coats	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Coats	O
were	O
not	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
at	O
his	O
apprehension	O
:	O
But	O
however	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
not	O
givingthe	O
Court	O
a	O
satisfactory	O
Account	O
of	O
his	O
Conversation	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
no	O
Witnesses	O
on	O
his	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
found	O
in	O
several	O
Stories	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Hugh	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
.	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Lyon	I-pers
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
was	O
William	B-pers
Lyon	I-pers
and	O
another	O
person	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
Lyon	O
's	O
,	O
house	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
with	O
one	O
Allen	O
a	O
Souldier	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
conveyed	O
away	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
Lyon	O
searching	O
after	O
it	O
,	O
had	O
Intelligence	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
offered	O
to	O
sale	O
at	O
a	O
Goldsmiths	O
Shop	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
kind	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
declared	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Tankard	O
in	O
the	O
Custody	O
of	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Allen	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
only	O
person	O
concerned	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Tankard	O
being	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Coat-pocket	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
S.	B-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
Gent	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Killing	O
Robert	B-pers
Sheapherd	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
.	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
giving	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Sheapherd	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
Four	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Wound	O
he	O
instantly	O
dyed	O
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
Christmas	O
last	O
was	O
Twelve	O
Month	O
,	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
happened	O
between	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
playing	O
at	O
Billiards	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
never	O
seeing	O
each	O
other	O
since	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
above-said	O
day	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
day	O
,	O
Sheapherd	O
espied	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Lincolns-Inn	O
Fields	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
satisfaction	O
of	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
former	O
Affront	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
willing	O
to	O
quarrel	O
a	O
fresh	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
present	O
satisfaction	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
withdrew	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
about	O
his	O
Business	O
,	O
which	O
lay	O
at	O
Grays-lane	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
passing	O
on	O
towards	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
place	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
followed	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Rose-Alley	B-place
in	I-place
Red-Lyon	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
and	O
there	O
the	O
Deceased	O
made	O
several	O
passes	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
which	O
forced	O
him	O
to	O
draw	O
his	O
Sword	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
defence	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
received	O
the	O
Wound	O
aforesaid	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
procuring	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
never	O
given	O
to	O
quarrel	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
stood	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
defence	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Glasborrow	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Roach	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
Breaking	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
on	O
the	O
28th	O
.	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Fringe	O
Gloves	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
Hatband	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
Hilted	O
Sword	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
other	O
Sword	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
from	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hargrave	I-pers
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
Nine	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
the	O
above	O
said	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
drinking	O
in	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
having	O
but	O
very	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
their	O
own	O
defence	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
known	O
before	O
to	O
be	O
former	O
Offenders	O
:	O
They	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Arnold	O
and	O
Glasborrow	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Roach	O
:	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Stoakes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Kensington	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Killing	O
Frances	B-pers
Pollard	I-pers
on	O
the	O
31th	O
.	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Pollard	I-pers
,	O
driving	O
his	O
Waggon	O
Wheele	O
over	O
the	O
hinder	O
part	O
of	O
her	O
Body	O
,	O
giving	O
her	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
she	O
immediately	O
dyed	O
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Pollard	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Gentlewoman	O
,	O
Riding	O
through	O
Kensington	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
occasionally	O
watering	O
their	O
Horses	O
at	O
Kensington	B-place
,	O
the	O
Deceaseds	O
Horse	O
standing	O
behind	O
the	O
rest	O
in	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Waggon	O
coming	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Horses	O
being	O
Five	O
Stone	O
Horses	O
,	O
and	O
unruly	O
justled	O
against	O
the	O
Deceaseds	O
Horse	O
and	O
threw	O
her	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
caught	O
under	O
the	O
Wheele	O
,	O
and	O
Bruised	O
to	O
Death	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Evidencing	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
stop	O
his	O
Horses	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sorry	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
all	O
that	O
in	O
him	O
lay	O
to	O
prevent	O
the	O
misfortune	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ashley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Copper	O
Kettle	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
.	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
Robert	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
missing	O
his	O
Kettle	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
Braziers	O
to	O
be-speak	O
another	O
Kettle	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
found	O
his	O
own	O
Kettle	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
sold	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
prosecutors	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
mark	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
defence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Kettle	O
of	O
another	O
person	O
,	O
one	O
John	O
Brown	O
who	O
is	O
since	O
fled	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
being	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
giving	O
but	O
a	O
weak	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
Credit	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Whale	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Fullham	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
attempting	O
to	O
Rob	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Frances	B-pers
Hurgrace	I-pers
Widow	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
Frances	O
Hurgrace	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
silver	O
Cup	O
and	O
some	O
money	O
,	O
about	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
Friend	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
alone	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
broak	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
came	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
defeated	O
of	O
his	O
purpose	O
:	O
He	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
half	O
open	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Trespass	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Nest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
T	O
after	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
silver	O
Box	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
three	O
pieces	O
of	O
Foreign	O
Silver	O
,	O
each	O
piece	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
half-French	O
Pistol	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
other	O
Piece	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
one	O
other	O
piece	O
of	O
King	O
Charles	O
the	O
Second	O
's	O
Coin	O
value	O
5	O
one	O
other	O
piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
King	O
James	O
's	O
piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
.	O
of	O
May	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Rhodes	I-pers
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Rhodes	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
to	O
drink	O
at	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
got	O
away	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Goods	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
defence	O
,	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
a	O
Box	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
back	O
Window	O
without	O
doors	O
but	O
that	O
being	O
contradicted	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
making	O
but	O
a	O
weak	O
and	O
frivelous	O
defence	O
in	O
the	O
General	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
so	O
clear	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Battison	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Killing	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Kell	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Girl	O
about	O
Eleven	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
.	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
giving	O
her	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
Right	O
part	O
of	O
her	O
Belly	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
never	O
been	O
well	O
since	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Chirurgeon	O
said	O
her	O
death	O
must	O
needs	O
proceed	O
from	O
the	O
Blow	O
or	O
Kick	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
having	O
good	O
Evidence	O
on	O
her	O
side	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
though	O
she	O
was	O
Mother	O
in	O
Law	O
to	O
the	O
Decased	O
Kell	O
,	O
yet	O
she	O
loved	O
her	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
gave	O
her	O
moderate	O
Correction	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
always	O
very	O
sickly	O
,	O
and	O
dyed	O
of	O
a	O
Natural	O
Disease	O
;	O
all	O
which	O
was	O
Corroborated	O
by	O
another	O
Chirurgeon	O
that	O
searched	O
the	O
Deceased	O
Kell	O
,	O
whereupon	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
[	O
not	O
]	O
Guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Legat	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Baptist	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Cornet	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Killing	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Cormon	I-pers
on	O
the	O
20th	O
.	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
value	O
5	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
wound	O
upon	O
the	O
Breast	O
near	O
the	O
Right	O
Pap	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
6	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
said	O
Cornet	O
instantly	O
dyed	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoners	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
coming	O
into	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
and	O
drinking	O
together	O
,	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
happened	O
between	O
them	O
and	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
in	O
drink	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
deceased	O
and	O
Cornet	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Friend	O
of	O
the	O
deceased	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
together	O
before	O
they	O
met	O
with	O
other	O
two	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Legat	O
and	O
Baptist	O
;	O
it	O
appeared	O
further	O
the	O
deceased	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
very	O
abusive	O
Language	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
Baptist	O
before	O
he	O
died	O
but	O
in	O
that	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
proved	O
which	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
gave	O
the	O
Wound	O
to	O
Cormon	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
like	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
Transaction	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
upon	O
a	O
hearing	O
,	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Legat	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Baptist	O
and	O
Cornet	O
:	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Cripshaw	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hempslow	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Matthew	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Gregorys	I-place
,	O
&	O
c.	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
21	O
s.	O
and	O
upwards	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
.	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
from	O
Mrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Baudy	I-pers
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
Robed	O
by	O
some	O
men	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Change	B-place
,	O
about	O
Ten	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
at	O
Nightas	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
homewards	O
,	O
and	O
missing	O
her	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
crying	O
out	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
immediately	O
Apprehended	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
passing	O
down	O
St.	O
Martins	O
Legrand	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
having	O
no	O
Witnesses	O
but	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
depose	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
the	O
persons	O
that	O
Robed	O
her	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripple-gate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
on	O
the	O
9th	O
.	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
one	O
Brass	O
Kettle	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
Pewter	O
Porringer	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
one	O
Copper	O
Pot	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
Thirty	O
two	O
pound	O
more	O
of	O
Brass	O
,	O
value	O
,	O
12	O
d.	O
Two	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
Flannenel	O
Blanket	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
Fire-shovel	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Collins	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Goods	O
were	O
all	O
in	O
his	O
house	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
he	O
lost	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
had	O
her	O
Apprehended	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
a	O
Broker	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
having	O
nothing	O
material	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
defence	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
as	O
a	O
person	O
of	O
no	O
good	O
Credit	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Gabriel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Killing	O
Caleb	B-pers
Giver	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Boy	O
about	O
Twelve	O
or	O
Thirteen	O
years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
.	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Kick	O
on	O
the	O
Left	O
Thigh	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
,	O
and	O
dyed	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
July	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
Strike	O
and	O
Kick	O
the	O
Deceased	O
upon	O
some	O
provocation	O
about	O
their	O
Work	O
;	O
(	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Weaver	O
)	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
before	O
his	O
death	O
,	O
the	O
Kick	O
was	O
given	O
him	O
by	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
dyed	O
,	O
that	O
that	O
Kick	O
was	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
his	O
death	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
declared	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
violent	O
Fever	O
,	O
which	O
might	O
proceed	O
from	O
some	O
heat	O
and	O
cold	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
,	O
which	O
Evidence	O
out	O
weighing	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
after	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
30	O
Yards	O
of	O
Stuffe	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
from	O
one	O
Edward	B-pers
Woolf	I-pers
,	O
to	O
which	O
,	O
upon	O
his	O
Arraignment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michaels	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
l.	O
one	O
silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
.	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
one	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Condey	I-pers
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Tisdale	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
taking	O
away	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
Day	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
past	O
,	O
two	O
silver	O
Tankards	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
l.	O
and	O
about	O
60	O
l.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
from	O
James	B-pers
Gallywell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
his	O
Servant	O
in	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
had	O
opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
absenting	O
her	O
self	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
more	O
suspicion	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
making	O
diligent	O
Enquiry	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Money	O
and	O
his	O
Tankards	O
brought	O
to	O
him	O
by	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Tisdale	O
,	O
who	O
Confessed	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
Apprehended	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
stole	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
:	O
But	O
Smith	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
other	O
in	O
her	O
Vindication	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samuel	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hazard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stoke	B-place
Newington	I-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
319	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
26	O
s.	O
On	O
the	O
the	O
1st	O
.	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
unknown	O
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
seen	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
a	O
Lane	O
near	O
Newington	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Horse	O
bearing	O
a	O
Sack	O
,	O
wherein	O
were	O
3	O
Sheets	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
suspected	O
to	O
be	O
persons	O
of	O
no	O
very	O
good	O
repute	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
outwardly	O
appeared	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
immediately	O
apprehended	O
and	O
carryed	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
;	O
they	O
both	O
confest	O
that	O
they	O
bought	O
the	O
Lead	O
of	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Poor	I-pers
,	O
at	O
Waltham	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
7	O
s.	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
making	O
but	O
a	O
frivolous	O
defence	O
for	O
themselves	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
one	O
person	O
appearing	O
on	O
their	O
behalf	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Matfellon	I-place
,	I-place
alias	I-place
White-chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Souldier	O
and	O
not	O
a	O
Captain	O
,	O
did	O
receive	O
a	O
Salery	O
from	O
the	O
King	O
as	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
but	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
did	O
depart	O
without	O
leave	O
from	O
his	O
Service	O
,	O
in	O
contempt	O
to	O
the	O
Laws	O
of	O
our	O
Sovereign	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
were	O
One	O
Serjeant	O
and	O
a	O
Souldier	O
that	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Company	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
Desert	O
himself	O
from	O
the	O
Kings	O
Service	O
at	O
the	O
Camp	O
on	O
Hounslow-heath	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
24th	O
.	O
of	O
June	O
Last	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
about	O
the	O
space	O
of	O
Eight	O
Days	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
in	O
White-chappel	O
near	O
his	O
own	O
house	O
;	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
drinking	O
in	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
,	O
and	O
carryed	O
before	O
Capt-Berry	O
,	O
who	O
Committed	O
him	O
to	O
Newgate	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
defence	O
alledged	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
a	O
Child	O
dead	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
home	O
to	O
the	O
Funeral	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Camp	O
aforesaid	O
to	O
take	O
Care	O
of	O
the	O
Burial	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
ask	O
leave	O
of	O
his	O
Lieutenant	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
absent	O
himself	O
with	O
the	O
least	O
intent	O
to	O
defraud	O
or	O
decieve	O
the	O
King	O
;	O
but	O
did	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
occasion	O
,	O
making	O
good	O
proof	O
of	O
his	O
Reputation	O
and	O
protesting	O
his	O
own	O
Loyalty	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
attested	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Neighbours	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
weighing	O
the	O
matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Barrow	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Levingstone	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michaels	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
as	O
being	O
Accessary	O
to	O
the	O
Robbery	O
Committed	O
by	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Thomas	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
On	O
the	O
26th	O
.	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
One	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
valued	O
11	O
l.	O
One	O
silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
valued	O
30	O
s.	O
One	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
The	O
Goods	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Condey	I-pers
:	O
But	O
it	O
appeared	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
no	O
further	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
than	O
the	O
meeting	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
by	O
chance	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
committed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
Drink	O
together	O
,	O
(	O
being	O
formerly	O
School	O
fellows	O
)	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
apprehended	O
together	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
so	O
full	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
as	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shorditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Alamode	O
Hood	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
Ounces	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Woosted	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
On	O
the	O
19th	O
day	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Walter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
,	O
Walter	O
as	O
Principal	O
,	O
and	O
Bird	O
as	O
Accessary	O
,	O
for	O
Robing	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
Lady	O
Lucy	B-pers
Bright	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
Day	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
taking	O
away	O
one	O
silver	O
Can	O
,	O
value	O
42	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
Potringer	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s	O
:	O
one	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
marked	O
each	O
with	O
R	O
:	O
L.	O
S.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
about	O
Nine	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
26th	O
.	O
Day	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Walter	O
Confess	O
'd	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
another	O
Boy	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
helps	O
the	O
other	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
pane	O
of	O
Glass	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Goods	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Hole	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
carryed	O
is	O
off	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
it	O
at	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
nothing	O
Material	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Bird	O
not	O
proving	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
purpose	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ralph	B-pers
Turfet	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Wilful	O
Perjury	O
,	O
in	O
offering	O
himself	O
in	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
Bail	O
for	O
another	O
person	O
that	O
had	O
a	O
Law-suit	O
depending	O
,	O
saying	O
and	O
asserting	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
Apothecary	O
by	O
his	O
Trade	O
,	O
and	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Buttolphs	O
Bishopsgate	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
Goods	O
and	O
was	O
a	O
House-keeper	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Credibly	O
worth	O
50	O
l	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
he	O
owned	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Poor	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
Charge	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
him	O
the	O
more	O
easie	O
to	O
be	O
induced	O
to	O
Commit	O
that	O
wicked	O
Act	O
;	O
not	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lived	O
in	O
Bishops-gate	O
street	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
date	O
;	O
so	O
in	O
Conclusion	O
,	O
the	O
Matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
being	O
so	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Wilful	O
Perjury	O
.	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
David	B-pers
James	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Panacrass	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
killing	O
William	B-pers
Farrer	I-pers
Gent	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
;	O
Day	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
Right	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
Body	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
2	O
Inches	O
of	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Farrer	O
instantly	O
dyed	O
;	O
The	O
Evidenceagainst	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
Peter	B-pers
Farrer	I-pers
,	O
Brother	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Brother	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
,	O
taking	O
a	O
walk	O
together	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
near	O
St.	O
Pancrass	O
Church	O
,	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Son	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
more	O
walking	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Spanniel	O
Dog	O
behind	O
them	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
whistled	O
to	O
the	O
Dog	O
and	O
drop	O
'd	O
his	O
Glove	O
to	O
entice	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Dog	O
coming	O
near	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
played	O
with	O
the	O
Dogs	O
Neck	O
,	O
and	O
led	O
the	O
Dog	O
along	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Son	O
looking	O
back	O
,	O
saw	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
after	O
the	O
Deceased	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
Dog	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Glove	O
lye	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
loosed	O
the	O
Dog	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Boy	O
for	O
his	O
Glove	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
their	O
strugling	O
together	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
Glove	O
,	O
the	O
Boy	O
happened	O
to	O
fall	O
to	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
looking	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
his	O
Childs	O
Assistance	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
struck	O
the	O
deceased	O
a	O
Box	O
on	O
the	O
Ear	O
,	O
biding	O
him	O
draw	O
,	O
drawing	O
his	O
Sword	O
first	O
;	O
and	O
passing	O
at	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
Assault	O
the	O
deceased	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
and	O
retreated	O
back	O
;	O
only	O
standing	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
defence	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pressing	O
upon	O
him	O
so	O
hard	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Wound	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
his	O
Son	O
,	O
which	O
so	O
highly	O
provoked	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
attempt	O
to	O
vindicate	O
him	O
,	O
not	O
with	O
any	O
intent	O
to	O
Kill	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
struck	O
him	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
being	O
proved	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
did	O
strike	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
hit	O
him	O
:	O
So	O
upon	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Cope	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
One	O
Velvet	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
Four	O
Pounds	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Mouldsworth	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
person	O
coming	O
into	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
to	O
Drink	O
about	O
Nine	O
or	O
Ten	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
drank	O
one	O
Tanckard	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
paying	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Esquire	O
's	O
Coach	O
standing	O
not	O
far	O
off	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
it	O
(	O
the	O
Coachman	O
being	O
absent	O
)	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Coat	O
off	O
the	O
Coach	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
an	O
Alley	O
with	O
it	O
near	O
that	O
place	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
Corroberated	O
by	O
the	O
Ale-house	O
keeper	O
,	O
who	O
saw	O
him	O
and	O
his	O
Comrade	O
do	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
such	O
full	O
Proof	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
in	O
Bridewell	O
for	O
a	O
former	O
Offence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
F.	B-pers
D.	I-pers
L	I-pers
.	I-pers
Was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Counterfeiting	O
of	O
Past-ports	O
or	O
Warrants	O
for	O
clearing	O
out	O
of	O
Ships	O
to	O
Sea	O
and	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
often	O
Guilty	O
of	O
such	O
Offences	O
;	O
That	O
making	O
some	O
small	O
Evasion	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
to	O
the	O
purpose	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Matter	O
alledged	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
North	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Lambeth	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Savoy	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
One	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
One	O
Stuffe	O
Coat	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
30	O
Yards	O
of	O
Flannel	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
with	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
small	O
value	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
past	O
;	O
from	O
Tobias	B-pers
Sedgwick	I-pers
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
upon	O
their	O
Arraigument	O
,	O
John	O
North	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
Lambeth	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Then	O
the	O
Court	O
Proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Sentence	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Order	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
Fifteen	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Glassborrow	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Legat	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Cane	I-pers
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Asbley	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Hugh	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
S.	O
P.	O
Gent	O
.	O
John	B-pers
North	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hazard	I-pers
,	O
David	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Cope	I-pers
.	O
Order	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
Three	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Roach	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Tisdale	I-pers
.	O
Order	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
Whipt	O
Three	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Whale	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Judgment	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cornet	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Baptist	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Deferred	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Turfet	I-pers
was	O
Sentenced	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
Three	O
times	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
next	O
in	O
the	O
Pallace-Yard	O
,	O
before	O
Westminster-Hall	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
May-Pole	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Friday	O
,	O
against	O
Chancery	O
Lane	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
pay	O
a	O
Fine	O
of	O
Twenty	O
Pounds	O
.	O
F.	O
D.	O
L.	O
Sentenced	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
on	O
Monday	O
next	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Royal-Exchange	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
next	O
in	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Friday	O
following	O
at	O
Temple	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
pay	O
a	O
Fine	O
of	O
Forty	O
Pound	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
remain	O
in	O
Prison	O
,	O
till	O
all	O
be	O
performed	O
.	O
