TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
Of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
,	O
And	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
Held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD	O
BAYLY	O
,	O
The	O
1st	O
.	O
3d	O
.	O
and	O
10th	O
.	O
Days	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
1686	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Reign	O
.	O
The	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
;	O
Held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bayly	O
;	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
and	O
Friday	O
the	O
1st	O
.	O
and	O
3d	O
.	O
Days	O
of	O
Septem	O
.	O
1686.	O
and	O
on	O
Friday	O
the	O
10th	O
.	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
following	O
:	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Jefferies	I-pers
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Holt	I-pers
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
City	O
,	O
with	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
for	O
London	O
and	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
follow	O
,	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Easton	I-pers
John	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Comport	I-pers
John	B-pers
Pearpoint	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Green	I-pers
Benjamin	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
James	B-pers
Carpenter	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Bentley	I-pers
Jasper	B-pers
Rawlins	I-pers
Nicholas	B-pers
Royall	I-pers
John	B-pers
Cannon	I-pers
William	B-pers
Edmonds	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Dinn	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
Edmond	B-pers
Yeamons	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Linn	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
John	B-pers
Franklin	I-pers
John	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
John	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Saney	I-pers
Daniel	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
White	I-pers
Nathaniel	B-pers
Child	I-pers
.	O
The	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
are	O
as	O
follow	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Christ-Church	B-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Marfin	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
was	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Marfin	O
;	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
coming	O
into	O
her	O
house	O
in	O
Warwick-Lane	B-place
,	O
called	O
for	O
two	O
Tankards	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
whil'st	O
she	O
and	O
her	O
Servant	O
were	O
busie	O
about	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
their	O
opportunity	O
to	O
steal	O
away	O
the	O
Tankard	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
had	O
but	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
they	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
never	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
using	O
many	O
other	O
frivolous	O
Excuses	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
taken	O
notice	O
of	O
in	O
Court	O
to	O
have	O
lived	O
very	O
Idle	O
Lives	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
no	O
one	O
to	O
appear	O
on	O
their	O
sides	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
being	O
very	O
possitive	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Hair	O
Camblet	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
One	O
Perriwig	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
The	O
Goods	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
.	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Andrews	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
above	O
said	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
Time	O
after	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
offering	O
the	O
Perriwig	O
to	O
Sale	O
in	O
a	O
Publick	O
house	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
owned	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
but	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
a	O
manner	O
Confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Hutchens	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolphs	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
.	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
One	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
from	O
Peter	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
of	O
the	O
same	O
Parish	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Cook	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
into	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
for	O
a	O
Tankard	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
after	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
not	O
much	O
denying	O
it	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
.	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
One	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
One	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
One	O
pair	O
of	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
Three	O
Yards	O
of	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
One	O
Neckcloath	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
with	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
small	O
value	O
,	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
of	O
the	O
same	O
Parish	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Allen	O
and	O
his	O
Maid	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Allen	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
Begging	O
Money	O
for	O
another	O
person	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
Prison	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
inveigled	O
with	O
the	O
Maid	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
,	O
she	O
consenting	O
to	O
it	O
so	O
far	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
fetch	O
the	O
Goods	O
down	O
Stairs	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
yielding	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
should	O
be	O
Pawned	O
in	O
her	O
Name	O
to	O
one	O
Moss	O
a	O
Broker	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
his	O
Part	O
denyed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
Maid	O
in	O
his	O
Days	O
,	O
neither	O
was	O
he	O
ever	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
but	O
once	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Bed	O
that	O
Morning	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
stolen	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Maid	O
being	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
actually	O
consenting	O
to	O
the	O
Pawning	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
not	O
being	O
very	O
Possitive	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Deane	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
One	O
Linnen	O
Bagg	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
4	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
.	O
Day	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
past	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Pool	I-pers
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
happening	O
in	O
to	O
Drink	O
at	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
in	O
White-Fryers	B-place
,	O
about	O
Fight	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
sitting	O
a	O
while	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
another	O
person	O
,	O
she	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
of	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Money	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
whilst	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
paying	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
say	O
nothing	O
that	O
was	O
to	O
purpose	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
Defence	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
found	O
in	O
several	O
Storys	O
and	O
Lyes	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
in	O
Court	O
as	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
wicked	O
Life	O
and	O
Conversation	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
aftes	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
on	O
both	O
wicked	O
sides	O
,	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Stanly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
One	O
Amber	O
Necklace	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
One	O
pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
One	O
Fine	O
Pillow-Bear	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
One	O
Lute-string	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
with	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
considerable	O
value	O
,	O
all	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
hireing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
as	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
before	O
the	O
Robery	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
following	O
to	O
Church	O
with	O
his	O
whole	O
Family	O
,	O
leaving	O
this	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
upon	O
his	O
return	O
found	O
his	O
Goods	O
taken	O
away	O
and	O
the	O
Maid	O
gone	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
but	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
on	O
her	O
own	O
behalf	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
another	O
Master	O
,	O
who	O
she	O
pretended	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
a	O
Certificate	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
false	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
having	O
made	O
several	O
frivolous	O
Excuses	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Durham	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Killingone	O
George	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
.	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
past	O
,	O
Riding	O
over	O
the	O
said	O
Thompson	O
with	O
a	O
Mare	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
l.	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Bruise	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
he	O
dyed	O
the	O
25th	O
.	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
happened	O
thus	O
;	O
the	O
Deceased	O
and	O
another	O
person	O
being	O
walking	O
together	O
towards	O
Bow	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
about	O
Mile-end	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Boy	O
:	O
came	O
Riding	O
with	O
full	O
speed	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Deceased	O
went	O
aside	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
so	O
happened	O
that	O
the	O
Horse	O
being	O
unruly	O
,	O
and	O
too	O
strong	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
beat	O
down	O
the	O
Deceased	O
to	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
falling	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
gave	O
the	O
Wound	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
offered	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Horse	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
design	O
of	O
hurt	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
possibly	O
stop	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
very	O
sorry	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wooly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
.	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
Two	O
Flanders	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Cravats	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
One	O
pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
Sleeves	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
One	O
Shirt	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
One	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Twillit	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
One	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
s.	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
small	O
value	O
,	O
from	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Boswell	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Boswell	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Lodging	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
house	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
missing	O
and	O
making	O
Enquiry	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
(	O
forasmuch	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
absented	O
herself	O
)	O
Apprehended	O
her	O
and	O
had	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
restored	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
as	O
good	O
as	O
Confess	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
Poverty	O
that	O
constrained	O
her	O
to	O
Commit	O
that	O
wicked	O
Act	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
So	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elias	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
Armer	I-pers
of	O
the	O
same	O
Parish	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Armer	O
himself	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
his	O
Horse	O
used	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
St.	B-place
Georges	I-place
Fields	I-place
to	O
Feed	O
,	O
and	O
missing	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
exposed	O
to	O
Sale	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
person	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
owned	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
the	O
Horse	O
of	O
one	O
Phillip	O
Stanes	O
who	O
owed	O
him	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
over-took	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Horse	O
going	O
to	O
Chelmsford	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
offered	O
the	O
Horse	O
to	O
Sale	O
to	O
an	O
Inn-keeper	O
at	O
Rumford	O
,	O
but	O
refused	O
(	O
or	O
was	O
shie	O
)	O
to	O
Tole	O
for	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
pursued	O
be	O
fled	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
aggravating	O
Circumstances	O
:	O
And	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
give	O
a	O
good	O
Account	O
of	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ambrose	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
Two	O
silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
19	O
s.	O
Two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
One	O
silver	O
Caudle	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
Forty	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cambrick	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
The	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Fairclor	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Fairclor	O
;	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
pawned	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Spoons	O
at	O
a	O
Brokers	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
fetched	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
pawn	O
:	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
owning	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Spoon	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
Evidence	O
enough	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
other	O
Goods	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
the	O
Fact	O
but	O
being	O
found	O
in	O
several	O
Storys	O
,	O
as	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Spoon	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
no	O
good	O
Evidence	O
on	O
his	O
side	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Wakeham	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	B-place
St.	I-place
Catherines	I-place
Cree-Church	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
One	O
Stuff-Gown	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
One	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
One	O
pair	O
of	O
BuckSkin	O
Gloves	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
One	O
little	O
Box	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
d.	O
and	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
.	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Kitchenham	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Kitchenham	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
under	O
pretence	O
to	O
Drink	O
with	O
him	O
from	O
an	O
Acquaintance	O
of	O
his	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
and	O
sitting	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
(	O
it	O
being	O
a	O
Publick	O
house	O
)	O
after	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
,	O
another	O
Man	O
and	O
Woman	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
Chamber	O
to	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
some	O
time	O
went	O
away	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
keeping	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
in	O
a	O
Story	O
till	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
the	O
Woman	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
missing	O
her	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Apprehended	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
thither	O
upon	O
no	O
other	O
account	O
but	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Robery	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
good	O
Repute	O
formerly	O
at	O
St.	O
Albans	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
actually	O
concerned	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Ester	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Undershaft	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
entering	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mr.	O
William	B-pers
Salsbury	I-pers
,	O
at	O
Barkin	B-place
in	I-place
Essex	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
.	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
stealing	O
from	O
him	O
One	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
One	O
siver	O
Salt	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
with	O
several	O
silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
One	O
Scarf	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
besides	O
other	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
of	O
good	O
value	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Salsbury	O
and	O
his	O
Maid	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
Apprehended	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
owned	O
to	O
have	O
stoled	O
the	O
Plate	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
induced	O
to	O
it	O
by	O
another	O
Maid	O
in	O
the	O
Town	O
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
it	O
the	O
rather	O
to	O
raise	O
her	O
self	O
a	O
Portion	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
in	O
Election	O
to	O
be	O
Married	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
offering	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
Sale	O
or	O
Exchange	O
in	O
a	O
Goldsmiths	O
Shop	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Salsburys	O
Maid	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
left	O
the	O
Plate	O
below	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
forgetting	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Doors	O
and	O
Windows	O
were	O
all	O
Fast	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
she	O
missed	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
window	O
open	O
;	O
the	O
Plate	O
being	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
owned	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Plate	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
confirmed	O
by	O
the	O
Maid	O
who	O
was	O
wont	O
to	O
keep	O
it	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
denyed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
given	O
her	O
by	O
another	O
person	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
out	O
weighing	O
hers	O
,	O
(	O
she	O
having	O
none	O
material	O
on	O
her	O
side	O
)	O
she	O
was	O
after	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
,	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
Anne	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Haynes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
One	O
Chirurgeons	O
Box	O
of	O
Instruments	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
.	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
Francis	B-pers
Osborn	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
prisoners	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
prosecutors	O
Shop	O
,	O
to	O
Buy	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
Clapses	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
working	O
silversmith	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Servant	O
being	O
at	O
work	O
upon	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
laid	O
it	O
by	O
,	O
whilst	O
he	O
look	O
'd	O
them	O
the	O
Clapses	O
and	O
immediately	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
the	O
Box	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
pursued	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
no	O
Box	O
about	O
them	O
,	O
forasmuch	O
as	O
they	O
had	O
Conveyed	O
away	O
the	O
Box	O
;	O
or	O
something	O
like	O
it	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
Fourth	O
persons	O
Hand	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
as	O
was	O
Evidenced	O
by	O
another	O
person	O
on	O
the	O
prosecutors	O
side	O
:	O
The	O
prisoners	O
denyed	O
that	O
they	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
to	O
Buy	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Clapse	O
only	O
:	O
And	O
altho	O
'	O
they	O
were	O
be	O
persons	O
of	O
bad	O
Lives	O
,	O
giving	O
a	O
very	O
slender	O
Account	O
of	O
their	O
Reputation	O
,	O
yet	O
the	O
Matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
Three	O
found	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
,	O
Martha	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Gold	O
Chain	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Golden	O
Locket	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
.	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Travell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
parish	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Travell	O
himself	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
in	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
to	O
offer	O
Cucumbers	O
to	O
Sale	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Morrow	O
Morning	O
he	O
missed	O
his	O
Chain	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
alledged	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
came	O
with	O
no	O
other	O
intent	O
but	O
to	O
sell	O
their	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
having	O
no	O
Evidence	O
besides	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
swear	O
possitively	O
against	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
looking	O
upon	O
it	O
as	O
a	O
kind	O
of	O
a	O
Malicious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Chelynor	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Three	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Neckcloaths	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
Two	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Quoives	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
One	O
single	O
Sleeve	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
The	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Giles	I-pers
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Giles	O
himself	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
Shop	O
in	O
Bartholomew	B-place
Fair	I-place
,	O
to	O
cheapen	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
imediately	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
he	O
missed	O
his	O
afore-said	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
Apprehended	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
satisfaction	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
purpose	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
alledged	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
afore-said	O
Fair	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
person	O
that	O
kept	O
a	O
publick	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
he	O
went	O
by	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Consent	O
,	O
to	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Cock	O
in	O
Birchin	O
Lane	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
on	O
his	O
side	O
,	O
to	O
satisfie	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
his	O
Behaviour	O
in	O
his	O
former	O
Service	O
which	O
were	O
known	O
in	O
Court	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gibs	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
uttering	O
and	O
delivering	O
a	O
false	O
piece	O
of	O
Mony	O
,	O
called	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
21	O
s.	O
6	O
l	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
.	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
to	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Magdalens	I-place
de	I-place
Malthea	I-place
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
(	O
it	O
being	O
a	O
Tavern	O
)	O
and	O
offered	O
the	O
Guinea	O
to	O
be	O
exchanged	O
to	O
pay	O
his	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
alledging	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
other	O
Money	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
one	O
crackt	O
Sixpence	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Birmingham	O
Groat	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
he	O
owned	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
other	O
Money	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
him	O
the	O
more	O
suspected	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
person	O
of	O
no	O
good	O
Fame	O
:	O
The	O
Guinea	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
and	O
Cut	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
mixt	O
Mettal	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
so	O
bad	O
but	O
any	O
person	O
might	O
have	O
taken	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
good	O
piece	O
,	O
so	O
upon	O
full	O
hearing	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Naylor	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolphs	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
High	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
speaking	O
Scandalous	O
and	O
Seditious	O
Words	O
against	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
Government	O
,	O
to	O
one	O
William	O
Frances	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
,	O
That	O
if	O
any	O
Man	O
in	O
England	O
(	O
or	O
the	O
King	O
himself	O
)	O
should	O
call	O
James	O
Duke	O
of	O
Monmouth	O
a	O
Traytor	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
affirm	O
to	O
his	O
Face	O
that	O
be	O
lyed	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
the	O
Trained	O
Bands	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
were	O
all	O
Rogues	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
would	O
shew	O
;	O
themselves	O
such	O
brave	O
Souldiers	O
as	O
Monmouth	O
had	O
done	O
.	O
All	O
which	O
,	O
was	O
Corroberated	O
and	O
confirmed	O
by	O
William	B-pers
Frances	I-pers
and	O
another	O
person	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
possitively	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
speak	O
the	O
very	O
same	O
Words	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Defence	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
remember	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
any	O
such	O
words	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
owed	O
him	O
a	O
Grudge	O
:	O
But	O
this	O
not	O
prevailing	O
with	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
so	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
a	O
High	O
Misdemeanour	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Lawrence	I-place
Jury	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
stealing	O
one	O
piece	O
of	O
Dyed	O
Serge	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hyde	I-pers
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
upon	O
his	O
Arraignment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
A	O
Woman	B-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Four	O
pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
.	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
past	O
,	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Bonnyface	I-pers
of	O
the	O
same	O
Parish	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
said	O
Bonnyface	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Charing	O
Cross	O
he	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
Tavern	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
stayed	O
there	O
to	O
Drink	O
but	O
one	O
pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
parted	O
from	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
aftermissed	O
his	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
Defence	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
prosecutors	O
Company	O
as	O
afore-said	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
hand	O
of	O
Robbing	O
him	O
of	O
his	O
Gold	O
afore-said	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
having	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
of	O
good	O
account	O
on	O
her	O
side	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
person	O
whose	O
Original	O
was	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
meanest	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
having	O
no	O
Evidence	O
besides	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
against	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Collwell	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Boy	O
about	O
14	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
8	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
from	O
another	B-pers
person	I-pers
,	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
John	B-pers
Raven	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Fellow	O
about	O
Seventeen	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Rape	O
,	O
Committed	O
upon	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Katt	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Child	O
aged	O
Eight	O
Years	O
and	O
Three	O
Weeks	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
prisoner	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Girl	O
being	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Stables	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Horse-keeper	O
,	O
to	O
leade	O
a	O
Horse	O
thither	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
got	O
the	O
Child	O
into	O
the	O
Stable	O
,	O
being	O
alone	O
,	O
and	O
shut	O
the	O
Door	O
fast	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
and	O
used	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
most	O
Barbarous	O
Manner	O
,	O
stopping	O
her	O
Mouth	O
as	O
she	O
cryed	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
Midwife	O
and	O
other	O
Women	O
that	O
searched	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
Rent	O
in	O
her	O
Secret	O
parts	O
,	O
and	O
doubted	O
whether	O
ever	O
she	O
would	O
be	O
well	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
being	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
deny	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
so	O
Odious	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Halford	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
from	O
Mark	B-pers
Speed	I-pers
,	O
but	O
no	O
prosecutor	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
Sunderland	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
Queen	I-place
Hieth	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
11	O
l.	O
and	O
One	O
silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
17	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
:	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
Stoke	B-place
Newington	I-place
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
who	O
was	O
Convicted	O
and	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
last	O
Sessions	O
for	O
Felony	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Dun	O
Gelding	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
.	O
August	O
from	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Kidhey	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Horse	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
being	O
exposed	O
to	O
Sale	O
by	O
another	O
person	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoners	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
making	O
search	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
immediatly	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
taken	O
into	O
custody	O
in	O
another	O
place	O
:	O
The	O
prisoner	O
could	O
say	O
little	O
or	O
nothing	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
only	O
that	O
his	O
Mother	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
Mother	O
being	O
sent	O
to	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
Apprehended	O
,	O
it	O
proved	O
false	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
so	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Husbands	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michales	I-place
Wood	I-place
street	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
.	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
for	O
Coining	O
and	O
Counterfeiting	O
Thirty	O
pieces	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
called	O
King	O
Charles	O
the	O
Seconds	O
Half	O
Crowns	O
,	O
made	O
of	O
Copper	O
Tin	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
false	O
Mettals	O
.	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
prisoners	O
Chamber	O
in	O
a	O
Trunk	O
,	O
several	O
sorts	O
of	O
Instruments	O
fit	O
for	O
Coining	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
pieces	O
of	O
Coined	O
Money	O
,	O
false	O
Mettals	O
,	O
all	O
which	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
put	O
off	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
that	O
wanted	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Weight	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
by	O
several	O
Names	O
;	O
sometimes	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Brown	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
by	O
Husbands	O
:	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
denyed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
left	O
at	O
his	O
Lodging	O
,	O
made	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Bundle	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
into	O
his	O
Trunk	O
(	O
it	O
being	O
open	O
)	O
by	O
another	O
person	O
,	O
who	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
leave	O
it	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
soon	O
after	O
call	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
therefore	O
the	O
prisoner	O
infarred	O
from	O
this	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
trick	O
put	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
possitively	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
only	O
was	O
to	O
find	O
Securitys	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
for	O
the	O
Future	O
.	O
An	O
Inhabitant	B-pers
of	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
likewise	O
,	O
in	O
inventing	O
,	O
Forging	O
,	O
Counterfeiting	O
and	O
Coining	O
,	O
Twenty	O
pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
called	O
Guinea	O
pieces	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
.	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
prisoner	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
one	O
V.	O
weere	O
Confederats	O
together	O
in	O
this	O
wicked	O
Act	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
had	O
once	O
made	O
Tryal	O
of	O
his	O
Art	O
in	O
Pewter	O
at	O
the	O
prosecutors	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
bring	O
it	O
to	O
any	O
perfection	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
at	O
only	O
for	O
his	O
Diversion	O
,	O
imitating	O
a	O
French-man	O
,	O
that	O
had	O
Coined	O
some	O
Guineas	O
after	O
the	O
same	O
manner	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
afore	O
said	O
V.	O
hired	O
a	O
House	O
at	O
Hogsden	B-place
fit	O
for	O
their	O
purpose	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
set	O
up	O
their	O
Trade	O
,	O
several	O
Tools	O
being	O
found	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Stamps	O
to	O
Coin	O
Lovis	O
d'Or	O
's	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Instruments	O
fit	O
for	O
the	O
work	O
:	O
The	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
tryed	O
to	O
Coin	O
with	O
Pewter	O
as	O
afore-said	O
for	O
Diversion	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
like	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
was	O
concerned	O
in	O
Coining	O
any	O
manner	O
of	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
several	O
credible	O
Witnesses	O
on	O
his	O
part	O
,	O
who	O
satisfied	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
always	O
a	O
very	O
civil	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
fair	O
dealer	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
received	O
Money	O
of	O
him	O
often-times	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
any	O
bad	O
or	O
suspicious	O
:	O
And	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
prisoner	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
plainly	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
Coin	O
those	O
Guineas	O
afore-said	O
.	O
After	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
An	O
inhabitant	B-pers
of	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
making	O
an	O
Assault	O
upon	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
B.	B-pers
R	I-pers
.	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
1685.	O
by	O
blowing	O
Powder	O
of	O
Mercury	O
into	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
which	O
caused	O
his	O
Right	O
Eye	O
to	O
consume	O
and	O
wast	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
5th	O
.	O
of	O
April	O
following	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
was	O
totally	O
consumed	O
and	O
lost	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
Mr.	O
R.	O
and	O
several	O
others	O
and	O
after	O
Mr.	O
R.	O
Council	O
had	O
opened	O
the	O
Cause	O
at	O
large	O
,	O
very	O
distinctly	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
Mr.	O
R.	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
wont	O
to	O
frequent	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
more	O
than	O
was	O
convenient	O
in	O
his	O
absence	O
,	O
which	O
occasioned	O
various	O
Discourses	O
,	O
and	O
Scandalous	O
Reports	O
amongst	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
,	O
touching	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Ladys	O
Reputation	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
forbid	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
frequenting	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
come	O
no	O
more	O
to	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
absented	O
himself	O
about	O
a	O
Month	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
came	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
about	O
Four	O
or	O
Five	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
enquired	O
for	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
at	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
time	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
home	O
that	O
Night	O
:	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
coming	O
home	O
about	O
Nine	O
or	O
Ten	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
coming	O
near	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
Door	O
,	O
observed	O
two	O
Men	O
to	O
go	O
softly	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
over	O
against	O
his	O
own	O
Door	O
,	O
(	O
by	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
a	O
Light	O
)	O
saw	O
a	O
person	O
stand	O
,	O
who	O
immediatly	O
made	O
towards	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
the	O
Powder	O
into	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
affirmed	O
upon	O
Oath	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
immediatly	O
after	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
Cure	O
his	O
Eyes	O
(	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Chymical	O
Doctor	O
,	O
on	O
purpose	O
to	O
strengthen	O
his	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
trembled	O
when	O
he	O
first	O
dressed	O
his	O
Eyes	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
observed	O
to	O
change	O
his	O
Countenance	O
,	O
which	O
occasioned	O
Suspicion	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
did	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
him	O
several	O
times	O
after	O
till	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
Evidence	O
sufficient	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
discharged	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
others	O
:	O
The	O
prisoner	O
sending	O
the	O
prosecutors	O
Man	O
to	O
his	O
Laboratory	O
for	O
a	O
Mortar	O
to	O
beat	O
some	O
Medicine	O
in	O
for	O
his	O
Eyes	O
,	O
found	O
one	O
with	O
Powder	O
in	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
compared	O
with	O
the	O
Powder	O
that	O
hung	O
in	O
the	O
prosecutors	O
Perriwig	O
was	O
exactly	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
both	O
for	O
Colour	O
and	O
Taste	O
,	O
Blistering	O
the	O
Tongue	O
of	O
them	O
that	O
tasted	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
after	O
this	O
fled	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
with	O
many	O
other	O
agreeing	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
The	O
prisoner	O
argued	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
another	O
place	O
when	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
on	O
his	O
side	O
,	O
all	O
which	O
,	O
prevailed	O
nothing	O
on	O
his	O
part	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
prisoner	O
outweighing	O
his	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
after	O
a	O
very	O
long	O
hearing	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
,	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Toslyn	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
of	O
Coach	O
Seats	O
,	O
One	O
Feather-Seat	O
with	O
a	O
Cloath	O
Cover	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
from	O
Valentine	B-pers
Crosbey	I-pers
,	O
Two	O
other	O
Coach	O
Seats	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
Two	O
other	O
Seats	O
of	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Phips	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
.	O
of	O
July	O
.	O
Edward	O
Phips	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Seats	O
of	O
his	O
Coach	O
made	O
into	O
a	O
Wastcoat	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Two	O
deposed	O
that	O
they	O
found	O
their	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Hands	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
:	O
whereupon	O
they	O
took	O
them	O
upon	O
Suspition	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
they	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Coach	O
Seats	O
being	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
full	O
Evidence	O
being	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
having	O
been	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
Idle	O
Fellows	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
Material	O
in	O
Defence	O
of	O
themselves	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
Drunk	O
when	O
they	O
did	O
the	O
Facts	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
after	O
a	O
distinct	O
hearing	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
three	O
afore-mentioned	O
Indictments	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Wells	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Edmunton	B-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
One	O
Callico	O
Neckcloath	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
Three	O
Holland	O
Quoives	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
past	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Spung	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
was	O
John	B-pers
Spung	I-pers
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
absent	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Goods	O
in	O
her	O
Custody	O
,	O
yet	O
she	O
threw	O
some	O
out	O
at	O
a	O
Window	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Witness	O
appearing	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
full	O
quantity	O
lost	O
not	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolphs	I-place
,	I-place
without	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
twice	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
.	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
One	O
Silk	O
Mantua	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
One	O
Silk	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
One	O
other	O
Silk	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
One	O
other	O
Silk	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
One	O
Scarf	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
Two	O
Silk	O
Hoods	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
Two	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
One	O
pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
Sleeves	O
Lac	O
'd	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
One	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
One	O
Silk	O
Scarf	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
One	O
Book	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
d.	O
Fifteen	O
pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
l.	O
Four	O
pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
called	O
King	O
Charles	O
the	O
Firsts	O
Ten	O
Shilling	O
pieces	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
The	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Carnall	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
.	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
One	O
Mantua	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
One	O
pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Stays	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
One	O
pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Sleeves	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Justin	B-pers
Trevary	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutors	O
proved	O
by	O
good	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
pieces	O
in	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
and	O
some	O
Linnen	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
they	O
never	O
had	O
all	O
the	O
Goods	O
again	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
a	O
small	O
Defence	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
stolen	O
by	O
another	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
that	O
person	O
drawed	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
Felonys	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
having	O
no	O
Witnesses	O
Material	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Felonys	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Deale	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Two	O
Dowlas	O
Smocks	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
Three	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
One	O
Flaxen	O
Napkin	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Arthur	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
.	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
past	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Jones	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
the	O
afore-said	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
them	O
and	O
no	O
possitive	O
Evidence	O
further	O
appearing	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
immediatly	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stitchbury	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pancrass	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Jesias	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
Four	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Diaper	O
Napkins	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
Six	O
Diaper	O
Table	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
Three	O
Cravats	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
Two	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Quoives	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
was	O
one	O
Martha	B-pers
Edin	I-pers
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
wore	O
a	O
Smock	O
of	O
the	O
Lodgers	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
being	O
missing	O
she	O
laid	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
And	O
that	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
other	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
besides	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
several	O
very	O
good	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
her	O
Honesty	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
never	O
being	O
taxed	O
before	O
in	O
any	O
Crime	O
of	O
the	O
like	O
Nature	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Humphrey	B-pers
Payton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
intending	O
to	O
Rob	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Susannah	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
.	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
broken	O
open	O
about	O
Twelve	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
come	O
out	O
at	O
a	O
Window	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
immediatly	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
confessed	O
that	O
himself	O
and	O
two	O
other	O
persons	O
had	O
intelligence	O
of	O
100	O
l	O
or	O
200	O
l.	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
further	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
drawn	O
in	O
by	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
persons	O
(	O
who	O
are	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
who	O
forced	O
him	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
using	O
many	O
such	O
like	O
Evasions	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
no	O
Witnesses	O
:	O
and	O
the	O
Matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
being	O
so	O
plainly	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Glasborrow	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Two	O
Cloath	O
Livery	O
Coats	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Lowther	I-pers
.	O
One	O
Cloath	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
One	O
Caster	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Coats	O
were	O
sold	O
to	O
a	O
Woman	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
found	O
hanging	O
,	O
up	O
in	O
Barbican	O
in	O
a	O
Sale-Shop	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
that	O
Bought	O
the	O
Coats	O
,	O
proved	O
that	O
Glassborrow	O
Received	O
the	O
Money	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
viz	O
16	O
s.	O
But	O
Arnold	O
said	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
:	O
and	O
although	O
the	O
prisoners	O
denyed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
yet	O
being	O
Idle	O
Follows	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
been	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
Glassborrow	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
Arnold	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Feversham	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Three	O
Holland	O
Smocks	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
One	O
Holland	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
One	O
Silk	O
Mantua	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
and	O
Two	O
pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
Drawers	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
On	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
one	O
Martha	B-pers
Jeeve	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
pawned	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
very	O
poor	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
another	O
person	O
was	O
suspected	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
Confederacy	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
not	O
denying	O
the	O
Matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
alledging	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
poverty	O
that	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
Commit	O
that	O
Crime	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Humphreys	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Alexander	B-pers
Wiggington	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
of	B-place
St.	I-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Two	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
53	O
s	O
and	O
9	O
d.	O
and	O
30	O
l.	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
3	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
day	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
past	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Mrs.	O
Smith	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
prisoners	O
and	O
one	O
Richard	B-pers
Floyd	I-pers
(	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
sell	O
her	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
taking	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Trunck	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
:	O
The	O
prisoners	O
observed	O
her	O
to	O
have	O
pretty	O
good	O
store	O
came	O
about	O
a	O
Week	O
after	O
all	O
three	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
some	O
disturbance	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
time	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
being	O
alone	O
,	O
and	O
Floyd	O
got	O
into	O
her	O
Chamber	O
where	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
came	O
thither	O
with	O
no	O
other	O
intent	O
but	O
to	O
get	O
Money	O
that	O
was	O
owing	O
to	O
them	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
other	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
besides	O
them	O
and	O
the	O
prisoners	O
produced	O
several	O
good	O
sufficient	O
House-keepers	O
to	O
testifie	O
their	O
manner	O
of	O
Life	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
honesty	O
and	O
good	O
Credit	O
;	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
kept	O
a	O
very	O
Naughty	O
and	O
Suspitious	O
House	O
(	O
no	O
less	O
than	O
a	O
Baudy	O
House	O
)	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
would	O
once	O
fain	O
have	O
withdrawn	O
her	O
prosecution	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
other	O
aggravating	O
Circumstances	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
after	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
,	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Payton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Holland	O
Smock	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
One	O
Bone	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Quoif	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
One	O
pair	O
of	O
Thred	O
Gloves	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
One	O
Callyco	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
August	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Gun	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
absent	O
from	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
leaving	O
no	O
one	O
there	O
but	O
one	O
MaidServant	O
only	O
,	O
at	O
her	O
return	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
afore-said	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
several	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
found	O
about	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
Lent	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
camp	O
on	O
Hounslow-Heath	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
proving	O
the	O
same	O
by	O
Good	O
Evidence	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Thornton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
Chypenham	B-place
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
absenting	O
himself	O
from	O
his	O
Majestys	O
Service	O
,	O
without	O
leave	O
or	O
Licence	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
.	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
past	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
Council	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
had	O
opened	O
the	O
Cause	O
against	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
entertained	O
in	O
Hull	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Earl	O
of	O
Huntingdons	O
Regiment	O
,	O
under	O
Command	O
of	O
Capt	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
Received	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
pay	O
and	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
space	O
of	O
Two	O
Months	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
Barnet	O
he	O
Received	O
New	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
his	O
Duty	O
as	O
the	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
Souldier	O
,	O
but	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
.	O
June	O
did	O
forsake	O
his	O
said	O
Service	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
from	O
his	O
Majestys	O
Camp	O
on	O
Hounslow-Heath	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
after	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
Bridewell	O
Committed	O
as	O
a	O
Vagabond	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
truly	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Souldier	O
,	O
and	O
Received	O
pay	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
with	O
an	O
intentent	O
to	O
return	O
,	O
not	O
being	O
sensible	O
of	O
the	O
Danger	O
of	O
Running	O
away	O
from	O
his	O
Colours	O
;	O
and	O
falling	O
into	O
ill	O
Company	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
his	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
his	O
Sword	O
in	O
the	O
camp	O
in	O
his	O
Tent	O
;	O
so	O
upon	O
a	O
very	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Judges	O
giving	O
in	O
their	O
Opinions	O
(	O
Nemine	O
Contradicente	O
)	O
that	O
he	O
ought	O
to	O
Dye	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
.	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
One	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s	O
One	O
Silk	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
One	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Cornet	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
One	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Quoife	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
One	O
Girdle	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
Two	O
Cambrick	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
One	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
Buckles	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
One	O
Set	O
of	O
Buttons	O
for	O
Sleeves	O
and	O
Three	O
Flaxen	O
Smocks	O
value	O
8	O
s	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Jones	O
and	O
others	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
Lodge	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
being	O
abroad	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
;	O
at	O
their	O
return	O
mist	O
their	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
new	O
Lodger	O
also	O
,	O
the	O
Door	O
being	O
found	O
open	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
about	O
4	O
a	O
Clock	O
by	O
the	O
Watch	O
;	O
And	O
searching	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
found	O
her	O
at	O
Colebrook	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
denyed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
produced	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
on	O
her	O
side	O
,	O
which	O
availed	O
but	O
little	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
a	O
person	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
Character	O
:	O
yet	O
the	O
matter	O
being	O
not	O
positively	O
proved	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
only	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Crispe	I-pers
of	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
Guineas	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
9	O
s.	O
and	O
16	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Abigail	B-pers
Elnecke	I-pers
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
she	O
Lodging	O
together	O
,	O
left	O
her	O
alone	O
one	O
day	O
in	O
her	O
Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Trunk	O
open	O
upon	O
her	O
return	O
found	O
her	O
Money	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
absented	O
the	O
Lodging	O
for	O
3	O
days	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
be	O
silent	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
make	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
satisfaction	O
The	O
prisoner	O
denyed	O
denyed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
key	O
to	O
the	O
Chamber	O
Door	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
toucht	O
her	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
maliciously	O
accused	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
full	O
enough	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
driving	O
the	O
Wheele	O
of	O
a	O
Cart	O
over	O
one	O
Margaret	B-pers
Kempson	I-pers
s	O
Neck	O
,	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
.	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
giving	O
her	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Bruise	O
whereon	O
she	O
instantly	O
Dyed	O
:	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
possitive	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
wilfully	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
alledging	O
it	O
was	O
late	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Child	O
being	O
on	O
the	O
Top	O
of	O
the	O
Cart	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
for	O
great	O
a	O
misfortune	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
only	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Baptist	I-pers
have	O
been	O
Convicted	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Manslaughter	O
,	O
was	O
likewise	O
Acquitted	O
by	O
Proclamation	O
in	O
Court	O
by	O
virtue	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
most	O
Gracious	O
Pardon	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
Eleven	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Stanly	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Deane	I-pers
,	O
Esther	B-pers
Sympson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Raven	I-pers
,	O
Elias	O
Smith	O
J.	O
S.	O
Samuel	O
Watkins	O
,	O
Edward	O
Thornton	O
,	O
Elianor	O
Jones	O
,	O
Humphrey	B-pers
Payton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wall	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
Convicted	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
Running	O
away	O
from	O
his	O
Colours	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Sentence	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Order	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
Five	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
R.	O
H.	O
William	O
,	O
Edwards	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
Richard	O
Hutchin	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
.	O
Order	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
Two	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
and	O
William	O
Jones	O
Order	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Whip	O
'd	O
Six	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wolly	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Glasborrow	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Feversham	I-pers
,	O
Tho	O
Johnson	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ambrose	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
Eleven	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Stanly	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Deane	I-pers
,	O
Esther	B-pers
Sympson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Raven	I-pers
,	O
Elias	O
Smith	O
J.	O
S.	O
Samuel	O
Watkins	O
,	O
Edward	O
Thornton	O
,	O
Elianor	O
Jones	O
,	O
Humphrey	B-pers
Payton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wall	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
Convicted	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
Running	O
away	O
from	O
his	O
Colours	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Stanly	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
pleading	O
their	O
Bellys	O
,	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
matrons	O
were	O
impannell	O
'd	O
,	O
who	O
search	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
in	O
Verdict	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
quick	O
with	O
Child	O
.	O
The	O
Judgment	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Naylour	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Deferred	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
