TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
And	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
at	O
Justice	O
Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
,	O
The	O
1st	O
.	O
2d	O
.	O
and	O
4th	O
.	O
of	O
July	O
;	O
1687	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
3d	O
.	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Reign	O
.	O
AT	O
the	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
;	O
Held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
on	O
Friday	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
the	O
1st	O
.	O
2d	O
.	O
and	O
4th	O
Days	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
1687	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Peake	I-pers
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
.	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Tate	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
with	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
London	O
and	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
Stephen	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Learner	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Acton	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
William	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
Simon	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
Abraham	B-pers
Hemingway	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Cows	I-pers
Simon	B-pers
Linc	I-pers
Abraham	B-pers
Trunket	I-pers
William	B-pers
Hayward	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Merrydale	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Woodman	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Tew	I-pers
William	B-pers
Wheatly	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Broomfield	I-pers
Edmund	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
John	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
John	B-pers
Preston	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Hains	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
follow	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
An	O
Indictment	O
being	O
preferred	O
against	O
John	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Ward	I-place
of	I-place
Farrandine	I-place
without	I-place
,	O
for	O
Stealing	O
11	O
l.	O
3	O
s.	O
from	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hillardon	I-pers
the	O
First	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
he	O
upon	O
his	O
Arraignment	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
Bono	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
Bone	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
House	O
with	O
an	O
other	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
the	O
Tankard	O
delivered	O
to	O
him	O
with	O
drink	O
;	O
found	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
pleading	O
Innocence	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Tankard	O
no	O
where	O
found	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
in	O
consideration	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
might	O
be	O
mistaken	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Haines	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Stealing	O
an	O
Alamode	O
Hood	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
from	O
Sarah	B-pers
Barret	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolphs	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
in	O
the	O
company	O
of	O
one	O
Sarah	B-pers
Green	I-pers
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
cheapening	O
the	O
Hood	O
though	O
at	O
an	O
under	O
rate	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
opportunity	O
to	O
convey	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
Ann	B-pers
Bunts	I-pers
who	O
stood	O
without	O
to	O
expect	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
having	O
nothing	O
material	O
to	O
offer	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
behalf	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Tomson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Stuff-Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Peck	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
Legrand	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
.	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
:	O
Upon	O
whose	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Petticoat	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
her	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
coming	O
to	O
buy	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Five	B-pers
Persons	I-pers
were	O
tryed	O
for	O
Murthering	O
Francis	B-pers
Ellet	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Tedington	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
.	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
for	O
Drink	O
,	O
they	O
created	O
a	O
Disturbance	O
about	O
paying	O
their	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
drew	O
their	O
swords	O
offering	O
to	O
Kill	O
and	O
Wound	O
all	O
that	O
stood	O
in	O
their	O
way	O
,	O
when	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Deceased	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
and	O
supposing	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
assistance	O
of	O
the	O
Man	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
provocation	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Morral	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
Left	O
side	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Breadth	O
of	O
an	O
Inch	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
Six	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
within	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
he	O
Dyed	O
and	O
they	O
having	O
nothing	O
material	O
to	O
offer	O
in	O
their	O
own	O
defence	O
,	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Wilful	O
Murther	O
.	O
One	O
Green	B-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
,	O
the	O
First	O
for	O
Murther	O
at	O
Common-Law	O
,	O
the	O
Second	O
upon	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
Stabing	O
,	O
for	O
Killing	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
and	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Moss	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
.	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
them	O
divers	O
Mortal	O
Wounds	O
with	O
his	O
Baionet	O
or	O
Sword	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
in	O
the	O
Company	O
of	O
divers	O
persons	O
,	O
knocking	O
at	O
his	O
door	O
at	O
an	O
unseasonable	O
time	O
for	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
gaining	O
Admittance	O
,	O
offered	O
some	O
Rudeness	O
by	O
breaking	O
the	O
Windows	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
whereupon	O
he	O
set	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
pursuit	O
,	O
gave	O
the	O
Deceased	O
the	O
Wounds	O
of	O
which	O
they	O
dyed	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
pleading	O
they	O
not	O
only	O
assaulted	O
his	O
house	O
but	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
defence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
only	O
at	O
Common-Law	O
,	O
and	O
Acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
upon	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
Stabing	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Four	B-pers
Persons	I-pers
were	O
tryed	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
Kings	O
pay	O
,	O
and	O
afterward	O
deserting	O
their	O
Colours	O
at	O
Plimouth	O
and	O
other	O
places	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
again	O
entered	O
into	O
the	O
Service	O
,	O
though	O
in	O
other	O
Companys	O
,	O
they	O
being	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
Camp	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
directed	O
the	O
Jury	O
to	O
Acquit	O
them	O
,	O
yet	O
ordered	O
that	O
they	O
should	O
be	O
returned	O
to	O
their	O
Captains	O
whom	O
they	O
deserted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
wastryed	O
for	O
firing	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Keck	I-pers
,	O
with	O
whom	O
she	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
Nature	O
of	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
June	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
nothing	O
appearing	O
but	O
that	O
it	O
happened	O
accidentally	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
in	O
Bed	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
its	O
breaking	O
out	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Pollard	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
Killing	O
James	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	O
.	O
Brides	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
Right	O
Breast	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
:	O
The	O
proof	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
three	O
other	O
persons	O
,	O
having	O
drank	O
hard	O
all	O
Night	O
at	O
the	O
Swan	B-place
Tavern	I-place
in	I-place
Fleet	I-place
street	I-place
,	O
went	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
to	O
play	O
at	O
Dice	O
in	O
the	O
paved	O
Alley	O
behind	O
the	O
said	O
Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
some	O
words	O
arising	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
felt	O
to	O
quarrelling	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
some	O
passes	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
unfortunately	O
received	O
his	O
Deaths	O
Wound	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Malice	O
being	O
proved	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Plumber	I-pers
and	O
G	B-pers
-	I-pers
O	I-pers
-	I-pers
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
from	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Brag	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
their	O
Arraignment	O
the	O
former	O
pleading	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
latter	O
putting	O
himself	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
that	O
He	O
comeing	O
with	O
Plumber	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
they	O
both	O
found	O
means	O
to	O
march	O
off	O
with	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
pursued	O
were	O
taken	O
;	O
his	O
plea	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
of	O
his	O
Fellows	O
intent	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
perceived	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
crying	O
out	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
yet	O
being	O
no	O
ways	O
able	O
to	O
give	O
any	O
good	O
account	O
of	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
a	O
Pettilarcenary	O
.	O
[	O
Plumber	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
G	O
-	O
O	O
-	O
:	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Jaxon	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
Killing	O
his	O
Wife	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jaxon	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
her	O
a	O
Kick	O
on	O
the	O
Belly	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
languished	O
from	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
January	O
to	O
the	O
4th	O
.	O
of	O
September	O
and	O
then	O
dyed	O
:	O
but	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
that	O
she	O
dyed	O
of	O
that	O
Bruise	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
recovered	O
of	O
the	O
Grief	O
it	O
occasioned	O
,	O
long	O
before	O
she	O
deceased	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
,	O
together	O
with	O
James	B-pers
Felton	I-pers
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Serge	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
Cloath	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
a	O
Pillowbeer	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Kensie	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
against	O
Philips	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
Sold	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Goods	O
supposed	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
possitive	O
proof	O
being	O
made	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
Goods	O
seen	O
after	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bond-Bavin	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
from	O
Michael	B-pers
Steevens	I-pers
of	O
Allhollows	B-place
Barkin	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
proved	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
yet	O
only	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Eley	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Mare	O
and	O
Colt	O
value	O
14	O
l.	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
Norman	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
against	O
whom	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
Toled	O
and	O
Sold	O
the	O
Mare	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
to	O
one	O
Ingram	O
for	O
four	O
pounds	O
,	O
in	O
whose	O
hands	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
her	O
of	O
one	O
Barton	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
proof	O
being	O
plain	O
by	O
his	O
former	O
confession	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
her	O
felloniously	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Grounds	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
F	I-pers
-	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wier	I-pers
of	O
Lumbard	B-place
Street	I-place
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
proof	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
with	O
another	O
person	O
to	O
Buy	O
a	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
Glass	O
was	O
opened	O
,	O
found	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
clap	O
in	O
a	O
brass	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
out	O
a	O
Gold	O
one	O
:	O
but	O
he	O
pleading	O
ignorance	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
positive	O
proof	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
Killing	O
Robert	B-pers
Travel	I-pers
at	O
the	O
Royal-Exchange	B-place
in	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
.	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
Shooting	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Breast	O
with	O
a	O
Musquet	O
Bullet	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
set	O
a	O
Sentinal	O
upon	O
the	O
Trained	O
Bands	O
,	O
and	O
Travel	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
then	O
upon	O
the	O
Gaurd	O
,	O
pressing	O
towards	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
fited	O
his	O
Musquet	O
,	O
and	O
Shot	O
him	O
dead	O
upon	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
intent	O
to	O
fire	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
his	O
Musquet	O
went	O
off	O
by	O
Misfortune	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Listed	O
Trained-Bandman	O
,	O
but	O
served	O
in	O
anothers	O
stead	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bourrus	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Criplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
Shooes	O
from	O
George	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
;	O
the	O
proof	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
to	O
cheapen	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shooes	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
agreeing	O
upon	O
the	O
price	O
,	O
Two	O
pair	O
of	O
Shooes	O
upon	O
their	O
departure	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
pursuit	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
Basket	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
upon	O
her	O
Arm	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
not	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
a	O
Woman	O
who	O
Accompanied	O
her	O
,	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
to	O
carry	O
,	O
yet	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
appearing	O
any	O
other	O
ways	O
than	O
by	O
her	O
own	O
Testimony	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Marriot	I-pers
of	B-place
Christ-Church	I-place
Parish	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
of	I-place
Farandine	I-place
within	I-place
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
upon	O
an	O
Indictment	O
of	O
Trespass	O
,	O
for	O
putting	O
away	O
Clipped	O
Monys	O
to	O
the	O
Encouragement	O
of	O
Clippers	O
knowingly	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
against	O
whom	O
it	O
appeared	O
she	O
had	O
both	O
done	O
and	O
attempted	O
that	O
sundry	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
known	O
to	O
subsist	O
for	O
the	O
most	O
part	O
by	O
such	O
unlawful	O
ways	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Tomson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Trevet	O
,	O
a	O
Beaver	O
Hat	O
,	O
a	O
Hatchet	O
,	O
a	O
Set	O
of	O
Brass	O
Weights	O
from	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Rous	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Musling	O
Neckcloath	O
from	O
Henry	B-pers
Cranford	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anthelines	I-place
Parish	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
.	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Proof	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
seemingly	O
to	O
be	O
drunk	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
their	O
being	O
missed	O
,	O
and	O
Enquirie	O
made	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
nor	O
could	O
he	O
deny	O
it	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
but	O
pretended	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
drink	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
manner	O
Distracted	O
and	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Excuse	O
not	O
availing	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
G	I-pers
-	I-pers
was	O
put	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
for	O
Listing	O
himself	O
in	O
the	O
Kings	O
Service	O
as	O
a	O
soldier	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
taking	O
Pay	O
,	O
deferring	O
his	O
Colours	O
at	O
Yarmouth	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
prosecution	O
being	O
made	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Sylvester	B-pers
Read	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
shirt	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sleves	O
:	O
and	O
a	O
Cravat	O
,	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Withinbrook	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Criplegate	I-place
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
they	O
appearing	O
rather	O
Lent	O
than	O
Stolen	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
long	O
familiarity	O
between	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Jennet	B-pers
Tendly	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
a	O
Mohair	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Badds	I-pers
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
the	O
proof	O
against	O
her	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
things	O
being	O
missed	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
apprehended	O
,	O
confessed	O
where	O
she	O
disposed	O
of	O
them	O
and	O
accordingly	O
by	O
her	O
directions	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
Piccadilly	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
other	O
places	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
not	O
being	O
capable	O
of	O
denying	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
yet	O
only	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Hawkwell	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Felony	O
in	O
Stealing	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Sleeves	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
of	O
Bishopgate	B-place
Street	I-place
,	O
by	O
taking	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Trunk	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
proof	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
offered	O
the	O
sleeves	O
to	O
pawn	O
to	O
a	O
person	O
in	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Fetherby	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Stealing	O
40	O
s.	O
in	O
Moneys	O
from	O
Isabel	B-pers
Allison	I-pers
,	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
she	O
was	O
perswaded	O
to	O
it	O
by	O
an	O
Ill	O
Woman	O
,	O
&	O
not	O
being	O
of	O
mature	O
years	O
to	O
understand	O
what	O
she	O
ought	O
to	O
have	O
done	O
in	O
that	O
Case	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
though	O
she	O
denyed	O
not	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
Mony	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Killing	O
James	B-pers
Walss	I-pers
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Field	I-place
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
blow	O
on	O
the	O
Right	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
with	O
a	O
Staff	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
to	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Dyed	O
:	O
the	O
proof	O
was	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
a	O
youth	O
fighting	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
came	O
out	O
amongst	O
them	O
and	O
some	O
Blows	O
passing	O
,	O
he	O
received	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
knocked	O
down	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
the	O
opinion	O
of	O
the	O
Chirurgeons	O
that	O
he	O
died	O
not	O
of	O
that	O
bruise	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Killing	O
Thomas	B-pers
Small	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Whitechappel	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Mortal	O
blow	O
on	O
the	O
head	O
with	O
a	O
Staff	O
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
some	O
words	O
happening	O
between	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
the	O
latter	O
being	O
a	O
Watchman	O
,	O
and	O
out	O
upon	O
Duty	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
between	O
a	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
seized	O
upon	O
his	O
Staff	O
,	O
and	O
wresting	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
gave	O
him	O
such	O
a	O
forcible	O
blow	O
over	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
broke	O
his	O
Scull	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
within	O
three	O
hours	O
afterward	O
Dyed	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
this	O
pleaded	O
Ignorance	O
,	O
alledging	O
himself	O
was	O
unarmed	O
,	O
and	O
consequently	O
could	O
not	O
commit	O
the	O
Crime	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
plain	O
by	O
sundry	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Mortal	O
stroke	O
was	O
given	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Morther	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Mordock	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Killing	O
Zekiel	B-pers
Pool	I-pers
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
with	O
a	O
Ninepin	O
Bowl	O
,	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
persons	O
being	O
at	O
Play	O
in	O
a	O
Ninepin-ground	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
became	O
there	O
an	O
assistant	O
in	O
setting	O
up	O
the	O
Pinns	O
,	O
or	O
as	O
a	O
lookeron	O
,	O
when	O
so	O
it	O
fortuned	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
Ting	O
his	O
Bowl	O
to	O
strike	O
any	O
Pin	O
that	O
was	O
barred	O
from	O
access	O
by	O
any	O
trundling	O
,	O
it	O
struck	O
against	O
a	O
Born	O
by	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
bounded	O
with	O
such	O
force	O
upon	O
the	O
Head	O
and	O
Shoulders	O
of	O
the	O
Decessed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
soon	O
after	O
Dyed	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
quarrel	O
,	O
nor	O
the	O
least	O
malice	O
appearing	O
,	O
not	O
that	O
it	O
altogether	O
happened	O
by	O
accident	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
concluded	O
it	O
Chance	O
medly	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
Acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Block	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Catherines	I-place
,	O
was	O
put	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
for	O
stealing	O
fifty	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Cable	O
Rope	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
from	O
a	O
person	O
unknown	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
Rope	O
being	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Boat	O
on	O
the	O
Surry-side	O
of	O
the	O
River	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
certain	O
place	O
known	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
court	O
give	O
Directions	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
to	O
acquite	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hews	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
Deal-Boards	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
from	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
upon	O
his	O
being	O
apprehended	O
,	O
having	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Court	O
making	O
only	O
a	O
slender	O
Excuse	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
Carpenters	O
Boy	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Christian	B-pers
Heartly	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
were	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
privily	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
,	O
without	O
his	O
knowledge	O
,	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Turtle	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolphs	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
12	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
Proof	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
picking	O
up	O
the	O
former	O
,	O
she	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
drinking	O
Cellar	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
misfortune	O
likewise	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
Company	O
of	O
the	O
latter	O
,	O
who	O
together	O
took	O
an	O
opportunity	O
under	O
the	O
umbrage	O
of	O
much	O
kindness	O
to	O
pick	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
apprehended	O
,	O
Heartly	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Circumstances	O
being	O
home	O
as	O
to	O
Burton	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Holt	I-pers
of	O
Tuttle	B-place
Fields	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Sow	O
,	O
two	O
Barrow	O
Hogs	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Pigs	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
Gilbert	B-pers
Nowel	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Proof	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
.	O
of	O
May	O
following	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
making	O
out	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
giving	O
a	O
pretty	O
good	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
Behaviour	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
supposed	O
the	O
Witness	O
might	O
be	O
mistaken	O
in	O
the	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Boswel	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
Linnen	O
and	O
other	O
wearing	O
Apparrel	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
value	O
,	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Bannister	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
.	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
discovered	O
and	O
pursued	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
as	O
laid	O
in	O
tthe	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Sheepherd	I-pers
,	O
was	O
put	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Purse	O
,	O
one	O
Knife	O
,	O
16	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
.	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Downs	I-pers
and	O
Clement	B-pers
Pomfret	I-pers
were	O
Tryed	O
the	O
first	O
as	O
Principal	O
,	O
the	O
second	O
as	O
Accessary	O
,	O
for	O
Killing	O
John	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Martins	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
wound	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
in	O
the	O
right	O
Breast	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
bredth	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
six	O
inches	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
Dyed	O
,	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
two	O
persons	O
Indicted	O
came	O
with	O
the	O
Deceased	O
from	O
a	O
Tavern	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
Drinking	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
an	O
Encounter	O
happened	O
in	O
the	O
Savoy	B-place
,	O
after	O
which	O
two	O
persons	O
were	O
observed	O
to	O
make	O
their	O
escape	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
thereupon	O
found	O
Dead	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
further	O
that	O
Downs	O
had	O
confessed	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
had	O
fought	O
with	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
former	O
malice	O
appearing	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Encounter	O
being	O
taken	O
to	O
proceed	O
from	O
the	O
effects	O
of	O
a	O
sudden	O
quarrel	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
only	O
,	O
and	O
Clement	O
Pomfret	O
(	O
against	O
whom	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
material	O
Evidence	O
)	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
J	B-pers
-	I-pers
J	I-pers
-	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
putting	O
away	O
Clipped	O
Money	O
knowingly	O
and	O
wilfully	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
advantage	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
incouragement	O
of	O
Clippers	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
divers	O
other	O
times	O
,	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
by	O
one	O
Coney	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
dealt	O
in	O
that	O
kind	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
in	O
Lumbard	O
street	O
with	O
one	O
Orchard	O
,	O
and	O
received	O
of	O
him	O
5	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
10	O
s.	O
for	O
helping	O
him	O
to	O
Broad	O
Money	O
of	O
his	O
Masters	O
Cash	O
,	O
and	O
receiving	O
it	O
again	O
in	O
small	O
or	O
Clipped	O
Moneys	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
gained	O
50	O
l.	O
thereby	O
,	O
and	O
further	O
that	O
he	O
solicited	O
him	O
to	O
Clip	O
Moneys	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
share	O
the	O
advantage	O
,	O
intimating	O
that	O
he	O
mistrusted	O
Orchard	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
for	O
being	O
any	O
longer	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
And	O
his	O
Master	O
likewise	O
declaring	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
often	O
questioned	O
him	O
about	O
Clipped	O
Mony	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
nothing	O
material	O
to	O
offer	O
to	O
his	O
Own	O
behalf	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Trespass	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
taking	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
Lionel	B-pers
Guest	I-pers
of	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
.	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
a	O
silver-hilted	O
Sword	O
,	O
a	O
Hat	O
and	O
Perriwig	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
,	O
Mr	O
Guest	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
striking	O
off	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Perriwig	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
snatched	O
his	O
Sword	O
from	O
his	O
side	O
and	O
ran	O
down	O
an	O
Alley	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
pursuing	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
dropped	O
it	O
,	O
yet	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
under	O
his	O
Feet	O
in	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
positive	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Plea	O
being	O
only	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
mistaken	O
in	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
and	O
Robery	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Basset	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
Killing	O
Mary	B-pers
Basset	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
June	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
Evidence	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
exceedingly	O
in	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
clamering	O
at	O
him	O
at	O
a	O
place	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
drinking	O
with	O
some	O
Friends	O
,	O
he	O
only	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
push	O
,	O
whereupon	O
she	O
staggering	O
about	O
fourteen	O
Foot	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
fell	O
backward	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
hinder	O
part	O
of	O
her	O
Head	O
upon	O
the	O
Edge	O
of	O
a	O
Free	O
stone	O
of	O
which	O
Bruise	O
and	O
Fracture	O
she	O
dyed	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
further	O
Malice	O
appearing	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Cowel	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
were	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Dram	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
Ann	B-pers
Hawworth	I-pers
on	O
the	O
20th	O
.	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
was	O
that	O
they	O
comeing	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
calling	O
for	O
Brandy	O
,	O
had	O
the	O
Cup	O
delivered	O
them	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
end	O
,	O
having	O
no	O
other	O
than	O
Brass	O
Monys	O
to	O
make	O
satisfaction	O
for	O
the	O
reconing	O
,	O
whileft	O
a	O
controversie	O
arose	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
made	O
their	O
escape	O
with	O
the	O
Cup	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
afterwards	O
seen	O
in	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
Cowel	O
,	O
and	O
neither	O
of	O
them	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
gave	O
any	O
satisfactory	O
account	O
of	O
themselves	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Tracy	I-pers
,	O
being	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
silver	O
,	O
Tankards	O
and	O
a	O
Dram	O
Cup	O
,	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Tracy	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolphs	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
.	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
upon	O
his	O
Arraignment	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Tomazine	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Mantua	O
Gown	O
and	O
two	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Hern	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
Against	O
her	O
it	O
appeared	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
with	O
one	O
Catharine	B-pers
Dod	I-pers
coming	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
buying	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
shewed	O
into	O
his	O
Ware-house	O
they	O
found	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
put	O
up	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
agreeing	O
,	O
departed	O
with	O
them	O
in	O
that	O
manner	O
concealed	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
Burton	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Petticoat	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
making	O
her	O
escape	O
with	O
the	O
Gown	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
,	O
were	O
tryed	O
upon	O
an	O
Indictment	O
of	O
Trespass	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Copper	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
fastened	O
to	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
.	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appearing	O
Griffin	O
had	O
confessed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
disposed	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
upon	O
a	O
second	O
Indictment	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
Moscovy	O
Ducks	O
and	O
a	O
Drake	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Coats	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
.	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
upon	O
searching	O
his	O
house	O
at	O
Newington	O
in	O
Surry	O
three	O
of	O
the	O
Geese	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
Ducks	O
and	O
the	O
Drake	O
were	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
giving	O
no	O
other	O
account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
left	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Pettelarcenary	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Alice	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Ames	I-pers
,	O
were	O
tryed	O
for	O
taking	O
secretly	O
and	O
without	O
his	O
knowledge	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
of	O
Heston	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
.	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
one	O
Purse	O
,	O
one	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
thirteen	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Biglin	I-pers
and	O
Elenor	B-pers
Bayly	I-pers
were	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Serge	O
Mantua	O
,	O
one	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Bodice	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
from	O
Jane	B-pers
Thacker	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonards	I-place
Shorditch	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
.	O
of	O
December	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
to	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
frevilous	O
Prosecution	O
grounded	O
upon	O
Malice	O
they	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Bristow	I-pers
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Stacy	I-pers
were	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Callico-Gurtains	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Vallaince	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
from	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Manningham	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
.	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Bristow	I-pers
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Mantle	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
taking	O
a	O
Lodgingand	O
the	O
Mantle	O
proved	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
at	O
Croyden	O
in	O
Surry	O
,	O
told	O
to	O
a	O
person	O
by	O
a	O
person	O
to	O
whom	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edw	B-pers
Wyde	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
Married	O
one	O
Liddia	B-pers
Ditch	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Harefield	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
October	O
in	O
the	O
29th	O
year	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
King	O
,	O
and	O
afterward	O
taking	O
to	O
Wife	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
,	O
his	O
first	O
Wife	O
being	O
then	O
alive	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
he	O
owning	O
the	O
first	O
Marriage	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
material	O
proof	O
being	O
made	O
of	O
the	O
Second	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gillson	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Hollined	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Stealing	O
50	O
s.	O
from	O
Sarah	B-pers
Almon	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Philip	B-pers
Bourn	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Stains	I-pers
coming	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
whilst	O
he	O
was	O
below	O
Bourn	O
picked	O
a	O
Lock	O
in	O
the	O
Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
pretending	O
business	O
,	O
departed	O
with	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Gillson	O
pleaded	O
Ignorance	O
,	O
alledging	O
he	O
came	O
not	O
in	O
with	O
Bourn	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
being	O
known	O
Companions	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
together	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Fellony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Bently	I-pers
and	O
Giles	B-pers
Barns	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Bar	O
of	O
iron	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
from	O
Edward	B-pers
Dalle	I-pers
of	O
Whitechappel	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
proof	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
taken	O
in	O
their	O
custody	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
only	O
pleading	O
they	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
brought	O
them	O
in	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Child	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Tisdale	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Smock	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
3	O
Hoods	O
,	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
Cambrick	O
Band	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
proof	O
against	O
her	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
entertained	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Wife	O
to	O
lodge	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
rose	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
Picking	O
the	O
Lock	O
of	O
a	O
Box	O
,	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
things	O
and	O
departed	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
found	O
after	O
taken	O
with	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
her	O
possession	O
,	O
she	O
then	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
nothing	O
material	O
to	O
offer	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Oliver	B-pers
Morrice	I-pers
and	O
Daniel	B-pers
Wheatly	I-pers
being	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Coach	O
harness	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Coach	O
Glasses	O
,	O
from	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Villars	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
upon	O
their	O
Arraignment	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Littleford	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Pits	I-pers
were	O
tryed	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
as	O
Principal	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
last	O
as	O
Accessary	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
&	O
c.	O
four	O
Curtains	O
one	O
Cloak	O
,	O
two	O
Coach	O
Glasses	O
,	O
two	O
Hammer-Cloaths	O
,	O
the	O
Canvas	O
Covering	O
,	O
and	O
inside	O
Lineing	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Sir	O
.	O
Edmund	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Barronet	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
Upon	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
Littleford	O
upon	O
his	O
being	O
apprehended	O
had	O
Confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
declaring	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
Pits	O
,	O
in	O
whose	O
house	O
and	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
disposed	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
upon	O
search	O
they	O
were	O
accordingly	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
in	O
Court	O
having	O
nothing	O
material	O
to	O
offer	O
for	O
themselves	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
as	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Littleford	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pits	O
:	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Creswell	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Le-Boon	I-place
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Pocket-Pistol	O
,	O
two	O
Aprons	O
,	O
one	O
Pillowbare	O
,	O
one	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Pinner	O
and	O
other	O
goods	O
from	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
leaving	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
trust	O
with	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
in	O
his	O
absence	O
conveyed	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
soon	O
after	O
found	O
at	O
a	O
Musick-house	O
,	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Court	O
having	O
little	O
or	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
A	B-pers
-	I-pers
J	I-pers
-	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Porringer	O
value	O
35	O
s.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Sewel	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
.	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
taking	O
a	O
Lodging	O
,	O
found	O
an	O
opportunitie	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Porringer	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
and	O
clapt	O
it	O
under	O
her	O
Scarfe	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
not	O
denying	O
the	O
Fact	O
in	O
Court	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
Guilty	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
like	O
nature	O
before	O
,	O
the	O
value	O
was	O
reduced	O
within	O
the	O
Penalty	O
of	O
Petty	O
Larcenary	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hicks	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Cunet	I-pers
were	O
put	O
upon	O
their	O
Tryal	O
for	O
stealing	O
twenty	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cable	O
Hope	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
Yards	O
of	O
small	O
Rope	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Ship	O
called	O
the	O
George	O
,	O
Riding	O
in	O
the	O
River	O
of	O
Thames	B-place
on	O
the	O
13th	O
.	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Indictment	O
being	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
one	O
Walter	B-pers
Watting	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
proper	O
owner	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
through	O
that	O
defect	O
they	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mellier	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Cornet	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Embrodered	O
Sleeves	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
living	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
in	O
the	O
Nature	O
of	O
a	O
Sarvant	O
,	O
took	O
her	O
opportunity	O
to	O
carry	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
upon	O
search	O
,	O
the	O
Sleeves	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Lodging	O
,	O
when	O
to	O
excuse	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
she	O
pleaded	O
her	O
Master	O
gave	O
her	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
not	O
appearing	O
by	O
any	O
other	O
Testimony	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Charles	B-pers
Demure	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Scarfe	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Girdle	O
,	O
a	O
Sersnet	O
Hood	O
&	O
c.	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
.	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
having	O
sent	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
with	O
a	O
Letter	O
on	O
a	O
frevilous	O
Errand	O
,	O
and	O
pretending	O
to	O
look	O
to	O
her	O
house	O
till	O
she	O
returned	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
she	O
deny	O
it	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
but	O
alledged	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
given	O
or	O
lent	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
no	O
other	O
ways	O
appearing	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Shipwash	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Walsh	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Cap	O
,	O
a	O
Cornet	O
,	O
a	O
Band	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
Yards	O
of	O
Tape	O
Lace	O
,	O
from	O
Charles	B-pers
Tison	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
when	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
gone	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
entering	O
a	O
Parlour	O
where	O
the	O
Goods	O
lay	O
,	O
took	O
them	O
and	O
fled	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
pursute	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
yet	O
had	O
he	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
Comrade	O
of	O
his	O
who	O
watched	O
his	O
return	O
,	O
e	O
're	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
against	O
this	O
Proof	O
having	O
nothing	O
material	O
to	O
offer	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
defence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Alice	B-pers
Mayor	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Golden	O
Locket	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Picture	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
from	O
Davenant	B-pers
Sherborn	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
confessing	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
were	O
10.	O
viz	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Downs	I-pers
,	O
One	O
Green	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Pollard	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Littleford	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Plumber	I-pers
,	O
Oliver	O
Morrice	O
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Wheatly	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Boswell	I-pers
and	O
John	O
Pits	O
had	O
the	O
Punishment	O
Remitted	O
.	O
The	O
persons	O
that	O
received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
were	O
11	O
viz	O
.	O
Thomas	O
C	O
-	O
John	O
S	O
-	O
Joseph	O
B	O
-	O
Timothy	O
S	O
-	O
John	O
R	O
-	O
William	O
Ely	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
S	I-pers
-	I-pers
Thomas	I-pers
Gilson	I-pers
,	O
Christian	O
Heartly	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Child	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	O
Melliet	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
incurr	O
'd	O
the	O
Penalty	O
of	O
this	O
Sentence	O
,	O
were	O
Reprieved	O
before	O
Judgment	O
.	O
Order	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
1.	O
viz	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tracy	I-pers
.	O
Sentenced	O
to	O
be	O
Whipp	O
'd	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Tomson	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Hains	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	O
Bondhavin	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
O	O
-	O
Sarah	B-pers
Burris	I-pers
,	O
Jennet	O
Tenly	O
,	O
Thomason	O
Burton	O
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Cowell	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
A	O
-	O
J	O
-	O
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Creswell	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Shipwash	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
Alice	B-pers
Mayer	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Bently	I-pers
,	O
Giles	B-pers
Barns	I-pers
,	O
Hannah	O
Bristol	O
,	O
Ann	O
Stacy	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Hews	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Hawkwell	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Tomson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
persons	O
Sentenced	O
for	O
Trespass	O
were	O
4	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
J	O
-	O
J	O
-	O
Fined	O
30	O
l.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Marriot	I-pers
Fined	O
5	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
find	O
Sureties	O
,	O
George	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
to	O
be	O
Whip	O
'd	O
at	O
Mile	O
End	O
.	O
