TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
And	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
,	O
The	O
12	O
and	O
13.	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
1687	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
3d	O
.	O
Tear	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Reign	O
.	O
AT	O
the	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
;	O
Held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bayly	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
and	O
Thursday	O
,	O
the	O
12th	O
and	O
13th	O
Days	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
1687	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Peak	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
with	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
London	O
and	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Purley	I-pers
James	B-pers
Marueon	I-pers
John	B-pers
Aimery	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
Morrice	B-pers
Waight	I-pers
Abraham	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Swingfield	I-pers
Daniel	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
John	B-pers
Guest	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Stepey	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Marshal	I-pers
William	B-pers
Turvil	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Randal	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
Randal	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
Jasper	B-pers
Hodson	I-pers
John	B-pers
Blot	I-pers
John	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
John	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Warrin	I-pers
Daneil	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
Michael	B-pers
Sheepherd	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
follow	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bartholomews	I-place
the	I-place
Less	I-place
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Yards	O
of	O
Bone	O
Lace	O
,	O
valued	O
at	O
16	O
s.	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Read	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
:	O
Upon	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
under	O
presence	O
of	O
buying	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sleeves	O
,	O
he	O
conveyed	O
the	O
Lace	O
Into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
and	O
fled	O
to	O
an	O
adjacent	O
Ale-house	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
threw	O
the	O
Lace	O
into	O
the	O
Celler	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
haying	O
nothing	O
material	O
to	O
offer	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
,	O
yet	O
but	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Handford	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
Mahew	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Alhallows	I-place
Staining	I-place
:	O
Upon	O
Tryal	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
in	O
the	O
Company	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
unknown	O
,	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
for	O
Drink	O
,	O
took	O
a	O
convenient	O
time	O
when	O
the	O
Woman	O
that	O
drew	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Celler	O
to	O
slip	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Tankard	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
pleading	O
ignorance	O
,	O
and	O
bringing	O
some	O
persons	O
to	O
testifie	O
her	O
being	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
the	O
day	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
sworn	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
never	O
absented	O
or	O
absconded	O
her	O
self	O
upon	O
that	O
occasion	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
concluded	O
the	O
Witness	O
might	O
be	O
mistaken	O
in	O
the	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Bartlet	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
fourteen	O
Yards	O
of	O
Bone	O
Lace	O
,	O
valued	O
at	O
2	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
from	O
Mary	B-pers
Chettle	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
October	O
:	O
The	O
Proof	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
,	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
cheapen	O
Lace	O
,	O
but	O
without	O
making	O
any	O
Agreement	O
,	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Lace	O
mentioned	O
,	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
afterward	O
taken	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
making	O
but	O
a	O
slender	O
defence	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
unknowingly	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
,	O
though	O
but	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Banister	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Done	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Lovewell	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Meek	I-pers
,	O
the	O
three	O
first	O
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Burret	I-pers
of	O
Hampstead	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
six	O
Table	O
Cloaths	O
two	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Napkins	O
,	O
two	O
Caps	O
,	O
a	O
Cravat	O
,	O
eight	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
four	O
silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
Porringer	O
,	O
four	O
Yards	O
of	O
Diaper	O
,	O
a	O
Curral	O
,	O
two	O
Rings	O
,	O
a	O
Rix	O
Doller	O
,	O
and	O
7	O
l.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
Mantua	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
wearing	O
Apparrel	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
value	O
.	O
Upon	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
upon	O
the	O
Robbery	O
being	O
Committed	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Mony	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
search	O
in	O
Lovewell	O
's	O
Lodging	O
,	O
hid	O
under	O
his	O
Pillow	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Doller	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
remarkable	O
pieces	O
,	O
as	O
like	O
wise	O
a	O
Cravat	O
lost	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
taken	O
about	O
his	O
Neck	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Meeks	O
Lodging	O
divers	O
parcels	O
of	O
the	O
Linnen	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
concealed	O
in	O
a	O
Cradle	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
they	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
give	O
any	O
good	O
account	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Banister	O
and	O
Done	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Lovewell	O
being	O
Arraigned	O
upon	O
a	O
second	O
Indictment	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cornet	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
a	O
Whisk	O
,	O
a	O
Ring	O
,	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
from	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Dod	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Rachel	B-pers
Pierce	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloath	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
two	O
Shirts	O
,	O
a	O
Hood	O
and	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Meedman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
A	B-pers
-	I-pers
S	I-pers
-	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
twenty	O
four	O
Yards	O
of	O
silver	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
16	O
s.	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Terry	I-pers
of	O
Lumbard-street	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
October	O
:	O
The	O
Proof	O
against	O
her	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
to	O
buy	O
and	O
cheapen	O
Lace	O
,	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Lace	O
immediately	O
upon	O
her	O
departure	O
was	O
found	O
wanting	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
being	O
brought	O
back	O
,	O
droped	O
it	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
Cloaths	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
,	O
she	O
alledged	O
that	O
she	O
never	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
accidentallyfalln	O
down	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
contrary	O
appearing	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
being	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
former	O
Offender	O
of	O
that	O
kind	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
within	O
the	O
Penalty	O
of	O
Petty	O
larcenary	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Pew	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
of	O
Fullham	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Day	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Saddle	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Boots	O
,	O
a	O
Bridle	O
and	O
a	O
Whip	O
:	O
Upon	O
Tryal	O
it	O
was	O
given	O
in	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
found	O
his	O
opportunity	O
to	O
force	O
open	O
a	O
Stable	O
Door	O
by	O
drawing	O
the	O
Staple	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
thence	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
only	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Whip	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
to	O
ride	O
to	O
a	O
place	O
whither	O
his	O
Master	O
had	O
ordered	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Low	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
a	O
Hood	O
,	O
a	O
Cane	O
with	O
an	O
Ivory	O
Head	O
,	O
from	O
James	B-pers
Dun	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
October	O
:	O
Upon	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
inquire	O
for	O
a	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
pretending	O
to	O
stay	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
but	O
notice	O
being	O
taken	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
stayed	O
,	O
upon	O
search	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
only	O
pleading	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
entring	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Marshal	I-pers
in	O
Arundel-street	B-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Strand	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
:	O
The	O
Proof	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Bars	O
broken	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
way	O
into	O
it	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
he	O
accidentally	O
fell	O
into	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
dark	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
Iron	O
Instruments	O
found	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
supposed	O
to	O
be	O
those	O
wherewith	O
the	O
Bars	O
were	O
broken	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
looked	O
upon	O
as	O
a	O
pilfering	O
Fellow	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
breaking	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
firing	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
Scituate	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Criplegate	I-place
on	O
the	O
1st	O
.	O
of	O
October	O
:	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
a	O
Smoak	O
being	O
discovered	O
,	O
and	O
search	O
made	O
between	O
the	O
Tiles	O
and	O
the	O
Cieling	O
,	O
a	O
Board	O
was	O
found	O
on	O
Fire	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
who	O
lived	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
in	O
the	O
Nature	O
of	O
a	O
Servant	O
examined	O
,	O
she	O
confessed	O
she	O
had	O
set	O
it	O
on	O
Fire	O
with	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
Court	O
pleading	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
it	O
accidentally	O
,	O
forgetting	O
her	O
Candle	O
upon	O
being	O
hastily	O
called	O
away	O
with	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
looking	O
for	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
she	O
had	O
laid	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
she	O
did	O
it	O
designedly	O
or	O
maliciously	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Summers	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Philip	B-pers
Minor	I-pers
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
entred	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Egles	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
thence	O
a	O
Violin	O
,	O
a	O
Flute	O
,	O
a	O
Knife	O
and	O
Fork	O
,	O
a	O
Night-Rail	O
,	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
Linnen	O
and	O
wearing	O
Apparrel	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
value	O
:	O
Upon	O
Tryal	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Violin	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
disposed	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
he	O
deny	O
it	O
,	O
pretending	O
only	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
Minor	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
no	O
way	O
capable	O
of	O
giving	O
any	O
good	O
account	O
of	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
only	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Wingfield	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Lutton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
which	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
by	O
his	O
own	O
Confession	O
,	O
as	O
likewise	O
how	O
he	O
had	O
disposed	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Gare	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Lewis	B-pers
Hegar	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
Scarf	O
,	O
Hood	O
,	O
Nightlining	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Sleeves	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
like	O
Nature	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
15	O
l.	O
from	O
Sarah	B-pers
Fauster	I-pers
in	O
Mark-Lane	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
.	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
.	O
The	O
Proof	O
against	O
them	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
Robbed	O
,	O
3	O
Men	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Swan	O
Ale-house	O
in	O
Fanchurch-street	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
upon	O
their	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
other	O
Company	O
having	O
been	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
of	O
these	O
appearing	O
upon	O
Oath	O
to	O
be	O
Hegar	O
and	O
Andrews	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
only	O
&	O
;	O
no	O
breaking	O
appearing	O
in	O
Court	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
upon	O
this	O
Indictment	O
no	O
possitive	O
Evidence	O
,	O
against	O
Gare	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
Robbing	O
the	O
Lodgings	O
of	O
Dionis	B-pers
Lyddal	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Alhollows	I-place
Barking	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
two	O
Perirwigs	O
,	O
a	O
Beaver	O
Hat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
two	O
Velvet	O
Caps	O
,	O
a	O
Back-Sword	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
it	O
appearing	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
was	O
taken	O
about	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
Swan	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
making	O
but	O
a	O
slender	O
defence	O
,	O
being	O
no	O
ways	O
able	O
to	O
give	O
any	O
satisfactory	O
account	O
of	O
themselves	O
as	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
joyntly	O
and	O
severally	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Gare	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Andrews	O
and	O
Hegar	O
:	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
David	B-pers
Faulconer	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Black	O
Jack	O
Tip	O
'd	O
with	O
Silver	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Proof	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
for	O
Drink	O
delayed	O
the	O
time	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
staying	O
for	O
a	O
person	O
he	O
then	O
Named	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
has	O
opportunity	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
the	O
Jack	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
Apprehended	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Possession	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Plea	O
being	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
ignorant	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
but	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Mary	B-pers
Tuft	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Searge	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
Philip	B-pers
Hardy	I-pers
,	O
with	O
whom	O
the	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
Nature	O
of	O
a	O
Servant	O
;	O
The	O
Proof	O
against	O
her	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
upon	O
her	O
leaving	O
her	O
Service	O
divers	O
things	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
the	O
Petticoat	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
defence	O
,	O
making	O
only	O
a	O
faint	O
dental	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
yet	O
only	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10.	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Neckcloaths	O
,	O
two	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Caps	O
,	O
a	O
Cravat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
of	O
small	O
value	O
,	O
from	O
George	B-pers
Prudence	I-pers
of	O
Stoke-Newington	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
October	O
:	O
The	O
Proof	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
made	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Scuffle	O
found	O
means	O
to	O
carry	O
off	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
but	O
soon	O
after	O
upon	O
their	O
being	O
Apprehended	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
found	O
about	O
Bishop	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
Harding	O
Strings	O
,	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
both	O
of	O
them	O
looked	O
upon	O
as	O
Suspicious	O
Persons	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Stanwick	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pauls	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
upon	O
an	O
Indictment	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Brade	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
six	O
pair	O
of	O
Stones	O
,	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Embroidered	O
Silk	O
,	O
several	O
parcels	O
of	O
Lace	O
and	O
other	O
goods	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
5	O
l.	O
The	O
Proof	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
Committed	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
a	O
very	O
unseasonable	O
time	O
of	O
Night	O
trying	O
on	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
the	O
Shooes	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
further	O
enquirie	O
,	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
found	O
packed	O
up	O
behind	O
him	O
and	O
it	O
further	O
appearing	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
house	O
had	O
been	O
entred	O
by	O
breaking	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
as	O
said	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
M	B-pers
-	I-pers
D	I-pers
-	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Christ	B-place
Church	I-place
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
upon	O
an	O
Indictment	O
for	O
a	O
Tresspass	O
,	O
in	O
exchanging	O
Broad	O
Mony	O
for	O
that	O
which	O
was	O
Clipped	O
,	O
and	O
puting	O
it	O
away	O
to	O
the	O
Encouragement	O
of	O
Clippers	O
,	O
at	O
2	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
pound	O
advantage	O
:	O
Against	O
whom	O
the	O
Proof	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
Yates	O
had	O
given	O
50	O
s.	O
in	O
Broad	O
Mony	O
for	O
55	O
that	O
was	O
Clipped	O
to	O
D	O
-	O
and	O
both	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
confessed	O
they	O
had	O
made	O
their	O
mutual	O
advantage	O
in	O
that	O
kind	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
likewise	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
about	O
50	O
s.	O
in	O
Clipped	O
Monys	O
taken	O
from	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
only	O
pleading	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
was	O
maliciously	O
designed	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
to	O
prevent	O
the	O
recovery	O
of	O
Monys	O
due	O
upon	O
Bond	O
from	O
the	O
most	O
material	O
of	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Trespass	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Shirts	O
,	O
one	O
Smock	O
,	O
two	O
Handkerchiefs	O
and	O
a	O
Pinner	O
,	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Wise	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Hackney	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
October	O
:	O
Upon	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
hanging	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Line	O
to	O
dry	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
took	O
them	O
thence	O
and	O
fled	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
Savage	O
's	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
being	O
all	O
a	O
long	O
in	O
his	O
Company	O
,	O
their	O
pretence	O
being	O
only	O
that	O
they	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
Hedge	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
of	O
them	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Silver	O
Tankards	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
l.	O
a	O
silver	O
Boat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
Tumbler	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
Salt	O
,	O
a	O
Mustard	O
Pot	O
,	O
two	O
Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
Porringer	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Snuffers	O
all	O
of	O
Silver	O
,	O
a	O
Brass	O
Snuff-Pan	O
,	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Point	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
Cravats	O
,	O
from	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hallis	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Savoy	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
October	O
:	O
The	O
proof	O
against	O
her	O
was	O
that	O
she	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
inquire	O
for	O
one	O
Madam	O
Jones	O
,	O
found	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
plate	O
and	O
Goods	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
26	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
her	O
flight	O
she	O
dropped	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
Point	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
a	O
person	O
that	O
accidentally	O
justled	O
against	O
her	O
found	O
her	O
out	O
by	O
the	O
ratling	O
of	O
the	O
Plate	O
in	O
her	O
Coat	O
,	O
which	O
upon	O
her	O
being	O
brought	O
back	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
hired	O
by	O
a	O
fine	O
Gentlewoman	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
up	O
Stairs	O
suddainly	O
returned	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
the	O
Place	O
and	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
,	O
to	O
carry	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
her	O
flight	O
appearing	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
escape	O
outfo	O
the	O
Gate	O
House	O
in	O
Mans	O
Apparrel	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
person	O
of	O
Credit	O
appearing	O
to	O
testifie	O
he	O
Reputation	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomazine	B-pers
Tally	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Charleton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
first	O
as	O
Principal	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
second	O
as	O
Accessary	O
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Grimes	I-pers
of	O
Spittle	B-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
silver	O
Salt	O
,	O
four	O
silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
value	O
:	O
Upon	O
the	O
Evidence	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
broken	O
open	O
and	O
entred	O
at	O
a	O
Casement	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
with	O
others	O
of	O
value	O
taken	O
thence	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
upon	O
search	O
a	O
silver	O
Salt	O
,	O
three	O
silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
of	O
value	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
a	O
Broakers	O
in	O
Petticoat	O
lane	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
former	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
had	O
disposed	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
as	O
likewise	O
that	O
upon	O
searching	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
latter	O
some	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
viz	O
,	O
Charleton	O
,	O
did	O
acknowledge	O
that	O
Tally	O
had	O
brought	O
divers	O
Goods	O
to	O
her	O
house	O
,	O
though	O
not	O
with	O
her	O
good	O
likeing	O
,	O
or	O
at	O
least	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
ignorant	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
honestly	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
Proof	O
being	O
slight	O
against	O
the	O
latter	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
former	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
Thomazine	O
Tally	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
of	O
White-Chappel	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
by	O
forcing	O
the	O
Bars	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
Sheets	O
,	O
Shirts	O
,	O
Pillowbears	O
,	O
Napkins	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
like	O
kind	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
value	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
Indictment	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
brought	O
those	O
Goods	O
to	O
a	O
Broakers	O
to	O
sell	O
or	O
otherwise	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
there	O
Seized	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
only	O
pleaded	O
they	O
were	O
given	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
looked	O
upon	O
as	O
a	O
Notorious	O
Pilferer	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
ways	O
able	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
A	O
third	O
Indictment	O
was	O
prefered	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Outry	I-pers
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
the	O
Proof	O
being	O
plain	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Gardener	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
uttering	O
false	O
Mony	O
knowingly	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
made	O
of	O
Brass	O
and	O
other	O
counterfeit	O
Mixtures	O
;	O
against	O
whom	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
often	O
done	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
more	O
current	O
or	O
passible	O
,	O
rubed	O
and	O
and	O
wash	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
nothing	O
material	O
to	O
offer	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
behalf	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Trespass	O
.	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Roger	B-pers
Smithers	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Coining	O
and	O
uttering	O
false	O
Farthings	O
:	O
The	O
Proof	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
into	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
,	O
he	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
in	O
payment	O
for	O
it	O
six	O
counterfeit	O
Farthings	O
with	O
two	O
good	O
ones	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
questioned	O
by	O
the	O
man	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
proceeded	O
to	O
have	O
him	O
searched	O
,	O
when	O
about	O
him	O
were	O
found	O
divers	O
other	O
false	O
and	O
Counterfeit	O
,	O
as	O
likewise	O
the	O
Clipping	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
or	O
over-pluss	O
Meltings	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
together	O
with	O
the	O
Counterfeits	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
as	O
likewise	O
other	O
Farthings	O
that	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Lodging	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
quantity	O
of	O
15	O
d.	O
but	O
having	O
formerly	O
acknowledged	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
in	O
Southwark	O
Fair	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Trespass	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Wotton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Mingo	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
of	O
French	O
Gold	O
and	O
Silver	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
24	O
l.	O
The	O
Witness	O
against	O
her	O
were	O
Mingo	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
meeting	O
him	O
in	O
Lambs-Conduit	O
Fields	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
continued	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
in	O
much	O
familiarity	O
,	O
till	O
such	O
time	O
as	O
she	O
found	O
means	O
to	O
pick	O
his	O
Pocket	O
and	O
depart	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Weeks	O
found	O
out	O
by	O
the	O
means	O
of	O
a	O
Boy	O
in	O
Grays-Inn	O
lane	O
,	O
who	O
directed	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
her	O
Lodging	O
,	O
she	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
first	O
of	O
that	O
Nature	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
distributed	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Whores	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
she	O
pleaded	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
much	O
familiarity	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
inticing	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
France	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
it	O
her	O
with	O
that	O
consideration	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
possitive	O
Testimony	O
being	O
otherwise	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Scarfs	O
,	O
a	O
Meddal	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
l.	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Bacon	I-pers
of	O
Thistleworth	B-place
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
;	O
The	O
Proof	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
Quartering	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Mony	O
and	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
being	O
taxed	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
confessed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
spent	O
and	O
laid	O
our	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Mony	O
at	O
London	O
upon	O
divers	O
necessaries	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
further	O
proved	O
that	O
the	O
Meddal	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Childrens	O
Frocks	O
and	O
two	O
Yards	O
of	O
Calico	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sabb	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
October	O
:	O
The	O
Proof	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
upon	O
taking	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
he	O
droped	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
upon	O
search	O
were	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
only	O
pleading	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
them	O
by	O
the	O
Kennel	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
not	O
knowing	O
to	O
whom	O
they	O
appertained	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
Yards	O
of	O
silver	O
Lace	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Ridgly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Edmund	I-place
the	I-place
King	I-place
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
:	O
The	O
Proof	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
seen	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
off	O
the	O
Stall	O
,	O
and	O
instantly	O
pursued	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
droped	O
,	O
but	O
giving	O
no	O
sufficient	O
Testimony	O
of	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Ratford	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
three	O
Shirts	O
,	O
a	O
Smock	O
,	O
six	O
Napkins	O
,	O
a	O
Corner	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
Grater	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
Buttons	O
,	O
a	O
5	O
s.	O
piece	O
of	O
old	O
Gold	O
,	O
from	O
Sarah	B-pers
Campfield	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Cauthorne	O
a	O
Broaker	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
Shift	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Mark	O
cut	O
out	O
and	O
very	O
much	O
altered	O
amongst	O
Linnen	O
she	O
had	O
put	O
out	O
to	O
wash	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
having	O
nothing	O
material	O
to	O
offer	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
behalf	O
,	O
nor	O
able	O
to	O
give	O
any	O
sufficient	O
Testimony	O
of	O
her	O
good	O
Life	O
and	O
Conversation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
though	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
9	O
s.	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Cibile	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
twenty	O
four	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Rushia	O
Beaver	O
Wool	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Wilks	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parsh	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
Black-Fryers	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
:	O
The	O
Proof	O
against	O
her	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
the	O
Wool	O
produced	O
likewise	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
was	O
upon	O
her	O
being	O
suspected	O
and	O
searched	O
,	O
found	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
being	O
charged	O
with	O
taking	O
more	O
,	O
confessed	O
she	O
had	O
so	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
a	O
parcel	O
or	O
two	O
to	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
Hatters	O
in	O
Bride-Lane	O
but	O
in	O
Court	O
she	O
pleaded	O
ignorance	O
,	O
alledging	O
the	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Proof	O
as	O
well	O
by	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
about	O
her	O
as	O
by	O
her	O
own	O
confession	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
9	O
s.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
S	B-pers
-	I-pers
W	I-pers
-	I-pers
alias	I-pers
P	I-pers
-	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Richard	B-pers
Earl	I-pers
of	I-pers
Burlington	I-pers
,	O
eight	O
Damask	O
Curtains	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
goods	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
value	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
her	O
Arrangement	O
she	O
pleading	O
not	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Dagnal	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Marrying	O
one	O
Sarah	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
at	O
the	O
Parish	O
Church	O
of	O
St.	O
Mary-Le-Boon	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
,	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
1684	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
being	O
yet	O
alive	O
,	O
Married	O
one	O
Debora	B-pers
Fell	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Church	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Catharines	I-place
C	I-place
leman-street	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
1685	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
first	O
Marriage	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
Clerk	O
of	O
St.	O
Mary-Le	O
Byon	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Marriage	O
was	O
Registered	O
in	O
that	O
Church	O
Book	O
,	O
and	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
likewise	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
Sarah	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
as	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
owned	O
her	O
so	O
in	O
every	O
Respect	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
the	O
second	O
Marriage	O
being	O
as	O
plainly	O
proved	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
manner	O
and	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
though	O
upon	O
his	O
Arraignment	O
he	O
had	O
denyed	O
both	O
Marriages	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Leaver	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
,	O
for	O
imposing	O
a	O
Cheat	O
upon	O
the	O
Post	B-pers
master	I-pers
of	I-pers
the	I-pers
General	I-pers
Post	I-pers
Office	I-pers
,	O
by	O
bringing	O
Letters	O
as	O
brought	O
by	O
Ships	O
from	O
Foreign	O
parts	O
by	O
Masters	O
of	O
Ships	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
,	O
and	O
receive	O
a	O
Penny	O
for	O
each	O
,	O
when	O
indeed	O
they	O
were	O
no	O
other	O
than	O
Blank	O
Papers	O
sealed	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
directed	O
by	O
Superscription	O
to	O
divers	O
persons	O
in	O
sundry	O
places	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
against	O
whom	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
imposed	O
upwards	O
of	O
100	O
upon	O
the	O
Office	O
,	O
and	O
received	O
Monys	O
for	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Rate	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
fraud	O
being	O
found	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
attempting	O
to	O
do	O
the	O
like	O
again	O
,	O
by	O
sending	O
a	O
Porter	O
with	O
another	O
parcel	O
of	O
upwards	O
70	O
of	O
the	O
like	O
pretended	O
Letters	O
,	O
with	O
Order	O
to	O
bring	O
a	O
Note	O
or	O
Mony	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Porter	O
was	O
stopped	O
,	O
who	O
for	O
his	O
own	O
safety	O
,	O
brought	O
those	O
that	O
questioned	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Hand	O
Superscribing	O
these	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
former	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
delivered	O
to	O
him	O
by	O
one	O
Grey	O
to	O
convey	O
to	O
the	O
Post	O
Office	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Lovewell	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
was	O
again	O
Indicted	O
and	O
Tryed	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
35	O
s.	O
,	O
a	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
two	O
silver	O
Bouls	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
Dish	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
four	O
other	O
Rings	O
,	O
three	O
pieces	O
of	O
Coined	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
100	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
May	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
by	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
three	O
more	O
having	O
broken	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
entred	O
the	O
Chamber	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
bound	O
him	O
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
Maid	O
&	O
c.	O
threatning	O
them	O
if	O
they	O
resisted	O
or	O
stirred	O
,	O
and	O
covering	O
the	O
former	O
with	O
the	O
Bed	O
Cloaths	O
the	O
better	O
to	O
hinder	O
the	O
discovery	O
of	O
their	O
Faces	O
,	O
they	O
ransacked	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
departed	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
;	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
sometime	O
after	O
were	O
found	O
about	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Cranbourn	O
street	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Martins	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
possitively	O
Sworn	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
of	O
those	O
that	O
entred	O
the	O
Chamber	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
only	O
an	O
obstinate	O
deny	O
of	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
being	O
urged	O
by	O
him	O
for	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
upon	O
the	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
Committed	O
in	O
Kent	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bear	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
taking	O
a	O
silver	O
Hilted	O
Sword	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Austins	O
coming	O
through	O
the	O
Street	O
in	O
the	O
dark	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
fell	O
down	O
in	O
his	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
whilst	O
he	O
catched	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
up	O
the	O
Sword	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
his	O
Side	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
being	O
found	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
appearance	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
though	O
it	O
was	O
supposed	O
a	O
trick	O
in	O
him	O
to	O
fall	O
down	O
,	O
the	O
better	O
to	O
give	O
his	O
Comrade	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hincham	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
assaulting	O
and	O
Robbing	O
Robert	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Sheriffs	O
Officer	O
s	O
in	O
West	B-place
Smithfield	I-place
,	O
during	O
the	O
late	O
Fair	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Proof	O
being	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
that	O
he	O
ment	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Rescue	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Doble	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Gaurd	O
house	O
by	O
White-Hall	B-place
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
73	O
Guineas	O
,	O
three	O
Jacobus	O
pieces	O
,	O
eight	O
half	O
Guineas	O
,	O
5	O
l.	O
in	O
Silver	O
and	O
a	O
Purse	O
,	O
the	O
Monys	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
about	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
The	O
Proof	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
house	O
being	O
entred	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
Garret	O
Window	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
a	O
crop	O
'd	O
Hat	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Gutter	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
Tiles	O
and	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
who	O
much	O
frequented	O
that	O
place	O
as	O
a	O
Black	O
Guard	O
Boy	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
sought	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
Notice	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
fled	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
pursued	O
and	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Purse	O
and	O
thirty	O
eight	O
Guineas	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
brought	O
up	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
he	O
denyed	O
the	O
Hat	O
and	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
asked	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
Guineas	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
got	O
them	O
by	O
Gaming	O
with	O
divers	O
persons	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
being	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
as	O
a	O
frivelous	O
pretence	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
and	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Dey	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
upon	O
another	O
Indictment	O
as	O
Accessary	O
to	O
Doble	O
,	O
in	O
knowing	O
him	O
to	O
have	O
Committed	O
the	O
aforementioned	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
and	O
afterward	O
harbouring	O
,	O
comforting	O
and	O
maintaining	O
him	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Proof	O
against	O
her	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
knowing	O
him	O
to	O
haunt	O
her	O
house	O
or	O
lodging	O
,	O
he	O
upon	O
discovery	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
went	O
thither	O
in	O
search	O
of	O
him	O
and	O
she	O
accordingly	O
promised	O
to	O
cause	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
Apprehended	O
in	O
twenty	O
four	O
hours	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
got	O
the	O
Warrant	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
yet	O
when	O
Doble	O
came	O
during	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
being	O
there	O
,	O
she	O
sent	O
him	O
away	O
unknown	O
to	O
another	O
house	O
and	O
immediately	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
him	O
sensible	O
how	O
he	O
was	O
discovered	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
intreated	O
her	O
to	O
conceal	O
him	O
shewing	O
her	O
his	O
hand	O
wherein	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
burnt	O
,	O
saying	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
biding	O
her	O
keep	O
fifteen	O
Guineas	O
she	O
had	O
of	O
his	O
and	O
convert	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
own	O
use	O
;	O
she	O
not	O
only	O
Aquiessed	O
but	O
became	O
instrumental	O
in	O
conveying	O
him	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
making	O
but	O
a	O
slender	O
defence	O
most	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
being	O
according	O
to	O
her	O
own	O
confession	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Simon	B-pers
Durrant	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Killing	O
Ann	B-pers
Sadler	I-pers
at	O
Leather-sellers	B-place
Hall	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
brusing	O
,	O
rowling	O
and	O
throwing	O
down	O
the	O
said	O
Sadler	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
September	O
and	O
then	O
dyed	O
.	O
The	O
Proof	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
Feast	O
heald	O
there	O
that	O
day	O
and	O
a	O
Dancing	O
Bout	O
ensuing	O
,	O
whilst	O
Durrant	O
was	O
Acting	O
the	O
Countryman	O
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Sadler	I-pers
came	O
in	O
to	O
call	O
her	O
Mistresses	O
Son	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
when	O
upon	O
intimation	O
Durrant	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
and	O
obliged	O
her	O
to	O
Dance	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
for	O
almost	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
being	O
about	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
escape	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
pursued	O
her	O
and	O
puling	O
her	O
back	O
by	O
force	O
threw	O
her	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
tumbled	O
with	O
her	O
over	O
and	O
over	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
being	O
bruised	O
thereby	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
home	O
and	O
sickned	O
and	O
languishing	O
to	O
the	O
day	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
dyed	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
plaaded	O
that	O
her	O
Dancing	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
own	O
consent	O
and	O
as	O
for	O
the	O
rest	O
it	O
was	O
but	O
a	O
Frolick	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
intended	O
no	O
harm	O
and	O
bringing	O
credible	O
persons	O
to	O
testifie	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
laid	O
her	O
down	O
very	O
easily	O
,	O
and	O
further	O
,	O
it	O
appearing	O
upon	O
the	O
Testimony	O
of	O
two	O
Chirurgeons	O
that	O
she	O
dyed	O
not	O
by	O
any	O
Bruise	O
thereby	O
occasioned	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroners	O
inquisition	O
for	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Boile	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Marrying	O
one	O
Loveday	B-pers
Billing	I-pers
,	O
at	O
a	O
place	O
called	O
Wainstead	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
1685	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
being	O
yet	O
alive	O
,	O
Married	O
one	O
Susannah	B-pers
Moise	I-pers
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
Janu	O
.	O
1687	O
at	O
Dukes	B-place
Place	I-place
.	O
As	O
for	O
the	O
second	O
Marriage	O
he	O
owned	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
denyed	O
the	O
first	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
sworn	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
Courted	O
Billing	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
used	O
Endeavours	O
to	O
get	O
her	O
Father	O
's	O
Consent	O
to	O
Marry	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
being	O
Averse	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
Married	O
her	O
privately	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
Married	O
by	O
one	O
Usher	O
an	O
Irish	O
Minister	O
,	O
and	O
further	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
her	O
in	O
Lodgings	O
as	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
publickly	O
owning	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
had	O
a	O
Child	O
by	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
his	O
Letters	O
to	O
her	O
Father	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
subscribed	O
himself	O
his	O
dutiful	O
Son	O
,	O
and	O
executed	O
Conveyances	O
with	O
her	O
Name	O
in	O
them	O
as	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
own	O
Witnesses	O
proving	O
that	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
her	O
mony	O
to	O
disclaim	O
the	O
marriage	O
that	O
instruments	O
purposing	O
a	O
disclaim	O
of	O
the	O
marriage	O
were	O
desired	O
to	O
be	O
sign	O
'd	O
by	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
refused	O
,	O
with	O
many	O
other	O
Circumstances	O
in	O
Words	O
and	O
Writing	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
only	O
insisting	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Certificate	O
appeared	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
person	O
who	O
Married	O
them	O
,	O
or	O
saw	O
them	O
Married	O
,	O
to	O
give	O
Testimony	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
many	O
probable	O
Circumstances	O
and	O
his	O
own	O
former	O
Confession	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
Marriage	O
.	O
&	O
c.	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
Proceeded	O
to	O
Judgment	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
Six	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
William	O
Wingfield	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Dolle	I-pers
,	O
William	O
Gare	O
,	O
Stephen	B-pers
Dagnal	I-pers
,	O
Cibile	O
Jones	O
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Ratford	I-pers
.	O
Ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
Three	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
Lewis	O
Hegar	O
,	O
Robert	O
Andrews	O
.	O
The	O
Persons	O
that	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
.	O
were	O
Nine	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lovewell	I-pers
,	O
John	O
Green	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Doble	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Stonwick	I-pers
,	O
Thomazine	O
Tally	O
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Dey	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Winton	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	O
Meek	O
.	O
The	O
Persons	O
to	O
be	O
Whip	O
'd	O
were	O
Twelve	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
James	O
Low	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
,	O
Will	O
.	O
Summers	O
,	O
Will	O
.	O
Scot	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Tuft	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Bartlet	I-pers
and	O
A	O
-	O
S	O
-	O
Persons	O
Fined	O
were	O
viz	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Gardener	I-pers
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
and	O
to	O
pay	O
a	O
Mark	O
as	O
a	O
fine	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
Convicted	O
for	O
puting	O
away	O
Brass	O
Mony	O
&	O
c.	O
William	O
Leaner	O
Fin	O
'd	O
done	O
Mark	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
;	O
Convicted	O
of	O
puting	O
a	O
Cheat	O
upon	O
the	O
Post	O
Office	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hincham	I-pers
Fined	O
6	O
s.	O
8	O
d.	O
Convicted	O
of	O
assaulting	O
and	O
Wounding	O
Robert	O
Cooper	O
.	O
M	O
-	O
D	O
-	O
and	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Yates	O
,	O
Fined	O
each	O
20	O
Mark	O
,	O
Convicted	O
of	O
puting	O
away	O
Clip	O
'd	O
Mony	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
