TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
And	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
,	O
The	O
14th	O
.	O
15th	O
.	O
and	O
17th	O
.	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
1687	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
;	O
Held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bayly	O
;	O
on	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
,	O
the	O
14th	O
.	O
15th	O
.	O
and	O
17th	O
.	O
Days	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
1687	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Peake	I-pers
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Holt	I-pers
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
City	O
,	O
with	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
for	O
London	O
and	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
follow	O
,	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Mynn	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Jenny	I-pers
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
Alexander	B-pers
Boddington	I-pers
William	B-pers
Love	I-pers
William	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
John	B-pers
Ridgley	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Shambrook	I-pers
John	B-pers
Peck	I-pers
Anthony	B-pers
Green	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Wetham	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Fuller	I-pers
William	B-pers
Parkinson	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Higgins	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Curtis	I-pers
Benjamin	B-pers
How	I-pers
William	B-pers
Gunstone	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Banes	I-pers
William	B-pers
Allom	I-pers
William	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Robins	I-pers
John	B-pers
Bayly	I-pers
John	B-pers
Cannon	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
follow	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Tudman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
Chamber-Pot	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
five	O
small	O
Cups	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
five	O
silver	O
Tobacco	O
Stoppers	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
three	O
silver	O
Bodkins	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
.	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Portyn	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
where	O
the	O
Goods	O
lay	O
,	O
(	O
it	O
being	O
a	O
Lottery	O
Shop	O
)	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
into	O
White-Fryers	O
with	O
it	O
for	O
Shelter	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
matter	O
being	O
so	O
plainly	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Judith	B-pers
Short	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Stephen	I-place
Coleman-street	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Yards	O
and	O
three	O
Quarters	O
of	O
Black	O
Cloath	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
four	O
Pillowbears	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
.	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Crundale	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Crundale	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
who	O
Evidenced	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
thereby	O
had	O
opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
carried	O
some	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
before	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
Corrob	O
rated	O
by	O
other	O
Evidence	O
;	O
and	O
altho	O
'	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
yet	O
the	O
matter	O
of	O
it	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
8	O
s.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Sword	O
with	O
a	O
silver	O
Hilt	O
,	O
value	O
59	O
s.	O
one	O
Watch	O
with	O
a	O
Gold	O
Case	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
l.	O
two	O
Stone	O
Seals	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
.	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Elvin	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
Rideing	O
along	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
suddenly	O
snatch	O
'd	O
away	O
his	O
Sword	O
from	O
his	O
side	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
charge	O
the	O
other	O
Goods	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
yet	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
but	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Donkin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael-Bashaw	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
6	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
.	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
January	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Little	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
about	O
Eight	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Tankard	O
of	O
Ale	O
(	O
it	O
being	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
)	O
and	O
being	O
alone	O
,	O
took	O
his	O
opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
stayed	O
to	O
pay	O
his	O
Reckoning	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
:	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
never	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Ballard	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Allhallows	I-place
Barkin	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Jackman	I-pers
,	O
did	O
steal	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
thirty	O
pounds	O
Weight	O
of	O
Princes	O
Wood	O
of	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wiseham	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Wood	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
the	O
Wood	O
was	O
missing	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
swear	O
positively	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
Wood	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
&	O
c.	O
J.	B-pers
W	I-pers
-	I-pers
and	O
J.	B-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
-	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Killing	O
one	O
Peter	B-pers
Penrose	I-pers
Bell-man	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
W	O
did	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
give	O
the	O
said	O
Bell-man	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
upon	O
the	O
Brest	O
,	O
near	O
to	O
the	O
Right	O
Pap	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
six	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
dyed	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
ringing	O
his	O
Bell	O
,	O
and	O
saying	O
his	O
Verses	O
,	O
on	O
St.	O
Andrews	O
day	O
,	O
above	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
hemet	O
with	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
who	O
bid	O
him	O
not	O
keepsuch	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
ill	O
Language	O
,	O
whereupon	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
arose	O
between	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
two	O
other	O
Bellmen	O
,	O
that	O
came	O
accidentally	O
into	O
the	O
deceaseds	O
company	O
,	O
being	O
upon	O
the	O
Watch	O
not	O
far	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
happened	O
to	O
receive	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
wound	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
making	O
up	O
towards	O
them	O
with	O
their	O
Swords	O
Drawn	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
argued	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
abused	O
by	O
the	O
Bell	O
men	O
and	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
very	O
highly	O
provoked	O
to	O
do	O
what	O
was	O
done	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Bell	O
man	O
set	O
his	O
Dog	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
Knock	O
'd	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
down	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
them	O
,	O
flie	O
for	O
Refuge	O
into	O
an	O
empty	O
Hackney-Coach	O
;	O
hard	O
by	O
that	O
place	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
Committed	O
to	O
the	O
Gate-House	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
their	O
Swords	O
were	O
Bloody	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
set	O
upon	O
by	O
the	O
Bell	O
men	O
and	O
others	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
for	O
Thieves	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
much	O
abused	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
several	O
persons	O
of	O
very	O
great	O
Quality	O
to	O
Evidence	O
on	O
their	O
sides	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
never	O
been	O
wont	O
to	O
quarrel	O
,	O
nor	O
to	O
keep	O
any	O
unseasonable	O
hours	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
a	O
long	O
hearing	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Isaac	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
alias	I-place
Ward	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
Salver	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
one	O
silver	O
Sugar-box	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
Pepper-box	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
Mustard-pot	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
seven	O
silver	O
Forks	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
four	O
silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
24	O
s.	O
The	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
20	O
th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
removed	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
Apprehended	O
,	O
had	O
not	O
opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
withstanding	O
he	O
denyed	O
it	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
yet	O
being	O
Branded	O
in	O
the	O
hand	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
Notorious	O
Offender	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barns	I-pers
the	O
Elder	O
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barns	I-pers
the	O
Younger	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Hounslow	B-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Hair	O
Shag	O
Breeches	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
and	O
5	O
l.	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Moneys	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
.	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
they	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Chamber	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
the	O
Key	O
being	O
over	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
the	O
Key	O
in	O
its	O
place	O
;	O
the	O
money	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Breeches	O
Pocket	O
:	O
The	O
Father	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
High	O
way	O
in	O
the	O
Dirt	O
,	O
and	O
washed	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
bid	O
his	O
Son	O
wear	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
so	O
strong	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barrow	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Covent	B-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Crape	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
Pettycoat	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
Silk	O
Mantua	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
one	O
Silk	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
one	O
other	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
Night-Gown	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
with	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Lady	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Abergavenis	I-pers
,	O
Widdow	O
.	O
The	O
Witness	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
seen	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
he	O
drop	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
denying	O
the	O
Fact	O
and	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
A	O
Woman	B-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Band	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
Black	O
Scarfe	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
.	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
upon	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
afterwards	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Custody	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
having	O
but	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
J.	B-pers
C.	I-pers
-	I-pers
J.	B-pers
S.	I-pers
-	I-pers
and	O
J	B-pers
.	I-pers
B	I-pers
.	I-pers
-	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Murthering	O
one	O
Ann	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
Widdow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
.	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
J.	O
C.	O
-	O
as	O
Principle	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
as	O
Accessaries	O
,	O
giving	O
her	O
the	O
said	O
Ann	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
Right	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
three	O
Inches	O
;	O
of	O
which	O
,	O
she	O
languished	O
from	O
the	O
day	O
abovesaid	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
9th	O
.	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
dyed	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
they	O
all	O
three	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
Coach	O
together	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
private	O
House	O
in	O
great	B-place
Queen-street	I-place
,	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Entertainer	O
of	O
idle	O
Persons	O
;	O
and	O
these	O
three	O
Men	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
the	O
Gang	O
:	O
And	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
C.	O
-	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
too	O
stayed	O
by	O
the	O
Coach	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
,	O
the	O
deceased	O
Woman	O
came	O
out	O
Screeking	O
,	O
and	O
Crying	O
out	O
Murther	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
down	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
C	O
-	O
ran	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
her	O
with	O
a	O
Bagonet	O
into	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
to	O
his	O
Fellows	O
,	O
told	O
them	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
fowerd	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
Sawcey	O
:	O
So	O
being	O
immediately	O
pursued	O
by	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Chirurgcon	O
gave	O
in	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
wound	O
was	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
her	O
death	O
.	O
C	O
-	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
touch	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
carryed	O
any	O
Bagonet	O
about	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
being	O
very	O
Fully	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
wilfull	O
Murther	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Michael	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Rachel	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Garret	I-pers
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
Break	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
one	O
Samuel	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
day	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
one	O
Brass	O
Pendula	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
one	O
Set	O
of	O
Hangings	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
l.	O
one	O
set	O
of	O
Vallens	O
Fringed	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
with	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
It	O
appeared	O
upon	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
Wilkinson	O
was	O
heretofore	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
her	O
Masters	O
house	O
at	O
Hampsted	B-place
,	O
and	O
so	O
might	O
be	O
Accessary	O
to	O
the	O
Robbery	O
;	O
But	O
it	O
further	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
Walker	O
actually	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Rachel	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
bought	O
the	O
Goods	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
stolen	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
far	O
privy	O
to	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
as	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
as	O
Accessary	O
and	O
Walker	O
as	O
Principle	O
,	O
but	O
Wilkinson	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
[	O
Walker	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Luke	B-pers
Norton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Savoy	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Mortymer	O
and	O
Kemp	O
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
Murther	O
one	O
Samuel	B-pers
Stephenson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
.	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
wound	O
on	O
the	O
Right	O
Groin	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
four	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
dyed	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Witnesses	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
gave	O
in	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
met	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
,	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
happened	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
deceased	O
received	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Wound	O
;	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
deceased	O
the	O
wound	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barrow	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Barrow	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pauls	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
one	O
Cornelion	O
Stone	O
set	O
in	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
one	O
Lute	O
string	O
Scarfe	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
one	O
Gold	O
Cross	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
two	O
Gold	O
Chains	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
one	O
Gold	O
Cross	O
set	O
with	O
a	O
Blood	O
Stone	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
with	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
value	O
all	O
about	O
40	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Corbet	B-pers
Henn	I-pers
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Custody	O
of	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
directly	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
house	O
;	O
yet	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
found	O
in	O
several	O
Storys	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
gone	O
by	O
several	O
Names	O
,	O
was	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
person	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
Life	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Woman	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
B	B-pers
-	I-pers
W	I-pers
-	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Olives	I-place
Jury	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
.	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
another	O
person	O
,	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Tankard	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
whilst	O
the	O
Maid	O
went	O
to	O
change	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Tankard	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
another	O
place	O
that	O
Night	O
that	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
stole	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
found	O
in	O
several	O
Storys	O
and	O
Lyes	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Read	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Peter	B-pers
Read	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Jacob	B-pers
Read	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
fourscore	O
Yards	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Crape	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Siner	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Crape	O
was	O
cut	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Loome	O
,	O
by	O
Jacob	B-pers
Read	I-pers
and	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
they	O
working	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
shop	O
with	O
Siner	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Accessary	O
to	O
the	O
Selling	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
Broker	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
4	O
d.	O
a	O
Yard	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
proved	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Yard	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Needle-work	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
.	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
:	O
The	O
Goods	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Youngman	I-pers
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
swearing	O
possitively	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Lace	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
denying	O
it	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Burrow	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bears	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
together	O
withone	O
Francis	B-pers
Ferris	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
steale	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
Rag	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Looking	O
Glass	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Newland	I-pers
,	O
Widdow	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
declared	O
that	O
Bears	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
Barrow	O
was	O
sitting	O
without	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
waiting	O
for	O
his	O
Comerade	O
Bears	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
another	O
person	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
go	O
from	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
of	O
Linnen	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
which	O
Bears	O
Confess	O
'd	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
Apprehended	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
Granadeer	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Gang	O
and	O
had	O
taken	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
Barrow	O
,	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
denyed	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
Bears	O
said	O
that	O
Barrow	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
meddle	O
with	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Box	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
and	O
ten	O
Holland	O
Half-Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
each	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Blow	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
.	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
who	O
dogg	O
'd	O
him	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
White-Hall	B-place
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
trod	O
upon	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Heels	O
,	O
and	O
Assaulted	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
far	O
,	O
as	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
the	O
Box	O
of	O
Linnen	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
soon	O
stopp	O
'd	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
would	O
fain	O
have	O
insinuated	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Ballard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bay	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
.	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
Henry	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Stable	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
Rid	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
the	O
Green-Man	O
in	O
Essex	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
left	O
him	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Groom	O
Lent	O
him	O
the	O
Horse	O
to	O
Ride	O
so	O
far	O
on	O
his	O
way	O
,	O
being	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
his	O
Friends	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Evidence	O
on	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
side	O
being	O
unable	O
to	O
contradict	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
immediately	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gibs	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hair	O
Camblet	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Breeches	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
13	O
l.	O
19	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
.	O
of	O
.	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Ashborn	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Ashborn	O
,	O
who	O
declared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
some	O
little	O
time	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
Committed	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
absented	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
Apprehended	O
he	O
Confess	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
much	O
deny	O
it	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
because	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
Execution	O
coming	O
out	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
other	O
frivolous	O
Excuses	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Humphrey	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
:	O
in	O
Robbing	O
Ralph	B-pers
Gore	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
January	O
,	O
of	O
one	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
one	O
silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
,	O
4	O
l.	O
two	O
silver	O
Porringers	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
other	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
with	O
a	O
dressing	O
Box	O
and	O
a	O
Picture	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
after	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
Robbed	O
,	O
they	O
made	O
search	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
dressing	O
Box	O
,	O
the	O
Picture	O
and	O
Pettycoat	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
owned	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Plate	O
was	O
not	O
discovered	O
.	O
Burton	O
Confessed	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
Scot	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
being	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
as	O
idle	O
Fellows	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
plain	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Vince	I-pers
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Stephenson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
,	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
three	O
Dowlas	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
Wastcoats	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
Tablecloaths	O
with	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
small	O
value	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Maston	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Maston	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
who	O
declared	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Family	O
being	O
abroad	O
,	O
upon	O
their	O
Return	O
about	O
six	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
making	O
search	O
for	O
the	O
Thief	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
not	O
far	O
from	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
standing	O
in	O
a	O
Corner	O
,	O
hiding	O
themselves	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Goods	O
in	O
Vince	O
's	O
Apron	O
:	O
Vince	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
her	O
house	O
by	O
one	O
Martha	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
going	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
home	O
to	O
a	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
whose	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
swearing	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
Vince	O
being	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Old	O
Thief	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ellinor	B-pers
Burt	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
one	O
Black	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
two	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Cornets	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
one	O
Cloath	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
November	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Tomson	I-pers
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Tomson	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
them	O
whilst	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
left	O
her	O
Mistress	O
's	O
Chamber	O
door	O
open	O
when	O
she	O
made	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
returned	O
the	O
Key	O
to	O
her	O
Mistress	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
suspicious	O
persons	O
had	O
that	O
day	O
been	O
lurking	O
about	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
argued	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
maliciously	O
prosecuted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
her	O
Master	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Cunning	O
Man	O
,	O
to	O
know	O
who	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
fix	O
any	O
thing	O
upon	O
her	O
as	O
to	O
matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
immediately	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Glass	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	B-pers
Bisco	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	B-pers
Bears	I-pers
and	O
Mr.	B-pers
Templeman	I-pers
,	O
upon	O
the	O
1st	O
.	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
material	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
making	O
good	O
Proof	O
of	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Fuller	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
one	O
flowered	O
Sattin	O
Gown	O
,	O
valued	O
3	O
l.	O
one	O
Petty	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
3	O
flowered	O
Pettycoats	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
6	O
Yards	O
of	O
Sattin	O
.	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
12	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Pendants	O
set	O
with	O
Stones	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
Guineas	O
in	O
Gold	O
,	O
with	O
80	O
l.	O
in	O
Monys	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
small	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
130	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Robert	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
:	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
was	O
Mrs	O
Atkins	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
her	O
hired	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
her	O
about	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
days	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
so	O
happened	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Mrs.	O
and	O
she	O
,	O
being	O
one	O
day	O
abroad	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
leaving	O
no	O
one	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
from	O
her	O
Mrs.	O
and	O
went	O
privily	O
home	O
and	O
ransackt	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
all	O
the	O
above	O
said	O
Goods	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
,	O
were	O
afterwards	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
in	O
other	O
places	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
used	O
several	O
evasions	O
and	O
insinuating	O
storys	O
,	O
whereby	O
to	O
extenuate	O
the	O
crime	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
looked	O
upon	O
of	O
no	O
value	O
on	O
her	O
behalf	O
;	O
and	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
person	O
of	O
very	O
bad	O
repute	O
;	O
She	O
was	O
after	O
a	O
full	O
and	O
distinct	O
hearing	O
,	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Summers	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Peters	I-place
Cornwal	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
piece	O
of	O
Sliesie	O
Holland	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
and	O
19	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
in	O
Monys	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
.	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Mony	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Abdey	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
upon	O
the	O
Tryal	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Porter	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
Holland	O
and	O
the	O
Mony	O
:	O
but	O
no	O
positive	O
proof	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
Parish	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bulcher	I-pers
:	O
It	O
appeared	O
upon	O
the	O
Tryal	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
with	O
another	O
person	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
positive	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Tanckard	O
being	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Audley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
high	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
speaking	O
Scandalous	O
and	O
Seditious	O
Words	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
Government	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Tryal	O
,	O
the	O
matter	O
of	O
fact	O
appeared	O
thus	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Edw	B-pers
.	I-pers
Audley	I-pers
,	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
)	O
being	O
in	O
discourse	O
together	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
serve	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
Answer	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
better	O
go	O
to	O
Holland	O
than	O
serve	O
the	O
King	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
and	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
Monmouth	O
was	O
an	O
honester	O
Man	O
than	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
more	O
right	O
to	O
the	O
Crown	O
than	O
be	O
hath	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
all	O
the	O
People	O
were	O
of	O
his	O
mind	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Monmouth	O
had	O
more	O
honesty	O
in	O
his	O
little	O
Finger	O
,	O
than	O
the	O
King	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
whole	O
Body	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
his	O
Kinsman	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Difference	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
owed	O
him	O
Mony	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
threatned	O
him	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
on	O
his	O
Side	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
always	O
behaved	O
himself	O
very	O
civilly	O
and	O
modestly	O
,	O
even	O
in	O
the	O
most	O
factions	O
seasons	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
And	O
upon	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
lookt	O
upon	O
as	O
a	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Fann	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
Condemned	O
,	O
two	O
Sessions	O
ago	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Mare	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Nath	O
.	O
Holton	O
:	O
Was	O
again	O
indicted	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bay	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Robert	B-pers
Pearson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Pearson	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Gelding	O
from	O
Islington	B-place
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
custody	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Adams	O
,	O
a	O
Justice	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
near	O
Daintry	O
in	O
Northampton	O
Shire	O
;	O
andthat	O
Jennings	O
owned	O
the	O
Gelding	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
:	O
But	O
Jennings	O
denyed	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
also	O
did	O
Fann	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
matter	O
of	O
fact	O
being	O
so	O
plain	O
against	O
Jennings	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
Fann	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Arrabella	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
in	O
Coining	O
20	O
false	O
pieces	O
of	O
Counterfiet	O
Mony	O
.	O
viz	O
.	O
Sixpences	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
She	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
very	O
Act	O
in	O
her	O
Chamber	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Mettal	O
boiling	O
on	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Mould	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Sixpenny	O
piece	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
false	O
pieces	O
of	O
Mony	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
custody	O
,	O
all	O
which	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
as	O
a	O
further	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
every	O
thing	O
at	O
her	O
Tryal	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
She	O
found	O
the	O
Mould	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
so	O
strong	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
noted	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
High	O
Treason	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Roger	B-pers
Harrup	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
Starving	O
a	O
Gelding	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Geo	B-pers
.	I-pers
Steward	I-pers
's	O
;	O
the	O
matter	O
of	O
fact	O
was	O
as	O
follows	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Steward	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
agreed	O
with	O
the	O
Innkeeper	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Oxford	B-place
Arms	I-place
in	I-place
Warwick-lane	I-place
,	O
to	O
keep	O
his	O
Horse	O
for	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
Week	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
Ostler	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
him	O
Mony	O
,	O
or	O
was	O
not	O
so	O
liberal	O
to	O
him	O
as	O
he	O
did	O
expect	O
,	O
took	O
some	O
Tallow	O
and	O
Bran	O
and	O
mixed	O
them	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
rubbed	O
the	O
Horses	O
Teeth	O
and	O
Gums	O
withall	O
,	O
which	O
caused	O
the	O
Horse	O
to	O
abstain	O
from	O
his	O
Meat	O
,	O
and	O
fall	O
away	O
to	O
a	O
prodigious	O
Poverty	O
;	O
which	O
Horse	O
at	O
first	O
cost	O
him	O
34	O
Guineas	O
,	O
but	O
now	O
was	O
not	O
worth	O
near	O
so	O
much	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Innkeeper	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
ever	O
his	O
Horse	O
was	O
worth	O
5	O
l.	O
he	O
was	O
worth	O
10	O
l.	O
now	O
;	O
and	O
no	O
Evidence	O
was	O
produced	O
to	O
swear	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Ostler	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
commit	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
high	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
counterfieting	O
himself	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Cleark	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
Doctors	O
Commons	O
,	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
sending	O
Processes	O
to	O
People	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
name	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
at	O
one	O
time	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Bell-Inn	O
in	O
Wood-street	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
Carriers	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
fain	O
have	O
juggled	O
mony	O
out	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
Spiritual	O
Court	O
,	O
for	O
getting	O
a	O
Maid	O
With	O
Child	O
;	O
withall	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
40	O
s.	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
it	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
should	O
come	O
to	O
no	O
further	O
trouble	O
:	O
This	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
Procter	O
that	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
Commons	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
any	O
Practice	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
but	O
a	O
Perriwigmaker	O
,	O
in	O
Long-lane	O
.	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
much	O
deny	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
no	O
Mony	O
.	O
So	O
upon	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
a	O
High	O
Misdemeanor	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gardiner	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Holland	O
Band	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
d.	O
One	O
K	O
nting	O
Corronet	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
One	O
Holland	O
Dressing	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
d	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Gunstone	I-pers
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
very	O
obscure	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
lookt	O
upon	O
as	O
a	O
malicious	O
prosecution	O
,	O
they	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
persons	O
of	O
better	O
worth	O
,	O
than	O
the	O
Accusers	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
immediately	O
discharged	O
.	O
Catharine	B-pers
Bedwell	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Lute-string	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
two	O
Silk	O
Gowns	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
Pettycoat	O
with	O
a	O
gold	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
goods	O
,	O
value	O
all	O
about	O
10	O
l.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
three	O
men	O
more	O
came	O
into	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
stayed	O
there	O
all	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
miss	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
a	O
favourable	O
account	O
of	O
her	O
Credit	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Walter	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
hundred	O
weight	O
of	O
Iron	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
from	O
James	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
.	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
George	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
fled	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
very	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
.	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
a	O
Trespass	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Grimstone	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Candlestick	O
and	O
a	O
Save-all	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Parsey	I-pers
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Candlestick	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
Table	O
;	O
but	O
another	O
person	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
Company	O
,	O
who	O
carryed	O
it	O
;	O
yet	O
notwithstanding	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Whiting	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
.	O
of	O
Sept.	O
last	O
,	O
one	O
Feather	O
Bed	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
one	O
Bolster	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
with	O
other	O
goods	O
of	O
small	O
value	O
,	O
from	O
Ann	B-pers
Walter	I-pers
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
that	O
the	O
Bed	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
his	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
Griffin	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
person	O
,	O
were	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
abscond	O
themselves	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Fordham	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Reams	O
of	O
white	O
Paper	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
.	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Staples	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Mr	O
.	O
Staples	O
,	O
who	O
arrested	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
in	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
oftentimes	O
robbed	O
him	O
before	O
;	O
so	O
upon	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Lewis	B-pers
Hedger	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Callico	O
Apron	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
one	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Quoif	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
Handkerchiefs	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
Musling	O
Crevat	O
.	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
goods	O
of	O
small	O
value	O
,	O
from	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
Widdow	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
(	O
she	O
being	O
a	O
Washer	O
Woman	O
)	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Linnen	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Dish	O
as	O
it	O
lay	O
wet	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Swan	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bracelet	O
set	O
with	O
Diamonds	O
and	O
Cornelion	O
Stones	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
.	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
matter	O
of	O
fact	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Salmons	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
:	O
It	O
appeared	O
upon	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
Oxbridge	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Waggon	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Salmons	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Waggon	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bamfield	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
several	O
small	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
Kathrine	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
;	O
the	O
matter	O
of	O
fact	O
against	O
her	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
She	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
hired	O
a	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
which	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Sentence	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Order	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
12.	O
viz	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Tudman	I-pers
,	O
Judith	B-pers
Short	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barns	I-pers
the	O
Elder	O
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barns	I-pers
the	O
Younger	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barrow	I-pers
,	O
Michael	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Barrow	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bears	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
,	O
Humphrey	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
,	O
and	O
E	O
-	O
W	O
-	O
Order	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
3	O
viz	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dunkin	I-pers
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gibs	I-pers
.	O
Order	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
Whip	O
'd	O
5	O
viz	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Grimstone	I-pers
,	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Fordham	I-pers
,	O
Lewis	B-pers
Hedger	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
9	O
viz	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Fuller	I-pers
,	O
J	O
-	O
C	O
-	O
Sarah	B-pers
Vince	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Stephenson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bamfield	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Arrabella	O
Reeves	O
,	O
the	O
last	O
of	O
which	O
,	O
was	O
order	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
Burnt	O
.	O
Arrabella	O
Reeves	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Fuller	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	O
Bamfield	O
pleaded	O
their	O
Bellys	O
,	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
were	O
Impannell	O
'd	O
,	O
who	O
brought	O
in	O
their	O
Verdict	O
in	O
the	O
Negative	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
two	O
latter	O
were	O
quick	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Judgments	O
of	O
T	O
-	O
W	O
-	O
and	O
J	O
-	O
P	O
-	O
was	O
deferred	O
till	O
the	O
Next	O
Sessions	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
an	O
Appeal	O
for	O
Murther	O
brought	O
against	O
them	O
.	O
