TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
Of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
In	O
the	O
OLD-BAILY	O
,	O
The	O
10th	O
.	O
and	O
13th	O
.	O
days	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
1688	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
Fourth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Reign	O
.	O
AT	O
the	O
Sessions	O
Held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
and	O
Saturday	O
the	O
10th	O
.	O
and	O
13th	O
.	O
days	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
1688	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
,	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
other	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Chowne	I-pers
William	B-pers
Skynner	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Atwood	I-pers
John	B-pers
Passel	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
Isaac	B-pers
Dyton	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Gibbs	I-pers
Humphrey	B-pers
Bellamye	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Ricards	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Jobber	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Goreing	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Winford	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
Nicholas	B-pers
Goddard	I-pers
William	B-pers
Happer	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Parriott	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Oakely	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Waldoe	I-pers
John	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Frampton	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
The	O
Tryals	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
as	O
follows	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Ast	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Peter	I-place
's	I-place
Paul's-Wharf	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Raven	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
day	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
near	O
his	O
right	O
Eye	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Hammer	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
Died	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
.	O
Instant	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
the	O
striking	O
of	O
Raven	O
;	O
But	O
the	O
Chirurgeon	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
not	O
Die	O
so	O
soon	O
with	O
the	O
Blow	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
might	O
by	O
some	O
irregularities	O
in	O
Drinking	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
like	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
on	O
his	O
side	O
,	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
strike	O
the	O
Deceased	O
with	O
the	O
Hammer	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
all	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
no	O
Hammer	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
struck	O
him	O
twice	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
but	O
a	O
kind	O
of	O
a	O
little	O
Scar	O
near	O
his	O
right	O
Eye	O
.	O
So	O
upon	O
a	O
full	O
Hearing	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Nowell	B-pers
Gawell	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
;	O
was	O
Indicted	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Francis	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
and	O
two	O
others	O
as	O
Accessories	O
,	O
not	O
yet	O
Taken	O
,	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
.	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
past	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
(	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
about	O
One	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
)	O
six	O
Womens	O
fine	O
Shifts	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
two	O
Table-cloaths	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Diaper	O
Napkins	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
one	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
Green	O
Cloth	O
Carpet	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Mrs.	O
Stone	O
and	O
others	O
;	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
kind	O
of	O
a	O
Labourer	O
about	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
might	O
have	O
opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
the	O
abovesaid	O
Goods	O
;	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
left	O
by	O
him	O
at	O
an	O
Ale	O
house	O
,	O
near	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Stone	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
given	O
him	O
by	O
another	O
Man	O
he	O
met	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
that	O
were	O
with	O
him	O
were	O
Fled	O
.	O
He	O
made	O
no	O
other	O
Defence	O
for	O
himself	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
looking	O
upon	O
himto	O
be	O
a	O
kind	O
of	O
an	O
Idle	O
Fellow	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
Acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Killing	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
a	O
Chair-man	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Baggonet	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
of	O
his	O
Body	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
six	O
Inches	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
immediately	O
Died	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
in	O
the	O
general	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
going	O
along	O
Covent-Garden	O
Plazza	O
,	O
Swearing	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
Kill	O
the	O
next	O
Man	O
he	O
met	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
pull	O
his	O
Baggonet	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
thrust	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
Jones	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
the	O
Baggonet	O
being	O
produced	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
dropt	O
in	O
his	O
pursuit	O
,	O
he	O
owned	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
shaking	O
his	O
Head	O
and	O
Cursing	O
Brandy	O
and	O
Women	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
He	O
had	O
not	O
much	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
have	O
insinuated	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
fell	O
upon	O
his	O
Baggonet	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
Scuffling	O
together	O
;	O
yet	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
willful	O
Murther	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Jeane	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
Danes	I-place
Gent	O
.	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Crisp	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
,	O
Jeane	O
as	O
Principal	O
,	O
and	O
Crisp	O
as	O
Accessory	O
,	O
for	O
willfully	O
Murthering	O
Samuel	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
July	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	B-place
,	O
at	O
a	O
House	O
near	O
the	O
Thames	O
side	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
upon	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
being	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
at	O
Anny-seed	O
Cleer	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
arose	O
between	O
Moore	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Jeane	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Crisp	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
Naked	O
Bitch	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
lost	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
heard	O
to	O
threaten	O
the	O
Deceased	O
that	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
his	O
Blood	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
like	O
:	O
Some	O
time	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Jeane	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
happened	O
to	O
meet	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
they	O
Quarreled	O
afresh	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Jeane	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
give	O
the	O
Deceased	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
seven	O
Inches	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
not	O
seen	O
to	O
strike	O
Mr.	O
Jeane	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Although	O
Mr.	O
Jeane	O
called	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
declared	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
and	O
another	O
Man	O
a	O
Black-a-More	O
,	O
were	O
seen	O
to	O
strike	O
Mr.	O
Jeane	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
several	O
Blows	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
stood	O
and	O
retired	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Defence	O
,	O
being	O
set	O
upon	O
by	O
them	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
But	O
Jeane	O
had	O
no	O
Bruises	O
nor	O
Wounds	O
about	O
him	O
to	O
satisfie	O
the	O
Court	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
hurt	O
:	O
Besides	O
the	O
Chirurgeon	O
declared	O
in	O
Court	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
Died	O
of	O
the	O
Wound	O
that	O
he	O
received	O
.	O
So	O
upon	O
a	O
very	O
full	O
and	O
distinct	O
hearing	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
,	O
Jeane	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Woman	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Barber	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
Danes	I-place
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
;	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Murther	O
,	O
in	O
Killing	O
Ann	B-pers
Stoner	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Stoner	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
day	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
giving	O
her	O
3	O
Mortal	O
Wounds	O
with	O
a	O
Pistol	O
loaded	O
with	O
three	O
Leaden	O
Bullets	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
every	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
of	O
eight	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
Died	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Month	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
declared	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
and	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
more	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
Witch-street	B-place
,	O
and	O
on	O
a	O
sudden	O
a	O
Pistol	O
was	O
Discharged	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
received	O
the	O
abovesaid	O
Wounds	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
fell	O
down	O
and	O
cryed	O
out	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
Shot	O
her	O
;	O
only	O
said	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
on	O
Horseback	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
on	O
Foot	O
went	O
along	O
the	O
Street	O
when	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
Shot	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Malice	O
against	O
her	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Newgate	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
further	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
removed	O
his	O
Goods	O
and	O
Lodging	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
the	O
Murther	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
found	O
for	O
a	O
considerable	O
time	O
after	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
But	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
on	O
Horse-back	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
;	O
and	O
further	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
Fled	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
Being	O
Arrested	O
,	O
being	O
much	O
in	O
Debt	O
;	O
to	O
prove	O
which	O
he	O
called	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
could	O
attest	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
any	O
where	O
else	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
.	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
the	O
Murther	O
was	O
done	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
Ratcliffe	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
get	O
none	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
:	O
Yet	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
Shot	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Howel	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
Richard	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
on	O
the	O
26th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
in	O
his	O
right	O
Eye	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
four	O
Inches	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Fray	O
was	O
thus	O
;	O
the	O
said	O
Harris	O
keeping	O
a	O
Brandy-shop	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
happened	O
between	O
them	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
Drinking	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Howel	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
Draw	O
his	O
Sword	O
against	O
Harris	O
,	O
and	O
Swore	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
do	O
Mischief	O
,	O
and	O
within	O
one	O
Month	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
him	O
the	O
said	O
Harris	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
other	O
desperate	O
Asseverations	O
;	O
all	O
which	O
was	O
confirmed	O
against	O
him	O
by	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Evidence	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
Swear	O
any	O
thing	O
against	O
the	O
Woman	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
set	O
upon	O
him	O
and	O
Drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
one	O
Witness	O
on	O
his	O
side	O
,	O
whose	O
Evidence	O
was	O
not	O
much	O
prevailing	O
on	O
his	O
behalf	O
;	O
and	O
although	O
he	O
urged	O
the	O
Court	O
hard	O
on	O
his	O
own	O
part	O
,	O
yet	O
the	O
Court	O
told	O
him	O
all	O
he	O
said	O
signified	O
nothing	O
:	O
So	O
being	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
last	O
Sessions	O
for	O
a	O
Manslaughter	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
idle	O
Fellow	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
:	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
material	O
appearing	O
against	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
only	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
kept	O
the	O
said	O
Howel	O
Company	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Cary	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Jefferyes	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Dutch	O
Man	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
John	B-pers
Portlock	I-pers
,	O
of	O
1	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Portlock	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Person	O
met	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
about	O
Eleven	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
Stand	O
and	O
deliver	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
but	O
2	O
s.	O
gave	O
him	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confessed	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
at	O
his	O
Apprehension	O
by	O
the	O
Constable	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
spake	O
so	O
in	O
English	O
to	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
pretended	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
speak	O
it	O
at	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
but	O
an	O
Interpreter	O
was	O
Sworn	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
account	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
said	O
against	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
Fled	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
Pursued	O
:	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
that	O
his	O
Companion	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Shilling	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
all	O
concurred	O
that	O
he	O
spake	O
English	O
.	O
The	O
Interpreter	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
sence	O
of	O
what	O
was	O
Swore	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
deny	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Savadge	I-pers
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
one	O
Prudence	B-pers
Cannell	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Edward	B-pers
Cannell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
one	O
Purse	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Mrs.	O
Cannell	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
who	O
declared	O
that	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
Southhampton	B-place
Buildings	I-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Justledher	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
lost	O
her	O
Money	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
Swear	O
positively	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
Robb	O
'd	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
other	O
Evidence	O
proved	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Person	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
known	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
no	O
Witness	O
on	O
his	O
side	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Josias	B-pers
Best	I-pers
,	O
Doctor	O
of	O
Physick	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
and	O
Tryed	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
in	O
Clipping	O
and	O
Coyning	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
last	O
Fact	O
being	O
done	O
about	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
forty	O
Pieces	O
of	O
King	O
Charles	O
the	O
First	O
's	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
forty	O
other	O
Pieces	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Coin	O
called	O
Half	O
Crowns	O
,	O
with	O
certain	O
Sheers	O
and	O
other	O
Instruments	O
fit	O
for	O
the	O
purpose	O
,	O
diminishing	O
from	O
each	O
Piece	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
2	O
d.	O
The	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
opened	O
the	O
Cause	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
chief	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
Stephen	B-pers
Bayley	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
taken	O
on	O
the	O
First	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
in	O
Red-lyon	O
Fields	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Dealer	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
to	O
have	O
Clipp	O
'd	O
Money	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
change	O
Broad	O
Money	O
for	O
Clipp	O
'd	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
rate	O
of	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
advantage	O
in	O
the	O
Pound	O
;	O
and	O
several	O
Filings	O
and	O
other	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Silver	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
Taken	O
;	O
and	O
Bayley	O
further	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
several	O
Lumps	O
of	O
Silver	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
owned	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
doing	O
and	O
Clipping	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Lumps	O
were	O
of	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
about	O
40	O
or	O
50	O
s.	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
confessed	O
to	O
Bayley	O
further	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
about	O
100	O
l.	O
peranum	O
by	O
it	O
:	O
All	O
which	O
was	O
very	O
fully	O
and	O
strenuously	O
Evidenced	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Thus	O
far	O
was	O
the	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
would	O
perswade	O
the	O
Court	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
,	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
what	O
was	O
charged	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
denied	O
all	O
the	O
matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
argued	O
very	O
weakly	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Defence	O
.	O
Whilest	O
he	O
was	O
Trying	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
ordered	O
Mr.	O
Massey	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
one	O
Turner	O
's	O
in	O
Milk-street	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
lately	O
Lodged	O
,	O
where	O
was	O
found	O
two	O
bits	O
of	O
Silver	O
in	O
the	O
Closet	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Filings	O
were	O
seen	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Hole	O
made	O
in	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Room	O
left	O
in	O
a	O
kind	O
of	O
a	O
Suspicious	O
sort	O
;	O
all	O
which	O
was	O
additionally	O
Sworn	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
as	O
it	O
were	O
one	O
Stupified	O
,	O
having	O
nothing	O
material	O
to	O
offer	O
for	O
himself	O
.	O
So	O
upon	O
a	O
very	O
full	O
and	O
clear	O
Hearing	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
last	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
;	O
but	O
yet	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
prepare	O
very	O
good	O
Sureties	O
,	O
(	O
at	O
least	O
300	O
l.	O
each	O
)	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
for	O
the	O
time	O
to	O
come	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Benneson	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Christ's-Church	B-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Stealing	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Normavill	I-pers
on	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
two	O
silver	O
Tankards	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
l.	O
two	O
silver	O
Porringers	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
Eight	O
silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
one	O
silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
Salt	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Normavill	I-pers
,	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
on	O
a	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
Search	O
being	O
made	O
,	O
the	O
Plate	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Custody	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Red-Cross	O
Ale-house	O
in	O
Newgate-street	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
offering	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
Sale	O
to	O
a	O
Gold-smith	O
in	O
St.	O
Ann	O
's	O
Lane	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
buy	O
it	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
how	O
the	O
Plate	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Ale-house	O
,	O
neither	O
would	O
he	O
give	O
any	O
account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
so	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
Second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
procuring	O
Sheers	O
and	O
other	O
Instruments	O
fit	O
for	O
Clipping	O
into	O
his	O
Custody	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
having	O
Clipp	O
'd	O
Money	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
intending	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
off	O
,	O
on	O
purpose	O
to	O
Cheat	O
and	O
Deceive	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Majesties	O
Subjects	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
the	O
Court	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
Clipt	O
Money	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
to	O
put	O
off	O
for	O
any	O
private	O
Advantage	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
And	O
said	O
further	O
that	O
any	O
Person	O
might	O
have	O
Clipt	O
Money	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
do	O
no	O
harm	O
with	O
it	O
:	O
So	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Misdemeanor	O
;	O
but	O
withal	O
the	O
Court	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
find	O
good	O
Sureties	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
for	O
the	O
future	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
one	O
Gray	O
Cloath	O
Suit	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
one	O
other	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
one	O
Waste-coat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
few	O
other	O
small	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
James	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
,	O
&	O
c.	O
But	O
the	O
Court	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
Plead	O
His	O
Majesties	O
most	O
Gracious	O
Pardon	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
accordingly	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Nelson	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Savoy	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
and	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Feather-bed	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
with	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
small	O
value	O
,	O
the	O
proper	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
by	O
vertue	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
most	O
Gracious	O
Pardon	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Isabella	B-pers
Constance	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Tomson	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Lawrence	I-place
Jury	I-place
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Yards	O
of	O
Black	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
.	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Wyatt	I-pers
;	O
but	O
both	O
likewise	O
received	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Pardon	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Phips	I-pers
was	O
like	O
wise	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gelding	O
of	O
a	O
considerable	O
value	O
;	O
but	O
pleaded	O
His	O
Majesties	O
most	O
Gracious	O
Pardon	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Barbey	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
's	I-place
Cornhil	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
.	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
from	O
Ann	B-pers
Gandy	I-pers
Widdow	O
,	O
one	O
Brass	O
Snuff	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Tortleshell	O
Handled	O
Knife	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Gandy	I-pers
aforesaid	O
;	O
but	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
by	O
pleading	O
his	O
Majesties	O
Gracious	O
Pardon	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Hedger	I-pers
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Wait	I-pers
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twelve	O
Yards	O
of	O
Bone-lace	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
but	O
were	O
presently	O
Advised	O
to	O
plead	O
as	O
the	O
others	O
did	O
before	O
;	O
which	O
they	O
did	O
accordingly	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
as	O
Principal	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Rice	I-pers
as	O
Accessories	O
,	O
(	O
not	O
yet	O
Taken	O
)	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Burgan	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
out	O
thence	O
fourteen	O
Ells	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
parsel	O
of	O
Muslin	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
eight	O
Smocks	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
two	O
Smocks	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
nine	O
other	O
Smocks	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
11	O
s.	O
nine	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
1	O
s.	O
five	O
pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
Sleeves	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
four	O
Childrens	O
Frocks	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
one	O
Suit	O
of	O
Child-bed	O
Linnen	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
seven	O
Yards	O
of	O
Fustion	O
,	O
value8	O
s.	O
three	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Childrens	O
Caps	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
three	O
Muslin	O
Aprons	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
with	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
considerable	O
value	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Burgan	I-pers
aforesaid	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Burgan	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
Broke	O
open	O
between	O
the	O
Hours	O
of	O
Twelve	O
and	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
aforesaid	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
whil'st	O
the	O
Family	O
was	O
in	O
Bed	O
:	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
afterwards	O
making	O
Search	O
and	O
Enquiry	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Sarah	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Falcon	O
in	O
Southwark	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
left	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
Sale	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
Accessories	O
,	O
who	O
are	O
since	O
Fled	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Breaking	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
neither	O
was	O
he	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Innocent	O
.	O
But	O
having	O
no	O
Evidence	O
on	O
his	O
side	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
Acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Chumley	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
Danes	I-place
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
taking	O
away	O
from	O
Peter	B-pers
Dormor	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
.	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
two	O
Feather-beds	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
Six	O
Cane-chairs	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
one	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
two	O
Trunks	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
&	O
c.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appeared	O
in	O
Court	O
against	O
him	O
yet	O
the	O
Court	O
thought	O
fit	O
to	O
continue	O
him	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
ensuing	O
Sessions	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
Tryal	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Husey	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
was	O
Arraigned	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
together	O
with	O
Charles	B-pers
Hacket	I-pers
,	O
did	O
Kill	O
and	O
Murther	O
William	B-pers
Endrick	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
six	O
Inches	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
Died	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Month	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
but	O
only	O
the	O
Widdow	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Endrick	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
being	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
give	O
in	O
Bail	O
before	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
,	O
to	O
appear	O
again	O
next	O
Sessions	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Widdow	O
bound	O
in	O
a	O
Recognizance	O
of	O
200	O
l.	O
to	O
appear	O
also	O
and	O
bring	O
in	O
her	O
Witnesses	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Vauson	I-pers
John	B-pers
Ratteray	I-pers
and	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Beck	I-pers
,	O
Servants	O
to	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Earl	O
of	O
Salisbury	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
tryed	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
Anthony	B-pers
Matson	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Beadle	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
;	O
Appeared	O
in	O
Court	O
and	O
Received	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
most	O
Gracious	O
Pardon	O
.	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Most	O
Gracious	O
and	O
Free	O
PARDON	O
WAS	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Pleaded	O
by	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
former	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
the	O
present	O
Convicted	O
Felons	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
whose	O
Names	O
were	O
called	O
over	O
Sucessively	O
,	O
which	O
are	O
these	O
Under-written	O
;	O
which	O
they	O
all	O
in	O
General	O
Pleaded	O
,	O
upon	O
their	O
several	O
and	O
respective	O
Knees	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Passford	I-pers
John	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
Ann	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Yates	I-pers
Mary	B-pers
Batters	I-pers
John	B-pers
Avery	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Hughs	I-pers
John	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mollard	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Trasey	I-pers
Margaret	B-pers
Meeka	I-pers
Mary	B-pers
Wotten	I-pers
Armington	B-pers
Poore	I-pers
Solomon	B-pers
Spring	I-pers
John	B-pers
Wyat	I-pers
Elizabeth	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
John	B-pers
Overton	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Prosoley	I-pers
Simon	B-pers
How	I-pers
John	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
Arrabella	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
Anthony	B-pers
Sanderson	I-pers
for	O
a	O
Fine	O
Henry	B-pers
Hurt	I-pers
Tabitha	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Woodcock	I-pers
James	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
William	B-pers
Goddard	I-pers
James	B-pers
Robins	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Pursival	I-pers
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Highway-men	O
.	O
John	B-pers
George	I-pers
.	O
James	B-pers
Pidgley	I-pers
William	B-pers
Goodman	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
Katherine	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
John	B-pers
Collet	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Lamborn	I-pers
George	B-pers
Emmet	I-pers
William	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
Valentine	B-pers
Cogswell	I-pers
For	O
Clipping	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
Nicholas	B-pers
Salter	I-pers
John	B-pers
Stafford	I-pers
Latimore	B-pers
Ridley	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Oxden	I-pers
For	O
Murther	O
.	O
These	O
Under-written	O
received	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
PARDON	O
upon	O
their	O
being	O
Arraigned	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
John	B-pers
Nelson	I-pers
William	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
Ann	B-pers
Hedger	I-pers
Ann	B-pers
Wait	I-pers
Peter	B-pers
Barbey	I-pers
Nowel	B-pers
Gawell	I-pers
George	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
Isabella	B-pers
Constance	I-pers
Mary	B-pers
Tomson	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Jean	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Howel	I-pers
.	O
AFter	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Most	O
Gracious	O
PARDON	O
was	O
Read	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
advised	O
all	O
those	O
who	O
were	O
Pardoned	O
,	O
to	O
consider	O
how	O
exceeding	O
Merciful	O
and	O
Gracious	O
His	O
Majesty	O
had	O
shewed	O
himself	O
unto	O
them	O
;	O
even	O
to	O
Save	O
them	O
Alive	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
them	O
as	O
it	O
were	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Jaws	O
of	O
a	O
deserved	O
Death	O
;	O
wishing	O
every	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
take	O
good	O
heed	O
for	O
the	O
future	O
how	O
they	O
spend	O
their	O
Precious	O
Time	O
;	O
and	O
bid	O
them	O
beware	O
of	O
falling	O
into	O
any	O
the	O
like	O
Errors	O
again	O
:	O
And	O
urged	O
them	O
all	O
to	O
let	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Clemency	O
Influence	O
them	O
to	O
live	O
and	O
lead	O
a	O
better	O
Life	O
than	O
ever	O
they	O
had	O
don	O
before	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
,	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
3	O
Persons	O
received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
for	O
Murther	O
;	O
James	B-pers
Cary	I-pers
alias	O
Jefferies	O
for	O
Robbing	O
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
;	O
William	B-pers
Savadge	I-pers
for	O
Robbing	O
in	O
the	O
Kings	O
High-way	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Vauson	I-pers
John	B-pers
Ratteray	I-pers
and	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Beck	I-pers
,	O
Servants	O
to	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Earl	O
of	O
Salisbury	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
tryed	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
Anthony	B-pers
Matson	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Beadle	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
;	O
Appeared	O
in	O
Court	O
and	O
Received	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
most	O
Gracious	O
Pardon	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
Mayor	O
.	O
October	O
the	O
13th	O
.	O
1688	O
.	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Most	O
Gracious	O
and	O
Free	O
PARDON	O
WAS	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Pleaded	O
by	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
former	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
the	O
present	O
Convicted	O
Felons	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
whose	O
Names	O
were	O
called	O
over	O
Sucessively	O
,	O
which	O
are	O
these	O
Under-written	O
;	O
which	O
they	O
all	O
in	O
General	O
Pleaded	O
,	O
upon	O
their	O
several	O
and	O
respective	O
Knees	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Passford	I-pers
John	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
Ann	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Yates	I-pers
Mary	B-pers
Batters	I-pers
John	B-pers
Avery	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Hughs	I-pers
John	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mollard	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Trasey	I-pers
Margaret	B-pers
Meeka	I-pers
Mary	B-pers
Wotten	I-pers
Armington	B-pers
Poore	I-pers
Solomon	B-pers
Spring	I-pers
John	B-pers
Wyat	I-pers
Elizabeth	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
John	B-pers
Overton	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Prosoley	I-pers
Simon	B-pers
How	I-pers
John	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
Arrabella	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
Anthony	B-pers
Sanderson	I-pers
for	O
a	O
Fine	O
Henry	B-pers
Hurt	I-pers
Tabitha	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Woodcock	I-pers
James	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
William	B-pers
Goddard	I-pers
James	B-pers
Robins	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Pursival	I-pers
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Highway-men	O
.	O
John	B-pers
George	I-pers
.	O
James	B-pers
Pidgley	I-pers
William	B-pers
Goodman	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
Katherine	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
John	B-pers
Collet	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Lamborn	I-pers
George	B-pers
Emmet	I-pers
William	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
Valentine	B-pers
Cogswell	I-pers
For	O
Clipping	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
Nicholas	B-pers
Salter	I-pers
John	B-pers
Stafford	I-pers
Latimore	B-pers
Ridley	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Oxden	I-pers
For	O
Murther	O
.	O
These	O
Under-written	O
received	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
PARDON	O
upon	O
their	O
being	O
Arraigned	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
John	B-pers
Nelson	I-pers
William	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
Ann	B-pers
Hedger	I-pers
Ann	B-pers
Wait	I-pers
Peter	B-pers
Barbey	I-pers
Nowel	B-pers
Gawell	I-pers
George	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
Isabella	B-pers
Constance	I-pers
Mary	B-pers
Tomson	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Jean	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Howel	I-pers
.	O
AFter	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Most	O
Gracious	O
PARDON	O
was	O
Read	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
advised	O
all	O
those	O
who	O
were	O
Pardoned	O
,	O
to	O
consider	O
how	O
exceeding	O
Merciful	O
and	O
Gracious	O
His	O
Majesty	O
had	O
shewed	O
himself	O
unto	O
them	O
;	O
even	O
to	O
Save	O
them	O
Alive	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
them	O
as	O
it	O
were	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Jaws	O
of	O
a	O
deserved	O
Death	O
;	O
wishing	O
every	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
take	O
good	O
heed	O
for	O
the	O
future	O
how	O
they	O
spend	O
their	O
Precious	O
Time	O
;	O
and	O
bid	O
them	O
beware	O
of	O
falling	O
into	O
any	O
the	O
like	O
Errors	O
again	O
:	O
And	O
urged	O
them	O
all	O
to	O
let	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Clemency	O
Influence	O
them	O
to	O
live	O
and	O
lead	O
a	O
better	O
Life	O
than	O
ever	O
they	O
had	O
don	O
before	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
