TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
Of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
,	O
And	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bayly	O
,	O
the	O
22th	O
.	O
and	O
23th	O
.	O
days	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
1688	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
fourth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Reign	O
.	O
AT	O
the	O
Sessions	O
Held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Baily	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
and	O
Thursday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
22th	O
.	O
and	O
23th	O
.	O
days	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
1688.	O
before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
,	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Shorter	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Shore	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
and	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
together	O
with	O
other	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
for	O
London	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Shrawly	I-pers
Christ	B-pers
.	I-pers
Raper	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Gardiner	I-pers
William	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
Bartholomew	B-pers
Sholver	I-pers
George	B-pers
Alder	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Parcell	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Willcox	I-pers
George	B-pers
Westray	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Greene	I-pers
Giles	B-pers
Westrore	I-pers
John	B-pers
Enderly	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
as	O
follows	O
.	O
THomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Callamy	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Alderman-bury	I-place
,	O
about	O
the	O
Hours	O
of	O
Eight	O
and	O
Nine	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
.	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
February	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
one	O
Cloath	O
Coat	O
fac	O
'd	O
with	O
Velvet	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
being	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Joshua	B-pers
Geering	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
and	O
the	O
Casement	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Coat	O
was	O
brought	O
down	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
the	O
Stairs	O
and	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Parlour	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
let	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
not	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
pleaded	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Pursued	O
and	O
run	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smalley	I-pers
and	O
Daniel	B-pers
Wheatly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Christ	B-place
Church	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
James	B-pers
Hayes	I-pers
,	O
Twenty	O
six	O
Spanish	O
Leather	O
Skins	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
Thirteen	O
Sheeps-Leather	O
Skins	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
It	O
appeared	O
upon	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
stole	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Warehouse	O
in	O
Southwark	B-place
,	O
and	O
sold	O
in	O
London	O
;	O
that	O
Smalley	O
profer	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
Sale	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
Apprehended	O
,	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
give	O
any	O
Account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
But	O
little	O
appearing	O
against	O
Wheatly	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Smalley	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Hopworth	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
.	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
from	O
Arthur	B-pers
Darcy	I-pers
,	O
one	O
Watch	O
with	O
a	O
Silver	O
Case	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
plain	O
upon	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
:	O
And	O
he	O
only	O
saying	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
dropp	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Walter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
25	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
Twelve	O
pair	O
of	O
Shooes	O
,	O
value	O
24	O
s.	O
Three	O
Boots	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
aforesaid	O
:	O
But	O
he	O
only	O
saying	O
he	O
found	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
his	O
Shooes	O
upon	O
her	O
Feet	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
she	O
offer	O
'd	O
any	O
to	O
Sale	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
very	O
slight	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Sconley	I-pers
of	O
Great	B-place
Alhallows	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Shackliffe	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
.	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
at	O
Eleven	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
four	O
Guinea	O
's	O
pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
one	O
French	O
Pistol	O
,	O
value	O
17	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
fourteen	O
pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
at	O
23	O
s.	O
per	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
116	O
l.	O
of	O
Silver	O
in	O
Mony	O
numbred	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Spareman	O
to	O
the	O
Brew-house	O
,	O
and	O
Lodged	O
in	O
a	O
Stable	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
Broke	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
with	O
a	O
Hatchet	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
was	O
Drunk	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Devil	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
rest	O
till	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Hannah	B-pers
Wascoate	I-pers
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Peter	I-place
's	I-place
Cornhil	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Henry	B-pers
Curtis	I-pers
forty	O
seven	O
yards	O
of	O
Bone	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
one	O
Gaws	O
Hood	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
yard	O
of	O
Muslin	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
goods	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
proving	O
to	O
be	O
insufficient	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
as	O
a	O
frivolous	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	B-pers
-	I-pers
S	I-pers
-	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Gregory	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Ward	I-place
of	I-place
Castle-Baynard	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Mugg	O
,	O
value	O
35	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Valentine	B-pers
Acton	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
keeping	O
a	O
Publick-house	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
others	O
was	O
Drinking	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
last	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
when	O
the	O
Mugg	O
was	O
missing	O
:	O
But	O
they	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
charge	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Procter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
.	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
one	O
Black	O
colour	O
'd	O
Gelding	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
,	O
Chattels	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Stiles	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
an	O
Horstler	O
at	O
an	O
Inn	O
,	O
he	O
employed	O
one	O
to	O
Ride	O
the	O
Horse	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
Seized	O
by	O
the	O
Owner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Horse	O
was	O
brought	O
into	O
the	O
Inn	O
by	O
an	O
unknown	O
Person	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
treating	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Buy	O
him	O
for	O
8	O
l.	O
odd	O
Money	O
,	O
intending	O
to	O
have	O
him	O
Toled	O
;	O
and	O
some	O
Persons	O
speaking	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Basfeild	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Latimore	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Ann	B-pers
Fitch	I-pers
Widdow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
.	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
one	O
Bay-Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
one	O
Mouse	O
colour	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
Busfeild	O
brought	O
the	O
Horses	O
to	O
Town	O
,	O
ordering	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
employed	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
to	O
put	O
up	O
the	O
Horses	O
in	O
an	O
Inn	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
found	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Busfeild	O
owned	O
the	O
Horses	O
as	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
pretended	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
produce	O
from	O
whom	O
,	O
or	O
where	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
Smith	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
for	O
cheating	O
one	O
Hannah	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
Marry	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
and	O
21	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
with	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
her	O
by	O
her	O
Name	O
,	O
got	O
acquainted	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
pretending	O
his	O
Wife	O
Died	O
in	O
Childbed	O
,	O
made	O
Love	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
they	O
had	O
several	O
Meetings	O
till	O
he	O
work	O
'd	O
his	O
opportunity	O
to	O
get	O
her	O
Money	O
and	O
Rings	O
from	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Wife	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Misdemeanour	O
.	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
ANthony	B-pers
Dier	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Fulham	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Breaking	O
open	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Elizab	B-pers
.	I-pers
Gilby	I-pers
on	O
the	O
11th	O
.	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
at	O
Nine	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
119	O
l.	O
11	O
s.	O
being	O
the	O
Moneys	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Board	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Felony	O
was	O
plain	O
,	O
he	O
also	O
having	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
restored	O
34	O
l.	O
9	O
s.	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bromley	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
.	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
one	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
32	O
s.	O
two	O
yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Needle-work	O
Lace	O
,	O
one	O
yard	O
of	O
Flanders-Lace	O
,	O
one	O
Sarsnet	O
Hood	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
goods	O
belonging	O
to	O
Martin	B-pers
Hazlebanck	I-pers
:	O
It	O
appearing	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
carrying	O
off	O
the	O
said	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
found	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
Sold	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Walter	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Merrit	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
.	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
Hours	O
of	O
Ten	O
and	O
One	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
one	O
Silver	O
Candle-Cup	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
two	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
Amber	O
Necklace	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
Sleeves	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
Thirty	O
six	O
pound	O
of	O
Beef	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
five	O
shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
main	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
wife	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Browne	O
came	O
into	O
her	O
House	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
and	O
Broke	O
open	O
a	O
Trunk	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
fore-mentioned	O
goods	O
;	O
but	O
little	O
of	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
his	O
Wife	O
or	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Dennis	B-pers
Kitton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Nicholls	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Friswell	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Barwick	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Eighteen	O
Pence	O
in	O
Money	O
numbred	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
found	O
one	O
Kelley	O
's	O
hand	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
since	O
Fled	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
only	O
in	O
Company	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Clancey	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Robert	B-pers
Starling	I-pers
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Banwell	I-pers
,	O
who	O
are	O
not	O
yet	O
Taken	O
,	O
did	O
break	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
.	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
Hours	O
of	O
Twelve	O
and	O
One	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
Eight	O
Holland	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
Eleven	O
Pillow-beers	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
s.	O
one	O
dozen	O
of	O
Napkins	O
,	O
Diaper	O
Table-cloaths	O
,	O
a	O
Sarsnet	O
Cloath	O
Wastecoat	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Constable	O
stuffed	O
in	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Burglary	O
not	O
being	O
proved	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
appearing	O
also	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
Morris	O
that	O
was	O
Executed	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Solomon	B-pers
Spring	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bartholomew	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Bushel	I-pers
,	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Hornsey	B-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Seigniour	O
Alvaro	B-pers
de	I-pers
Costo	I-pers
a	O
Jew	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
.	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
at	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
three	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
Sleeves	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
Holland	O
Cap	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
one	O
Gold	O
Chain	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Felony	O
was	O
plain	O
upon	O
them	O
all	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
Seized	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
running	O
away	O
from	O
the	O
Officers	O
;	O
had	O
Swords	O
and	O
Pistols	O
about	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
a	O
Vizard	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Spring	O
pull	O
'd	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Breeches	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
Seized	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Burglary	O
not	O
appearing	O
plainly	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Spring	O
:	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Bartholomew	O
and	O
Bushel	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Blakestone	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Tovey	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Matthew	B-pers
Shanno	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
.	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
at	O
Two	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
two	O
Hatts	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.six	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
considerable	O
value	O
:	O
Francis	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
was	O
also	O
Indicted	O
as	O
Accessory	O
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
,	O
harbouring	O
and	O
abbetting	O
the	O
said	O
Persons	O
,	O
and	O
Buying	O
the	O
goods	O
.	O
The	O
sum	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
Tovey	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
door	O
on	O
the	O
inside	O
to	O
let	O
in	O
his	O
Companions	O
,	O
while	O
others	O
staid	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
to	O
receive	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
after	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Drinking	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
Savoy	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
shared	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
afterward	O
Pawned	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
Broker	O
in	O
Long-lane	O
;	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
Booth	O
's	O
Cellar	O
;	O
their	O
Examinations	O
and	O
Confessions	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
were	O
also	O
read	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
being	O
positive	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Window	O
being	O
open	O
or	O
shut	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
,	O
and	O
Booth	O
the	O
Accessory	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Talbot	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement-Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
Samuel	B-pers
Grove	I-pers
,	O
one	O
Cloath	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Cloath	O
Breeches	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
goods	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
goods	O
in	O
a	O
Box	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
:	O
He	O
only	O
said	O
for	O
himself	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Drunk	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Box	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Backer	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
.	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
Four	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
two	O
Firkins	O
of	O
Butter	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
Cheeses	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Evidence	O
relating	O
nothing	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
that	O
could	O
be	O
proved	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
that	O
he	O
carried	O
some	O
of	O
these	O
goods	O
from	O
one	O
Place	O
to	O
another	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
hired	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
his	O
Master	O
appearing	O
for	O
him	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
served	O
as	O
a	O
Shooe-maker	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Clayton	I-pers
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Deserting	O
his	O
Colours	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Jordan	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Matin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Matthew	B-pers
Stanno	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
.	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
at	O
Two	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
other	O
Persons	O
stealing	O
thence	O
two	O
Beaver	O
Hats	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
two	O
Caster	O
Hats	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
Eleven	O
dozen	O
of	O
Cordubeck	O
Hats	O
,	O
value	O
44	O
l.	O
and	O
20	O
yards	O
of	O
Ribbon	O
Galloone	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
his	O
Examination	O
was	O
read	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
set	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
share	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
goods	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Philip	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pauls	I-place
Shadwel	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Lamprey	I-pers
on	O
the	O
fourteenth	O
day	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
past	O
,	O
at	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
thence	O
one	O
Serge	O
Pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
Shillings	O
one	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
value	O
twenty	O
Shillings	O
,	O
one	O
Caster	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
Shillings	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
upon	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Coat	O
and	O
Breeches	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
hole	O
made	O
through	O
the	O
Wall	O
into	O
the	O
lower	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
:	O
but	O
he	O
pretending	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
proof	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
upon	O
him	O
not	O
being	O
positive	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Vaucks	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
small	O
Cistern	O
,	O
value	O
twelve	O
Shillings	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
twelfth	O
day	O
of	O
February	O
Instant	O
,	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
.	O
She	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
being	O
a	O
Rag-Woman	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
among	O
Rags	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
against	O
Mary	B-pers
Aubry	I-pers
,	O
for	O
Murthering	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
Dennis	B-pers
Fanet	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Fauet	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Desermo	I-pers
,	O
as	O
Accessaries	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
AUBRY	I-pers
,	O
a	O
French	O
Woman	O
,	O
had	O
her	O
Indictment	O
read	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Interpreter	O
for	O
that	O
purpose	O
,	O
For	O
that	O
she	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	O
Aubry	O
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
Dennis	B-pers
Aubry	I-pers
,	O
not	O
having	O
the	O
Fear	O
of	O
God	O
before	O
her	O
eyes	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
moved	O
and	O
seduced	O
by	O
the	O
Instigation	O
of	O
the	O
Devil	O
,	O
the	O
27th	O
.	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
third	O
Year	O
of	O
our	O
Soveraign	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
Assault	O
upon	O
Dennis	B-pers
Aubry	I-pers
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
Feloniously	O
,	O
Wilfully	O
,	O
and	O
Traiterously	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	O
Aubry	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Pack-thread	O
which	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	O
Aubry	O
then	O
and	O
there	O
had	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
Neck	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Dennis	O
Aubry	O
,	O
feloniously	O
,	O
wilfully	O
,	O
traiterously	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
Malice	O
aforethought	O
,	O
did	O
put	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	O
Aubry	O
;	O
with	O
the	O
Pack-thread	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Dennis	O
thy	O
Husband	O
,	O
feloniously	O
,	O
wilfully	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
malice	O
aforethought	O
,	O
then	O
and	O
there	O
did	O
it	O
choak	O
and	O
strangle	O
;	O
of	O
which	O
said	O
choaking	O
and	O
strangling	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Dennis	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Dennis	O
then	O
and	O
there	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
So	O
that	O
thou	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	B-pers
Aubry	I-pers
,	O
the	O
same	O
Dennis	O
thy	O
Husband	O
,	O
in	O
manner	O
and	O
form	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
feloniously	O
,	O
wilfully	O
;	O
traiterously	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
malice	O
aforethought	O
,	O
didst	O
kill	O
and	O
murther	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
Peace	O
of	O
our	O
Soveraign	O
Lord	O
,	O
his	O
Crown	O
and	O
Dignity	O
.	O
And	O
being	O
asked	O
by	O
her	O
Interpreter	O
,	O
If	O
she	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
this	O
Felony	O
,	O
Murther	O
,	O
and	O
Petty-Treason	O
,	O
or	O
not	O
;	O
she	O
pleaded	O
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
After	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
ordered	O
the	O
Interpreter	O
to	O
tell	O
her	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
having	O
confessed	O
she	O
was	O
guilty	O
,	O
she	O
must	O
suffer	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
Court	O
was	O
so	O
favourable	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
the	O
were	O
minded	O
to	O
put	O
her	O
self	O
upon	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
her	O
Tryal	O
,	O
she	O
might	O
have	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
still	O
the	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Confession	O
was	O
recorded	O
.	O
Dennis	B-pers
Fanet	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Fanet	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Desermo	I-pers
,	O
all	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
as	O
Accessaries	O
,	O
for	O
concealing	O
the	O
laid	O
Murther	O
,	O
and	O
harbouring	O
,	O
and	O
relieving	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	O
Aubry	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
asked	O
whether	O
they	O
desired	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
half	O
Aliens	O
,	O
they	O
answered	O
in	O
the	O
Affirmative	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
a	O
Jury	O
was	O
Impanel	O
.	O
Their	O
Names	O
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
Peter	B-pers
Mariscoe	I-pers
Peter	B-pers
Templeman	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Corboyer	I-pers
John	B-pers
Page	I-pers
James	B-pers
Deprie	I-pers
Abraham	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
Gerrard	B-pers
Bocquet	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
King	I-pers
Claudius	B-pers
Aquee	I-pers
Matthew	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Alexander	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Council	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
pleaded	O
learnedly	O
in	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
laying	O
open	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
,	O
That	O
Mary	B-pers
Aubrey	I-pers
had	O
confessed	O
,	O
that	O
after	O
several	O
resolutions	O
to	O
perpetate	O
the	O
death	O
of	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
he	O
accordingly	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
.	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
coming	O
home	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
at	O
five	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
fast	O
Asleep	O
,	O
through	O
Excess	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
his	O
Garter	O
,	O
and	O
tied	O
a	O
Noose	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
about	O
his	O
Neck	O
and	O
strangled	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
she	O
rises	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
Confusion	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
remained	O
till	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
great	O
inquiry	O
after	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
Son	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
then	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Dubois	O
,	O
desiring	O
his	O
Master	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
leave	O
to	O
come	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
carried	O
him	O
and	O
shewed	O
him	O
his	O
dead	O
Father-in-law	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Body	O
being	O
too	O
big	O
to	O
be	O
carried	O
off	O
,	O
she	O
cut	O
off	O
the	O
Legs	O
and	O
Arms	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
Savoy	O
House-of-Office	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
the	O
Thighs	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
the	O
Trunk	O
of	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
laying	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
common	O
place	O
in	O
Parker's-Lane	O
,	O
wrapping	O
the	O
Head	O
also	O
in	O
a	O
Cloth	O
,	O
and	O
flinging	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Inquisition	O
made	O
of	O
the	O
Murther	O
,	O
her	O
Husband	O
being	O
missing	O
,	O
she	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
known	O
by	O
a	O
Mark	O
as	O
was	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
upon	O
his	O
Hand	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
House-of-Office	O
.	O
After	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
being	O
called	O
and	O
sworn	O
,	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
their	O
Evidence	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
after	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
they	O
talking	O
with	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
say	O
,	O
That	O
we	O
have	O
sent	O
him	O
,	O
meaning	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Indies	O
to	O
fetch	O
Diamonds	O
:	O
but	O
all	O
that	O
was	O
given	O
in	O
Evidence	O
,	O
being	O
not	O
full	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
did	O
not	O
look	O
upon	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
sufficient	O
proof	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
were	O
either	O
aiding	O
,	O
assisting	O
,	O
or	O
abetting	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Murther	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
grounding	O
their	O
Discourse	O
chiefly	O
upon	O
what	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
the	O
Deceafed	O
had	O
said	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
,	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
But	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
to	O
find	O
Sureties	O
for	O
their	O
Good	O
Behaviour	O
,	O
and	O
John	O
Desermo	O
,	O
the	O
Son	O
,	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Aubry	O
:	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
,	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
3	O
Persons	O
received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
:	O
viz	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Sconly	I-pers
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Busfeild	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
.	O
The	O
said	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
pleaded	O
her	O
Belly	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Women	O
were	O
Impannel	O
'd	O
,	O
who	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
with	O
Child	O
.	O
Seven	O
Persons	O
were	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bartholomew	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Bushel	I-pers
John	B-pers
Blakestone	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Tovey	I-pers
,	O
Phillip	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hopeworth	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smally	I-pers
.	O
Four	O
Persons	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Dier	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
,	O
Solomon	B-pers
Spring	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Jordan	I-pers
.	O
Three	O
Persons	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Whipt	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bromley	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Talbot	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Vaucks	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
Fined	O
Forty	O
Shillings	O
.	O
The	O
Sentence	O
against	O
Mary	B-pers
Aubry	I-pers
was	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
should	O
be	O
carried	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
from	O
whence	O
she	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
thence	O
be	O
drawn	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
of	O
Execution	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
be	O
burnt	O
with	O
Fire	O
till	O
she	O
is	O
dead	O
.	O
