TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
&	O
Queen	O
's	O
Commissions	O
OF	O
THE	O
PEACE	O
,	O
And	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
At	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
,	O
Began	O
on	O
Thursday	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
1689	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
First	O
Year	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bayly	O
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
1689	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honorable	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pilkington	I-pers
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
Holt	O
,	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
Pollexsen	O
,	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
follow	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Jenks	I-pers
John	B-pers
Barwick	I-pers
John	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Chase	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Falconer	I-pers
James	B-pers
Oades	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Ayleworth	I-pers
Downall	B-pers
Thursbey	I-pers
Humphrey	B-pers
Dyer	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Moasley	I-pers
John	B-pers
Read	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Daniel	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sanders	I-pers
William	B-pers
Hunsden	I-pers
William	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
John	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
Nicholas	B-pers
Sterne	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Kypping	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Arundel	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Swayne	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Saney	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Saney	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Cooke	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Arding	I-pers
.	O
After	O
the	O
Court	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
set	O
,	O
a	O
Messenger	O
appeared	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
presenting	O
the	O
Court	O
with	O
a	O
Writ	O
from	O
the	O
High	O
Court	O
of	O
Parliament	O
,	O
having	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
Queen	O
's	O
Broad	O
Seal	O
affixed	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
taking	O
off	O
the	O
Attainder	O
of	O
High	O
Treason	O
against	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
William	O
Lord	O
Russel	O
;	O
which	O
the	O
Court	O
did	O
accept	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
it	O
was	O
immediately	O
taken	O
off	O
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
these	O
:	O
Jacob	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolphs	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
and	O
Tryed	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
his	O
Wife	O
Mary	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
giving	O
her	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
upon	O
her	O
Back	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
3	O
Inches	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
day	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
She	O
died	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
fell	O
upon	O
his	O
Wife	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
outragious	O
manner	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
wound	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
She	O
declared	O
upon	O
her	O
Death-Bed	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
wound	O
with	O
the	O
Knife	O
in	O
her	O
back	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
very	O
ill	O
Language	O
to	O
those	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
sorry	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
design	O
to	O
murder	O
her	O
for	O
about	O
these	O
Six	O
years	O
and	O
acknowledged	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
he	O
struck	O
her	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
All	O
which	O
was	O
proved	O
by	O
very	O
concurring	O
Evidence	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
being	O
not	O
himself	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
other	O
feigned	O
Stories	O
and	O
Insinuations	O
,	O
how	O
that	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
was	O
not	O
careful	O
of	O
her	O
wounds	O
.	O
All	O
which	O
prevailed	O
but	O
little	O
on	O
his	O
side	O
;	O
so	O
,	O
after	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
wilful	O
Murder	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
and	O
Wilfully	O
Murdering	O
his	O
Wife	O
one	O
Susannah	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
,	O
giving	O
her	O
one	O
mortal	O
wound	O
near	O
the	O
Right	O
Pap	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
4	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
She	O
died	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
very	O
clear	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
shot	O
off	O
the	O
Pistol	O
in	O
the	O
Passage	O
between	O
the	O
Temple	O
and	O
White-Fryars	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Woman	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
wound	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
And	O
he	O
being	O
asked	O
the	O
Reason	O
why	O
he	O
shot	O
at	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
he	O
answered	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
gave	O
him	O
very	O
abusive	O
language	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
bear	O
.	O
But	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
made	O
a	O
very	O
plausible	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
very	O
little	O
material	O
,	O
only	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Wife	O
called	O
him	O
Highway-man	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
shot	O
off	O
his	O
Pistol	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
withal	O
he	O
shot	O
it	O
against	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
All	O
which	O
did	O
not	O
satisfie	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
last	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
wilful	O
Murder	O
also	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Killing	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Carr	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
past	O
;	O
giving	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Carr	O
several	O
Mortal	O
Bruises	O
about	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
Breast	O
,	O
but	O
especially	O
upon	O
the	O
Head	O
of	O
him	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Carr	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
believed	O
to	O
be	O
Mortal	O
by	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
who	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
there	O
was	O
Coagulated	O
Blood	O
settled	O
between	O
the	O
Skull	O
and	O
the	O
Dure	O
Matur	O
:	O
Which	O
Contused	O
Blood	O
was	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
the	O
Patient	O
's	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
Sequel	O
of	O
the	O
Story	O
in	O
short	O
was	O
thus	O
;	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
others	O
in	O
their	O
Company	O
,	O
were	O
Drinking	O
at	O
the	O
Sun	O
Tavern	O
behind	O
the	O
Exchange	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
stayed	O
pretty	O
late	O
,	O
till	O
at	O
last	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
desired	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
Captain	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
raw	O
Souldiers	O
under	O
his	O
Command	O
;	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Carr	O
being	O
very	O
desirous	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Company	O
,	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
He	O
should	O
Lodge	O
with	O
him	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
which	O
afterwards	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
seemed	O
to	O
consent	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
entred	O
Mr.	O
Carr	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Candle	O
happened	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
;	O
at	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
grew	O
inraged	O
,	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
dark	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
be	O
gone	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
would	O
kill	O
the	O
next	O
Man	O
he	O
met	O
,	O
or	O
words	O
to	O
that	O
Effect	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Door	O
being	O
shot	O
and	O
fast	O
lockt	O
,	O
he	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
upon	O
the	O
said	O
Carr	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
person	O
,	O
Wounding	O
them	O
sorely	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
strike	O
the	O
said	O
Carr	O
with	O
the	O
Pummel	O
of	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
being	O
afraid	O
what	O
Mischief	O
might	O
be	O
done	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Dark	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
design	O
'd	O
to	O
hurt	O
no	O
Man	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
lookt	O
upon	O
to	O
be	O
much	O
in	O
Drink	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
:	O
so	O
upon	O
the	O
Conclusion	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
only	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Marrying	O
Two	O
Wives	O
viz	O
.	O
One	O
Dianah	B-pers
Lymeburne	I-pers
,	O
and	O
one	O
Jane	B-pers
Stanley	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Stavely	I-pers
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Lotman	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
and	O
Hermond	B-pers
Croyver	I-pers
a	O
Dutch	O
Souldier	O
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
and	O
Tryed	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
Even	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
a	O
Chair	O
man	O
:	O
Lotman	O
as	O
principal	O
,	O
and	O
Croyver	O
as	O
accessary	O
.	O
It	O
happened	O
that	O
some	O
Dutchmen	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Lotman	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
upon	O
him	O
with	O
naked	O
Swords	O
.	O
Croyver	O
being	O
the	O
first	O
Man	O
that	O
made	O
the	O
Assault	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Lotman	O
giving	O
the	O
said	O
Davis	O
one	O
mortal	O
wound	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
about	O
an	O
Inch	O
;	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
further	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
said	O
Davis	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Assistance	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Lotman	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
midst	O
of	O
the	O
Scuffle	O
,	O
lost	O
his	O
Life	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Lotman	O
excused	O
himself	O
what	O
he	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
:	O
Who	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Dutchmen	O
met	O
him	O
and	O
fell	O
upon	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
to	O
provehow	O
the	O
Quarrel	O
began	O
,	O
nor	O
upon	O
what	O
occasion	O
;	O
nor	O
did	O
it	O
appear	O
that	O
Lotman	O
gave	O
the	O
Dutchmen	O
any	O
provocation	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
fly	O
after	O
the	O
said	O
Davis	O
was	O
killed	O
,	O
So	O
upon	O
a	O
fair	O
Hearing	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
them	O
both	O
.	O
One	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gibbons	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
Upon	O
his	O
Araignment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Petticoat	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
from	O
Andrew	B-pers
Meredith	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Turpin	I-pers
a	O
Notorious	O
Pick	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
Light	O
finger	O
'd	O
Youth	O
,	O
yet	O
very	O
Young	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Banfeild	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
day	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
2	O
and	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
one	O
Gold	O
Tooth-picker	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
Eight	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Salt	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
One	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
One	O
Pepper	O
Box	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
and	O
Plate	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Pillowber	O
,	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
about	O
17	O
l.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
at	O
least	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
deny	O
,	O
only	O
said	O
,	O
He	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
High-way	O
:	O
So	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
Acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Alcroft	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
killing	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Clement	B-pers
Pomfret	I-pers
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
wound	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
5	O
Inches	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Evidence	O
it	O
appeared	O
thus	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
drinking	O
in	O
a	O
Tavern	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Pomfret	O
began	O
a	O
Health	O
,	O
(	O
saying	O
,	O
Here	O
is	O
a	O
Health	O
to	O
King	O
James	B-pers
II	I-pers
.	O
and	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Son	O
of	O
a	O
Whore	O
that	O
will	O
not	O
pledge	O
it	O
)	O
or	O
words	O
to	O
that	O
effect	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
a	O
farther	O
Quarrel	O
arose	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
perswade	O
Mr.	O
Pomfret	O
not	O
to	O
drink	O
the	O
Health	O
.	O
So	O
their	O
Swords	O
were	O
both	O
drawn	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
Drawers	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
both	O
their	O
Swords	O
were	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Pomfret	O
holding	O
his	O
hand	O
upon	O
his	O
Belly	O
,	O
cryed	O
out	O
,	O
He	O
was	O
wounded	O
;	O
saying	O
,	O
That	O
this	O
Mischief	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
by	O
his	O
own	O
seeking	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Surgeon	O
evidenced	O
,	O
that	O
Pomfret	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
wound	O
was	O
mortal	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
his	O
death	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
wound	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
but	O
hapned	O
into	O
his	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
drank	O
the	O
Health	O
that	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
drink	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
quarrelled	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
death	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
on	O
his	O
side	O
;	O
So	O
upon	O
a	O
full	O
Hearing	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Man	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Man	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
were	O
both	O
Tryed	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
Jacob	B-pers
Mack-wart	I-pers
a	O
Dutchman	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Dutchmen	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Parish	I-place
in	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
supposed	O
and	O
reputed	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Evil	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
turned	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
that	O
the	O
Woman	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
yet	O
the	O
said	O
Mark	O
wart	O
was	O
presently	O
killed	O
in	O
the	O
Entry	O
.	O
Man	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
He	O
was	O
seiz	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Dutchmen	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
how	O
the	O
Deceased	O
came	O
by	O
his	O
Death	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
positively	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Feild	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Stephen	I-place
Coleman-street	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
taking	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Rebeccah	B-pers
Dorrington	I-pers
two	O
Silver	O
Cups	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
2	O
Silver	O
Poringers	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
2	O
Spoons	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
The	O
Goods	O
of	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Dorrington	O
abovesaid	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
kind	O
of	O
a	O
Chair-woman	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Darrington	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
took	O
her	O
opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
by	O
the	O
Constable	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Direction	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
yet	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
clear	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Darrycoat	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
Stue	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
taking	O
away	O
Feloniously	O
from	O
Jeremy	B-pers
Dod	I-pers
,	O
one	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Dod	O
's	O
House	O
with	O
another	O
Person	O
attending	O
on	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
his	O
Man	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
a	O
Pewter	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
stead	O
thereof	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
Sworn	O
home	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
And	O
Stue	O
Pleaded	O
Guilty	O
upon	O
the	O
Arraignment	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Katharine	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Whitewood	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Read	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
being	O
about	O
14	O
yards	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Tamerlain	B-pers
Rufford	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Rufford	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
some	O
Silk	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
one	O
piece	O
too	O
much	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
under	O
the	O
Coats	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
White	O
:	O
But	O
there	O
was	O
none	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Custody	O
of	O
Read	O
.	O
They	O
both	O
stifly	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
yet	O
they	O
were	O
lookt	O
upon	O
to	O
be	O
Idle	O
House-wives	O
.	O
White	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
Read	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ellis	B-pers
Skynner	I-pers
was	O
Arraigned	O
and	O
Tryed	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
with	O
a	O
Musquet	O
laden	O
with	O
Bullets	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
six	O
Inches	O
:	O
But	O
forasmuch	O
as	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
charged	O
,	O
the	O
Piece	O
going	O
off	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
mending	O
of	O
it	O
(	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Gunsmith	O
:	O
)	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
Immediately	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Wardrobe	I-place
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Simonsons	I-pers
,	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
40	O
Diaper	O
Napkins	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
2	O
Table	O
Cloaths	O
8	O
s.	O
4	O
pair	O
of	O
flaxen	O
Sheets	O
40	O
s.	O
2	O
Napkins	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
5	O
pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
Sheets	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
12	O
other	O
Napkins	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
4	O
Towels	O
8	O
s.	O
3	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
small	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Custody	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
hired	O
a	O
Carman	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Baker	O
and	O
Basket	O
in	O
cloth	O
Fair	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
the	O
Carman	O
stay	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
hours	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
give	O
no	O
account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
:	O
But	O
no	O
proof	O
appeared	O
against	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
broke	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
neither	O
was	O
it	O
laid	O
Burglary	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Mullinax	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
28	O
yards	O
of	O
linen	O
Cloth	O
value	O
13	O
s.	O
from	O
Joseph	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
in	O
the	O
month	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
with	O
another	O
Woman	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Callico	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Cloth	O
.	O
which	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
pursued	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
flatly	O
deny	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
known	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
an	O
old	O
Practitioner	O
in	O
the	O
Art	O
of	O
Legerdemain	O
,	O
so	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Bowen	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barloe	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
Four	O
Indicted	O
together	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
from	O
one	O
Richard	B-pers
Twigg	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolphs	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Tankard	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
could	O
not	O
fasten	O
the	O
Felony	O
in	O
particular	O
on	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
only	O
Roberts	O
was	O
lookt	O
upon	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
most	O
suspicious	O
person	O
among	O
them	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
other	O
three	O
Prisoners	O
Company	O
being	O
a	O
stranger	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
Roberts	O
owned	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
(	O
to	O
the	O
Constable	O
)	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
Tankard	O
;	O
yet	O
,	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
three	O
were	O
Neighbors	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
the	O
Court	O
gave	O
the	O
more	O
favourable	O
Report	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
of	O
them	O
:	O
So	O
Roberts	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
three	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
an	O
Ancient	O
Man	O
of	O
86	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
killing	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Fairbeard	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
;	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
in	O
his	O
left	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
6	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
and	O
died	O
within	O
7	O
Weeks	O
after	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
numerous	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
agreed	O
in	O
their	O
Depositions	O
:	O
How	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
some	O
Women	O
in	O
his	O
Company	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Groat	O
to	O
pay	O
,	O
which	O
Russel	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
refused	O
to	O
pay	O
,	O
giving	O
the	O
said	O
Fairbeard	O
very	O
ill	O
Language	O
.	O
The	O
said	O
Fairbeard	O
deceased	O
took	O
off	O
his	O
Hat	O
for	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
:	O
Upon	O
which	O
the	O
said	O
Russel	O
pulled	O
a	O
great	O
Pocket	O
Knife	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Sheath	O
,	O
and	O
Stabbed	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
proved	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
side	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
drew	O
out	O
his	O
Knife	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
the	O
deceased	O
came	O
to	O
fall	O
upon	O
his	O
Knife	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
no	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
call	O
on	O
his	O
behalf	O
,	O
yet	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
were	O
pleased	O
to	O
commiserate	O
him	O
being	O
very	O
old	O
:	O
And	O
gave	O
in	O
thier	O
Verdict	O
Guilty	O
only	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
a	O
Notorious	O
Shop	O
lifter	O
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
yards	O
of	O
broad	O
Silver	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
The	O
Goods	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
day	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
's	O
Shop	O
and	O
cheapned	O
some	O
Lace	O
,	O
and	O
Juggled	O
away	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
Lace	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
she	O
dropt	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
Shop	O
where	O
she	O
ran	O
in	O
for	O
Shelter	O
;	O
She	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
several	O
Evasions	O
whereby	O
to	O
extenuate	O
her	O
Crime	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
no	O
effect	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Shooter	I-pers
and	O
Wyne	B-pers
Drury	I-pers
were	O
both	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Stanton	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Evidence	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
into	O
Stanton	O
's	O
House	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
Drink	O
and	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
the	O
Maid	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
House	O
being	O
empty	O
,	O
they	O
slipt	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Tankard	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appeared	O
that	O
see	O
them	O
take	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
Drury	O
called	O
a	O
Witness	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
another	O
place	O
when	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
alledged	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
So	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Set	O
of	O
old	O
Curtains	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
The	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Bowter	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Robbery	O
was	O
done	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
time	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bowter	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
that	O
could	O
Swear	O
positively	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
And	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
taking	O
away	O
from	O
one	O
Francis	B-pers
Elican	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
one	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
one	O
Kan	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
some	O
Spoons	O
of	O
small	O
value	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
proved	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
tookaway	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
in	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
confessed	O
in	O
Bridewel	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
7	O
l.	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Luffe	I-pers
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
also	O
confessed	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
Bridewel	O
,	O
as	O
abovesaid	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
denied	O
all	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
,	O
yet	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Laureson	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
Cornhil	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
The	O
Matter	O
was	O
thus	O
,	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
taken	O
off	O
the	O
Bar	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
how	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
no	O
positive	O
Proof	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Felony	O
,	O
in	O
Robbing	O
John	B-pers
Frost	I-pers
of	O
one	O
Serge	O
Mantle	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
two	O
Blankets	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
Crape	O
Gown	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
Gown	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
And	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
small	O
value	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
enticed	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Goods	O
by	O
one	O
Alice	B-pers
Ashby	I-pers
;	O
who	O
appeared	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
Custody	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
be	O
Tryed	O
,	O
as	O
an	O
accessary	O
:	O
So	O
the	O
said	O
Bradshaw	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
only	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
9	O
s.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Peter	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Bruff	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
2000	O
l.	O
weight	O
of	O
old	O
Nets	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
2000	O
l.	O
weight	O
of	O
old	O
,	O
Ropes	O
called	O
old	O
Stuff	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
proved	O
it	O
,	O
That	O
Mansfield	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Boy	O
Bruff	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
Mansfield	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Barret	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
in	O
St.	B-place
Thomas	I-place
Apostles	I-place
.	O
For	O
Felony	O
,	O
in	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
from	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Newell	I-pers
in	O
Bone	B-place
lane	I-place
.	O
Cox	O
's	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
that	O
he	O
entered	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
that	O
Charge	O
.	O
As	O
for	O
the	O
stealing	O
of	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
thus	O
:	O
He	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Newel	O
with	O
another	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confessed	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
but	O
denied	O
both	O
the	O
Indictments	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
never	O
in	O
Newel	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Tankard	O
when	O
the	O
Watch	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
20	O
s.	O
yet	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
call	O
no	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
his	O
Allegations	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Heretage	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
several	O
small	O
Goods	O
from	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Hellens	I-place
within	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
about	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
one	O
Shift	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
3	O
Aprons	O
3	O
s.	O
2	O
Holland	O
Coives	O
&	O
c.	O
all	O
about	O
30	O
s.	O
value	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Clarke	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
their	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
her	O
Trunk	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Trunk	O
was	O
not	O
lockt	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
further	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
Bridewel	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
looked	O
upon	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
idle	O
Woman	O
;	O
yet	O
no	O
positive	O
proof	O
coming	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Knowles	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
brass	O
Sconces	O
from	O
Esquire	B-pers
Neale	I-pers
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
offering	O
them	O
to	O
Sale	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Privy	O
Chamber	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
discharged	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
.	O
Almond	B-pers
Marsman	I-pers
a	O
Dutchman	O
and	O
Serjeant	O
,	O
of	O
Islington	B-place
Parish	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Harwood	I-pers
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
wound	O
6	O
Inches	O
deep	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
body	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
flatly	O
sworn	O
against	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
3	O
several	O
pushes	O
at	O
the	O
deceased	O
before	O
he	O
wounded	O
him	O
.	O
It	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
that	O
Harwood	O
struck	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
although	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Fire-Tongs	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
And	O
no	O
premeditated	O
Malice	O
was	O
proved	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
very	O
familiar	O
together	O
.	O
The	O
Surgeon	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
wound	O
was	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
his	O
death	O
.	O
All	O
which	O
was	O
signified	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
by	O
an	O
Interpreter	O
,	O
who	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
defence	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Dutch	O
Soldiers	O
,	O
who	O
could	O
not	O
charge	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
began	O
the	O
Quarrel	O
:	O
so	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Stanninot	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Parish	I-place
,	O
were	O
both	O
tryed	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
a	O
Brewer	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
in	O
giving	O
him	O
several	O
bruises	O
upon	O
the	O
right	O
Eye	O
of	O
him	O
the	O
said	O
Davis	O
,	O
Breast	O
and	O
Members	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
from	O
the	O
7th	O
day	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
until	O
the	O
both	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
in	O
the	O
general	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
drinking	O
together	O
late	O
at	O
Night	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Stanninot	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
arose	O
about	O
a	O
Health	O
to	O
King	O
James	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prince	O
of	O
Wales	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
quarrelled	O
further	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
to	O
blows	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
did	O
not	O
prove	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Davis	O
dyed	O
of	O
the	O
Bruises	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
said	O
he	O
believed	O
that	O
he	O
dyed	O
a	O
natural	O
death	O
for	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Fractures	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
head	O
,	O
only	O
a	O
Coagulation	O
or	O
setling	O
of	O
Blood	O
in	O
his	O
privy	O
Parts	O
.	O
So	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Boyle	I-pers
was	O
three	O
times	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
of	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
silk	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
,	O
which	O
the	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
.	O
The	O
second	O
was	O
for	O
stealing	O
25	O
yards	O
of	O
Silk	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Pretty	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
third	O
was	O
for	O
stealing	O
30	O
yards	O
of	O
silk	O
from	O
Henry	B-pers
Pope	I-pers
,	O
to	O
all	O
which	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
could	O
not	O
deny	O
any	O
of	O
it	O
:	O
So	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
all	O
Three	O
indictments	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Highway-man	O
,	O
in	O
setting	O
upon	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Trot	I-pers
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
forcing	O
him	O
with	O
Pistol	O
to	O
deliver	O
his	O
Mony	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
done	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Money	O
was	O
four	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
all	O
about	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
Sword	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Belt	O
6	O
d.	O
All	O
which	O
was	O
very	O
plainly	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
deny	O
it	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Martin	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
and	O
Wilfully	O
Murthering	O
(	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
Morral	O
Wound	O
near	O
his	O
left	O
Pap	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
4	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
died	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
instant	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Evidence	O
it	O
was	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
deceased	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
amongst	O
others	O
,	O
where	O
was	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
about	O
some	O
Women	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
midst	O
of	O
it	O
Ward	O
lost	O
his	O
Life	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Sword	O
was	O
Bloody	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
alledged	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
was	O
Wounded	O
before	O
Powel	O
was	O
ingaged	O
in	O
the	O
Quarrel	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
abused	O
and	O
urged	O
draw	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
Witnessed	O
by	O
some	O
whom	O
the	O
Pris	O
called	O
:	O
But	O
Powel	O
's	O
Sword	O
,	O
as	O
before	O
was	O
found	O
bloody	O
in	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Ward	O
did	O
say	O
before	O
his	O
Death	O
,	O
That	O
Powel	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
Wound	O
.	O
Yet	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
strenuous	O
enough	O
to	O
fix	O
it	O
upon	O
him	O
:	O
So	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
M	O
slaughter	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Roger	B-pers
Leadman	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Le	I-place
Bone	I-place
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Stafford	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
giving	O
a	O
mo	O
Wound	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
3	O
Inches	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
day	O
of	O
March	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
being	O
at	O
a	O
Tavern	O
,	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
arose	O
about	O
Government	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
Challenged	O
each	O
other	O
into	O
the	O
Field	O
,	O
there	O
Fought	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Stafford	O
was	O
killed	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
fart	O
was	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
intimate	O
Friends	O
before	O
,	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
defence	O
,	O
rather	O
than	O
any	O
premed	O
ted	O
Malice	O
;	O
So	O
upon	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Franks	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
killing	O
Mr.	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
a	O
Pilot	O
belonging	O
to	O
Dover	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
Robinson	O
came	O
to	O
Whitehall	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Guard	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
Prisoner	O
interposed	O
and	O
put	O
him	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
him	O
over	O
Head	O
with	O
his	O
Halbert	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
likewise	O
that	O
the	O
decea	O
was	O
very	O
Rude	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
two	O
several	O
Assaults	O
upon	O
the	O
Guar	O
and	O
besides	O
struck	O
a	O
Grand-child	O
of	O
the	O
Lord	O
Grandersons	O
near	O
Privy-Chamber	O
;	O
and	O
called	O
them	O
Papists	O
Rogues	O
.	O
There	O
w	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Bradey	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Le	I-place
Bone	I-place
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Scrivenor	I-pers
,	O
the	O
2d	O
day	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Third	O
Year	O
of	O
King	O
James	O
the	O
Second	O
,	O
Wounding	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
left	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
Belly	O
,	O
3	O
Inches	O
deep	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
died	O
the	O
4th	O
instant	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prison	O
met	O
the	O
said	O
Scrivenor	O
in	O
the	O
High	O
way	O
and	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
a	O
Swore	O
,	O
God	O
Damn	O
you	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
stand	O
,	O
I'le	O
stab	O
you	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
Scrivenor	O
had	O
a	O
Wound	O
in	O
his	O
Groyn	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
bled	O
inwardly	O
,	O
the	O
Blood	O
being	O
coagulated	O
in	O
his	O
Body	O
.	O
But	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
one	O
Witness	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
declare	O
before	O
his	O
Death	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Wound	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
his	O
death	O
,	O
but	O
rather	O
by	O
drinking	O
of	O
stale	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
came	O
his	O
own	O
seeking	O
.	O
So	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joshua	B-pers
Salter	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Shooting	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Tinson	I-pers
with	O
Gun	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
own	O
Confession	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
time	O
when	O
the	O
Alaru	O
was	O
of	O
the	O
Irishmen	O
rising	O
in	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Prison	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
Watch	O
with	O
his	O
Gun	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
and	O
the	O
sai	O
Tynson	O
came	O
by	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
dark	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
speak	O
.	O
Whereupon	O
the	O
said	O
Salter	O
thought	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Irishman	O
,	O
or	O
one	O
who	O
designe	O
some	O
harm	O
to	O
the	O
Country	O
;	O
so	O
was	O
put	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
discharge	O
his	O
Gun	O
and	O
killed	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
Ambrose	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Sewell	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
about	O
Putney	B-place
Heath	I-place
,	O
of	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
Seal	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Sewell	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
Men	O
upon	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
Swear	O
positively	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
Robbed	O
him	O
,	O
yet	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
on	O
his	O
side	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Watch	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
of	O
one	O
Buckle	O
wh	O
is	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
who	O
Lodges	O
in	O
White	O
Fryers	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Lancelot	B-pers
Thornhill	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Thorne	I-pers
at	O
the	O
Globe	B-place
Tavern	I-place
in	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
of	O
2	O
silver	O
,	O
Tankards	O
value	O
15	O
l.	O
one	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
let	O
home	O
by	O
his	O
Wife	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Thorne	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
he	O
to	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
steal	O
the	O
Tankards	O
himself	O
,	O
but	O
laid	O
it	O
upon	O
another	O
person	O
that	O
was	O
fled	O
;	O
but	O
at	O
knowledged	O
that	O
he	O
sold	O
the	O
Tankard	O
to	O
the	O
Goldsmith	O
f	O
6	O
l.	O
17	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
they	O
were	O
stolen	O
yet	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Meeres	I-pers
and	O
Susannah	B-pers
Vicars	I-pers
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
Richard	B-pers
Goozey	I-pers
of	O
one	O
Ruff	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
3	O
Sheets	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
one	O
Skillet	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
smoothing	O
Iron	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
small	O
value	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
take	O
Lodging	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
lodged	O
there	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
,	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
slip	O
and	O
too	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
abovesaid	O
,	O
so	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
taking	O
the	O
Goods	O
only	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Slaughter	I-pers
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
in	O
Pinners	O
value	O
8	O
.	O
2	O
Hoods	O
20	O
d.	O
3	O
Neckcloths	O
18	O
d.	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Mens	O
Gloves	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
1	O
Frock	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
she	O
was	O
seen	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
a	O
Man	O
who	O
carried	O
the	O
Trunk	O
along	O
th	O
street	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
which	O
Trunk	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
he	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
Trunk	O
in	O
the	O
Kennel	O
an	O
tumbled	O
over	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
called	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
,	O
and	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Trunk	O
but	O
some	O
other	O
sorts	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
small	O
value	O
.	O
So	O
the	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Harrow	B-place
on	I-place
the	I-place
Hill	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicated	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
with	O
10	O
men	O
more	O
unknownnot	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
Esquire	B-pers
Page	I-pers
s	O
House	O
at	O
Uxenden	B-place
in	I-place
row	I-place
Parish	O
,	O
at	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
about	O
10	O
a	O
clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Closets	O
and	O
Trunks	O
b	O
a	O
Hatcher	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
having	O
first	O
bound	O
he	O
People	O
and	O
Servants	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
these	O
:	O
pair	O
of	O
Buttons	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
some	O
Pistols	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
1	O
s.	O
Silver	O
tons	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
one	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
a	O
Candlesticks	O
ue	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Medal	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Chafindish	O
40	O
s.	O
another	O
s.	O
20	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
and	O
4	O
other	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
ers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
considerable	O
value	O
,	O
besides	O
several	O
Gui	O
s	O
,	O
and	O
55	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
It	O
did	O
appear	O
upon	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
several	O
Guinea	O
's	O
and	O
old	O
Watch	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
owned	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Cuttr	O
's	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
nily	O
,	O
all	O
which	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
much	O
deny	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
ore	O
positively	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
although	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
uld	O
fain	O
have	O
incensed	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
Watch	O
s	O
given	O
him	O
by	O
some	O
other	O
persons	O
:	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Darsey	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Tayler	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Horton	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
dicted	O
,	O
Darsey	O
as	O
Principal	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
others	O
as	O
Accessaries	O
,	O
for	O
Murder	O
of	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lepper	I-pers
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
with	O
Rapier	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
moral	O
wound	O
near	O
to	O
his	O
left	O
Pap	O
,	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
6	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
died	O
instantly	O
.	O
It	O
hapned	O
us	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
reputed	O
Bawdy-House	O
in	O
Rose	B-place
street	I-place
at	I-place
Long-Acre	I-place
,	O
kept	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Taylor	O
,	O
the	O
deceased	O
was	O
ere	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
killed	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
Darsey	O
owned	O
the	O
Sword	O
,	O
d	O
had	O
threatned	O
Lepper	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
kill	O
him	O
whenever	O
he	O
d	O
him	O
in	O
Tayler	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
as	O
was	O
alledged	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Lepper	O
's	O
life	O
:	O
But	O
no	O
one	O
swore	O
that	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
seen	O
to	O
ll	O
Lepper	O
.	O
Taylor	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
Lepper	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
he	O
was	O
lled	O
.	O
Taylor	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
a	O
very	O
weak	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
ot	O
tell	O
what	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
from	O
one	O
story	O
to	O
another	O
,	O
only	O
at	O
st	O
declar	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
his	O
death	O
,	O
nor	O
how	O
he	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
killed	O
,	O
neither	O
could	O
she	O
be	O
persuaded	O
to	O
confess	O
any	O
ing	O
.	O
Darsey	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
when	O
the	O
Murder	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
some	O
Witness	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Murder	O
was	O
one	O
between	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
a	O
clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
another	O
place	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
on	O
his	O
side	O
did	O
testifie	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
So	O
after	O
a	O
full	O
and	O
large	O
Hearing	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
acquitted	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
at	O
all	O
appeared	O
against	O
the	O
said	O
rton	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
Indicated	O
for	O
stealing	O
81	O
Saddle-Trees	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Whips	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
proved	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
selling	O
of	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Saddle-Trees	O
in	O
Bishopsgate	O
street	O
,	O
nd	O
in	O
Southwark	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
All	O
which	O
was	O
fully	O
sworn	O
against	O
him	O
:	O
et	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
at	O
Queenhithe	O
ut	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Duaring	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
taking	O
away	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Stratford	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Edward	O
the	O
king	O
,	O
one	O
Peticoat	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
other	O
Coat	O
30	O
s.	O
6	O
Holland	O
Pillowbers	O
,	O
one	O
Silk	O
carf	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
a	O
Knife	O
tipt	O
with	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
good	O
value	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
Stratford	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
her	O
Mistress	O
was	O
abroad	O
,	O
she	O
ifled	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
a	O
Hood	O
upon	O
her	O
Head	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
no	O
Goods	O
from	O
her	O
Mistress	O
,	O
She	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
J	B-pers
-	I-pers
-S	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cap	O
50	O
s.	O
value	O
,	O
one	O
Porringer	O
20	O
s.	O
2	O
other	O
small	O
Cups	O
50	O
s.	O
4	O
Guinea	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
16	O
l.	O
in	O
Silver	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
could	O
not	O
charge	O
it	O
home	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
nothing	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
some	O
Witness	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
account	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
always	O
been	O
of	O
good	O
Reputation	O
,	O
but	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
hand	O
the	O
Constable	O
allowed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
his	O
Chest	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
saw	O
the	O
Chest	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
the	O
constable	O
was	O
much	O
blamed	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Coving	I-pers
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Tobacco	O
Box	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
15	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
from	O
Edward	B-pers
Hampsted	I-pers
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
but	O
Hampsted	O
,	O
who	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
positively	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
She	O
denied	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
a	O
Robbery	O
in	O
stealing	O
a	O
half	O
hundred	O
Iron	O
weights	O
worth	O
10	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
day	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
weights	O
in	O
the	O
Rubbish	O
at	O
Wapping	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	B-pers
owned	O
the	O
weights	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
them	O
restored	O
.	O
So	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Elisha	B-pers
Puppey	I-pers
,	O
aged	O
16	O
years	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
Webb	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
year	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
Tankard	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
yet	O
the	O
Jury	O
were	O
so	O
merciful	O
as	O
to	O
acquit	O
him	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
two	O
several	O
Felonies	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
,	O
and	O
one	O
John	B-pers
West	I-pers
of	O
3	O
Peticoasts	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
3	O
Coives	O
3	O
s.	O
Diaper	O
Napkins	O
3	O
s	O
one	O
Looking	O
Glass	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
Shirt	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
small	O
Goods	O
of	O
little	O
value	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
apprehended	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
further	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
their	O
House	O
were	O
both	O
broke	O
open	O
whilest	O
they	O
were	O
abroad	O
at	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Custody	O
,	O
as	O
was	O
clearly	O
proved	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
which	O
She	O
could	O
not	O
contrariwise	O
prove	O
.	O
She	O
called	O
a	O
Witness	O
or	O
two	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
she	O
bought	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
some	O
at	O
Bristol	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
at	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
White-Horse	O
in	O
Bedlam	O
;	O
so	O
being	O
found	O
in	O
several	O
stories	O
,	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Lofters	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
Holman	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Hill	I-place
.	O
It	O
was	O
evidenced	O
against	O
her	O
thus	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
drinking	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
another	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Tankard	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
custody	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
stealing	O
of	O
the	O
Tankard	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
several	O
who	O
proved	O
his	O
Reputation	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
very	O
honest	O
and	O
faithful	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
Rowland	B-pers
St.	I-pers
John	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
killing	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Rich	I-pers
a	O
Footman	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
wound	O
near	O
the	O
left	O
Pap	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
8	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
died	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Rich	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	B-place
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
Rich	O
struck	O
him	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
Blows	O
with	O
a	O
Stick	O
or	O
Club	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Rich	O
having	O
stunned	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
upon	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Sword	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
held	O
up	O
the	O
Sword	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
defence	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
Rich	O
fell	O
down	O
dead	O
.	O
All	O
this	O
was	O
proved	O
by	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Witness	O
was	O
produced	O
that	O
could	O
prove	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
the	O
said	O
Rich	O
any	O
manner	O
of	O
provocation	O
.	O
So	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
it	O
Special	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
killed	O
the	O
said	O
Rich	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
defence	O
of	O
himself	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Stoner	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
wound	O
upon	O
the	O
left	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
Belly	O
6	O
Inches	O
deep	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
about	O
one	O
a	O
clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
into	O
Drury	B-place
lane	I-place
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
fought	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
wounded	O
Mr.	O
Stoner	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
further	O
testified	O
also	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Stoner	O
had	O
no	O
Sword	O
,	O
nor	O
other	O
Weapon	O
.	O
And	O
Mr.	O
Walsingham	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
That	O
if	O
he	O
lived	O
he	O
must	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
Care	O
;	O
if	O
he	O
died	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
suffer	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Stoner	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Walsingham	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
the	O
Wound	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Stoner	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
persued	O
him	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
very	O
ill	O
Language	O
,	O
calling	O
of	O
him	O
Coward	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
And	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
draw	O
his	O
Sword	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
pulled	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
hair	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
fell	O
upon	O
his	O
sword	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
some	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
full	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
any	O
Affront	O
,	O
only	O
pulled	O
his	O
hair	O
,	O
after	O
Mr.	O
Walsingham	O
had	O
draw	O
his	O
sword	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Defence	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
further	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
drew	O
upon	O
a	O
Naked	O
Man	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
looked	O
upon	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
most	O
desperate	O
and	O
wilful	O
Act	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
beneath	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
.	O
So	O
after	O
a	O
distinct	O
Hearing	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
directed	O
the	O
Jury	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
careful	O
in	O
their	O
Verdict	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
it	O
to	O
their	O
own	O
Consciences	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
after	O
which	O
they	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
wilful	O
Murder	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
was	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
killing	O
John	B-pers
Harbin	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
wound	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
6	O
Inches	O
,	O
under	O
his	O
right	O
Arm-hole	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Evidence	O
he	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
day	O
of	O
May	O
1688	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
went	O
abroad	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
Mr	O
Harbin	O
returned	O
in	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
after	O
alone	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
much	O
wounded	O
,	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
swore	O
he	O
died	O
immediately	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
drest	O
his	O
wound	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
further	O
declared	O
by	O
very	O
credible	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
received	O
great	O
Abuses	O
while	O
they	O
went	O
abroad	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
Hide	B-place
Park	I-place
,	O
they	O
drew	O
upon	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
him	O
his	O
Life	O
and	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
the	O
deceased	O
had	O
struck	O
him	O
twice	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Thrust	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
confessed	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Coroner	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
was	O
lookt	O
upon	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
grudge	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
because	O
of	O
the	O
precedent	O
Quarrel	O
going	O
to	O
Hide	O
Park	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
further	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Harbin	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
very	O
abusive	O
Language	O
,	O
calling	O
him	O
Rogue	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
infamous	O
Titles	O
,	O
and	O
urged	O
him	O
to	O
fight	O
him	O
,	O
This	O
was	O
evidenced	O
by	O
the	O
Witness	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
side	O
,	O
how	O
that	O
they	O
quarrelled	O
about	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
about	O
10	O
a	O
clock	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
wounds	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
.	O
So	O
after	O
the	O
Court	O
had	O
well	O
weighed	O
the	O
whole	O
course	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
dangerously	O
wounding	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Nelson	I-pers
,	O
but	O
upon	O
his	O
Arraignment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
for	O
which	O
Trespass	O
and	O
Misdemeanor	O
the	O
Court	O
Fined	O
him	O
only	O
Ten	O
Groats	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
very	O
poor	O
Man	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Trotts	I-pers
for	O
the	O
same	O
Offence	O
as	O
Clark	O
,	O
was	O
Arraign	O
'd	O
and	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Sentence	O
past	O
on	O
him	O
as	O
yet	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Ashley	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
brown	O
Gelding	O
price	O
10	O
l.	O
from	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Whittear	I-pers
of	O
Tosseter	O
in	O
Northamptonshire	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
day	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
confessed	O
it	O
whilest	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Poultry	O
Compter	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Horse	O
instead	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
;	O
the	O
Horse	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Castle-Inn	O
in	O
Woodstreet	O
,	O
as	O
was	O
evidenced	O
by	O
the	O
Ostler	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Owner	O
of	O
the	O
Horse	O
had	O
his	O
Horse	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
likewise	O
charged	O
with	O
a	O
Tankard	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
at	O
Tosseter	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
no	O
Evidence	O
on	O
his	O
side	O
.	O
So	O
being	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samuel	B-pers
Knightly	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Emmerson	I-pers
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
dangerously	O
wounding	O
one	O
Richard	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
proved	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Knightly	O
strock	O
Hawkins	O
first	O
,	O
whil'st	O
he	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
part	O
them	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
fighting	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
both	O
complained	O
that	O
their	O
Heads	O
were	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
received	O
much	O
Abuse	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
parting	O
some	O
Dutchmen	O
that	O
were	O
Fighting	O
.	O
So	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Trespass	O
.	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Nelson	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
May	O
1688.	O
from	O
one	O
Charles	B-pers
Tippet	I-pers
unto	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
another	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
from	O
one	O
Miles	B-pers
Steed	I-pers
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
also	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
C	B-pers
-	I-pers
A	I-pers
Esquire	O
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Walter	B-pers
Littleton	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
day	O
of	O
May	O
1689.	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
wound	O
upon	O
the	O
Breast	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
6	O
Inches	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
deposed	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Littleton	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
;	O
were	O
drinking	O
in	O
a	O
Tavern	O
near	O
Charing	O
cross	O
,	O
where	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
arose	O
about	O
Mr.	O
Littletons	O
leaving	O
the	O
Regiment	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
Major	O
Littleton	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Mr.	O
A	O
-	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
put	O
by	O
his	O
Pass	O
:	O
But	O
after	O
Mr.	O
Littleton	O
was	O
killed	O
,	O
which	O
Mr.	O
A	O
-	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Malice	O
proved	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
between	O
them	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
killing	O
one	O
Edward	B-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
with	O
a	O
Musquet	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
shooting	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Belly	O
with	O
a	O
leaden	O
Bullet	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
wound	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
6	O
Inches	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
sworn	O
that	O
Bradshaw	O
was	O
upon	O
a	O
House	O
at	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
over	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
Gun	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
which	O
he	O
held	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
went	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
killed	O
him	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
a	O
Bullet	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
did	O
not	O
lay	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
charge	O
at	O
his	O
death	O
,	O
yet	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Beldam	I-pers
a	O
Butcher	O
,	O
Spencer	B-pers
Brandal	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
Tryed	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pawlet	I-pers
a	O
Soldier	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pauls	I-place
Shadwel	I-place
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
wound	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
dropt	O
down	O
dead	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Window	O
Bar	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
There	O
was	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
flatly	O
against	O
Beldam	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
knockt	O
down	O
Pawlet	O
with	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
against	O
Shaw	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
further	O
,	O
that	O
Beldam	O
was	O
very	O
abusive	O
,	O
and	O
knockt	O
down	O
several	O
besides	O
Pawlet	O
.	O
Another	O
Witness	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Brandal	O
knockt	O
down	O
Pawlet	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
person	O
could	O
tell	O
how	O
the	O
Quarrel	O
began	O
first	O
.	O
Two	O
Witnesses	O
swore	O
positively	O
against	O
Beldam	O
,	O
who	O
behaved	O
himself	O
very	O
uncivilly	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Surgeon	O
gave	O
Evidence	O
that	O
he	O
died	O
of	O
the	O
wound	O
immediately	O
.	O
Beldam	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
could	O
depose	O
any	O
thing	O
material	O
on	O
Beldam	O
's	O
side	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
some	O
had	O
been	O
before	O
hand	O
tampering	O
with	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Evidence	O
,	O
to	O
persuade	O
them	O
to	O
speak	O
less	O
than	O
they	O
really	O
knew	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Pawlet	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
swore	O
positively	O
against	O
Seldom	O
,	O
how	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
Blow	O
upon	O
Pawlet	O
with	O
the	O
Bar	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
She	O
knew	O
him	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
seeming	O
circumstantial	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
satisfie	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
enough	O
,	O
whereupon	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Sir	O
Henry	B-pers
Firebrass	I-pers
of	O
Four	O
Coach-Glasses	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
which	O
he	O
owned	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
but	O
denied	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
Tryal	O
;	O
having	O
no	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
his	O
Honesty	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
matter	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
brown	O
bay	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
from	O
Daniel	B-pers
Nicholas	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
Horses	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
sold	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Nicholas	O
owned	O
the	O
Horse	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Horse	O
of	O
one	O
Jenkins	O
at	O
the	O
Horse	O
Ferry	O
as	O
Westminster	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
several	O
on	O
his	O
side	O
,	O
who	O
proved	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Horse	O
of	O
Jenkins	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Abigail	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
one	O
holland	O
Frock	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
17	O
pieces	O
of	O
Linen	O
called	O
double	O
Clouts	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Peticoat	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
small	O
Goods	O
,	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
about	O
50	O
s.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
Woman	O
went	O
before	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
dropt	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
B	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
d	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
de	I-pers
Mo	I-pers
of	O
Westminster	B-place
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
Marc	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thereout	O
3	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
Flanders	O
Lac	O
value	O
15	O
d.	O
a	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
4	O
l.	O
a	O
Peticoat	O
3	O
l.	O
another	O
Silk	O
quilte	O
Peticoat	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
Childs	O
Gown	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Campagne	O
Coat	O
40	O
s.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Windows	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
were	O
broken	O
open	O
about	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
only	O
the	O
piec	O
of	O
Lace	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
the	O
Court	O
tha	O
She	O
bought	O
it	O
5	O
years	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Lace	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
th	O
Prosecutors	O
;	O
in	O
that	O
case	O
the	O
indictment	O
was	O
mislaid	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sams	I-pers
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
of	O
two	O
Coats	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
Sams	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
a	O
Bayonet	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
bidding	O
him	O
Stand	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Coats	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
swearing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
robbed	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
William	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
o	O
3	O
s.	O
8	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
.	O
He	O
likewise	O
attempted	O
to	O
Rob	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Men	O
more	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Norway	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
County	I-place
of	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
all	O
which	O
was	O
flatly	O
sworn	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
attested	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
abroad	O
armed	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Jack	O
Boots	O
on	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
Robbed	O
the	O
Men	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Coats	O
were	O
found	O
on	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
the	O
Countrey	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
Evidence	O
on	O
his	O
behalf	O
could	O
say	O
nothing	O
very	O
material	O
,	O
only	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
bred	O
well	O
heretofore	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
never	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
.	O
He	O
swore	O
God	O
damn	O
you	O
to	O
Sams	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
kill	O
him	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
put	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Fellows	O
in	O
Newgate	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
both	O
the	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Poor	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Cane	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
100	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
value	O
60	O
l.	O
2	O
more	O
value	O
30	O
l.	O
One	O
Emerald	O
Ring	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
another	O
Diamond	O
6	O
l.	O
2	O
other	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
3	O
Stone	O
Rings	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
and	O
Chattels	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
,	O
as	O
abovesaid	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
Swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
seen	O
to	O
hover	O
about	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
9	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
was	O
produced	O
that	O
could	O
Swear	O
positively	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
yet	O
they	O
were	O
lookt	O
upon	O
to	O
be	O
persons	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
Life	O
.	O
However	O
they	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Alice	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Fenton	I-pers
.	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
Indicted	O
the	O
two	O
former	O
as	O
principal	O
the	O
latter	O
as	O
Accessary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Buck-skin	O
Gloves	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Drawers	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
about	O
5	O
l.	O
In	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
not	O
strenuous	O
enough	O
to	O
fasten	O
it	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Stealing	O
2	O
Cocks	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
28	O
Hens	O
40	O
s.	O
from	O
a	O
Waggoner	O
coming	O
between	O
Acton	O
and	O
London	O
to	O
Market	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
which	O
Goods	O
were	O
owned	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Williams	O
's	O
Custody	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
:	O
Watson	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Williams	O
when	O
he	O
stole	O
them	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
but	O
Williams	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Felton	I-pers
were	O
all	O
three	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
taking	O
away	O
one	O
black	O
Hat	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
Knives	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
36	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
Numbered	O
,	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Stansom	O
was	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
Thieves	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
the	O
Trunks	O
were	O
broke	O
open	O
about	O
9	O
or	O
10	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Felton	O
was	O
met	O
standing	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
all	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Hat	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
Felton	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
Davis	O
left	O
his	O
Staff	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
Bed	O
cloaths	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Watkins	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Company	O
.	O
Felton	O
discovered	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
directed	O
the	O
Countrymen	O
where	O
to	O
Apprehend	O
them	O
at	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
threatned	O
Atkinson	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
That	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
hang	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
hang	O
him	O
(	O
viz	O
.	O
Atkinson	O
:	O
)	O
And	O
Felton	O
Swore	O
Damn	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
Fire	O
some	O
of	O
their	O
Houses	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
Newgate	O
.	O
Watkins	O
denied	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
did	O
Davis	O
.	O
Felton	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
there	O
were	O
Thieves	O
in	O
the	O
poor	O
Mans	O
House	O
and	O
so	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
several	O
Stories	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
lookt	O
upon	O
and	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
all	O
of	O
a	O
Gang	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
wicked	O
Persons	O
.	O
So	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hubbard	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
George	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Daniel	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
all	O
Four	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Durel	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
carrying	O
away	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Ondirons	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
Laced	O
Neck	O
cloths	O
6	O
s.	O
one	O
Flowered	O
Peticoat	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
small	O
Goods	O
of	O
little	O
value	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
,	O
upon	O
search	O
,	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
Whitecross	O
street	O
,	O
in	O
one	O
Blizzard	O
's	O
House	O
(	O
viz	O
.	O
)	O
the	O
pair	O
of	O
Ondirons	O
,	O
which	O
George	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
carry	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Whitecross	O
street	O
,	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Ribbonfound	O
in	O
Hubbards	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Ribbon	O
in	O
Gregories	O
Shirt	O
eller	O
,	O
which	O
gave	O
great	O
Suspicion	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
In	O
their	O
Defence	O
White	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Ondirons	O
of	O
one	O
Susannah	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
ut	O
would	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
found	O
in	O
divers	O
Stories	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Proof	O
that	O
Gregory	O
stole	O
the	O
Ondirons	O
,	O
nor	O
the	O
her	O
Ribbons	O
,	O
only	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
one	O
Susannah	O
Jones	O
,	O
ut	O
that	O
they	O
avail	O
'd	O
them	O
little	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
found	O
Guilty	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Doller	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
uttering	O
offalse	O
Money	O
.	O
It	O
appears	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
amongst	O
some	O
Persons	O
who	O
offered	O
false	O
money	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
one	O
Thirteen	O
pence	O
half	O
penny	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
produced	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
bag	O
of	O
false	O
Money	O
,	O
besides	O
both	O
Shillings	O
and	O
half	O
Crowns	O
,	O
and	O
Five	O
Shilling	O
Pieces	O
of	O
our	O
English	O
Coyn	O
,	O
be	O
des	O
some	O
Dollars	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
brass	O
Five	O
Shilling	O
Piece	O
and	O
about	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
1688	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
Drink	O
with	O
one	O
Price	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
meer	O
Stranger	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
good	O
,	O
Price	O
having	O
the	O
other	O
Money	O
in	O
the	O
bag	O
.	O
So	O
e	O
was	O
Discharged	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
having	O
in	O
her	O
Custody	O
a	O
certain	O
arcel	O
of	O
Clippings	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
diminished	O
from	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coyne	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
also	O
a	O
Rubbing	O
Stone	O
and	O
a	O
Melting	O
Pot	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Lodging	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
intend	O
to	O
elt	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
new	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Melting	O
Pot	O
.	O
So	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
without	O
a	O
seasonable	O
Caution	O
from	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
beware	O
of	O
tampering	O
in	O
the	O
like	O
Nature	O
again	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Kirby	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Pauls	I-place
Covent-garden	I-place
,	O
tried	O
or	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
roke	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Reese	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
robbing	O
him	O
of	O
a	O
Coat	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
Cloth	O
Wastecoat	O
15	O
s.	O
4	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
28	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Ruffles	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
Crevat	O
15	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Sleeves	O
12	O
s.	O
5	O
d.	O
3	O
yards	O
of	O
Persian	O
Silk	O
,	O
and	O
40	O
odd	O
pounds	O
in	O
money	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
plain	O
that	O
the	O
Coat	O
was	O
seen	O
upon	O
Kirby	O
's	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
found	O
(	O
some	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
)	O
by	O
Gardner	O
's	O
direction	O
;	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Key	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
James	O
's	O
Pocket	O
,	O
as	O
his	O
Breeches	O
lay	O
by	O
the	O
Beds-side	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Gardner	O
confest	O
that	O
he	O
Robbed	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
a	O
Back	O
way	O
to	O
let	O
Kirby	O
in	O
,	O
which	O
Evidence	O
was	O
corroboraed	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Jones	O
,	O
how	O
that	O
Gardner	O
directed	O
her	O
to	O
one	O
Coppingers	O
on	O
Tower	O
hill	O
,	O
where	O
under	O
some	O
Bricks	O
was	O
a	O
Bag	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
accordingly	O
.	O
It	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
that	O
they	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Doors	O
being	O
open	O
,	O
all	O
which	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
Gardner	O
confest	O
upon	O
the	O
Tryal	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
.	O
Kirby	O
had	O
not	O
so	O
strong	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
only	O
he	O
was	O
let	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
by	O
Gardner	O
,	O
as	O
Gardner	O
confest	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
lookt	O
upon	O
as	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
in	O
Law	O
.	O
So	O
after	O
a	O
distinct	O
Hearing	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
acquired	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Katharine	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Walter	B-pers
South	I-pers
Esq	O
.	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
4	O
Silver	O
Salvers	O
value	O
18	O
l.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Candlesticks	O
value	O
9	O
l.	O
4	O
Silver	O
Plates	O
8	O
l	O
,	O
3	O
Silver	O
Boxes	O
12	O
l.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Pots	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Jug	O
of	O
Silver	O
50	O
s.	O
a	O
Bason	O
8	O
l.	O
a	O
Cup	O
4	O
l.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Bell	O
7	O
l.	O
9	O
Spoons	O
4	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
9	O
other	O
Spoons	O
45	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Pot	O
40	O
s.	O
12	O
Silver	O
Sales	O
11	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
12	O
silver	O
handed	O
Knives	O
6	O
l.	O
a	O
Camblet	O
Cloak	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
and	O
Plate	O
,	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
125	O
l.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
that	O
Mr.	O
South	O
's	O
Chamber	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appeared	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
she	O
stole	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
,	O
altho	O
she	O
had	O
confest	O
before	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Plate	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Goodman	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
sold	O
some	O
Plate	O
to	O
one	O
Jolly	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
in	O
Lombard-street	O
.	O
So	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
but	O
circumstantial	O
,	O
and	O
somewhat	O
dubious	O
,	O
after	O
a	O
long	O
Hearing	O
She	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ingham	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Forgery	O
,	O
in	O
making	O
a	O
false	O
Warrant	O
,	O
procuring	O
one	O
Edward	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
to	O
be	O
discharged	O
out	O
of	O
Newgate	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
sent	O
a	O
Writing	O
for	O
his	O
Discharge	O
signed	O
by	O
two	O
Justices	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Ri	O
.	O
Fowler	O
,	O
and	O
H.	O
Roe	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Roe	O
was	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
that	O
was	O
none	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
dated	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sollicited	O
him	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
Justice	O
of	O
Peace	O
his	O
Head	O
to	O
a	O
Warrant	O
for	O
the	O
Discharge	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
get	O
some	O
Guinea	O
's	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
that	O
Effect	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
4	O
l.	O
that	O
morning	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
forged	O
the	O
Hands	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
But	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
all	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
yet	O
in	O
the	O
end	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Forgery	O
.	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Fortunate	B-pers
Frumental	I-pers
3	O
Mantua	O
Gowns	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s	O
8	O
pair	O
of	O
Sleeves	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
Peticoat	O
6	O
s.	O
3	O
other	O
Peticoats	O
24	O
s.	O
with	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
l.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
found	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Gowns	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
about	O
9	O
a	O
clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
carried	O
away	O
in	O
a	O
Trunk	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Gown	O
of	O
two	O
Fellows	O
that	O
drank	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
who	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
.	O
Denying	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
She	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Jonas	B-pers
Ratcliffe	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
from	O
Eliza	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
proved	O
by	O
credible	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
in	O
Hounds	O
Ditch	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
Tryal	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
given	O
him	O
by	O
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Rape	O
committed	O
upon	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Eliza	B-pers
Penn	I-pers
a	O
Virgin	O
of	O
the	O
age	O
of	O
Ten	O
years	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Taylor	O
,	O
and	O
workt	O
in	O
an	O
upper	O
chamber	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Child	O
went	O
up	O
for	O
a	O
Needle	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
committed	O
the	O
Rape	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
some	O
few	O
days	O
after	O
question	O
'd	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
leapt	O
out	O
at	O
a	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
hiding	O
himself	O
in	O
a	O
Ditch	O
.	O
The	O
Midwife	O
urg	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
hurt	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
that	O
he	O
Entered	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
So	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
made	O
a	O
Rape	O
,	O
only	O
an	O
Assault	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Bargeer	I-pers
and	O
Abigail	B-pers
Bargeer	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Rape	O
committed	O
upon	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Deer	I-pers
in	O
St.	B-place
Katharines	I-place
Parish	I-place
,	O
a	O
Virgin	O
of	O
about	O
16	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
did	O
entice	O
her	O
from	O
her	O
Aunts	O
House	O
in	O
St.	O
Katharines	O
,	O
to	O
the	B-place
Cock	I-place
in	I-place
Aldersgate-street	I-place
,	O
and	O
there	O
made	O
her	O
Lie	O
all	O
Night	O
with	O
them	O
in	O
one	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Morrow	O
kept	O
her	O
all	O
Day	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
next	O
Night	O
in	O
another	O
place	O
in	O
St.	O
Katharines	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
in	O
Bed	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lay	O
with	O
her	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
Bargeer	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
Bed	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
perswaded	O
her	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
strugling	O
and	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
stopt	O
her	O
Month	O
,	O
and	O
pinch	O
'd	O
her	O
and	O
abused	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
most	O
egregious	O
manner	O
,	O
Swearing	O
at	O
her	O
and	O
puting	O
her	O
in	O
great	O
Fear	O
,	O
saying	O
.	O
He	O
would	O
throw	O
her	O
out	O
at	O
a	O
Window	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
from	O
him	O
:	O
So	O
far	O
was	O
produced	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
John	B-pers
Bargeer	I-pers
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
offered	O
Marriage	O
to	O
her	O
before	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
Bed	O
at	O
the	O
Cock	O
,	O
and	O
disowned	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
lawfully	O
Married	O
to	O
Abigail	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
an	O
Inclination	O
to	O
Marry	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
was	O
a	O
kind	O
of	O
Extenuation	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
hesitated	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
consented	O
to	O
write	O
a	O
Letter	O
to	O
one	O
that	O
was	O
her	O
Aunt	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
know	O
of	O
her	O
Welfare	O
.	O
&	O
c.	O
Abigail	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
hurt	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
denied	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
intention	O
of	O
Evil	O
against	O
her	O
.	O
So	O
that	O
after	O
a	O
clear	O
hearing	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
he	O
for	O
committing	O
the	O
Rape	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
for	O
Abetting	O
him	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
Wife	O
of	O
Zachary	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Gloves	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Isabella	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
December	O
1688	O
.	O
Baker	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Gloves	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
hands	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
Year	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
very	O
good	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
proceeded	O
from	O
Malice	O
rather	O
than	O
from	O
Justice	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Horne	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Hollaway	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
taking	O
away	O
36	O
yards	O
of	O
Cotton	O
Ribboning	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
and	O
Two	O
Shillings	O
six	O
Pence	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
could	O
not	O
Swear	O
to	O
the	O
breaking	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Cotton	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Pocket	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
say	O
but	O
little	O
or	O
nothing	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
only	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Ribbon	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Adam	B-pers
Osborn	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Drugget	O
Frock	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
brass	O
Cock	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
Buff	O
Belt	O
5	O
s.	O
The	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
Swore	O
positively	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Frock	O
upon	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
owned	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Frock	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
produced	O
the	O
Salesman	O
of	O
whom	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Frock	O
;	O
After	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
not	O
so	O
forward	O
in	O
his	O
Evidence	O
at	O
to	O
the	O
particular	O
marks	O
of	O
the	O
Frock	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
credible	O
Witnesses	O
for	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Edmond	B-pers
Buckley	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
one	O
Book	O
called	O
Virgil	O
,	O
with	O
Cuts	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
Book	O
called	O
Markham	O
's	O
a	O
Countrey	O
Farmer	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
could	O
Swear	O
nothing	O
positive	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Books	O
of	O
two	O
Boys	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
Discharged	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Bullen	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Peter	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
Robbed	O
Thomas	B-pers
Meadows	I-pers
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
January	O
of	O
one	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
two	O
old	O
Coats	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
other	O
coats	O
about	O
3	O
s.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
were	O
Meadows	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
men	O
broke	O
in	O
upon	O
his	O
House	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
and	O
his	O
Family	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Rifled	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
Katherine	O
Wheel	O
at	O
Mile	O
End	O
.	O
Bullen	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
did	O
not	O
Swear	O
that	O
Miller	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
Back	O
Door	O
.	O
So	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Savadge	I-pers
of	O
Hendon	B-place
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Cows	O
,	O
price	O
each	O
3	O
d.	O
13	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Buckingham	I-pers
;	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
left	O
his	O
cows	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
our	O
Smith	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
called	O
Master	O
,	O
drove	O
away	O
the	O
Cows	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
one	O
Robert	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
drove	O
the	O
other	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
what	O
did	O
,	O
was	O
persuant	O
to	O
his	O
Masters	O
Orders	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
be	O
Felony	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
T	B-pers
-	I-pers
H	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
stealing	O
a	O
Stone	O
Horse	O
value	O
50	O
l.	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Paston	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
and	O
breaking	O
the	O
Stable	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
Horse	O
in	O
his	O
custody	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
stopt	O
,	O
the	O
Horse	O
was	O
owned	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Rogers	O
to	O
be	O
Mr.	O
Paston	O
's	O
,	O
William	O
denied	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
Tryal	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
afrighted	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
be	O
did	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
but	O
discharged	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Peter	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
from	O
one	O
George	B-pers
Blow	I-pers
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
three	O
men	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
as	O
Mrs.	O
Blow	O
knew	O
by	O
the	O
Token	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
with	O
n	O
Orenge-coloured	O
Ribon	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
pon	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
at	O
the	O
Bear	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Red	O
Lyon	O
Fields	O
.	O
But	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
weigh	O
with	O
the	O
Jury	O
enough	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ricks	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
taking	O
away	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
2	O
Flanders	O
lac't	O
Crevats	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Ruffles	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sleeves	O
4	O
s.	O
2	O
Neckcloths	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
aces	O
and	O
Linens	O
of	O
a	O
considerable	O
value	O
.	O
All	O
which	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
deny	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Woolfe	I-pers
,	O
Hugh	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
Toby	B-pers
Sancky	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tuckey	I-pers
were	O
all	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
Four	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Richard	B-pers
Woolfe	I-pers
,	O
who	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
,	O
being	O
Bailed	O
out	O
)	O
did	O
steal	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
from	O
Isaac	B-pers
Light	I-pers
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
The	O
said	O
r	O
Light	O
told	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
custody	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
all	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
be	O
mist	O
his	O
Tankard	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
Ligut	O
's	O
House	O
altogether	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Light	O
would	O
have	O
compounded	O
with	O
them	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
none	O
to	O
confirm	O
Light	O
's	O
Evidence	O
,	O
they	O
have	O
all	O
Four	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Moses	B-pers
Hidgcock	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Axe	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Augres	O
and	O
Chizels	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Carpenters	O
Tools	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
axton	I-pers
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
found	O
then	O
in	O
,	O
be	O
Yard	O
by	O
Wild-house	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
thought	O
he	O
had	O
as	O
much	O
Right	O
to	O
as	O
any	O
one	O
else	O
.	O
So	O
in	O
the	O
Conclusion	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
Goodborn	I-pers
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
which	O
Coat	O
was	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
direction	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
found	O
at	O
a	O
Pawnbrokers	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
laid	O
it	O
for	O
7	O
s.	O
yet	O
She	O
denied	O
it	O
at	O
er	O
Tryal	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
gave	O
her	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
her	O
confess	O
,	O
all	O
which	O
signified	O
nothing	O
,	O
for	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Feloly	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Christopher	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
robbing	O
Samuel	B-pers
Locker	I-pers
on	O
the	O
25th	O
f	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
3	O
holland	O
Shirts	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Drawers	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
Wastecoat	O
and	O
a	O
Looking-Glass	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
he	O
confessed	O
when	O
e	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
House-back	O
at	O
St.	O
Albans	O
from	O
Samuel	O
Locker	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
at	O
his	O
Tryal	O
yet	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
Four	O
Dutchmen	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
John	O
Webber	O
,	O
desired	O
their	O
Jury	O
might	O
consist	O
of	O
half	O
English	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
Out-landish	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
granted	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
Their	O
Names	O
follow	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sanders	I-pers
Abraham	B-pers
Demorre	I-pers
William	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
Abraham	B-pers
Montford	I-pers
John	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
Isaac	B-pers
Lawrell	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kipping	I-pers
Gerrard	B-pers
Mausaaker	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Arundell	I-pers
Nicholas	B-pers
Romane	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Swayne	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Musaake	I-pers
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Sam	I-pers
,	O
Erect	B-pers
Vandoventer	I-pers
,	O
Lodwick	B-pers
Marss	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Baltas	I-pers
were	O
four	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Webber	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
f	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
value	O
s.	O
upon	O
his	O
Breast	O
near	O
to	O
his	O
left	O
Pap	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
6	O
Inches	O
,	O
f	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
Died	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
one	O
Gerrard	B-pers
Vanoven	I-pers
amongst	O
them	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
since	O
fled	O
.	O
The	O
Murther	O
was	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
these	O
Dutchman	O
Lodged	O
at	O
the	O
Bell	O
Inn	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
and	O
two	O
ore	O
came	O
to	O
them	O
and	O
Drank	O
with	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Tap	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
serve	O
,	O
before	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
Cane	O
from	O
one	O
Joshua	B-pers
Hood	I-pers
in	O
he	O
Street	O
,	O
about	O
9	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
pursuing	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
their	O
Quarters	O
and	O
bringing	O
a	O
Constable	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
his	O
Cane	O
,	O
nd	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
perceiving	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
out	O
and	O
forced	O
the	O
Constable	O
upon	O
the	O
,	O
and	O
threatned	O
all	O
that	O
came	O
nigh	O
them	O
,	O
Drawing	O
their	O
Swords	O
,	O
and	O
clashing	O
them	O
about	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
outragious	O
manner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
said	O
Webber	O
coming	O
amongst	O
them	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Dutchmen	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
thrust	O
his	O
Sword	O
into	O
the	O
said	O
Webber	O
's	O
Body	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
Swear	O
which	O
of	O
them	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
gave	O
the	O
Thrust	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
said	O
that	O
Sam	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
all	O
Bloody	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
his	O
Sword	O
blunted	O
.	O
Another	O
Constable	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
the	O
Persons	O
that	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
Bell	O
Inn	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
Swore	O
that	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
Mortal	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
prickt	O
to	O
the	O
very	O
Heart	O
.	O
Head	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Tap	O
house	O
to	O
the	O
Bell	O
Inn	O
to	O
ask	O
for	O
his	O
Cane	O
,	O
they	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
his	O
Sword	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
Cane	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
Constable	O
was	O
called	O
,	O
they	O
drew	O
their	O
Swords	O
as	O
abovesaid	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
in	O
Drink	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
when	O
the	O
Murther	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
And	O
they	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
,	O
by	O
an	O
Interpreter	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Hood	O
staggered	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
denied	O
that	O
they	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
any	O
Man	O
.	O
So	O
after	O
a	O
large	O
hearing	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Smithson	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
robbing	O
Mary	B-pers
Belcher	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Box	O
tipt	O
with	O
Silver	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
a	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
6	O
l.	O
a	O
Silk	O
Peticoat	O
laced	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Mrs.	O
Belcher	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
lost	O
several	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
any	O
thing	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elinor	B-pers
Royle	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tickle	I-pers
,	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Francis	B-pers
Hillier	I-pers
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
20	O
yards	O
of	O
Lace	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
several	O
Gloves	O
40	O
s.	O
3	O
yards	O
of	O
Lawn	O
10	O
s.	O
2	O
Caps	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
sundry	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
about	O
7	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Shop	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Gloves	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
that	O
Hillier	O
brought	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
called	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
which	O
did	O
her	O
little	O
good	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
but	O
circumstantial	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
from	O
Ann	B-pers
Gifford	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
18	O
l.	O
