TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
and	O
Queens	O
Commissions	O
OF	O
THE	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
and	O
Thursday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
9th	O
,	O
and	O
10th	O
Days	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
1689	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
First	O
Year	O
of	O
Their	O
MAJESTIES	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
and	O
Thursday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
9th	O
and	O
10th	O
Days	O
of	O
October	O
1689	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pilkington	I-pers
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
follow	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Lapley	I-pers
Daniel	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Atwood	I-pers
John	B-pers
Pursell	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Emmet	I-pers
Isaac	B-pers
Dyghton	I-pers
Arthur	B-pers
Eveling	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Essington	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Phillingham	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Goreing	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Leaver	I-pers
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
Jonas	B-pers
Morley	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Mead	I-pers
John	B-pers
Milgate	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
King	I-pers
William	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Arundall	I-pers
Abraham	B-pers
Lock	I-pers
William	B-pers
Russell	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Levigg	I-pers
Stephen	B-pers
Sharpe	I-pers
William	B-pers
Munday	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Pearson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
these	O
:	O
Abel	B-pers
Dodson	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
George	B-pers
Dodson	I-pers
,	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
wound	O
near	O
his	O
Left-Eye	O
with	O
a	O
Musquet	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
6	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
Indicted	O
for	O
wilful	O
Murther	O
by	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Musquet	O
was	O
shot	O
off	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
accidently	O
,	O
firing	O
it	O
off	O
into	O
a	O
Ditch	O
near	O
where	O
the	O
Deceased	O
stood	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Malice	O
against	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Stranger	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
all	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Latham	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
Alice	B-pers
Haman	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Strand	B-place
,	O
making	O
an	O
Assault	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
taking	O
away	O
a	O
Silver	O
Medal	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
declared	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
met	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
upon	O
her	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
some	O
other	O
Women	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
did	O
not	O
swear	O
positively	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Medal	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
one	O
that	O
helpt	O
to	O
commit	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
all	O
which	O
was	O
very	O
clearly	O
sworn	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
lookt	O
upon	O
as	O
an	O
idle	O
Housewife	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Hoane	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Maudlin	I-place
,	I-place
Old	I-place
Fish-street	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
evidenced	O
against	O
them	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
in	O
the	O
very	O
Act	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
found	O
upon	O
them	O
were	O
one	O
Silver	O
Salt	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
a	O
Periwig	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Silk	O
Hood	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
small	O
parcel	O
more	O
of	O
Goods	O
,	O
amounting	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
about	O
30	O
s.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
no	O
concern	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
matter	O
being	O
plainly	O
evinced	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Bacon	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ethelborrow	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Ward	I-place
of	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
day	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
ten	O
Hats	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
ten	O
Hatbands	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
Coat	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
small	O
Goods	O
of	O
little	O
value	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
unknown	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
chiefly	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
they	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
fled	O
away	O
from	O
the	O
Watch	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
taken	O
,	O
the	O
Box	O
of	O
Hats	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
custody	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Wagon	O
belonging	O
to	O
Yarmouth	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
hired	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
Box	O
into	O
Southwark	O
by	O
another	O
Man	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
:	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Wights	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
marrying	O
one	O
Letitia	B-pers
Kirkham	I-pers
at	O
Dublin	O
in	O
Ireland	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
day	O
of	O
January	O
in	O
the	O
35th	O
year	O
of	O
King	O
Charles	O
II	O
.	O
and	O
afterwards	O
for	O
marrying	O
one	O
Thomasin	B-pers
West	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Kingdom	O
of	O
England	O
at	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Duke	I-place
Place	I-place
.	O
The	O
chief	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Kirkham	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
Chamber	O
in	O
St.	O
Andrew	O
's	O
Parish	O
in	O
Dublin	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
West	O
in	O
Dukes	O
Place	O
in	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
her	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
.	O
So	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Dye	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Pauls	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
24	O
Yards	O
of	O
Norwich	O
Stuff	O
,	O
value	O
42	O
s.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Phillips	O
's	O
Man	O
,	O
who	O
declared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
to	O
cheapen	O
some	O
Crape	O
,	O
and	O
whiles	O
his	O
back	O
was	O
turn	O
'd	O
,	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Stuff	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
altho	O
'	O
the	O
Stuff	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
no	O
Witness	O
to	O
prove	O
their	O
Lives	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
honest	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Dye	O
:	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
away	O
from	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Delaster	I-pers
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
one	O
Allamode	O
Scarf	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
one	O
Quilt	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
positive	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
whole	O
and	O
she	O
producing	O
persons	O
as	O
to	O
her	O
honest	O
Behaviour	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Stealing	O
on	O
the	O
23	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
one	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
from	O
one	O
Bernard	B-pers
Bartlet	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
the	O
only	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
declared	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Watch	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
produced	O
the	O
Watch	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
Apprehended	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
that	O
ever	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
the	O
Jury	O
was	O
so	O
well	O
Informed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Peter	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Syms	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Dofell	I-pers
at	O
the	B-place
Swan	I-place
in	I-place
Clare-Market	I-place
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
that	O
they	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
drank	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
Deane	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
the	O
Plates	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
search	O
in	O
Deanes	O
Britches	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
denyed	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
that	O
affected	O
Syms	O
:	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Deane	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Agnes	B-pers
Charles	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Anne	B-pers
Constable	I-pers
on	O
the	O
14	O
of	O
May	O
of	O
one	O
Bonelace	O
Cornet	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
another	O
Cornet	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
an	O
Apron	O
2	O
s.	O
three	O
Lace	O
Coifes	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
Smock	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
4	O
Ells	O
of	O
Holland	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
another	O
Smock	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
that	O
the	O
Lace	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Custody	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
which	O
was	O
owned	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
Witness	O
to	O
prove	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
look't	O
upon	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
after	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
,	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
9	O
s.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Huggins	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Perjury	O
,	O
in	O
swearing	O
before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
worth	O
40	O
l.	O
per	O
Annum	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
personal	O
Estate	O
at	O
Newport	O
Pagnel	O
,	O
whereas	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
worth	O
so	O
much	O
which	O
he	O
confessed	O
upon	O
his	O
second	O
arraignment	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
throw	O
himself	O
upon	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
;	O
and	O
besides	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
Witnesses	O
that	O
proved	O
it	O
fully	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Perjury	O
.	O
PARTY-JURY	O
.	O
Jonas	B-pers
Motley	I-pers
Jeremy	B-pers
Gazeat	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Mead	I-pers
David	B-pers
Minnell	I-pers
John	B-pers
Milgate	I-pers
Claudius	B-pers
Vannier	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
King	I-pers
Isaac	B-pers
Monnicot	I-pers
William	B-pers
Fynch	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Levalidy	I-pers
Abraham	B-pers
Lock	I-pers
Peter	B-pers
Kasaron	I-pers
.	O
James	B-pers
Walnitch	I-pers
a	O
Frenchman	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
on	O
the	O
22	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
whereupon	O
a	O
party	O
Jury	O
was	O
Sworn	O
as	O
above	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
at	O
Westminster	B-place
,	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
one	O
Mathew	B-pers
Christopher	I-pers
and	O
two	O
other	O
Men	O
,	O
who	O
are	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
played	O
at	O
Dice	O
,	O
and	O
Bailey	O
being	O
amongst	O
them	O
,	O
a	O
quarrel	O
arose	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
threw	O
a	O
Cup	O
of	O
drink	O
into	O
Christophers	O
face	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
their	O
Swords	O
were	O
drawn	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
received	O
a	O
Wound	O
of	O
6	O
inches	O
from	O
the	O
said	O
Mathew	B-pers
Christopher	I-pers
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
immediately	O
dyed	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
that	O
affected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Discharged	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Noon	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anne	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
John	B-pers
Lord	I-pers
Lovelace	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
one	O
Cloth	O
Cloak	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
a	O
Frize	O
Coat	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
another	O
Coat	O
35	O
s.	O
a	O
Caster	O
Hat	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Evidence	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Coach-house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
about	O
12	O
or	O
1	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
taken	O
till	O
about	O
eight	O
days	O
after	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Lace	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
rip	O
's	O
off	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Coats	O
;	O
which	O
Lace	O
was	O
owned	O
by	O
the	O
Servants	O
of	O
the	O
Lord	O
Lovelace	O
,	O
and	O
prov	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
Gold	O
and	O
Silver	O
Woman	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
her	O
and	O
another	O
Boy	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
called	O
out	O
of	O
Newgate	O
to	O
Witness	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
Said	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
met	O
him	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
and	O
shewed	O
him	O
the	O
Lace	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
sold	O
to	O
the	O
Woman	O
above	O
said	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
Evidence	O
that	O
could	O
prove	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
other	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Coach-house	O
,	O
although	O
he	O
did	O
confest	O
it	O
before	O
;	O
yet	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Maye	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
that	O
the	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Anne	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
break	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Stanton	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
taking	O
one	O
Gown	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
Amber	O
Necklace	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
four	O
Silk	O
Hoods	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
Cornet	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
four	O
yards	O
of	O
Flanders	O
Lace	O
value	O
20	O
s	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
about	O
14	O
l.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
plain	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
altho	O
'	O
she	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
yet	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
that	O
she	O
pawned	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Noble	O
a	O
Broker	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Handscome	I-pers
of	O
Westminster	B-place
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
taking	O
from	O
Edward	B-pers
Symons	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24	O
day	O
of	O
September	O
one	O
black	O
lac't	O
Tippet	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
Apron	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
18	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
in	O
Guineas	O
:	O
It	O
was	O
Evidenced	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
were	O
inmates	O
together	O
.	O
And	O
on	O
the	O
24	O
of	O
September	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
missing	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
:	O
upon	O
search	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Guineas	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
scattered	O
about	O
a	O
shelf	O
in	O
a	O
Closet	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
dropt	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
bosom	O
.	O
They	O
could	O
give	O
but	O
a	O
lame	O
Account	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
Guinea	O
's	O
,	O
nor	O
of	O
their	O
Lives	O
and	O
Conversation	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
seeming	O
to	O
proceed	O
some	O
what	O
from	O
Malice	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Moss	I-pers
of	O
St	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
value	O
27	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
August	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Lord	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
person	O
(	O
one	O
Reynolds	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
House	O
and	O
drank	O
in	O
the	O
Cup	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
the	O
Cup	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
one	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
Cup	O
,	O
so	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Delacore	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Capt	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
in	O
Red-Lyon	B-place
Court	I-place
in	I-place
Watling-street	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
two	O
Silver	O
Watches	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
one	O
Silver	O
,	O
hilted	O
Sword	O
40	O
s.	O
two	O
Rings	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
silk	O
Peticoat	O
10	O
l.	O
one	O
cloth	O
Coat	O
with	O
Silver	O
Button	O
10	O
l.	O
one	O
piece	O
of	O
coined	O
Silver	O
20	O
s.	O
with	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
considerable	O
value	O
,	O
amounting	O
near	O
to	O
400	O
l.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
a	O
Sunday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
day	O
above	O
mentioned	O
,	O
the	O
Family	O
being	O
at	O
Church	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
come	O
out	O
at	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
lock	O
it	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
another	O
man	O
,	O
with	O
things	O
in	O
their	O
custody	O
and	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
viz	O
.	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Rings	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
in	O
Southwark	O
.	O
He	O
denied	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
given	O
him	O
by	O
another	O
Man	O
to	O
keep	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
indeed	O
very	O
fully	O
proved'upon	O
him	O
,	O
altho	O
'	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
never	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
Yet	O
,	O
after	O
a	O
distinct	O
Hearing	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Solomon	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
uttering	O
False	O
and	O
Counterfeit	O
Money	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
at	O
a	O
Shoemaker	O
's	O
Shop	O
where	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
buy	O
shoes	O
,	O
was	O
there	O
discovered	O
to	O
be	O
False	O
.	O
And	O
it	O
was	O
further	O
evidenced	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
Half-Crowns	O
and	O
Shillings	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
:	O
And	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
great	O
handful	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
amongst	O
the	O
Croud	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
all	O
naught	O
,	O
and	O
conjectured	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
cast	O
in	O
a	O
Mold	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
Fields	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
and	O
was	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
give	O
any	O
good	O
account	O
of	O
himself	O
:	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Lichfield	I-pers
was	O
Arraigned	O
upon	O
two	O
several	O
Indictments	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
August	O
one	O
Red	O
Cow	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
another	O
Cow	O
from	O
one	O
Richard	B-pers
Bayley	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
to	O
both	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
;	O
and	O
to	O
all	O
other	O
within	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
his	O
Clerg	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Walter	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Biggs	I-pers
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
September	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
Shifts	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
Gown	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Table	O
Cloth	O
2	O
s.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Mrs.	O
Biggs	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Table	O
Cloth	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
a	O
Line	O
in	O
Hunt	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
denied	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
given	O
him	O
by	O
one	O
George	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
no	O
Witness	O
on	O
his	O
side	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Dunstone	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
from	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
Shaw	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Cup	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Room	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
he	O
apprehending	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
confest	O
to	O
have	O
stole	O
the	O
Cup	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
for	O
30	O
s.	O
(	O
to	O
viz	O
.	O
)	O
to	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Huggins	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
had	O
former	O
dealings	O
with	O
her	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
buy	O
the	O
Cup	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Tho	O
'	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryed	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Higgs	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Chiswick	B-place
in	O
the	O
Country	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
Gent	O
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
Christopher	B-pers
Reinhart	I-pers
Mentz	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
near	O
to	O
the	O
right	O
Pap	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
two	O
Inches	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Rapler	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
of	O
which	O
Wound	O
the	O
said	O
Christopher	O
Reinhart	O
Mentz	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Dutch	O
Lieutenant	O
)	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
Box	O
on	O
the	O
Ear	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
another	O
Blow	O
on	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
.	O
Afterwards	O
they	O
drew	O
their	O
Swords	O
,	O
and	O
past	O
at	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Higgs	O
falling	O
down	O
first	O
,	O
the	O
Dutchman	O
presently	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
died	O
,	O
It	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
former	O
Quarrel	O
or	O
old	O
Grudge	O
betwixt	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
was	O
to	O
defend	O
himself	O
;	O
likewise	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
before	O
in	O
all	O
his	O
Life-time	O
.	O
So	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
premeditated	O
Malice	O
proved	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Se	O
Defendendo	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kelsey	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Samuel	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
with	O
an	O
intention	O
to	O
steal	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
Charles-street	B-place
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
home	O
about	O
Nine	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Sash-window	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
to	O
let	O
in	O
some	O
others	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
it	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Comrade	O
,	O
but	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
a	O
dark	O
Lanthorn	O
in	O
his	O
Face	O
;	O
but	O
stopping	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
the	O
dark	O
Lanthorn	O
away	O
and	O
an	O
old	O
Periwig	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
shewn	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
worn	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
when	O
taken	O
.	O
Being	O
known	O
in	O
Court	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Tipevell	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Merry	I-pers
of	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Hat	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
Mr.	O
Merry	O
evidenced	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Cut-throat-lane	B-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
met	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
snatcht	O
off	O
his	O
Hat	O
from	O
his	O
Head	O
;	O
he	O
making	O
a	O
noise	O
,	O
they	O
threatned	O
to	O
kill	O
him	O
:	O
But	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Hat	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
Indicted	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Chivery	I-pers
,	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Richard	B-pers
Diansfeild	I-pers
Gent	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Sword	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Case	O
embroidered	O
with	O
Gold	O
and	O
Silver	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Beaver	O
Hat	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Silver	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
5	O
l.	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
that	O
the	O
above	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Merry	O
was	O
Robbed	O
of	O
his	O
Hat	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
flatly	O
against	O
Tivedell	O
,	O
and	O
Chivery	O
's	O
Sword	O
was	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
Lord	O
Lucas	O
's	O
hands	O
.	O
The	O
Robbery	O
was	O
sworn	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
in	O
Hangman	B-place
's	I-place
Acre	I-place
near	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
whistled	O
for	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
set	O
upon	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
,	O
and	O
rifled	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Goods	O
.	O
They	O
both	O
denied	O
all	O
that	O
was	O
sworn	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
yet	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
and	O
Robbery	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Burchey	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Diaper	O
Napkins	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Sleeves	O
12	O
d.	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Woollaston	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
so	O
She	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Violins	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
from	O
Ann	B-pers
Hylliard	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
in	O
general	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
shop	O
with	O
the	O
Fiddles	O
in	O
her	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
behind	O
the	O
next	O
Neighbours	O
door	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
denied	O
it	O
stifly	O
;	O
having	O
no	O
Evidence	O
on	O
her	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
matter	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
A	B-pers
-	I-pers
B	I-pers
-	I-pers
Was	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gelding	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
unknown	O
;	O
But	O
the	O
chief	O
Evidence	O
being	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
order	O
'd	O
to	O
give	O
to	O
Bail	O
to	O
appear	O
next	O
Sessions	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
accordingly	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Wignal	I-pers
of	O
Hampstead	B-place
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Bayonet	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
near	O
to	O
the	O
short	O
Ribs	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
two	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
immediately	O
died	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
given	O
in	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
with	O
others	O
,	O
were	O
at	O
Hampstead	O
at	O
,	O
Dinner	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
very	O
good	O
Friends	O
.	O
But	O
going	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
Fields	O
to	O
Hunting	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Wignal	O
reflected	O
upon	O
Smith	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
borrowed	O
Money	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
pay	O
him	O
,	O
yet	O
could	O
pull	O
one	O
his	O
Guinea	O
(	O
or	O
to	O
that	O
purpose	O
.	O
)	O
Upon	O
which	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
they	O
fell	O
to	O
Fighting	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Scuffle	O
Smith	O
was	O
mortally	O
wounded	O
,	O
and	O
falling	O
down	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
have	O
killed	O
me	O
;	O
Upon	O
which	O
he	O
immediately	O
died	O
.	O
One	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
both	O
Bayonets	O
,	O
but	O
another	O
said	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Wignal	O
only	O
had	O
out	O
.	O
They	O
Fought	O
at	O
first	O
with	O
their	O
Sticks	O
,	O
throwing	O
one	O
another	O
to	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Wignal	O
being	O
undermost	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
malice	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
loved	O
him	O
as	O
his	O
own	O
Brother	O
;	O
and	O
none	O
being	O
proved	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
;	O
but	O
a	O
sudden	O
heat	O
of	O
Passion	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Barringer	I-pers
in	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
and	O
bearing	O
thence	O
three	O
Silver	O
Watches	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
0	O
s.	O
40	O
Rings	O
15	O
l.	O
some	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Box	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
besides	O
40	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
about	O
100	O
l.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
in	O
the	O
general	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
sold	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Watches	O
to	O
one	O
Neagle	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
confest	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
yet	O
denied	O
it	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
.	O
And	O
being	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
Criminal	O
heretofore	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
being	O
very	O
well	O
satisfied	O
with	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Togood	I-pers
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Malin	I-pers
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Doane	I-pers
.	O
Togood	O
thrusting	O
an	O
Oken	O
Stick	O
into	O
the	O
Left	O
Eye	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Doane	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
two	O
Inches	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
died	O
the	O
22d	O
Instant	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Trinity	B-place
Minories	I-place
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
were	O
not	O
positive	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
the	O
persons	O
that	O
killed	O
the	O
said	O
Doane	O
,	O
neither	O
would	O
they	O
swear	O
that	O
they	O
knew	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
chief	O
Evidences	O
were	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
.	O
So	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Hullar	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tittle	I-pers
;	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
stealing	O
20	O
yards	O
of	O
Bone	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
50	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appeared	O
against	O
him	O
that	O
were	O
material	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
neglected	O
to	O
appear	O
,	O
being	O
out	O
upon	O
Bail	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
ordered	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
continue	O
till	O
next	O
Sessions	O
&	O
c.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Burrows	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Dye	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Whiterod	I-pers
,	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
32	O
Yards	O
of	O
Muslin	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
one	O
Robert	B-pers
Bampton	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Strand	B-place
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
They	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
to	O
cheapen	O
Goods	O
,	O
with	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
more	O
Women	O
,	O
and	O
tookaway	O
the	O
Muslin	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
on	O
Sarah	O
Burrows	O
upon	O
the	O
pursuit	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
besides	O
other	O
Goods	O
which	O
they	O
denied	O
upon	O
their	O
Tryal	O
:	O
But	O
being	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
base	O
Shoplifters	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Rowlston	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Hog	O
and	O
a	O
Sow	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
ago	O
from	O
one	O
Richard	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Agnes	B-pers
Charles	I-pers
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Bryan	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
of	O
4	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
value	O
26	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
She	O
not	O
much	O
denying	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
William	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Scotchman	O
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Boots	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gibbons	I-pers
on	O
the	O
7th	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
positive	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Katharine	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
from	O
Jane	B-pers
Merry	I-pers
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
her	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
had	O
opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Servant	O
procuring	O
several	O
persons	O
upon	O
the	O
account	O
of	O
her	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
the	O
Court	O
lookt	O
upon	O
it	O
to	O
proceed	O
from	O
Malice	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Noon	I-pers
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
September	O
one	O
Coach	O
Scar	O
of	O
Flowr	O
'd	O
crimson	O
Velvet	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
a	O
Camblet	O
Cloak	O
30	O
s.	O
from	O
Alexander	B-pers
Cambel	I-pers
Esquire	O
,	O
a	O
cloth	O
Coat	O
15	O
s.	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Coach-house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
and	O
the	O
Cloak	O
found	O
at	O
one	O
Boyces	O
a	O
Brokers	O
in	O
Long-Acre	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Cloak	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
from	O
one	O
Johnson	O
,	O
who	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
Cloak	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
for	O
4	O
s.	O
At	O
last	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
being	O
pleased	O
to	O
Adjourn	O
till	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
the	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
follows	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Newell	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Coach	O
Seats	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Edward	B-pers
Earl	I-pers
of	I-pers
Lincoln	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
clear	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Barrett	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
22	O
yards	O
of	O
Cloth	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Tarpen	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
that	O
the	O
Cloth	O
was	O
taken	O
off	O
the	O
Racks	O
near	O
Moorfields	B-place
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
l.	O
from	O
Hugh	B-pers
Gibbons	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutors	O
swore	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
confest	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
notwithstanding	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Franck	B-pers
Hyllar	I-pers
appeared	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Order	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Mr.	B-pers
Tickle	I-pers
,	O
&	O
c.	O
No	O
Evidence	O
coming	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
immediately	O
discharged	O
.	O
One	O
Truder	B-pers
a	O
Cook	O
was	O
likewise	O
accused	O
for	O
selling	O
stinking	O
Pyes	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
.	O
For	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
Fin	O
'd	O
20	O
Nobles	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Caveley	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Table	O
Cloth	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
from	O
Henry	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
West	I-pers
a	O
Papist	O
(	O
who	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
Popish	O
Schools	O
that	O
were	O
formerly	O
held	O
in	O
the	O
Savoy	O
)	O
was	O
accused	O
of	O
an	O
High	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
writing	O
and	O
publishing	O
a	O
scandalous	O
Libel	O
,	O
Intituled	O
,	O
Elementa	O
Politica	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
The	O
Grounds	O
of	O
Government	O
opened	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Being	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
he	O
could	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
Guilty	O
of	O
carrying	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Press	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
was	O
intended	O
by	O
the	O
Paper	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
great	O
Offence	O
to	O
the	O
Government	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
in	O
saying	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Great	O
Magna	O
Charta	O
Law	O
of	O
England	O
was	O
a	O
Nullity	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
no	O
Force	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
written	O
in	O
Answer	O
to	O
another	O
Book	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
is	O
was	O
no	O
ways	O
designed	O
as	O
an	O
offence	O
to	O
the	O
Government	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
look	O
upon	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
any	O
Treason	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
confest	O
it	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
his	O
Sentence	O
being	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
stand	O
three	O
times	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
at	O
Temple-Bar	O
,	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
Two	O
Swans	O
without	O
Bishopsgate	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Delacore	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
Convicted	O
upon	O
another	O
Indictment	O
for	O
Felony	O
,	O
was	O
this	O
day	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Hayward	I-pers
of	O
Ipswich	O
Goldsmith	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
Instant	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
considerable	O
quantity	O
of	O
Plate	O
,	O
Watches	O
,	O
Rings	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
about	O
300	O
l.	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Also	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Bill	O
presented	O
by	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Majesties	O
Authority	O
,	O
upon	O
an	O
Act	O
made	O
by	O
the	O
present	O
Parliament	O
,	O
bearing	O
Date	O
in	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
taking	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
utterly	O
obliterating	O
,	O
cancelling	O
and	O
defacing	O
of	O
the	O
Bill	O
of	O
Attainder	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
against	O
Henry	B-pers
Cornish	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
who	O
was	O
Tryed	O
in	O
that	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
Executed	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
it	O
was	O
immediately	O
cancelled	O
in	O
open	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Indictment	O
delivered	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Cornish	O
Son	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Cornish	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
&	O
c.	O
One	O
Elephant	B-pers
an	O
Ostler	O
at	O
the	O
White-House	O
in	O
Fetter-lane	O
,	O
was	O
accused	O
to	O
have	O
sold	O
Oats	O
in	O
a	O
False	O
Measure	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
in	O
Bail	O
to	O
appear	O
near	O
Sessions	O
.	O
One	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Boyce	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
living	O
in	O
Long	O
Acre	O
,	O
was	O
accused	O
for	O
buying	O
stolen	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
in	O
Bail	O
to	O
appear	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Dowdle	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Reputed	O
Mass-Priest	O
,	O
was	O
called	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
to	O
answer	O
directly	O
or	O
indirectly	O
,	O
Whether	O
he	O
were	O
so	O
or	O
no	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Act	O
made	O
in	O
the	O
35th	O
year	O
of	O
Queen	O
Elizabeth	O
which	O
he	O
refusing	O
,	O
was	O
remanded	O
to	O
Newgate	O
.	O
A	O
Bill	O
of	O
Indictment	O
was	O
presented	O
by	O
the	O
Grand	O
Inquest	O
against	O
Alexander	B-pers
Macdonnel	I-pers
,	O
and	O
others	O
.	O
for	O
spreading	O
the	O
Late	O
King	O
James	O
's	O
Declaration	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
Released	O
upon	O
Bail	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
to	O
appear	O
the	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
Several	O
other	O
persons	O
were	O
like	O
wise	O
called	O
over	O
for	O
writing	O
false	O
News	O
and	O
Libels	O
;	O
of	O
whom	O
some	O
were	O
discharged	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
gave	O
Bail	O
for	O
their	O
Appearance	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
gave	O
Judgment	O
as	O
follows	O
:	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
Ten	O
.	O
Abel	B-pers
Dodson	I-pers
,	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Bacon	I-pers
Jonath	I-pers
.	O
Wights	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Noon	O
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Lejchfield	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Wignail	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Barret	I-pers
,	O
Agnes	B-pers
Charles	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Maye	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Caveley	I-pers
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
Ten	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hoane	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Delacore	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kelsey	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Tivedel	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Chivery	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Burrows	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Hill	O
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Dye	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Thomas	O
,	O
alias	O
Whitwood	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Burrows	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Dye	I-pers
pleading	O
their	O
Bellies	O
,	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
were	O
call	O
'd	O
who	O
affirm	O
'd	O
they	O
were	O
quick	O
with	O
Child	O
.	O
Solomon	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
was	O
Fin	O
'd	O
100	O
Marks	O
;	O
and	O
to	O
find	O
Sureties	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
a	O
Twelvemonth	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
Walter	O
Hunt	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
,	O
were	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
whipt	O
from	O
Newgate	O
to	O
Hicks	O
Hall	O
.	O
Advertisements	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
to	O
give	O
Notice	O
to	O
all	O
Persons	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
the	O
Publick	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Elmy	O
Professor	O
of	O
Physick	O
;	O
and	O
Operator	O
of	O
known	O
Integrity	O
,	O
and	O
above	O
25	O
Years	O
Practice	O
,	O
Liveth	O
at	O
the	O
Blue	O
Hall	O
in	O
Whale-Bone-Court	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Lower	O
End	O
of	O
Bartholomew	O
lane	O
by	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
who	O
most	O
safely	O
and	O
expeditiously	O
Cures	O
Deafness	O
and	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
Ears	O
in	O
any	O
of	O
what	O
Age	O
soever	O
,	O
(	O
if	O
Curable	O
)	O
and	O
at	O
First	O
Sight	O
,	O
by	O
Inspection	O
,	O
Resolves	O
the	O
Patient	O
if	O
so	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
as	O
most	O
Eminent	O
Persons	O
of	O
Quality	O
in	O
this	O
City	O
can	O
Testifie	O
.	O
He	O
hath	O
likewise	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Gargurism	O
or	O
Mouth	O
water	O
,	O
will	O
make	O
black	O
or	O
yellow	O
Teeth	O
as	O
white	O
as	O
Ivory	O
.	O
In	O
Plow-Yard	O
in	O
Grays-in	O
Lane	O
lives	O
Dr.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kirleus	I-pers
,	O
who	O
with	O
a	O
Drink	O
and	O
Pill	O
,	O
Cures	O
Ulcers	O
,	O
Scabs	O
,	O
Scarfs	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
or	O
elsewhere	O
:	O
Kings	O
Evil	O
,	O
Leprosie	O
,	O
and	O
Venereal	O
Disease	O
,	O
expecting	O
nothing	O
if	O
he	O
Cures	O
not	O
.	O
Of	O
the	O
last	O
,	O
he	O
bath	O
Cured	O
above	O
500	O
persons	O
,	O
many	O
after	O
Fluxing	O
.	O
The	O
Drink	O
is	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Quart	O
;	O
the	O
Pill	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
two	O
Purges	O
.	O
They	O
excel	O
all	O
Purges	O
,	O
Curing	O
many	O
Diseases	O
,	O
especially	O
the	O
Gout	O
and	O
Stone	O
.	O
In	O
all	O
Diseases	O
he	O
gives	O
his	O
Opinion	O
for	O
nothing	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Medicines	O
for	O
little	O
.	O
