TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
and	O
Queens	O
Commissions	O
OF	O
THE	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
11th	O
,	O
12th	O
,	O
13th	O
,	O
and	O
14th	O
Days	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
1689	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
First	O
Tear	O
of	O
Their	O
MAJESTIES	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
11th	O
,	O
12th	O
,	O
13th	O
,	O
and	O
14th	O
Days	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
1689	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pilkington	I-pers
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
other	O
Justices	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
follow	O
,	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Stamper	I-pers
Benj	B-pers
.	I-pers
Fitzer	I-pers
Maurice	B-pers
Wait	I-pers
William	B-pers
Osborne	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Maddox	I-pers
John	B-pers
Woodcroft	I-pers
Anthony	B-pers
Lawson	I-pers
William	B-pers
Millward	I-pers
John	B-pers
Spragman	I-pers
Jeremy	B-pers
Lammas	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Partridge	I-pers
William	B-pers
Parkinson	I-pers
Humph	B-pers
.	I-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Fitzgerald	I-pers
John	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
John	B-pers
Outing	I-pers
Christo	B-pers
.	I-pers
Chambers	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
Giles	B-pers
Burrows	I-pers
Daniel	B-pers
Badger	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Jewell	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Hooper	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
these	O
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Groves	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Boy	O
about	O
16	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Alhallows	I-place
Lumbard	I-place
street	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Firing	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Foster	O
,	O
with	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
an	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
Chopt	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Link	O
,	O
and	O
clapt	O
it	O
between	O
the	O
Boards	O
in	O
a	O
partition	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
took	O
Fire	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
soon	O
quench	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Instigated	O
to	O
Commit	O
the	O
Fact	O
by	O
the	O
Temptations	O
of	O
the	O
Devil	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Baker	O
;	O
yet	O
he	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Davies	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bartho	I-place
.	I-place
Exchange	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Fact	O
,	O
(	O
viz	O
.	O
)	O
for	O
Firing	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
Evidenced	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
with	O
another	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Boy	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
threw	O
a	O
Quart	O
Pot	O
at	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
made	O
his	O
Escape	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Cellar	O
Door	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
the	O
Fire	O
was	O
found	O
between	O
the	O
Partition	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
easily	O
put	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
stifly	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Master	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
his	O
Servant	O
Swore	O
that	O
they	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
wont	O
to	O
frequent	O
the	O
Kidnapping-Office	O
,	O
(	O
so	O
called	O
,	O
)	O
near	O
to	O
the	O
Royal-Exchange	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
in	O
St.	O
Soizbin	O
's	O
Alley	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
hard	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Wronged	O
:	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Jury	O
had	O
a	O
severe	O
Reprimand	O
from	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Jury	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
immediately	O
Empanelled	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Spearing	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Maw	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolph	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Maw	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
to	O
have	O
taken	O
away	O
his	O
Tankard	O
before	O
Sir	O
James	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
Broadnick	O
a	O
Broker	O
in	O
Holborn	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
surprized	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
denyed	O
it	O
all	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
;	O
Upon	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
highly	O
blamed	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
for	O
Davis	O
's	O
Verdict	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Voucher	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Dyer	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
about	O
12	O
or	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
Day	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
one	O
Gold	O
Hatband	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
15	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
a	O
Boy	O
brought	O
out	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
besides	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
them	O
Break	O
open	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Voucher	O
promised	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
Money	O
to	O
Conceal	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
Coffee-House	O
near	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
denyed	O
all	O
that	O
was	O
alledged	O
,	O
and	O
Dyer	O
called	O
numerous	O
Evidences	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
an	O
account	O
,	O
that	O
Smith	O
had	O
Malice	O
against	O
Dyer	O
:	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
Lodged	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
put	O
him	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
fairly	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
Lease	O
was	O
not	O
expired	O
.	O
Dyer	O
's	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
further	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
always	O
been	O
a	O
very	O
Honest	O
Person	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Reputation	O
.	O
Vouchar	O
had	O
likewise	O
some	O
Persons	O
on	O
his	O
side	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
the	O
Court	O
a	O
very	O
favourable	O
account	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
So	O
that	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
looked	O
very	O
obscure	O
,	O
and	O
seemed	O
to	O
proceed	O
from	O
Malice	O
on	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
side	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
arrested	O
the	O
said	O
Dyer	O
in	O
an	O
Action	O
of	O
100	O
l.	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
owed	O
him	O
but	O
5	O
l.	O
Besides	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
Swear	O
positively	O
against	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
Evidence	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
being	O
but	O
Circumstantial	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Melton	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
with	O
Gold	O
and	O
Silver	O
Buttons	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Lane	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
Robbed	O
in	O
Watlin-street	B-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Coat	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Custody	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
attempted	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
denyed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Coat	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
Turn	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Taylor	O
,	O
by	O
one	O
George	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Killing	O
one	O
Samuel	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
on	O
the	O
first	O
Day	O
of	O
Novemb	O
.	O
last	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
near	O
to	O
his	O
Left	O
Groin	O
with	O
a	O
Pistol-Bullet	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
10	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
dyed	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
Queen	O
,	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
Pistol	O
among	O
some	O
old	O
Iron	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
and	O
trying	O
it	O
how	O
it	O
gave	O
Fire	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
decreased	O
dead	O
,	O
who	O
stood	O
near	O
him	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Pistol	O
among	O
the	O
old	O
Iron	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
Charged	O
:	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Killing	O
the	O
said	O
Fox	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
by	O
Misadventure	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
another	O
Pewter	O
Dish	O
value	O
15	O
d.	O
one	O
Salt	O
4	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Hawson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
December	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Pewter	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
in	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
deny	O
:	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ben	B-pers
.	I-pers
Hall	I-pers
of	O
Northern-Falgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Stone-Horse	O
,	O
Coloured	O
Black	O
,	O
Price	O
6	O
l.	O
from	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
:	O
the	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
positively	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Horse	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
custody	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Ride	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Horse	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
whose	O
Horse	O
it	O
was	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Walter	B-pers
Mooney	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Timothy	B-pers
Hartican	I-pers
,	O
Soldier	O
s	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
;	O
Mooney	O
as	O
principal	O
,	O
Hartican	O
as	O
accessary	O
;	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
Left	O
Buttock	O
,	O
near	O
to	O
the	O
Left	O
Hip	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
4	O
Inches	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
Septemb	O
.	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
Languished	O
until	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
October	O
following	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
upon	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
arose	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
between	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
about	O
carrying	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
to	O
Spittle-fields	O
in	O
his	O
Coach	O
;	O
which	O
Marsh	O
(	O
the	O
deceased	O
)	O
denyed	O
,	O
and	O
drove	O
away	O
his	O
Coach	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Two	O
Prisoners	O
persued	O
him	O
:	O
and	O
immediately	O
he	O
Cryed	O
out	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Run	O
into	O
the	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
Mooney	O
's	O
Sword	O
was	O
found	O
under	O
his	O
Coat	O
naked	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
Bloody	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
as	O
a	O
further	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
was	O
able	O
to	O
Swear	O
that	O
Harticans	O
Sword	O
was	O
drawn	O
,	O
the	O
Chyrurgeon	O
gave	O
in	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
Marsh	O
dyed	O
of	O
the	O
Wound	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
denyed	O
that	O
they	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
until	O
the	O
Coachman	O
struck	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
a	O
Belt	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
:	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
fair	O
and	O
distinct	O
hearing	O
:	O
so	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Wilful	O
Murther	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Ferguson	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Barrels	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
which	O
he	O
confest	O
upon	O
his	O
Arraignment	O
;	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Newcomb	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
and	O
Tryed	O
as	O
Accessary	O
to	O
Ferguson	O
;	O
for	O
entertaining	O
the	O
said	O
Ferguson	O
,	O
and	O
Receiving	O
the	O
Barrels	O
into	O
his	O
House	O
:	O
Upon	O
which	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
examined	O
,	O
they	O
declared	O
that	O
the	O
Barrels	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
Newcomb	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
but	O
none	O
were	O
produced	O
that	O
could	O
fasten	O
any	O
thing	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
only	O
that	O
he	O
owned	O
,	O
that	O
Bennet	O
's	O
Mark	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
Barrels	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
deny	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Tryal	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
being	O
proved	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
discharg	O
'd	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Peartman	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Hozey	I-pers
upon	O
the	O
Road	O
between	O
London	O
and	O
Bristoll	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Gelding	O
Price	O
12	O
l.	O
a	O
Hat	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Hatband	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Point	O
Cap	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Linnen	O
for	O
a	O
Child	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
with	O
a	O
Box	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Evidence	O
Swore	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
near	O
Hampton	O
Court	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Inn	O
with	O
the	O
Carryer	O
(	O
viz	O
.	O
)	O
Hozey	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
the	O
Pack-Horses	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
confest	O
it	O
before	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
the	O
Carrier	O
produced	O
a	O
Glove	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
Rob	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
upon	O
the	O
high	O
way	O
,	O
only	O
took	O
the	O
Horse	O
into	O
the	O
Meadow	O
near	O
the	O
Inn	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samuel	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
Andrew	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
of	O
St.	O
Andrews	O
Holborn	O
giving	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Tuck	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
upon	O
the	O
Left	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
Body	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
four	O
Inches	O
deep	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
died	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
Instant	O
following	O
;	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
they	O
met	O
each	O
other	O
in	O
Bromley-street	B-place
,	O
and	O
Jostled	O
for	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
and	O
Quarelled	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
Scuffle	O
Edwards	O
received	O
the	O
Wound	O
:	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
any	O
Affront	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
two	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
set	O
upon	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
seen	O
to	O
Fence	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Edwards	O
began	O
the	O
Quarrel-first	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Lamb	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Story	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
chief	O
witness	O
against	O
her	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
spoon	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
it	O
in	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
it	O
to	O
Sale	O
at	O
a	O
Goldsmiths	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
fully	O
sworn	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
altho	O
'	O
she	O
denied	O
it	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
;	O
yet	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dance	I-pers
on	O
the	O
13th	O
day	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
200	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
Numbered	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
upon	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
quartered	O
in	O
the	O
prosecutors	O
house	O
,	O
about	O
18	O
Weeks	O
:	O
and	O
sometime	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
Mr	O
.	O
Dances	O
house	O
and	O
where	O
the	O
Money	O
used	O
to	O
Lye	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
thither	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
Committed	O
the	O
Robbery	O
;	O
he	O
owned	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
hid	O
100	O
l.	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Earth	O
at	O
Southern	O
Bridge	O
4	O
Miles	O
from	O
London	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
accordingly	O
found	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
further	O
owned	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
he	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Window	O
of	O
the	O
Closet	O
where	O
the	O
Money	O
lay	O
:	O
And	O
with	O
a	O
Chissel	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Till	O
of	O
the	O
drawer	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
got	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
Elbow	O
Lane	O
in	O
a	O
Garret	O
.	O
Unto	O
all	O
this	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
answered	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Money	O
upon	O
the	O
Road	O
in	O
a	O
Wallet	O
;	O
and	O
buryed	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
very	O
frivolous	O
excuses	O
:	O
and	O
denied	O
all	O
that	O
was	O
alledged	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
So	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Bristow	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Stealing	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
one	O
Bay	O
Horse	O
price	O
10	O
l.	O
The	O
goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Cornwall	I-pers
Esquire	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Horse	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Custody	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
Riding	O
him	O
from	O
Enfield	O
Chase	O
towards	O
London	O
:	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
could	O
swear	O
that	O
he	O
Stole	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Flower	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Dutchess	B-pers
of	I-pers
Mazareen	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Dutchess	O
's	O
House	O
under	O
a	O
pretence	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
family	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Spoon	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
while	O
the	O
Maid	O
went	O
to	O
draw	O
him	O
some	O
Ale	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
sold	O
the	O
Spoon	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
all	O
which	O
he	O
confest	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
upon	O
his	O
apprehension	O
,	O
but	O
denied	O
it	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
striving	O
to	O
Extenuate	O
the	O
Crime	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
would	O
not	O
prevail	O
with	O
the	O
Jury	O
to	O
believe	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
innocent	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Martin	B-pers
Seward	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Harwood	I-pers
,	O
two	O
little	O
Youth	O
s	O
,	O
were	O
both	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
Richard	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
Novemb	O
.	O
last	O
:	O
Seward	O
Confest	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
House	O
,	O
got	O
into	O
Halls	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
in	O
Harwood	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Harwood	O
took	O
away	O
12	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Clasps	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
20	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
one	O
Silver	O
Bell	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
40	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Silver	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
with	O
some	O
Silver	O
Buttons	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
It	O
was	O
Credibly	O
Evidenced	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Cellar	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Seward	O
let	O
the	O
other	O
Boy	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Dust-hole	O
for	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
about	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
Committed	O
the	O
Robbery	O
:	O
but	O
Harwood	O
had	O
good	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
his	O
Honesty	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Seward	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Feild	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
Four	O
score	O
and	O
Ten	O
Knives	O
from	O
Benj	B-pers
Choyce	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
which	O
altho	O
he	O
stifly	O
denyed	O
,	O
by	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
hired	O
to	O
Carry	O
them	O
to	O
Fleet-Bridge	O
by	O
one	O
at	O
Holborn	O
Bridge	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
old	O
Shop	O
lifter	O
,	O
so	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Joh	B-pers
Pensick	I-pers
of	O
Chatham	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
Novemb	O
.	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
40	O
Yards	O
of	O
Serge	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
4	O
s.	O
5	O
yards	O
of	O
Crimson	O
shag	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
17	O
yards	O
of	O
Drugget-Stuff	O
value	O
Fifty	O
Shillings	O
.	O
Twenty	O
Seven	O
yards	O
of	O
Crape	O
value	O
39	O
s.	O
27	O
yards	O
of	O
Norwich	O
Stuff	O
value	O
29	O
s.	O
120	O
yards	O
of	O
Coloured	O
Stuff	O
value	O
9	O
l.	O
8	O
Gowns	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
8	O
Petticoats	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
one	O
stript	O
Silk	O
Woman	O
's	O
Gown	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
one	O
Covering	O
for	O
a	O
Bed	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
5	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockins	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
3	O
Silk	O
Wastcoats	O
trim	O
'd	O
with	O
Gold	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
trim	O
'd	O
with	O
Gold	O
value	O
45	O
s.	O
with	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
great	O
value	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
Intrusted	O
to	O
work	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
(	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Taylor	O
,	O
)	O
at	O
Chatham	O
,	O
and	O
whilst	O
Mr.	O
Pensick	O
was	O
at	O
London	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
their	O
opportunity	O
to	O
Murther	O
the	O
Servant	O
who	O
was	O
Intrusted	O
in	O
Chief	O
,	O
tying	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Tape	O
twice	O
about	O
his	O
Neck	O
;	O
with	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
strangled	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
they	O
carried	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
them	O
in	O
White-Fryars	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
did	O
he	O
ways	O
deny	O
.	O
So	O
they	O
viz	O
.	O
the	O
two	O
Men	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Woman	O
discharged	O
.	O
Giles	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
17	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Elliot	I-pers
in	O
Thames-street	B-place
,	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
Pawn-Broker	O
in	O
Southwark	O
:	O
The	O
prisoner	O
denyed	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Tryal	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
plain	O
,	O
so	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Kentish	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
Stealing	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
from	O
Margaret	B-pers
Umble	I-pers
one	O
Red	O
Petticoat	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
black	O
Sarsnet	O
petty-coat	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stockins	O
8	O
s.	O
one	O
Muslin	O
Night	O
Rail	O
8	O
s.	O
one	O
Yard	O
of	O
Cloth	O
3	O
s.	O
2	O
Muslin	O
Cornets	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
Farendine	O
Petty	O
coat	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
With	O
several	O
other	O
small	O
goods	O
,	O
besides	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
;	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
liv	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
charged	O
with	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
she	O
confest	O
how	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
at	O
a	O
brokers	O
,	O
throwing	O
her	O
self	O
upon	O
the	O
Mercy	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
;	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Peel	I-pers
a	O
Girle	O
was	O
indicted	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
for	O
Stealing	O
9	O
s.	O
from	O
Mary	B-pers
Peelsworth	I-pers
a	O
2d	O
time	O
for	O
Stealing	O
,	O
5	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
5	O
more	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
one	O
Pearl	O
Neck-Lace	O
value	O
30	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
above	O
said	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
swore	O
that	O
the	O
Girle	O
was	O
a	O
servant	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
She	O
Lodged	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
lost	O
her	O
goods	O
:	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Neck	O
Lace	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
discharged	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
former	O
so	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Eades	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
privily	O
stealing	O
Ten	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
from	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Kule	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
Novemb	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
Kule	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
her	O
hand	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
she	O
cast	O
her	O
hand	O
behind	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
near	O
her	O
was	O
supposed	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Money	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
it	O
,	O
yet	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Rowland	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
in	O
Counterfeiting	O
a	O
Letter	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
one	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Blackerby	I-pers
,	O
directed	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Draper	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Draper	O
in	O
Bishopsgate	O
street	O
,	O
for	O
divers	O
Goods	O
,	O
as	O
Holland	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Linnens	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Letter	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Blackerby	O
desired	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
send	O
immediately	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
pieces	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
odd	O
things	O
:	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Draper	O
suspecting	O
,	O
sent	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Blackerby	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Cheat	O
:	O
and	O
she	O
declared	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
never	O
sent	O
for	O
any	O
Goods	O
,	O
neither	O
writ	O
any	O
Letter	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Counterfeit	O
.	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Sherwood	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
as	O
principal	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
others	O
as	O
Accessaries	O
to	O
Sherwood	O
,	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Richard	B-pers
Comer	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
Novemb	O
.	O
of	O
10	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Clasps	O
for	O
a	O
Cloak	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
Five	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Money	O
and	O
the	O
Rings	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Trunk	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
away	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Constable	O
found	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Rings	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
confest	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Money	O
:	O
So	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
the	O
Woman	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
latter	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Campion	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
smothering	O
her	O
Female	O
Infant	O
Bastard	O
Child	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
Decemb	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
found	O
Dead	O
in	O
a	O
Box	O
under	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
owned	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
hers	O
:	O
and	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
full	O
grown	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
appearance	O
of	O
hurt	O
was	O
seen	O
on	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
as	O
was	O
Evidenced	O
by	O
the	O
Midwife	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
near	O
her	O
time	O
;	O
and	O
no	O
proof	O
was	O
made	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
Born	O
alive	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
being	O
found	O
to	O
make	O
good	O
Provision	O
for	O
the	O
Child	O
against	O
the	O
Birth	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
deemed	O
to	O
be	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Statute	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Elinor	B-pers
Fluellin	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Bernard	B-pers
Bickerdyke	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
Novemb	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
Evidenced	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
and	O
a	O
Man	O
went	O
to	O
drink	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
on	O
Safforn-Hill	B-place
,	O
and	O
the	O
Man	O
took	O
the	O
Tankard	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Woman	O
behind	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
it	O
,	O
altho	O
'	O
she	O
Confest	O
it	O
before	O
that	O
the	O
Man	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
immediately	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Daniel	B-pers
Ashford	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Rape	O
Committed	O
upon	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
one	O
Ruth	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
Day	O
of	O
July	O
.	O
The	O
King	O
's	O
Counsel	O
opened	O
the	O
Nature	O
of	O
the	O
fact	O
:	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
Committed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
he	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
considerable	O
time	O
after	O
:	O
Mrs.	O
Turner	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
at	O
Cambridge-Heath	B-place
,	O
when	O
no	O
one	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
besides	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
her	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
Forced	O
her	O
:	O
she	O
Cryed	O
out	O
for	O
help	O
,	O
but	O
yet	O
not	O
withstanding	O
he	O
over	O
came	O
her	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
Corroborated	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
that	O
saw	O
him	O
upon	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
given	O
him	O
5	O
s.	O
to	O
hold	O
his	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
promised	O
to	O
spend	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
by	O
way	O
of	O
a	O
Treat	O
.	O
The	O
Woman	O
farther	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
followed	O
her	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
she	O
going	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
Glass	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
which	O
was	O
fully	O
Evidenced	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
offer	O
any	O
Money	O
to	O
any	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Woman	O
kept	O
a	O
Bad	O
House	O
,	O
of	O
no	O
good	O
Credit	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
several	O
Evil	O
Deeds	O
were	O
done	O
there	O
.	O
Others	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
person	O
of	O
a	O
fair	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
Sick	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
when	O
the	O
Rape	O
was	O
said	O
to	O
be	O
Committed	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
Scandalous	O
Reproaches	O
,	O
and	O
Ugly	O
Reflections	O
,	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
course	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
there	O
was	O
abundance	O
of	O
Malice	O
appeared	O
,	O
which	O
weighed	O
so	O
much	O
with	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
Acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Auttey	I-pers
the	O
Elder	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Auttey	I-pers
the	O
Younger	O
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
Novemb	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Witness	O
was	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
Charge	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Longstaff	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Riggs	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
Three	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honorable	O
the	O
Marquis	B-pers
of	I-pers
Caermarthen	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
Septemb	O
.	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
Hours	O
of	O
9	O
or	O
10	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
3	O
pieces	O
of	O
Point	O
for	O
a	O
Bed	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
one	O
Point	O
Cion	O
Cloth	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
another	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Point	O
Apron	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Set	O
Twilit	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
good	O
value	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
evidence	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
Butler	O
confest	O
that	O
Longstaff	O
went	O
in	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
carried	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
But	O
Longstaff	O
and	O
Riggs	O
denyed	O
it	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
Apprehended	O
.	O
Butler	O
produced	O
all	O
the	O
Goods	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Evidence	O
affected	O
Longstaff	O
and	O
Riggs	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Butler	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dyer	I-pers
,	O
Peregrin	B-pers
Barret	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Barret	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
about	O
two	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
Novemb	O
.	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
a	O
Silver-Strainer	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
Pound	O
of	O
Candles	O
value	O
9	O
d.	O
a	O
Pot	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
3	O
Pound	O
of	O
Honey	O
value	O
11	O
d.	O
a	O
little	O
Box	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
12	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Honey	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
Peregrin	O
Barret	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
Dyer	O
called	O
good	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Evidence	O
was	O
produced	O
against	O
John	B-pers
Barret	I-pers
,	O
they	O
2	O
were	O
acquitted	O
,	O
but	O
Barret	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Noon	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Winifred	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
in	O
Robbing	O
the	O
Chamber	O
of	O
Herald	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
in	O
Novemb	O
.	O
last	O
,	O
taking	O
away	O
5	O
yards	O
of	O
Cloth	O
value	O
35	O
s.	O
3	O
yards	O
of	O
Callico	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
8	O
yards	O
of	O
Silk	O
value	O
58	O
s.	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
Young	O
confest	O
it	O
upon	O
his	O
Arraignment	O
,	O
and	O
Noone	O
denyed	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
did	O
Jones	O
.	O
And	O
no	O
Evidence	O
affected	O
them	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Togood	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Breaking	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
of	O
Edmund	B-pers
Waller	I-pers
Esq	O
:	O
at	O
Westminster	B-place
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
saken	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
before	O
he	O
had	O
time	O
to	O
carry	O
any	O
thing	O
away	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
only	O
of	O
a	O
Trespass	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Trunk	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
4	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
Novemb	O
.	O
from	O
Anthony	B-pers
Waller	I-pers
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
Swore	O
that	O
he	O
hid	O
the	O
Trunk	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
owned	O
it	O
before	O
,	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
walking	O
Cane	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
December	O
from	O
George	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
of	O
Foster-lane	B-place
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
with	O
another	O
Man	O
to	O
cheapen	O
some	O
Buckles	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Man	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Cane	O
;	O
yet	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
company	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Waller	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Five	O
Shilling	O
Piece	O
from	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Earle	I-pers
in	O
Fleet	B-place
street	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
October	O
1688	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
to	O
offer	O
some	O
what	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
credible	O
persons	O
to	O
clear	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Basset	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
60	O
yards	O
of	O
Scotch	O
Taby	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
from	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Brigg	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
proved	O
that	O
the	O
Taby	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
confest	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
saying	O
it	O
was	O
given	O
her	O
by	O
another	O
Woman	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Tamplin	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
marrying	O
two	O
Wives	O
:	O
The	O
first	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Oakes	I-pers
,	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
was	O
married	O
in	O
Aldgate	O
Parish	O
.	O
The	O
second	O
one	O
Frances	B-pers
Tomlinson	I-pers
,	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
was	O
married	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
November	O
in	O
Bishopsgate	B-place
Parish	I-place
.	O
The	O
evidence	O
was	O
weak	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Ghoste	I-pers
of	O
Crutchet	B-place
Fryars	I-place
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
speaking	O
contemptuous	O
and	O
reproachful	O
words	O
against	O
our	O
most	O
Gracious	O
King	O
William	O
III	O
of	O
England	O
&	O
c.	O
saying	O
,	O
That	O
King	O
William	O
was	O
the	O
Son	O
of	O
an	O
Whore	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
evidenced	O
by	O
some	O
Women	O
who	O
heard	O
her	O
speak	O
the	O
words	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Evidence	O
had	O
a	O
Spight	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
because	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Law	O
together	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
It	O
appeared	O
further	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
would	O
have	O
put	O
up	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Court	O
lookt	O
upon	O
it	O
as	O
a	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
For	O
pretending	O
himself	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Irish	O
Protestant	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
40	O
s.	O
of	O
the	O
Commissioners	O
at	O
Mercers	O
Hall	O
.	O
It	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Sanders	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Offence	O
as	O
Steward	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
much	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
purpose	O
that	O
he	O
received	O
40	O
s.	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Misdemeanor	O
.	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
N	B-pers
-	I-pers
C	I-pers
-	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Baskerfield	I-pers
on	O
the	O
10th	O
Instant	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Gun	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
wound	O
upon	O
his	O
Forehead	O
near	O
to	O
his	O
right	O
Eye	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
died	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
more	O
were	O
shooting	O
at	O
Wild	O
Ducks	O
on	O
the	O
Thames	B-place
near	I-place
Blackwall	I-place
,	O
and	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
shot	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
C	O
-	O
shot	O
after	O
,	O
the	O
Waterman	O
thinking	O
that	O
all	O
the	O
Guns	O
went	O
off	O
,	O
rose	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Boat	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
C	O
-	O
shooting	O
,	O
the	O
Waterman	O
received	O
the	O
Shot	O
into	O
his	O
head	O
.	O
He	O
confessing	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
a	O
Misfortune	O
,	O
was	O
discharged	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Slade	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
killing	O
Jane	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
by	O
shooting	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
left	O
part	O
of	O
her	O
head	O
with	O
a	O
Musquet	O
Barrel	O
value	O
2	O
s.fixed	O
in	O
an	O
Engin	O
,	O
giving	O
her	O
one	O
mortal	O
wound	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
3	O
Inches	O
of	O
which	O
She	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Woman	O
was	O
shot	O
in	O
Bunhil	B-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
others	O
were	O
trying	O
of	O
their	O
Musquets	O
out	O
of	O
an	O
Engin	O
in	O
the	O
Artillery	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Bullet	O
glancing	O
over	O
the	O
Wan	O
,	O
shot	O
the	O
Woman	O
dead	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
servant	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
was	O
in	O
obedience	O
to	O
his	O
Masters	O
Commands	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
death	O
of	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
only	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
doing	O
it	O
by	O
misfortune	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mechiones	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
being	O
Accessary	O
with	O
Edward	B-pers
Ferguson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
stealing	O
3	O
Barrels	O
from	O
one	O
Bennet	B-pers
,	O
as	O
before	O
Incerted	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
Evidence	O
that	O
gave	O
a	O
favourable	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
Credit	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
discharg	O
'd	O
.	O
A	B-pers
-	I-pers
B	I-pers
-	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
one	O
Jacob	B-pers
a	O
Saxon	O
,	O
one	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Crevat	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Ruffles	O
15	O
s.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
making	O
good	O
proof	O
of	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
formerly	O
intimate	O
Friends	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
adjust	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bolt	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Cornets	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
one	O
Scarf	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Draper	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
positive	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Noon	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Noon	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
one	O
Spoon	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Sayers	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
Newgate	O
&	O
c.	O
Which	O
being	O
proved	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
and	I-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
his	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	O
his	O
Wife	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Point	O
Crevat	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Point	O
Band	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
Cornet	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
10	O
s.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
did	O
not	O
touch	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Man	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Shoot	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Deverel	I-pers
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
November	O
one	O
Gown	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
2	O
Silk	O
Peticoats	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Point	O
Sleeves	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
Cornet	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Apron	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
Sir	O
Walter	B-pers
Plunket	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
that	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
Shoot	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Evidence	O
affected	O
Deverel	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
but	O
Shoot	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Knott	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
27	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
from	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Purbridge	I-pers
.	O
She	O
declared	O
that	O
she	O
lost	O
her	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
hole	O
in	O
the	O
Chimney	O
corner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
remarkable	O
Shilling	O
about	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
swore	O
was	O
hers	O
;	O
whereupon	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
and	O
Hannah	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Cembeson	I-pers
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
taking	O
one	O
cloth	O
Coat	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
from	O
him	O
:	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Gouge	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Boy	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
yards	O
of	O
Bone	O
Lace	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Box	O
1	O
d.	O
from	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Fellowes	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
clear	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elinor	B-pers
Hatfeild	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
James	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
24	O
yards	O
of	O
printed	O
Calicoe	O
value	O
28	O
s.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
,	O
offering	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Calicoe	O
to	O
Sale	O
for	O
5	O
s.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
She	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
one	O
Powel	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
9	O
s.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Lebone	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bay	O
Coloured	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
No	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
immediately	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Patrick	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
usual	O
Method	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
For	O
waging	O
and	O
levying	O
War	O
against	O
our	O
Sovereign	O
Lord	O
and	O
Lady	O
King	O
William	O
and	O
Queen	O
Mary	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Chairman	O
to	O
the	O
Pope	O
's	O
Nancio	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
Communication	O
with	O
one	O
Taffe	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
presence	O
of	O
one	O
Mannors	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
produced	O
as	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
raised	O
16	O
Men	O
,	O
allowing	O
them	O
6	O
d.	O
per	O
diem	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
already	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
in	O
November	O
sent	O
them	O
into	O
France	O
for	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
King	O
James	O
in	O
Ireland	O
.	O
And	O
further	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
That	O
if	O
they	O
could	O
procure	O
any	O
Friends	O
of	O
theirs	O
,	O
they	O
should	O
presently	O
Enter	O
into	O
Pay	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
kindly	O
Entertained	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
a	O
Captain	O
ere	O
long	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
long	O
before	O
King	O
James	O
would	O
be	O
in	O
England	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
the	O
subject	O
matter	O
brought	O
in	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
all	O
.	O
Some	O
difference	O
hapned	O
to	O
arise	O
between	O
the	O
Court	O
and	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Councel	O
about	O
the	O
laying	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
the	O
Court	O
were	O
of	O
Opinion	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
made	O
Treason	O
upon	O
that	O
Indictment	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
only	O
of	O
raising	O
and	O
hiring	O
Men	O
to	O
fight	O
against	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
Queen	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
the	O
Court	O
and	O
King	O
's	O
Councel	O
agreed	O
to	O
find	O
it	O
Special	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
defer	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
judges	O
could	O
meet	O
maturely	O
to	O
debate	O
the	O
Case	O
:	O
So	O
Judgement	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
respited	O
till	O
further	O
Order	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Mary	B-pers
Oliver	I-pers
was	O
Arraigned	O
,	O
for	O
pretending	O
herself	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Irish	O
Protestant	O
,	O
and	O
receiving	O
Money	O
of	O
the	O
Commissioners	O
at	O
Mercers	O
Hall	O
,	O
whereas	O
She	O
was	O
never	O
in	O
Ireland	O
;	O
which	O
Cheat	O
She	O
confessed	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Judgement	O
,	O
was	O
Inflicted	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
commiserating	O
her	O
Poverty	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
Night	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Grand	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
was	O
discharged	O
,	O
they	O
delivered	O
a	O
Presentment	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
:	O
First	O
,	O
Against	O
Alehouses	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
should	O
no	O
Drink	O
be	O
sold	O
on	O
Sunday	O
.	O
Secondly	O
,	O
Against	O
the	O
Lewd	O
Sort	O
of	O
Women	O
,	O
commonly	O
called	O
Night	O
walkers	O
.	O
Thirdly	O
,	O
Against	O
Beggars	O
,	O
that	O
go	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
the	O
streets	O
.	O
Fourthly	O
,	O
Against	O
Pedlars	O
and	O
Hawkers	O
.	O
Fifthly	O
,	O
Against	O
Butchers	O
,	O
that	O
make	O
it	O
their	O
practice	O
to	O
sell	O
Meat	O
on	O
the	O
Lord	O
's	O
day	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
great	O
Dishonour	O
of	O
Almighty	O
God	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Violation	O
of	O
the	O
Laws	O
of	O
the	O
Kingdom	O
.	O
Walter	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Feather	O
Bed	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Wastecoat	O
,	O
both	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Coat	O
20	O
s.	O
The	O
Indictment	O
being	O
laid	O
in	O
a	O
wrong	O
Name	O
,	O
were	O
ordered	O
to	O
amend	O
it	O
against	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgement	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
9.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Field	I-pers
,	O
Giles	O
Hall	O
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Ferguson	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
Peregrin	O
Barret	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Moor	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elinor	B-pers
Hatfeild	I-pers
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
5.	O
Walter	B-pers
Mooney	I-pers
,	O
Timothy	B-pers
Hartican	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Peartman	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Knott	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
Respited	O
after	O
Judgement	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
10.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Grove	I-pers
,	O
Martin	B-pers
Seward	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Eades	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Kentish	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	O
Hall	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Sherwood	I-pers
,	O
Elinor	B-pers
Fluellin	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Noone	O
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Shoot	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Knott	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
7.	O
Jane	B-pers
Peel	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Hannah	O
Baslet	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
Whipt	O
from	O
Newgate	O
to	O
Aldgate	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Flower	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Johnsons	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Lamb	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Peter	B-pers
Gouge	I-pers
,	O
to	O
be	O
Whipt	O
from	O
Newgate	O
to	O
Holborn	O
Bars	O
.	O
Hen	O
.	O
Lawrence	O
and	O
Hen	O
.	O
Ward	O
sent	O
to	O
Kent	O
Assizes	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Toogood	I-pers
was	O
Fined	O
Four	O
Nobles	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Slade	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
gave	O
in	O
Bail	O
to	O
appear	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
was	O
set	O
by	O
till	O
further	O
Order	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Tamplin	I-pers
was	O
order	O
'd	O
to	O
find	O
Sureties	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
.	O
Rowland	O
Smith	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
Cheat	O
,	O
was	O
order	O
'd	O
to	O
stand	O
upon	O
the	O
Pillory	O
at	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
one	O
hour	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
and	O
Edward	O
Sanders	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
Cheat	O
,	O
were	O
Sentenced	O
to	O
stand	O
on	O
the	O
Pillory	O
at	O
Mercers-Hall	O
Door	O
and	O
fined	O
20	O
Nobles	O
each	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
One	O
Pennington	O
,	O
a	O
Cabinet-maker	O
,	O
gave	O
in	O
Bail	O
to	O
a	O
pear	O
next	O
Sessions	O
,	O
for	O
saying	O
,	O
God	O
Dames	O
King	O
William	O
and	O
Queen	O
Mary	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
One	O
John	B-pers
Bowles	I-pers
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
remain	O
for	O
speaking	O
Seditious	O
Words	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Richard	B-pers
Shuttleworth	I-pers
and	O
one	O
Albert	O
were	O
accused	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Crime	O
being	O
committed	O
in	O
Laxcashire	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
order	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
Try	O
'd	O
at	O
Lancaster	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Glass	I-pers
and	O
Roger	B-pers
Tylley	I-pers
,	O
with	O
some	O
others	O
,	O
gave	O
in	O
Bail	O
to	O
appear	O
next	O
Sessions	O
for	O
speaking	O
Seditious	O
Words	O
against	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
Government	O
.	O
Advertisements	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
to	O
give	O
Notice	O
to	O
all	O
Persons	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
the	O
Publick	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Elmy	O
Professor	O
of	O
Physick	O
,	O
and	O
Operator	O
,	O
of	O
known	O
Integrity	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
25	O
Years	O
Practice	O
,	O
Liveth	O
at	O
the	O
Blue	O
Ball	O
in	O
Whale-Bone-Court	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Lower	O
End	O
of	O
Bartholomew-lane	O
by	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
who	O
most	O
safely	O
and	O
expeditiously	O
Cures	O
Deafness	O
and	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
Ears	O
in	O
any	O
of	O
what	O
Age	O
soever	O
,	O
(	O
if	O
Curable	O
)	O
and	O
at	O
First	O
Sight	O
,	O
by	O
Inspection	O
,	O
Resolves	O
the	O
Patient	O
if	O
so	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
as	O
most	O
Eminent	O
Persons	O
of	O
Quality	O
in	O
this	O
City	O
can	O
Testifie	O
.	O
He	O
hath	O
likewise	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Gargarism	O
or	O
Mouth	O
water	O
,	O
will	O
make	O
black	O
or	O
yellow	O
Teeth	O
as	O
white	O
as	O
Ivory	O
.	O
In	O
Plow-Vard	O
in	O
Grays-in	O
Lane	O
,	O
lives	O
Dr.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kirlens	I-pers
,	O
who	O
with	O
a	O
Drink	O
and	O
Pill	O
,	O
Cures	O
Ulcers	O
,	O
Scabs	O
,	O
Scurfs	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
or	O
elsewhere	O
:	O
Kings-Evil	O
,	O
Leprosie	O
,	O
and	O
Venereal	O
Disease	O
,	O
expecting	O
nothing	O
if	O
he	O
Cures	O
not	O
.	O
Of	O
the	O
last	O
,	O
he	O
hath	O
Cured	O
above	O
500	O
persons	O
,	O
many	O
after	O
Fluxing	O
.	O
The	O
Drink	O
is	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Quart	O
,	O
the	O
Pill	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
two	O
Purges	O
.	O
They	O
excel	O
all	O
Purges	O
,	O
Curing	O
many	O
Diseases	O
,	O
especially	O
the	O
Gout	O
and	O
Stone	O
.	O
In	O
all	O
Diseases	O
he	O
gives	O
his	O
Opinion	O
for	O
nothing	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Medicines	O
for	O
little	O
.	O
