TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
AND	O
QUEENS	O
COMMISSIONS	O
OF	O
THE	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
and	O
Thursday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
28th	O
,	O
and	O
29th	O
Days	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
1689	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
First	O
Year	O
of	O
Their	O
MAJESTIES	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
and	O
Thursday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
Twenty	O
eighth	O
,	O
and	O
Twenty	O
ninth	O
Days	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
1689	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pilkington	I-pers
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
follow	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Ranew	I-pers
James	B-pers
Croyle	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Mortlack	I-pers
John	B-pers
King	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Panton	I-pers
Christopher	B-pers
Wistcow	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Merryman	I-pers
William	B-pers
Boyce	I-pers
George	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
John	B-pers
Weekes	I-pers
Stephen	B-pers
Ragg	I-pers
James	B-pers
Medwells	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Cogghill	I-pers
Randale	B-pers
Nicholl	I-pers
John	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
John	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
John	B-pers
Horsley	I-pers
Michael	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Harbort	I-pers
John	B-pers
Green	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Young	I-pers
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Brent	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Odell	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
these	O
:	O
Diana	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
were	O
tryed	O
upon	O
two	O
several	O
Indictments	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
18	O
yards	O
of	O
Indian	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
38	O
s.	O
from	O
Ann	B-pers
Young	I-pers
.	O
A	O
2d	O
time	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
yards	O
of	O
Cloth	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
things	O
of	O
small	O
value	O
,	O
from	O
a	O
person	O
unknown	O
;	O
which	O
first	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
person	O
owning	O
the	O
latter	O
,	O
Fisher	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
9	O
s.	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
Indictment	O
,	O
but	O
Thomson	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
both	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Barbary	B-pers
Woolse	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Silver	O
Tankards	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
from	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
took	O
upon	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
as	O
She	O
was	O
persued	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
All	O
which	O
She	O
was	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
deny	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
Necklace	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
small	O
value	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Cooke	I-pers
,	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
the	O
stealing	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
,	O
yet	O
after	O
all	O
the	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Greenaway	B-pers
Field	I-pers
of	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
Gent	O
.	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
killing	O
one	O
Andrew	B-pers
Charleton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
August	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
near	O
the	O
right	O
Pap	O
(	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
)	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
6	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
died	O
the	O
20th	O
instant	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
First	O
Witness	O
proved	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Sohoe	O
where	O
Charleton	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
him	O
and	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
half	O
out	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
And	O
another	O
declared	O
that	O
he	O
owned	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
Wounded	O
the	O
Deceased	O
after	O
the	O
Quarrel	O
was	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Field	O
had	O
Challenged	O
the	O
other	O
to	O
fight	O
,	O
which	O
Challenge	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
and	O
afterwards	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
Charleton	O
was	O
a	O
Coward	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
whereever	O
he	O
met	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
kill	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
that	O
he	O
sent	O
any	O
Challenge	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
it	O
was	O
fully	O
Sworn	O
against	O
him	O
and	O
owned	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
hand	O
before	O
the	O
Murther	O
was	O
committed	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
further	O
proved	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
declared	O
upon	O
his	O
Death-bed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Field	O
run	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Body	O
as	O
he	O
sat	O
in	O
his	O
Chair	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
fled	O
away	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
leaving	O
the	O
Sword	O
in	O
his	O
Body	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Malice	O
against	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
several	O
Evasions	O
whereby	O
to	O
clear	O
his	O
Innocency	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
on	O
his	O
side	O
,	O
who	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
behaved	O
himself	O
fairly	O
heretofore	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
how	O
he	O
might	O
live	O
for	O
these	O
Three	O
Years	O
last	O
past	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
looking	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
have	O
had	O
Malice	O
against	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
altho	O
'	O
he	O
argued	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
;	O
yet	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Wilful	O
Murther	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Womens	O
Shoes	O
value	O
3	O
s	O
,	O
another	O
pair	O
18	O
d.	O
The	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
,	O
and	O
altho	O
'	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
yet	O
he	O
being	O
burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
before	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
a	O
Petti-lacenary	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Alexander	B-pers
Cockle	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Boy	O
of	O
about	O
12	O
years	O
old	O
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Silver	O
Ring	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
7	O
pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
7	O
l.	O
and	O
35	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Meakins	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
said	O
that	O
8	O
l	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
the	O
Boy	O
at	O
Tatnam	O
Highcross	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
drinking	O
Cyder	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
but	O
one	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
at	O
Cambridge	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Boy	O
taken	O
in	O
Middlesex	O
:	O
So	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
fasten	O
it	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
yet	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
prefer	O
a	O
Bill	O
of	O
Indictment	O
against	O
him	O
at	O
Cambridge	O
,	O
next	O
Assizes	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
here	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Rumbal	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Joseph	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
August	O
of	O
9	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Box	O
under	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
unlock	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
left	O
alone	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Crime	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
several	O
who	O
gave	O
a	O
favourable	O
account	O
of	O
her	O
Reputation	O
.	O
So	O
she	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Kedge	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
person	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
convey	O
'd	O
away	O
the	O
Tankard	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
extenuated	O
the	O
Crime	O
's	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
that	O
he	O
neglected	O
to	O
appear	O
two	O
Sessions	O
before	O
:	O
Yet	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
positive	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomasin	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
60	O
yards	O
of	O
black	O
Crape	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Katharine	B-pers
Steers	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
to	O
cheapen	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
the	O
Crape	O
under	O
her	O
Apron	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
denied	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
idle	O
Housewife	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Welsh	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
a	O
brown	O
Gelding	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Greene	I-pers
.	O
Several	O
persons	O
were	O
produced	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Gelding	O
was	O
lost	O
in	O
Kings	B-place
street	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Brewer	O
's	O
Dray	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
offering	O
the	O
Horse	O
to	O
Sale	O
at	O
Broken	O
Wharf	O
at	O
the	O
Water-House	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
Tryal	O
,	O
although	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
positive	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cary	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Woolnoth	I-place
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Matthew	B-pers
Coates	I-pers
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
one	O
Sheet	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
Petticoat	O
50	O
s.	O
one	O
Coif	O
40	O
s.	O
one	O
Crevat	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
good	O
value	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
Woman-Broker	O
;	O
which	O
she	O
confessed	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
:	O
But	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
she	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
never	O
took	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
:	O
Yet	O
it	O
was	O
produced	O
against	O
her	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
Bridewel	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Night	O
Walker	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
no	O
Friend	O
to	O
appear	O
on	O
her	O
behalf	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barloe	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
John	B-pers
Reeve	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
one	O
Hat	O
value	O
20	O
s	O
one	O
Cornbeck	O
Hat	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
Gown	O
15	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Shag	O
Breeches	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
Six	O
Bands	O
6	O
s.	O
with	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
small	O
value	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
Clements	B-place
Inn	I-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
Confederacy	O
with	O
one	O
Ann	B-pers
May	I-pers
,	O
who	O
being	O
called	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
in	O
Court	O
;	O
as	O
also	O
with	O
one	O
Burton	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
not	O
as	O
yet	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
that	O
ever	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
Ann	B-pers
May	I-pers
,	O
or	O
any	O
one	O
else	O
:	O
Yet	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Crout	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
Box	O
12	O
d.	O
one	O
Angel	O
piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
5	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Her	O
Master	O
and	O
Mistress	O
to	O
whom	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
hired	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
whiles	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
Church	O
,	O
the	O
Maid	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
abovementioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
Swear	O
positively	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
denied	O
it	O
.	O
So	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
taking	O
from	O
Carew	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
one	O
Necklace	O
set	O
in	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
past	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
to	O
have	O
taken	O
away	O
the	O
Necklace	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
seen	O
upon	O
a	O
Gentlewomans	O
Neck	O
at	O
Westminster	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
a	O
Person	O
,	O
where	O
Mrs.	O
Carew	O
Newton	O
Lodged	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Necklace	O
was	O
dropt	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
nothing	O
material	O
to	O
offer	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
.	O
So	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Amor	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
and	O
Tryed	O
upon	O
two	O
several	O
Indictments	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Austick	I-pers
one	O
Silver	O
Porringer	O
value	O
35	O
s.	O
one	O
lac't	O
Cornet	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
positive	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
The	O
2d	O
Indictment	O
was	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Silver	O
Mug	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
18	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Buckles	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
Edward	B-pers
Millet	I-pers
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Eling	B-place
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
likewise	O
positive	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
confest	O
to	O
have	O
sold	O
them	O
,	O
yet	O
she	O
denied	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
Tryal	O
:	O
Notwithstanding	O
which	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Trustrum	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Samuel	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Enfeild	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
taking	O
away	O
one	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
Ten	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Townsend	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
who	O
could	O
not	O
positively	O
charge	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
taking	O
away	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
.	O
So	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Katterns	I-pers
,	O
Philip	B-pers
Charlton	I-pers
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Winkle	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
Four	O
tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Ann	B-pers
Congring	I-pers
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
one	O
Watch	O
with	O
a	O
Silver	O
Case	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
Four	O
King	O
Charles	O
20	O
s.	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
4	O
l.	O
14	O
s.	O
two	O
Guinea	O
's	O
,	O
one	O
French	O
Piece	O
of	O
Mony	O
16	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
28	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
upon	O
the	O
Tryal	O
.	O
That	O
Heath	O
and	O
Katterns	O
were	O
principals	O
,	O
and	O
Charlton	O
and	O
Winkle	O
,	O
were	O
Accessaries	O
.	O
It	O
happened	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
Ann	B-pers
Congring	I-pers
being	O
oneNight	O
at	O
Katterns	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
,	O
they	O
perswaded	O
her	O
to	O
stay	O
all	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
whiles	O
she	O
was	O
asleep	O
,	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Watch	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
never	O
had	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
swore	O
positively	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
Katterns	O
have	O
her	O
purse	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Katterns	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
would	O
make	O
her	O
prove	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
her	O
Money	O
,	O
before	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
Katterns	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
did	O
Heath	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
never	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
:	O
Charlton	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Woman	O
(	O
viz	O
.	O
)	O
Congring	O
in	O
another	O
Room	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
how	O
the	O
Money	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
lost	O
;	O
Winkle	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
also	O
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
could	O
not	O
Swear	O
who	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
Congring	O
was	O
in	O
drink	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
Court	O
was	O
doubtful	O
whether	O
she	O
lost	O
any	O
Money	O
or	O
no	O
:	O
So	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
circumstantial	O
,	O
and	O
proceeding	O
somewhat	O
from	O
Malice	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
four	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
60	O
yards	O
of	O
Indian	O
Sattins	O
value	O
12	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
who	O
declared	O
that	O
the	O
Sattins	O
were	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
person	O
who	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
as	O
a	O
Witness	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
behalf	O
,	O
and	O
Mills	O
owned	O
the	O
Sattins	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
Woman	O
to	O
sell	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
yet	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
swearing	O
flatly	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Holding	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Roger	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
of	O
three	O
gold	O
Rings	O
value	O
24	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
Box	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
11	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
Allen	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
opportunity	O
to	O
steal	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
confess	O
to	O
have	O
sold	O
in	O
Wapping	O
.	O
She	O
denied	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
Tryal	O
;	O
yet	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
clear	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
PARTY-JURY	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cogghill	I-pers
Nicho	B-pers
,	I-pers
Romane	I-pers
Randal	B-pers
Nicholl	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Umbloe	I-pers
John	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
Nicholas	B-pers
Duffee	I-pers
John	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
Joshua	B-pers
Merrisaw	I-pers
John	B-pers
Horsley	I-pers
Abraham	B-pers
Hewet	I-pers
Nicholas	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
Joshua	B-pers
Morray	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Harman	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Peppermaker	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Degrove	I-pers
,	O
all	O
Dutch	O
Men	O
,	O
were	O
tryed	O
upon	O
a	O
Party-Jury	O
,	O
whose	O
Names	O
are	O
above	O
incerted	O
,	O
half	O
English	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
Aliens	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jennaway	I-pers
an	O
Infant	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
giving	O
her	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
upon	O
the	O
Right	O
Pap	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Business	O
was	O
thus	O
:	O
Two	O
of	O
these	O
Dutch	O
Men	O
were	O
drinking	O
in	O
Harman	O
's	O
Quarters	O
and	O
took	O
occasion	O
(	O
being	O
in	O
Drink	O
)	O
to	O
begin	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
Jennaway	O
,	O
the	O
Father	O
of	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Neighbors	O
that	O
were	O
drinking	O
there	O
,	O
calling	O
them	O
Papists	O
;	O
and	O
abused	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
most	O
egre	O
ious	O
manner	O
,	O
drawing	O
their	O
Knives	O
,	O
Swords	O
and	O
pistols	O
,	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
murther	O
them	O
.	O
And	O
Harman	O
was	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
alone	O
,	O
(	O
where	O
the	O
Child	O
lay	O
in	O
a	O
Cradle	O
asleep	O
)	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
drawn	O
and	O
upon	O
a	O
sudden	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
heard	O
to	O
screek	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
after	O
was	O
found	O
dead	O
in	O
the	O
Cradle	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
Harman	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
utterly	O
denied	O
at	O
his	O
Tryal	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
were	O
Indicted	O
as	O
being	O
accessary	O
to	O
the	O
Murther	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
what	O
they	O
did	O
was	O
in	O
their	O
own	O
Defence	O
,	O
being	O
assaulted	O
by	O
some	O
persons	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
death	O
of	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
no	O
Pistols	O
:	O
Yet	O
it	O
was	O
farther	O
evidenced	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
made	O
their	O
Escape	O
.	O
And	O
upon	O
Oath	O
it	O
was	O
made	O
out	O
,	O
that	O
Harman	O
was	O
only	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
drawn	O
where	O
the	O
Child	O
lay	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Child	O
dyed	O
of	O
the	O
Wound	O
received	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
that	O
heard	O
it	O
,	O
resented	O
it	O
as	O
a	O
most	O
villainous	O
Act	O
,	O
and	O
base	O
Murther	O
that	O
was	O
hardly	O
to	O
be	O
parallel	O
'd	O
;	O
so	O
upon	O
a	O
full	O
Hearing	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
,	O
no	O
Evidence	O
was	O
produced	O
to	O
fasten	O
the	O
Murther	O
upon	O
Pepper-maker	O
and	O
Degrove	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
;	O
but	O
Harman	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
wilful	O
Murther	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Job	B-pers
Medison	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
from	O
Isaac	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Cup	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
,	O
being	O
stopt	O
by	O
a	O
Smith	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
have	O
it	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
Cup	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
a	O
drunken	O
Woman	O
at	O
Fleet-bridge	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
:	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
immediately	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Locker	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Mary	B-pers
Chester	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Silver	O
Bason	O
value	O
12	O
l.	O
one	O
Chafin-Dish	O
and	O
two	O
Silver	O
Salts	O
,	O
some	O
Spoons	O
and	O
other	O
Plate	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
about	O
21	O
l.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
plain	O
against	O
her	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
heretofore	O
;	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
she	O
sold	O
to	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
in	O
Cheapside	O
.	O
She	O
denied	O
it	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
,	O
altho	O
'	O
she	O
had	O
confest	O
it	O
before	O
:	O
So	O
she	O
was	O
Convicted	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Remington	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Armstrong	I-pers
with	O
a	O
Penknife	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Wound	O
in	O
his	O
right	O
Knee	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
three	O
Inches	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
died	O
the	O
22th	O
of	O
August	O
following	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
Armstrong	O
's	O
Wife	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
who	O
could	O
not	O
positively	O
Charge	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
have	O
committed	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
only	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
Company	O
but	O
Remington	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
that	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
conjectured	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
Deceased	O
the	O
Wound	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
declared	O
upon	O
his	O
Death	O
bed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Wound	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Company	O
only	O
to	O
keep	O
the	O
peace	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
no	O
Wound	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Malice	O
proved	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
between	O
them	O
before	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
only	O
at	O
Common	O
Law	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Nelson	I-pers
Wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Nelson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
John	B-pers
Gibbons	I-pers
of	O
one	O
Tankardvalue	O
5	O
l.	O
one	O
Cup	O
50	O
s.	O
five	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
50	O
s.	O
one	O
Scarf	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
about	O
a	O
Week	O
in	O
August	O
,	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Gibbons	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
Plate	O
and	O
things	O
abovesaid	O
committed	O
to	O
her	O
Charge	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
her	O
Mastar	O
was	O
at	O
Dinner	O
,	O
she	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Custody	O
,	O
only	O
a	O
Scarf	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
the	O
borrowed	O
of	O
another	O
Person	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
owned	O
the	O
Scarf	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Wives	O
;	O
yet	O
the	O
Evidence	O
did	O
not	O
influence	O
the	O
Jury	O
enough	O
to	O
find	O
her	O
Guilty	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
discharged	O
Anthony	B-pers
Sattinger	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
stealing	O
from	O
Sir	O
Adam	B-pers
Oately	I-pers
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
one	O
Gown	O
wrought	O
with	O
Silver	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
one	O
Wastecoat	O
8	O
l.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
Sir	O
Adam	O
and	O
his	O
Family	O
were	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Doors	O
were	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
lost	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
affected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
them	O
:	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Sarah	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Highway	O
:	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
material	O
appeared	O
against	O
him	O
:	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
Discharged	O
.	O
Leonard	B-pers
Hutton	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Maul	I-pers
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
past	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
sworn	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
an	O
Ale	O
house	O
to	O
drink	O
in	O
Drury-lane	B-place
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Tankard	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
missing	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
but	O
a	O
slender	O
account	O
how	O
he	O
lived	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Maid	O
swore	O
positively	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
called	O
for	O
the	O
Drink	O
,	O
which	O
weighed	O
so	O
much	O
with	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Several	O
suspected	O
Popish	O
Priests	O
were	O
called	O
and	O
examined	O
whether	O
they	O
were	O
so	O
or	O
no	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
refused	O
to	O
answer	O
any	O
such	O
question	O
directly	O
or	O
indirectly	O
:	O
So	O
they	O
were	O
recommitted	O
to	O
Gaol	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
form	O
of	O
the	O
Statute	O
in	O
that	O
case	O
made	O
and	O
provided	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
,	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
3.	O
Diana	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Remington	I-pers
.	O
Leonard	B-pers
Hutton	I-pers
.	O
Ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
2.	O
John	B-pers
Medison	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barloe	I-pers
.	O
Ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Whipt	O
3.	O
John	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cary	I-pers
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
.	O
Thomasin	O
Burton	O
order	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
to	O
Bridewel	O
,	O
there	O
to	O
remain	O
till	O
next	O
Sessions	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
Correction	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
8.	O
Barbara	B-pers
Woolfe	I-pers
.	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Welsh	I-pers
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
.	O
Greenaway	O
Feild	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Amor	I-pers
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Holding	I-pers
John	B-pers
Harman	I-pers
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Locker	I-pers
.	O
Barbara	B-pers
Woolfe	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Amor	I-pers
,	O
Hannah	B-pers
Holding	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Locker	I-pers
were	O
Respited	O
after	O
Judgment	O
was	O
past	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
Transportation	O
;	O
which	O
the	O
Court	O
was	O
pleased	O
to	O
allow	O
of	O
.	O
Advertisement	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
to	O
give	O
Notice	O
to	O
all	O
Persons	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
the	O
Publick	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Elmy	O
Professor	O
of	O
Physick	O
,	O
and	O
Operator	O
,	O
of	O
known	O
Integrity	O
,	O
and	O
above	O
25	O
Years	O
Practice	O
,	O
Liveth	O
at	O
the	O
Blue	O
Ball	O
in	O
Whale	O
Bone	O
Court	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Lower	O
End	O
of	O
Bartholomew	O
lane	O
by	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
who	O
most	O
safely	O
and	O
expeditiously	O
Cures	O
Deafness	O
and	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
Ears	O
in	O
any	O
of	O
what	O
Age	O
soever	O
,	O
(	O
if	O
Curable	O
)	O
and	O
at	O
First	O
Sight	O
,	O
by	O
Inspection	O
,	O
Resolve	O
the	O
Patient	O
if	O
so	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
as	O
most	O
Eminent	O
Person	O
of	O
Quality	O
in	O
the	O
City	O
can	O
Testifie	O
.	O
He	O
hath	O
likewise	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Gargarism	O
or	O
Mouth	O
water	O
will	O
make	O
black	O
or	O
yellow	O
Teeth	O
as	O
white	O
as	O
Ivory	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
times	O
using	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
will	O
certainly	O
cure	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
Diseases	O
incident	O
to	O
the	O
Mouth	O
,	O
Teeth	O
and	O
Gums	O
,	O
which	O
in	O
many	O
persons	O
can	O
seth	O
a	O
stinking	O
Breath	O
,	O
which	O
(	O
by	O
the	O
blessing	O
of	O
God	O
and	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
this	O
Water	O
)	O
I	O
dare	O
affirm	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
freed	O
from	O
those	O
Maladies	O
beforementioned	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
.	O
His	O
pills	O
only	O
prepared	O
for	O
the	O
French	O
Disease	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Running	O
of	O
the	O
Reins	O
,	O
may	O
had	O
in	O
Boxes	O
of	O
several	O
prices	O
with	O
other	O
Veuerca	O
Arcana	O
's	O
,	O
as	O
occasion	O
requires	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
.	O
