TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
and	O
Queens	O
Commissions	O
OF	O
THE	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILY	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
and	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
10th	O
,	O
11th	O
,	O
12th	O
,	O
13th	O
,	O
and	O
17th	O
Days	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
1690	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
Second	O
Year	O
of	O
Their	O
MAJESTIES	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
and	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
10th	O
,	O
11th	O
,	O
12th	O
,	O
13th	O
and	O
17th	O
Days	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
1690	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pilkington	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Deputy-Recorder	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties-Justices	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
follow	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
Gilbert	B-pers
East	I-pers
John	B-pers
Leuker	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
Ralph	B-pers
Hadley	I-pers
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
Peter	B-pers
Ware	I-pers
John	B-pers
Hamden	I-pers
Philip	B-pers
Lamb	I-pers
Daniel	B-pers
Hickman	I-pers
Anthony	B-pers
Lawson	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Hurst	I-pers
Simon	B-pers
Althee	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Cannon	I-pers
John	B-pers
Baly	I-pers
John	B-pers
Outing	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Fitzgerard	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Hemsteed	I-pers
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
James	B-pers
Fern	I-pers
George	B-pers
Clisby	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Lynn	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Birch	I-pers
William	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Weeks	I-pers
,	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
these	O
:	O
William	B-pers
York	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Salver	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
two	O
Salts	O
value	O
24	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
Cup	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Countess	B-pers
Dowager	I-pers
of	I-pers
Plymouth	I-pers
,	O
the	O
proof	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
that	O
being	O
seen	O
in	O
the	O
Company	O
of	O
another	O
Person	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
they	O
upon	O
finding	O
themselves	O
discovered	O
betook	O
them	O
to	O
their	O
heels	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
pursuit	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
stopped	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
making	O
his	O
escape	O
,	O
also	O
several	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Plate	O
were	O
found	O
scattered	O
in	O
their	O
flight	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
a	O
loaden	O
Pistol	O
with	O
Powder	O
,	O
Brimstone	O
,	O
Marches	O
,	O
a	O
Steel	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
he	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
alledging	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
that	O
way	O
accidentally	O
,	O
and	O
learing	O
a	O
cry	O
out	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
the	O
like	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
to	O
overtake	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
appearing	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
former	O
Offender	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
a	O
Closet	O
joyning	O
to	O
the	O
Mansion-house	O
being	O
broke	O
wherein	O
the	O
Plate	O
was	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
it	O
as	O
it	O
appeared	O
upon	O
Matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
further	O
Consideration	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
John	B-pers
Pearson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
40	O
Hones	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
thirty	O
pound	O
Weight	O
of	O
Steal	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
by	O
Dean	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
that	O
working	O
with	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Closet	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
about	O
12	O
Hones	O
were	O
delivered	O
by	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
Woman	O
that	O
was	O
a	O
Nurse	O
,	O
who	O
upon	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
Robberies	O
being	O
discovered	O
,	O
restored	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
right	O
Owner	O
.	O
He	O
made	O
some	O
trivial	O
Excuses	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
clear	O
the	O
Charge	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
robbing	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Farmer	I-pers
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
November	O
of	O
7	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
l.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
the	O
proof	O
against	O
her	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
lodging	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
Harp-Alley	B-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
Fleet-Ditch	I-place
,	O
the	O
had	O
a	O
Person	O
that	O
come	O
to	O
her	O
as	O
her	O
Husband	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Landlady	O
being	O
sent	O
for	O
into	O
Wood	O
street	O
by	O
a	O
forged	O
Note	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
Absence	O
had	O
her	O
Chamber	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
taken	O
out	O
as	O
also	O
Brown	O
absented	O
herself	O
till	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
a	O
Coachman	O
and	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
To	O
this	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Ignorance	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
coming	O
back	O
to	O
her	O
Lodging	O
,	O
giving	O
likewise	O
some	O
Evidence	O
of	O
her	O
former	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
positive	O
Proof	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	I-pers
and	I-pers
Mary	I-pers
his	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	O
his	O
Wife	O
were	O
tried	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Gregory	B-pers
Archer	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolphs	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
silver	O
Cup	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
A	O
Suit	O
of	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
9	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
silk	O
and	O
woosted	O
Stockings	O
with	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Value	O
,	O
and	O
53	O
l.	O
7	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
proof	O
against	O
them	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Night	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
Jones	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
pawned	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
as	O
a	O
Brokers	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
confessed	O
she	O
had	O
received	O
them	O
of	O
one	O
Paul	B-pers
Grover	I-pers
,	O
and	O
one	O
Lucas	O
to	O
pawn	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
for	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
likewise	O
brought	O
a	O
Trunk	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
but	O
soon	O
removed	O
it	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
she	O
deny	O
them	O
upon	O
her	O
Trial	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
appearing	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
had	O
been	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Grover	O
and	O
Lucas	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
the	O
Robbery	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
other	O
Circumstances	O
appearing	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
being	O
indicted	O
as	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Law	O
in	O
that	O
Case	O
favourable	O
,	O
presuming	O
a	O
Husband	O
may	O
constrain	O
a	O
Wife	O
to	O
such	O
an	O
Enterprize	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Hutton	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
a	O
Rape	O
committed	O
on	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Marriot	I-pers
a	O
Virgin	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
Age	O
of	O
Ten	O
Years	O
.	O
The	O
Mother	O
of	O
the	O
Girl	O
as	O
also	O
a	O
Midwife	O
and	O
Chirurgeon	O
declared	O
upon	O
Oath	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
Condition	O
and	O
much	O
hurt	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
concluded	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
force	O
of	O
some	O
Man	O
that	O
had	O
violently	O
penetrated	O
her	O
Body	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Girl	O
deposed	O
that	O
Hutton	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Stable	O
dressing	O
her	O
Mother	O
Horses	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
light	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
neglect	O
them	O
;	O
when	O
taking	O
his	O
opportunityhe	O
took	O
her	O
in	O
his	O
Lap	O
behind	O
the	O
Stable-door	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
first	O
with	O
his	O
Fingers	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
his	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
very	O
much	O
abused	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
Carnal	O
knowledge	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
called	O
out	O
to	O
a	O
Neighbours	O
Maid	O
for	O
help	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
not	O
heard	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
she	O
went	O
crying	O
to	O
her	O
Mother	O
,	O
but	O
durst	O
not	O
discover	O
it	O
because	O
she	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
an	O
angry	O
Mood	O
,	O
till	O
some	O
days	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
pained	O
,	O
and	O
compelled	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
only	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
and	O
clapt	O
her	O
Breech	O
,	O
for	O
hazarding	O
the	O
Horses	O
kicking	O
her	O
by	O
pulling	O
their	O
Tails	O
:	O
however	O
it	O
plainly	O
appearing	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
Ravished	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
,	O
the	O
Law	O
of	O
the	O
Land	O
making	O
it	O
death	O
,	O
whether	O
with	O
or	O
without	O
her	O
consent	O
,	O
to	O
carnally	O
know	O
a	O
female	O
Infant	O
under	O
the	O
Age	O
of	O
10	O
Years	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Titcomb	I-pers
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
60	O
Yards	O
of	O
Bone-lace	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Huckle	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
Legrand	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
November	O
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Sheet	O
of	O
Paper	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
returning	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Lace	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
pursued	O
he	O
dropt	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
by	O
a	O
Woman	O
that	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
thrown	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
the	O
Party	O
robbed	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
had	O
again	O
without	O
Imbeslement	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
only	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
35	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Burningham	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Gregories	I-place
by	I-place
St.	I-place
Pauls	I-place
on	O
the	O
11th	O
.	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
upon	O
Evidence	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
sell	O
a	O
half	O
French	O
Pistol	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
agreeing	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
watching	O
his	O
opportunity	O
when	O
there	O
was	O
only	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
came	O
with	O
a	O
Milled	O
half	O
Crown	O
to	O
know	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
good	O
,	O
and	O
whilst	O
the	O
Boy	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
show	O
it	O
,	O
his	O
Master	O
he	O
broke	O
the	O
Goldsmith	O
's	O
Glass	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
away	O
the	O
Paper	O
of	O
Rings	O
,	O
he	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
shift	O
off	O
to	O
a	O
Boy	O
then	O
in	O
Custody	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
positive	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Litchfield	I-pers
being	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cow	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Islingtone	I-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
sixth	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
upon	O
his	O
Arraignment	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
He	O
pleaded	O
likewise	O
guilty	O
to	O
a	O
second	O
Indictment	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Cows	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Binson	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Pancras	I-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
County	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
To	O
a	O
third	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bullock	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
and	O
to	O
a	O
fourth	O
Indictment	O
,	O
for	O
another	O
Cow	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Long	I-pers
and	O
Simon	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
for	O
killing	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
.	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
price	O
coming	O
into	O
Long	O
's	O
Company	O
at	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
called	O
the	B-place
Artechoak	I-place
near	I-place
Sommerset-house	I-place
,	O
the	O
deceased	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bad	O
Language	O
,	O
yet	O
e	O
're	O
they	O
parted	O
a	O
Reconciliation	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
things	O
in	O
a	O
good	O
temper	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
Long	O
's	O
refusing	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Wine	O
a	O
fresh	O
quarrel	O
happened	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
wherein	O
Price	O
gave	O
Long	O
a	O
blow	O
on	O
his	O
Face	O
with	O
his	O
Fist	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
several	O
Swords	O
were	O
drawn	O
and	O
Matthews	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
pass	O
at	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
cryed	O
out	O
to	O
stop	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
wounded	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
Matthews	O
being	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
blow	O
or	O
two	O
over	O
the	O
Head	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
soon	O
after	O
died	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
proof	O
,	O
that	O
Long	O
or	O
Rogers	O
drew	O
their	O
Swords	O
,	O
or	O
were	O
assisting	O
to	O
Matthews	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Noon	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Trant	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
together	O
with	O
Joseph	B-pers
Trant	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Noon	I-pers
;	O
the	O
two	O
latter	O
breaking	O
Goal	O
at	O
Windsor	O
,	O
not	O
being	O
yet	O
retaken	O
,	O
the	O
proof	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Duncom	I-pers
was	O
entred	O
at	O
a	O
Garret	O
Window	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
.	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
with	O
divers	O
Lockets	O
,	O
Rings	O
,	O
Cloths	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
of	O
considerable	O
Value	O
taken	O
thence	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
soon	O
after	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Trant	I-pers
offering	O
to	O
sell	O
or	O
pawn	O
the	O
Watch	O
and	O
Lockets	O
to	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
at	O
Windsor	O
,	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
being	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
a	O
Lady	O
who	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Bristol	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
four	O
seised	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
two	O
Men	O
escaped	O
,	O
as	O
has	O
been	O
said	O
by	O
breaking	O
Prison	O
:	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Trant	I-pers
alledged	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
things	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Trant	I-pers
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Watch	O
in	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Lockets	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
in	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
nor	O
give	O
any	O
good	O
account	O
of	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
considerable	O
proof	O
against	O
Noon	O
,	O
more	O
than	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Company	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Catharines	I-place
by	I-place
the	I-place
Tower	I-place
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Dozen	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
twelve	O
Shirts	O
,	O
Parcels	O
of	O
Cloth	O
,	O
Stuff	O
,	O
Drawers	O
,	O
two	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shag-breeches	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
of	O
considerable	O
value	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
Rattle	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
.	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
The	O
proof	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
outward	O
Doors	O
being	O
only	O
put	O
too	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
four	O
more	O
came	O
rushing	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
whilst	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
back	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
seizing	O
upon	O
what	O
came	O
to	O
hand	O
and	O
fled	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
Pursuit	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
twelve	O
Shirts	O
,	O
and	O
Drawers	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
.	O
To	O
this	O
he	O
alledged	O
he	O
was	O
newly	O
come	O
from	O
Sea	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
an	O
outcry	O
of	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
in	O
following	O
them	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
dropt	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
give	O
no	O
further	O
account	O
of	O
himself	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
proof	O
of	O
the	O
Doors	O
being	O
fastened	O
,	O
the	O
Burglary	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
A.	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
53	O
Yards	O
of	O
black	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
about	O
9	O
l.	O
4	O
s.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Coniers	I-pers
near	O
Ludgate	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
September	O
;	O
As	O
likewise	O
about	O
48	O
Yards	O
of	O
striped	O
Silk	O
from	O
Henry	B-pers
Rapier	I-pers
,	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
pawn	O
at	O
one	O
Moulenex	O
a	O
Brokers	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
produced	O
one	O
Sarah	B-pers
Cane	I-pers
a	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
owned	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
disposed	O
of	O
the	O
Piece	O
of	O
striped	O
Silk	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
of	O
one	O
Jones	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
bring	O
plain	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
upon	O
an	O
Indictment	O
of	O
Burglary	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Dukes-Place	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
.	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
stealing	O
two	O
brass	O
Pots	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Mortar	O
and	O
Pestle	O
,	O
5	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
a	O
Coat	O
and	O
Breeches	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
Hood	O
,	O
Neckcloath	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
things	O
of	O
value	O
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Windows	O
were	O
forced	O
open	O
by	O
shoving	O
back	O
the	O
Bolt	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
carried	O
out	O
.	O
He	O
having	O
been	O
a	O
Lodger	O
before	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Constable	O
and	O
Watch	O
being	O
abroad	O
,	O
saw	O
him	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
over	O
London	O
Wall	O
:	O
As	O
likewise	O
a	O
Woman	O
who	O
looked	O
out	O
at	O
an	O
overtkwart	O
Window	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
then	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
;	O
yet	O
being	O
afterwards	O
apprehended	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
stole	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
in	O
a	O
Neighbouring	O
Shop	O
,	O
whither	O
he	O
had	O
carried	O
them	O
:	O
So	O
that	O
not	O
giving	O
any	O
satisfactory	O
Account	O
of	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
and	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
James	I-pers
and	O
Johanna	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
were	O
tried	O
upon	O
an	O
Indictment	O
of	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
for	O
clipping	O
,	O
fileing	O
and	O
diminishing	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Coin	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
20	O
Half	O
Crowns	O
,	O
20	O
Shillings	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
was	O
that	O
James	O
,	O
offering	O
a	O
considerable	O
Parcel	O
of	O
melted	O
silver	O
to	O
a	O
Refiner	O
,	O
was	O
seized	O
upon	O
suspition	O
of	O
unlawful	O
coining	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
carried	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
an	O
Officer	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
search	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
Lodging	O
in	O
Stone-Cutters-street	B-place
near	I-place
Fleet-ditch	I-place
,	O
where	O
two	O
Files	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Sizzars	O
,	O
a	O
melting	O
pot	O
,	O
a	O
few	O
Clippings	O
with	O
some	O
clipped	O
Mony	O
,	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
an	O
upper	O
Closet	O
:	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
melted	O
Silver	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
melted	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Spanish	O
Wreck	O
of	O
Jameca	O
,	O
and	O
produced	O
several	O
to	O
testifie	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
brought	O
some	O
of	O
that	O
Mony	O
home	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Implements	O
he	O
denyed	O
their	O
being	O
his	O
:	O
The	O
woman	O
alledged	O
a	O
Countryman	O
had	O
lodged	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
her	O
House	O
just	O
before	O
the	O
finding	O
them	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
producing	O
several	O
Persons	O
to	O
testifie	O
they	O
took	O
pains	O
for	O
their	O
Living	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
by	O
Trade	O
a	O
Wheelwright	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
James	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
upon	O
an	O
Indictment	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Cornelius	B-pers
Dutch	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolphs	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Looking-glass	O
,	O
a	O
Wigg	O
,	O
a	O
needle	O
Case	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
Dutche	O
's	O
Brother	O
,	O
finding	O
the	O
Doors	O
open	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
next	O
House	O
to	O
the	O
Maid	O
,	O
to	O
enquire	O
how	O
it	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
being	O
ignorant	O
of	O
it	O
he	O
presently	O
entred	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
packing	O
up	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
But	O
upon	O
his	O
asking	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
there	O
,	O
James	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
forced	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hands	O
,	O
and	O
persued	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
he	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
justifie	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
as	O
layed	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Pee	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Luetstring	O
,	O
valued	O
at	O
4	O
l.	O
4	O
s.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Coniers	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Martins	I-place
Ludgate	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
:	O
And	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
15	O
Yards	O
of	O
the	O
Silk	O
was	O
found	O
pawned	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
a	O
Brokers	O
in	O
Wich-street	O
,	O
thereupon	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
.	O
To	O
this	O
he	O
pleaded	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
being	O
a	O
Taylor	O
by	O
Trade	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
a	O
Sute	O
of	O
Cloaths	O
for	O
a	O
Person	O
,	O
who	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
finished	O
them	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
Money	O
to	O
pay	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
having	O
been	O
a	O
Mercers	O
Man	O
,	O
whose	O
Master	O
had	O
failed	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
take	O
Silk	O
for	O
his	O
Wages	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
,	O
pulling	O
out	O
a	O
Parcel	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
pawn	O
it	O
for	O
40	O
s.	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
25	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
for	O
his	O
Work	O
,	O
giving	O
the	O
other	O
Party	O
the	O
overplus	O
,	O
and	O
since	O
heard	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
.	O
He	O
produced	O
many	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
arrest	O
his	O
honest	O
Dealing	O
,	O
and	O
way	O
of	O
Living	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
cautiond	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
to	O
undertake	O
such	O
things	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
W	B-pers
-	I-pers
W	I-pers
-	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
killing	O
Giles	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
in	O
the	O
Belly	O
.	O
Upon	O
Evidence	O
it	O
appeared	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
were	O
drinking	O
together	O
at	O
the	O
Horse-shoe	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Drury-lane	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
both	O
somewhat	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
to	O
all	O
appearance	O
very	O
friendly	O
,	O
when	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
they	O
drew	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Encounter	O
Morgan	O
received	O
the	O
Wound	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
dyed	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Month	O
;	O
and	O
before	O
his	O
Death	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
Misfortune	O
,	O
by	O
drawing	O
upon	O
Mr.	O
W	O
-	O
and	O
compelling	O
him	O
to	O
fight	O
him	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Munford	I-pers
of	O
S.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
upon	O
an	O
Indictment	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
for	O
Clipping	O
the	O
Current	O
Coyn	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
on	O
November	O
26th	O
last	O
.	O
And	O
upon	O
Evidenceit	O
appeared	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
tempted	O
one	O
Van	B-pers
Vincenburg	I-pers
,	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Vandress	O
Paymaster	O
to	O
the	O
Dutch-soldiers	O
,	O
to	O
help	O
him	O
to	O
Large	O
Money	O
,	O
offering	O
ten	O
Pounds	O
per	O
cent	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
many	O
plausible	O
Stories	O
tending	O
to	O
great	O
Advantage	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
,	O
Mistrusting	O
the	O
bad	O
Consequence	O
,	O
revealed	O
it	O
to	O
some	O
Friends	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
;	O
who	O
acquainted	O
Count	O
Solms	O
and	O
the	O
Earl	O
of	O
Portland	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
end	O
it	O
was	O
concluded	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
further	O
Discovery	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
should	O
humour	O
the	O
Business	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
Broad	O
Mony	O
for	O
his	O
Money	O
which	O
was	O
clipp	O
'd	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
twice	O
or	O
thrice	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
15	O
l.	O
and	O
to	O
gain	O
further	O
Evidence	O
in	O
this	O
Matter	O
two	O
Persons	O
were	O
planted	O
behind	O
a	O
Wainscot	O
Partition	O
,	O
adjoyning	O
to	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
the	O
Exchange	O
was	O
made	O
,	O
observing	O
through	O
a	O
Hole	O
,	O
purposely	O
made	O
,	O
all	O
that	O
passed	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Delivery	O
of	O
the	O
one	O
Mony	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Discourse	O
that	O
passed	O
between	O
them	O
:	O
And	O
soon	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
Apprehended	O
,	O
begg	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
Released	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
so	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
In	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
,	O
he	O
denyed	O
what	O
the	O
Evidence	O
had	O
alledged	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
and	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
prove	O
something	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
Life	O
and	O
Conversation	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
18	O
of	O
Eliz	O
.	O
being	O
read	O
,	O
so	O
far	O
as	O
it	O
concerned	O
this	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
full	O
against	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Furnier	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
40	O
s.	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
Hitchan	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
;	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
were	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
they	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
often	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
usually	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
pint	O
in	O
his	O
Bottle	O
to	O
carry	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
his	O
coming	O
they	O
had	O
missed	O
Money	O
in	O
the	O
Bill	O
of	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
when	O
one	O
Morning	O
the	O
Wife	O
,	O
watching	O
,	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
put	O
a	O
small	O
Whale-bone	O
into	O
the	O
Crevis	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Mony	O
is	O
usually	O
drop	O
'd	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
drew	O
up	O
two	O
pieces	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
being	O
apprehended	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
stuck	O
Bird-lime	O
to	O
the	O
Whale-bone	O
,	O
and	O
drawn	O
up	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
giving	O
a	O
slender	O
account	O
of	O
himself	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Fellony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
A	B-pers
-	I-pers
S	I-pers
-	I-pers
of	O
S.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
robbing	O
Thomas	B-pers
Marty	I-pers
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
of	O
28	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
being	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
several	O
times	O
lost	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pockets	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Night	O
,	O
feigning	O
himself	O
drunk	O
,	O
he	O
watched	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
carrying	O
them	O
down	O
Stairs	O
soon	O
after	O
returned	O
them	O
under	O
his	O
Bolster	O
,	O
when	O
telling	O
his	O
Mony	O
he	O
missed	O
28	O
s.	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
positive	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
:	O
And	O
that	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
before	O
she	O
had	O
shewed	O
several	O
pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
her	O
things	O
above	O
her	O
degree	O
,	O
as	O
laced	O
Smocks	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
To	O
this	O
she	O
alledged	O
,	O
She	O
had	O
Money	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Service	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
received	O
more	O
of	O
her	O
Brother	O
;	O
saying	O
her	O
Master	O
laid	O
the	O
Money	O
to	O
her	O
Charge	O
because	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
suffer	O
him	O
to	O
debauch	O
her	O
;	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
she	O
had	O
wronged	O
a	O
former	O
Master	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
yet	O
only	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Searle	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Blow	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Staff	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
dyed	O
.	O
Damaris	B-pers
Dessin	I-pers
swore	O
positively	O
against	O
him	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Stroke	O
:	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
he	O
was	O
of	O
the	O
deceased	O
's	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
ever	O
been	O
very	O
friendly	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
this	O
Disaster	O
were	O
drinking	O
at	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
when	O
Powel	O
going	O
out	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
news	O
coming	O
he	O
was	O
like	O
to	O
be	O
knock	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
Searle	O
run	O
to	O
his	O
Assistance	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
Disaster	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
it	O
being	O
unlikely	O
that	O
Powel	O
should	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
Blow	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Meed	I-pers
as	O
Principal	O
,	O
and	O
Anne	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
as	O
Accessary	O
,	O
were	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
36	O
yards	O
of	O
Ribon	O
,	O
value	O
28	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
l	O
10	O
s.	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Peat	I-pers
of	O
S.	B-place
Buttolphs	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
July	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
Bird	O
recommended	O
Meed	O
,	O
who	O
then	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Smith	O
as	O
a	O
lodger	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
House	O
,	O
when	O
soon	O
after	O
he	O
rushed	O
into	O
a	O
Chamber	O
,	O
where	O
Peat	O
's	O
Wife	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
Ribon	O
,	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
Bird	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
following	O
him	O
,	O
got	O
it	O
again	O
:	O
And	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
observed	O
him	O
to	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
into	O
a	O
Drawer	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Money	O
lay	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
a	O
chinking	O
,	O
but	O
missed	O
not	O
her	O
Money	O
and	O
some	O
Writings	O
till	O
a	O
while	O
after	O
Meed	O
had	O
left	O
her	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
apprehending	O
or	O
Taxing	O
Bird	O
as	O
a	O
Confederate	O
the	O
Writings	O
were	O
brought	O
again	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Letter	O
,	O
from	O
Meed	O
alias	O
Smith	O
,	O
promising	O
Satisfaction	O
.	O
He	O
alledged	O
Innocency	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
several	O
to	O
prove	O
he	O
had	O
lived	O
well	O
,	O
but	O
failed	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
when	O
upon	O
the	O
Consideration	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
Meed	O
Guilty	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
Bird	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Warder	O
of	O
the	O
Tower	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
negligent	O
Escape	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Rycant	I-pers
,	O
committed	O
to	O
his	O
Custody	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
his	O
Arraingment	O
confessed	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Peter	B-pers
Hesey	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Clements	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
's	I-place
Foster-lane	I-place
,	O
on	O
November	O
4	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
five	O
suspicious	O
Persons	O
being	O
discovered	O
by	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
to	O
hanker	O
about	O
the	O
House	O
at	O
an	O
unseasonable	O
hour	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
a	O
Watchman	O
so	O
well	O
observed	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
some	O
runing	O
off	O
,	O
as	O
perceiving	O
they	O
were	O
discovered	O
,	O
the	O
5th	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
under	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
not	O
pursuit	O
made	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
Cane	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
appearing	O
the	O
House	O
had	O
been	O
entred	O
,	O
Goods	O
taken	O
out	O
and	O
removed	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
he	O
giving	O
no	O
satisfactory	O
account	O
of	O
himself	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Middlemore	I-pers
in	O
Thames-street	B-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
the	I-place
Custome-house	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
Sheets	O
,	O
Table-Cloaths	O
and	O
other	O
Linnen	O
:	O
Upon	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Maid	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
coming	O
up	O
Stairs	O
see	O
him	O
jump	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
of	O
the	O
Ballast	O
Office	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
,	O
upon	O
search	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
a	O
large	O
bunch	O
of	O
Pick	O
locks	O
and	O
a	O
Chizel	O
.	O
He	O
made	O
many	O
frivolous	O
Excuses	O
,	O
but	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mac-Donel	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Digs	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
were	O
tryed	O
upon	O
an	O
Indictment	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
for	O
Cliping	O
,	O
Filing	O
,	O
and	O
Diminishing	O
the	O
Current	O
Coyn	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
was	O
a	O
Servant-Maid	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
Digs	O
;	O
she	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
her	O
Master	O
frequently	O
clip	O
and	O
rub	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Macdonel	O
had	O
assisted	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
her	O
making	O
Discovery	O
some	O
Clipings	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
Place	O
where	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
Digs	O
used	O
to	O
lay	O
his	O
Tools	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
a	O
Bag	O
of	O
new-clipt	O
Money	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
heap	O
of	O
Malt	O
.	O
To	O
this	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Ignorance	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
His	O
Maid	O
had	O
wronged	O
him	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
because	O
he	O
went	O
about	O
to	O
prosecute	O
her	O
she	O
had	O
sworn	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
testifie	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
However	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Cave	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
striped	O
Lutestring	O
from	O
Henry	B-pers
Rapier	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
Wise	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Martins-Ludgate	I-place
,	O
and	O
the	O
Silk	O
being	O
charged	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
pretended	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Jones	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
producing	O
her	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Bussey	I-pers
of	O
S.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
was	O
put	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
for	O
robbing	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Hatton	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Beaver	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Point	O
Cravat	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
laced	O
Sleves	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
W.	B-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
and	O
M.	B-pers
his	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
,	O
were	O
tryed	O
upon	O
an	O
Indictment	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
for	O
cliping	O
the	O
current	O
Coyn	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
:	O
And	O
upon	O
Evidence	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
a	O
Letter	O
being	O
sent	O
to	O
Captain	O
Richardson	O
,	O
intimating	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
used	O
that	O
unlawful	O
Trade	O
:	O
The	O
House	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
where	O
,	O
a	O
Box	O
of	O
Filings	O
and	O
some	O
Clipings	O
of	O
Silver	O
were	O
found	O
,	O
also	O
a	O
rough	O
half	O
Crown	O
,	O
with	O
many	O
Instruments	O
suitable	O
to	O
that	O
Undertaking	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Bag	O
of	O
19	O
l.	O
11	O
s.	O
of	O
broad	O
Money	O
,	O
hid	O
under	O
the	O
Stairs	O
in	O
the	O
Celler	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
lump	O
of	O
Melted	O
Silver	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Silver-Smith	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Tools	O
properly	O
belonged	O
to	O
his	O
Trade	O
,	O
and	O
sundry	O
persons	O
testifying	O
for	O
his	O
Course	O
of	O
Life	O
and	O
Behaviour	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
Wife	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Glandeny	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
transporting	O
Lead	O
to	O
Dunkirk	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
the	O
French	O
King	O
:	O
Being	O
put	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Moor	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Cane	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Flowered	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Manly	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Bedford	B-place
street	I-place
by	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
to	O
cheapen	O
Silk	O
immediately	O
,	O
upon	O
her	O
Departure	O
,	O
the	O
Silk	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
the	O
Apprentice	O
pursuing	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
silk	O
found	O
about	O
her	O
;	O
yet	O
being	O
in	O
many	O
frivolous	O
Stories	O
,	O
and	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
notorious	O
Shop	O
lift	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
several	O
Yards	O
of	O
Stuff	O
,	O
4	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
of	O
value	O
,	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
of	O
S.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Criple-gate	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
Allen	O
's	O
Wife	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
things	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
Cross	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
testimony	O
of	O
the	O
Wife	O
,	O
who	O
appeared	O
in	O
his	O
behalf	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
the	O
Matter	O
in	O
that	O
case	O
not	O
amounting	O
to	O
Felony	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Margrets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cornet	O
,	O
3	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
Yard	O
of	O
Lace	O
and	O
two	O
Bodkins	O
,	O
from	O
Samuel	B-pers
Eastman	I-pers
:	O
But	O
nothing	O
except	O
the	O
Lace	O
appearing	O
on	O
her	O
Tryal	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
producing	O
Witnesses	O
that	O
she	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Daughter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Constance	B-pers
Wainright	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Anne	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
and	O
Anne	B-pers
Hereford	I-pers
were	O
tryed	O
for	O
setting	O
the	O
Gaol	O
of	O
Newgate	O
on	O
fire	O
:	O
Against	O
whom	O
it	O
appeared	O
in	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
had	O
pulled	O
down	O
the	O
Laths	O
of	O
the	O
Wall	O
on	O
the	O
Master	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
Fire	O
to	O
a	O
Door	O
which	O
burnt	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
case	O
,	O
promising	O
to	O
themselves	O
an	O
Escape	O
in	O
the	O
Conflagration	O
and	O
general	O
Consternation	O
it	O
might	O
occasion	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
timely	O
discovered	O
by	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
same	O
Floor	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
quenched	O
by	O
the	O
Keepers	O
.	O
Yates	O
pleaded	O
she	O
dissented	O
in	O
this	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
laboured	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
contrary	O
appearing	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Fellony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Bret	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Silver	O
Tankards	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sarjeant	I-pers
of	O
S.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripple-gate	I-place
:	O
And	O
it	O
appearing	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
about	O
him	O
at	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Old	O
Bethlem	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Yats	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
9	O
Yards	O
of	O
Plush	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
of	O
S.	B-place
Buttolphs	I-place
Bishops	I-place
gate	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
Instant	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
the	O
Lineing	O
of	O
a	O
Coach	O
;	O
he	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Tabby	O
Pettycoat	O
,	O
withGold	O
Lace	O
,	O
a	O
laced	O
Cravat	O
,	O
5	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
Corner	O
and	O
Quoif	O
,	O
from	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Buttolphs	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
pawned	O
at	O
a	O
Brokers	O
in	O
Rosemary-Lane	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
House	O
privately	O
,	O
deserting	O
his	O
Service	O
.	O
She	O
alledged	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
found	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
Entrance	O
of	O
her	O
Master	O
's	O
Door	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
appearing	O
only	O
a	O
frivolous	O
Excuse	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
9	O
s.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
of	O
S.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
together	O
with	O
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
one	O
Margaret	B-pers
Seymour	I-pers
,	O
were	O
tryed	O
upon	O
an	O
Indictment	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
for	O
Cliping	O
,	O
Filing	O
and	O
Deminishing	O
the	O
the	O
current	O
Coyn	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
as	O
half	O
Crowns	O
,	O
Shillings	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
And	O
upon	O
Evidence	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
latter	O
having	O
borrowed	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Scales	O
,	O
in	O
returning	O
them	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Clipings	O
found	O
hanging	O
on	O
the	O
Strings	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
which	O
occasioned	O
the	O
Search	O
of	O
Porter	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
Seymour	O
lodged	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shears	O
,	O
Files	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Cliping	O
,	O
clip	O
'd	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Materials	O
were	O
found	O
;	O
but	O
many	O
Witnesses	O
appearing	O
on	O
their	O
behalf	O
,	O
to	O
testifie	O
they	O
got	O
their	O
Livings	O
by	O
honest	O
Labour	O
and	O
Industry	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
utterly	O
denying	O
any	O
knowledge	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
so	O
found	O
,	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
E	B-pers
-	I-pers
P	I-pers
-	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
robbing	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Laady	I-pers
of	O
S.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
Sleeves	O
,	O
4	O
Musling	O
Neck-cloaths	O
,	O
a	O
Cravat	O
,	O
laced	O
Ruffles	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
of	O
value	O
.	O
Upon	O
Evidence	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
Lodging	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
for	O
himself	O
and	O
one	O
he	O
called	O
his	O
Wife	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
two	O
days	O
end	O
going	O
away	O
without	O
the	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
the	O
Landlady	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
missing	O
.	O
He	O
pleaded	O
the	O
Woman	O
he	O
brought	O
thither	O
was	O
a	O
Whore	O
,	O
pick	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
things	O
without	O
his	O
Knowledg	O
;	O
but	O
owning	O
her	O
for	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
giving	O
no	O
very	O
good	O
Account	O
of	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Fellony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Abby	I-pers
of	O
Harrow-on-the-hill	B-place
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
was	O
tryed	O
upon	O
3	O
Indictment	O
,	O
1	O
.	O
For	O
stealing	O
a	O
Grindstone	O
with	O
an	O
Iron-Handle	O
,	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Crane	I-pers
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
Septemb	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
For	O
stealing	O
Geese	O
from	O
Jane	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
For	O
stealing	O
a	O
Ewe	O
and	O
a	O
Lamb	O
from	O
Edward	B-pers
Joyce	I-pers
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
October	O
:	O
And	O
upon	O
Evidence	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
,	O
or	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
disposed	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Fellony	O
upon	O
the	O
three	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
and	I-pers
Jane	I-pers
his	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
and	O
Jane	O
his	O
Wife	O
were	O
tryed	O
for	O
robbing	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Nettleship	I-pers
of	O
S.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
December	O
instant	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
out	O
of	O
two	O
Trunks	O
in	O
a	O
Garret	O
3	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
Laced	O
Cravat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Charles	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Banister	I-pers
,	O
persons	O
that	O
had	O
intrusted	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
:	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
positive	O
proof	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Baly	I-pers
of	O
S.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Silver	O
Drachm-Cups	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
a	O
Coconut-Cup	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
8	O
l.	O
in	O
Moneys	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
20	O
l.	O
from	O
Edward	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
Upon	O
Evidence	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
several	O
Persons	O
broke	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
bound	O
the	O
Family	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
:	O
But	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Chiswick	B-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
for	O
marrying	O
Margaret	B-pers
Knap	I-pers
,	O
at	O
S.	O
Bartholomews	O
near	O
Oxford	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
;	O
And	O
after	O
that	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Dillo	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Parish	O
Church	O
of	O
S.	O
Mary	O
le	O
Bone	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
denying	O
both	O
Marriages	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
later	O
being	O
only	O
proved	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Foulks	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Savory	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
were	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Cloath	O
Coat	O
,	O
2	O
Wast-coats	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
value	O
,	O
from	O
Edward	B-pers
Roman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
November	O
:	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
positive	O
Proof	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Harvy	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Fulham	B-place
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Skinner	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Bible	O
,	O
Looking-glass	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
a	O
Pillow	O
and	O
other	O
Bedding	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
3	O
Years	O
past	O
,	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
by	O
breaking	O
the	O
Glass	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
lifting	O
up	O
the	O
Bar	O
that	O
closed	O
the	O
Shutters	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
through	O
the	O
Crevis	O
:	O
And	O
being	O
discovered	O
by	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
upon	O
a	O
Falling	O
out	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
being	O
well	O
able	O
to	O
deny	O
it	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
,	O
or	O
give	O
any	O
good	O
Account	O
of	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Fellony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
White-Chapel	B-place
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
upon	O
an	O
Indictment	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
for	O
Coyning	O
False	O
and	O
Counterfeit	O
Money	O
,	O
as	O
King	O
James	O
I	O
Shillings	O
,	O
King	O
Charles	O
I	O
's	O
Half	O
Crowns	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
first	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
Coyn	O
and	O
assist	O
in	O
Coyning	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
especially	O
at	O
one	O
Pitchers	O
:	O
And	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
That	O
going	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
some	O
Money	O
due	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
paid	O
her	O
40	O
s.	O
in	O
Counterfeit	O
Money	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
To	O
counterballance	O
this	O
Evidence	O
he	O
produced	O
a	O
considerable	O
number	O
of	O
credible	O
persons	O
,	O
with	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
worked	O
(	O
as	O
being	O
a	O
Naylor	O
by	O
Trade	O
)	O
and	O
dealt	O
with	O
,	O
on	O
sundry	O
occasions	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
a	O
good	O
Testimony	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
honest	O
Dealings	O
and	O
Reputation	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Buttolphs	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
's	O
Box	O
of	O
Silver	O
Instruments	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Box	O
of	O
Salves	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
Peter	B-pers
Petman	I-pers
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
November	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
taken	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
offered	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Fellony	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joyce	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Chamber	O
pot	O
,	O
Candlestick	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
Attee	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
November	O
:	O
The	O
Proof	O
against	O
her	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
taking	O
a	O
Lodging	O
,	O
after	O
a	O
Nights	O
continuance	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
carried	O
away	O
the	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
in	O
offering	O
them	O
to	O
sale	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Circumstances	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
,	O
only	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Earle	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Leatherby	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
by	O
entring	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
November	O
about	O
7	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
Neck-cloth	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
of	O
value	O
.	O
Upon	O
Evidence	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Closet	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
hid	O
himself	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
upon	O
Examination	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
thrown	O
the	O
Cup	O
out	O
to	O
his	O
Consorts	O
:	O
And	O
it	O
appearing	O
in	O
Court	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
and	O
Fellony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Ray	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dellafountain	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
30	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Brazeil	O
Cabinet	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
in	O
which	O
divers	O
Letters	O
were	O
inclosed	O
.	O
Upon	O
Evidence	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
from	O
an	O
empty	O
House	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Confederates	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
Tops	O
of	O
the	O
adjacent	O
Houses	O
,	O
and	O
entred	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
at	O
a	O
Garrat-Window	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
discovered	O
and	O
pursued	O
they	O
fled	O
by	O
the	O
same	O
way	O
they	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
empty	O
House	O
had	O
broke	O
the	O
Cabinet	O
in	O
pieces	O
,	O
in	O
hopes	O
of	O
a	O
Booty	O
when	O
upon	O
Search	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
a	O
considerable	O
heighth	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Chimneys	O
.	O
He	O
denyed	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
destitute	O
of	O
a	O
Lodging	O
,	O
betook	O
himself	O
to	O
that	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
a	O
suddain	O
Noise	O
,	O
hid	O
himself	O
,	O
as	O
not	O
knowing	O
what	O
it	O
meant	O
:	O
But	O
this	O
being	O
looked	O
upon	O
as	O
frivolous	O
Excuses	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
giving	O
no	O
good	O
Account	O
of	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
and	O
Fellony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
T	B-pers
-	I-pers
H	I-pers
-	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
Yards	O
of	O
Stuff	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Waight	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Strand	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
September	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
coming	O
with	O
some	O
Patterns	O
to	O
the	O
Mercer	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
under	O
Pretence	O
to	O
buy	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Stuff	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
again	O
about	O
2	O
Months	O
after	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
Pretence	O
,	O
a	O
Coat	O
made	O
of	O
the	O
Stuff	O
was	O
found	O
on	O
his	O
Back	O
,	O
whereupon	O
,	O
being	O
Apprehended	O
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
but	O
faintly	O
denying	O
it	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Fellony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
W	B-pers
-	I-pers
D	I-pers
-	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
13	O
Cornet-Wyers	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
from	O
James	B-pers
Welding	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Proof	O
against	O
her	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
off	O
the	O
stall	O
and	O
held	O
them	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
about	O
3	O
Paces	O
from	O
it	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
seized	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
used	O
very	O
roughly	O
:	O
But	O
she	O
pleading	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
buy	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
giving	O
an	O
ample	O
Testimony	O
of	O
her	O
Life	O
and	O
Conversation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonards	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Curtains	O
a	O
Basket	O
,	O
a	O
Bolster	O
,	O
matted	O
Chair	O
,	O
and	O
134	O
Yards	O
of	O
Galloon	O
,	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Chettwood	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
Upon	O
Evidence	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
Andrew	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Beggerman	O
,	O
dying	O
left	O
Chettwood	O
his	O
Executor	O
;	O
but	O
before	O
he	O
could	O
remove	O
the	O
Goods	O
most	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
embasled	O
and	O
purloyned	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
only	O
an	O
empty	O
Basket	O
charged	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Chaplain	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
upon	O
3	O
Indictments	O
for	O
Fellony	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
For	O
stealing	O
a	O
Purse	O
and	O
22	O
s.	O
from	O
Debora	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
,	O
under	O
Presence	O
of	O
buying	O
Apples	O
of	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
September	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
For	O
stealing	O
a	O
Purse	O
and	O
40	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Buckland	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
upon	O
buying	O
some	O
Oysters	O
of	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
Celler	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
For	O
stealing	O
a	O
Purse	O
with	O
6	O
s	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Clasps	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
from	O
Joan	B-pers
Hide	I-pers
,	O
upon	O
his	O
buying	O
Pears	O
and	O
Apples	O
of	O
her	O
:	O
All	O
which	O
being	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
,	O
though	O
young	O
in	O
Years	O
,	O
yet	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
not	O
giving	O
any	O
good	O
Account	O
of	O
himself	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
3	O
several	O
Fellonies	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
but	O
more	O
notoriously	O
known	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
the	O
GOLDEN	O
FARMER	O
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
by	O
fireing	O
a	O
Pistol	O
laden	O
with	O
Bullet	O
,	O
and	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
in	O
the	O
Breast	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
dyed	O
the	O
28th	O
.	O
But	O
before	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
examine	O
the	O
Evidence	O
relating	O
to	O
the	O
Murther	O
charged	O
on	O
him	O
in	O
this	O
Indictment	O
,	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Palmer	O
was	O
examined	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
others	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
nine	O
came	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
October	O
1689	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
at	O
Grays	O
in	O
Essex	O
,	O
and	O
entring	O
forcibly	O
,	O
pretended	O
,	O
with	O
horrid	O
Oaths	O
and	O
Excerations	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
had	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Broad	O
Seal	O
to	O
seize	O
all	O
the	O
Mony	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
having	O
Vizard	O
Marks	O
on	O
and	O
Pistols	O
in	O
their	O
Hands	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
drove	O
her	O
Husband	O
and	O
Servants	O
into	O
the	O
Celler	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
set	O
a	O
Guard	O
over	O
them	O
,	O
threathing	O
Death	O
to	O
those	O
that	O
Stirred	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
forc	O
'd	O
this	O
Deponent	O
,	O
with	O
many	O
Threats	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
and	O
often	O
clapping	O
Pistols	O
to	O
her	O
Breast	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
from	O
Room	O
to	O
Room	O
to	O
shew	O
them	O
where	O
the	O
Plate	O
;	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
Goods	O
of	O
value	O
were	O
;	O
and	O
perceiving	O
a	O
Soldier	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Block-house	O
coming	O
by	O
whilst	O
they	O
were	O
rifling	O
,	O
they	O
fetched	O
him	O
in	O
,	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
drinking	O
with	O
some	O
good	O
Fellows	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Gutter	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
carryed	O
off	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
5	O
or	O
600	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
Plate	O
and	O
Jewels	O
.	O
Then	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
near	O
Ware	O
,	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Hartford	O
,	O
entering	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
others	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
Hours	O
of	O
3	O
and	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
binding	O
or	O
securing	O
all	O
but	O
a	O
Maidservant	O
,	O
whom	O
they	O
made	O
go	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
,	O
to	O
shew	O
them	O
the	O
ways	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
they	O
lifted	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
500	O
and	O
odd	O
Pounds	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
carried	O
off	O
.	O
One	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
his	O
Confederate	O
in	O
several	O
Robberies	O
,	O
accused	O
him	O
of	O
robing	O
the	O
Lady	O
Butler	O
In	O
Essex	O
of	O
140	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
and	O
Plate	O
;	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Read	I-pers
of	O
1000	O
l.	O
in	O
Mony	O
and	O
value	O
;	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Draper	I-pers
of	O
100	O
and	O
odd	O
Pounds	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
chief	O
Accomplices	O
in	O
these	O
and	O
other	O
Robberies	O
were	O
one	O
Marshal	O
,	O
Jenkins	O
,	O
a	O
Barber	O
,	O
a	O
Fellow	O
called	O
Old	O
Mob	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
:	O
And	O
it	O
further	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
discovered	O
by	O
him	O
as	O
a	O
High-way	O
man	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
my	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
's	O
Warrant	O
procured	O
,	O
search	O
was	O
made	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
reason	O
of	O
his	O
often	O
shifting	O
his	O
Lodging	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
concluded	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Evidence	O
's	O
Wife	O
and	O
Sister	O
should	O
dog	O
his	O
Wife	O
;	O
which	O
they	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
by	O
that	O
means	O
discovered	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Salisbury	O
court	O
crying	O
out	O
upon	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
High-wayman	O
,	O
he	O
knock	O
'd	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
down	O
and	O
made	O
off	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
following	O
with	O
the	O
same	O
Cry	O
,	O
Taylor	O
the	O
party	O
killed	O
,	O
being	O
Soldier	O
,	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
apprehend	O
him	O
,	O
received	O
the	O
Wound	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
dyed	O
;	O
and	O
Benet	O
escaped	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
discovered	O
on	O
Southwark	O
side	O
soon	O
after	O
by	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Tucker	O
,	O
he	O
seized	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
after	O
some	O
grapling	O
he	O
got	O
loose	O
again	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Companions	O
coming	O
to	O
his	O
Assistance	O
;	O
however	O
,	O
the	O
Cry	O
being	O
made	O
after	O
him	O
several	O
pursued	O
to	O
apprehend	O
him	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
shot	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Wound	O
he	O
soon	O
after	O
dyed	O
,	O
he	O
wounded	O
another	O
in	O
the	O
Thigh	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
taken	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
by	O
Brick-bats	O
.	O
He	O
made	O
little	O
Defence	O
on	O
his	O
Trial	O
,	O
casting	O
himself	O
at	O
length	O
on	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Wilful	O
Murther	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
Esq	I-pers
;	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Captain	I-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
sir	O
John	O
Johnson	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Clewer	I-pers
professor	O
of	O
Divinity	O
,	O
S	B-pers
-	I-pers
C	I-pers
-	I-pers
and	O
Grace	B-pers
Wiggan	I-pers
,	O
were	O
tryed	O
for	O
Forcibly	O
,	O
Violently	O
and	O
Felloniously	O
Taking	O
Away	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
her	O
Consent	O
,	O
Marrying	O
Mary	B-pers
Wharton	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Virgin	O
under	O
the	O
Age	O
of	O
14	O
Years	O
,	O
to	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Cambel	I-pers
,	O
she	O
being	O
the	O
sole	O
Heiress	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Wharton	I-pers
Esq	O
decesed	O
,	O
and	O
possessed	O
of	O
1500	O
l.	O
per	O
annum	O
Estate	O
;	O
and	O
1000	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
and	O
Effects	O
.	O
Upon	O
Tryal	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
Mrs.	O
Bierly	O
,	O
Gardioness	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Wharton	O
,	O
had	O
carried	O
her	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
her	O
own	O
Daughters	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Archibald	B-pers
Montgomery	I-pers
in	O
Greek-street	O
at	O
Soho	O
,	O
upon	O
his	O
inviting	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
Dinner	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
purposely	O
delayed	O
them	O
to	O
stay	O
Supper	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
they	O
departed	O
not	O
till	O
about	O
9	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
when	O
in	O
Long-acre	O
they	O
saw	O
a	O
Coach	O
with	O
six	O
Horses	O
pass	O
them	O
,	O
as	O
in	O
much	O
haste	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
stand	O
a	O
little	O
off	O
their	O
own	O
Door	O
in	O
Queen	B-place
street	I-place
,	O
where	O
Mrs.	O
Wharton	O
allighting	O
was	O
violently	O
seized	O
and	O
thrust	O
into	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
crying	O
out	O
for	O
Help	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Footman	O
running	O
to	O
take	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
was	O
knocked	O
down	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Daughters	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Bierly	O
thrown	O
in	O
the	O
Channel	O
and	O
much	O
bruised	O
insomuch	O
that	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Word	O
of	O
Command	O
,	O
drove	O
away	O
into	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
towards	O
Tyburn	O
,	O
so	O
swift	O
that	O
those	O
who	O
followed	O
lost	O
the	O
sight	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
10	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
Watson	O
the	O
Coachman	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
Westminster	O
,	O
where	O
Captain	O
Cambel	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
Lodging	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
they	O
found	O
Parson	O
Clewer	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
C	O
-	O
and	O
her	O
Maid	O
,	O
when	O
Mrs.	O
C	O
-	O
accosting	O
her	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
perswading	O
way	O
,	O
bid	O
her	O
not	O
be	O
concerned	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
was	O
sure	O
she	O
would	O
be	O
very	O
happy	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Cambel	O
for	O
a	O
Husband	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
after	O
many	O
Perswasions	O
,	O
the	O
Lady	O
sheding	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Tears	O
,	O
Parson	O
Clewer	O
pulling	O
out	O
his	O
Book	O
read	O
the	O
Offices	O
of	O
Matrimony	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
spoke	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Coachman	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
having	O
before	O
been	O
called	O
up	O
as	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
the	O
Marriage	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Ring-lent	O
by	O
Mrs	O
C	O
-	O
after	O
which	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
Turkey	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Neck	O
of	O
Mutton	O
to	O
supper	O
but	O
the	O
young	O
Lady	O
refused	O
to	O
eat	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
supped	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Montgomerys	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
only	O
drank	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Wine	O
and	O
then	O
her	O
going	O
to	O
bed	O
being	O
proposed	O
,	O
she	O
opposed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
seemed	O
very	O
unwilling	O
,	O
till	O
such	O
Time	O
as	O
Mrs.	O
C	O
-	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
be	O
her	O
Bed	O
fellow	O
but	O
having	O
undressed	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
her	O
in	O
Captain	O
Cambel	O
came	O
to	O
bed	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
rest	O
came	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
Joy	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
they	O
dined	O
at	O
Puntacks	O
a	O
French	O
Ordinary	O
near	O
Charing	O
Cross	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
her	O
to	O
write	O
a	O
Letter	O
to	O
her	O
Aunt	O
to	O
bid	O
her	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
concerned	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
Captain	O
James	B-pers
Cambel	I-pers
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
suddainly	O
intended	O
to	O
wait	O
on	O
her	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
At	O
this	O
Place	O
it	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Master	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
she	O
seemed	O
discontented	O
and	O
from	O
hence	O
they	O
removed	O
her	O
to	O
an	O
Apothecaries	O
in	O
Newgate-street	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
discovered	O
,	O
and	O
restored	O
to	O
her	O
Friends	O
;	O
she	O
utterly	O
denied	O
in	O
Court	O
that	O
she	O
ever	O
gave	O
any	O
Consent	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
she	O
was	O
constrained	O
to	O
by	O
Fear	O
and	O
Surprize	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
ever	O
seen	O
Captain	O
Cambel	O
before	O
.	O
This	O
being	O
the	O
Summ	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
alledged	O
that	O
Captain	O
Cambel	O
had	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
good	O
Will	O
of	O
a	O
young	O
Lady	O
,	O
but	O
her	O
Friends	O
obstructed	O
the	O
Business	O
,	O
and	O
intreated	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
assisting	O
in	O
the	O
carrying	O
her	O
off	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
a	O
Marriage	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
,	O
not	O
being	O
well	O
knowing	O
in	O
the	O
Laws	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
he	O
consented	O
,	O
but	O
denied	O
he	O
used	O
any	O
force	O
himself	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
thrusting	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
as	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
thither	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
discerned	O
not	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
Complacency	O
,	O
especially	O
at	O
Watson	O
the	O
Coachman	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
French	O
Ordinary	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
purpose	O
he	O
call	O
his	O
Evidence	O
;	O
Dr.	O
Clewer	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
pleaded	O
the	O
like	O
Ignorance	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
summing	O
up	O
what	O
had	O
been	O
given	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
alledged	O
on	O
either	O
side	O
,	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
acquitted	O
,	O
Sir	O
John	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
to	O
receive	O
Sentence	O
desired	O
his	O
Indictment	O
might	O
be	O
read	O
in	O
Latin	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
some	O
Exceptions	O
at	O
to	O
matter	O
and	O
form	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
being	O
overruled	O
,	O
he	O
patiently	O
submitted	O
to	O
the	O
Sentence	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
After	O
Judgment	O
was	O
given	O
,	O
the	O
following	O
Persons	O
formerly	O
convicted	O
,	O
pleaded	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
most	O
gracious	O
Pardon	O
on	O
their	O
it	O
knees	O
,	O
Viz	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Mereday	I-pers
a	O
free	O
Pardon	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Lowbridg	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Spencer	I-pers
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Henderson	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Braseby	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Chaulk	I-pers
.	O
conditionally	O
for	O
Transportation	O
.	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
over	O
to	O
Saturday	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
adjourned	O
till	O
Wednesday	O
Morning	O
at	O
what	O
Time	O
being	O
set	O
they	O
proceeded	O
to	O
Judgment	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
9	O
viz	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Meed	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Smith	B-pers
,	I-pers
F.	I-pers
P	I-pers
.	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Chaplain	I-pers
,	O
John	O
Davis	O
.	O
W.	B-pers
W.	I-pers
George	I-pers
Ferraur	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Brett	I-pers
,	O
Anne	B-pers
Batton	I-pers
T.	O
H.	O
Received	O
Sentences	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
22.	O
viz	O
.	O
William	O
Jones	B-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
Trant	I-pers
,	O
Bartholomew	O
Mumford	O
,	O
Francis	O
Yates	O
Richard	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
George	O
Hutton	O
,	O
A.	B-pers
C	I-pers
.	I-pers
John	O
Benner	O
,	O
alias	O
Freeman	O
,	O
Sarah	O
Cane	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Diggs	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mackdonnel	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Healy	I-pers
,	O
Constance	B-pers
Wainright	I-pers
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Ann	O
Herreford	O
Ann	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Raye	I-pers
John	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	O
Harvy	O
,	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Browning	I-pers
:	O
The	O
latter	O
upon	O
a	O
Conviction	O
of	O
a	O
former	O
Sessions	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Samuel	O
Jackson	O
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
York	I-pers
,	O
being	O
found	O
guilty	O
upon	O
a	O
special	O
Verdict	O
was	O
respited	O
to	O
the	O
near	O
Sessions	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
the	O
Determination	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Verdict	O
by	O
the	O
of	O
the	O
Judges	O
.	O
Ordered	O
for	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Person	I-pers
and	O
Francis	B-pers
Luchfield	I-pers
was	O
far	O
aside	O
till	O
the	O
ensuing	O
Sessions	O
.	O
Sentenced	O
to	O
be	O
6	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
William	O
comb	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
,	O
A.S.	B-pers
John	I-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
Joyce	O
Fletcher	O
Henry	B-pers
Abby	I-pers
:	O
These	O
was	O
Committed	O
the	O
walls	O
in	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
from	O
Newgate	O
to	O
Holbourn	O
Bars	O
and	O
those	O
who	O
committed	O
the	O
facts	O
in	O
London	O
,	O
from	O
Newgate	O
to	O
Aldgate	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Warder	O
was	O
fined	O
100	O
l.	O
and	O
in	O
find	O
Seventies	O
for	O
the	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
.	O
Of	O
the	O
Women	O
condemned	O
.	O
A.	O
C.	O
Sarah	O
Cane	O
and	O
Elizabeth	O
Trant	O
pleaded	O
their	O
Beffies	O
,	O
yet	O
only	O
the	O
former	O
was	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
quick	O
with	O
Child	O
.	O
After	O
Judgment	O
was	O
given	O
,	O
the	O
following	O
Persons	O
formerly	O
convicted	O
,	O
pleaded	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
most	O
gracious	O
Pardon	O
on	O
their	O
it	O
knees	O
,	O
Viz	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Mereday	I-pers
a	O
free	O
Pardon	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Lowbridg	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Spencer	I-pers
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Henderson	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Braseby	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Chaulk	I-pers
.	O
conditionally	O
for	O
Transportation	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
The	O
Triennial	O
Mayor	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
New	O
Rappartes	O
:	O
A	O
Poem	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Beastsellers	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
Westminster	O
,	O
Price	O
6	O
d.	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
The	O
History	O
of	O
the	O
flairs	O
of	O
Scotland	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
Restauration	O
of	O
king	O
Chatles	O
2d	O
in	O
the	O
year	O
1660	O
.	O
And	O
of	O
late	O
great	O
Revolution	O
in	O
that	O
kingdom	O
.	O
With	O
particular	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
Extraordinary	O
Occurences	O
which	O
happened	O
thereupon	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Transaction	O
of	O
the	O
convention	O
and	O
Parliament	O
to	O
Midsomer	O
,	O
1690	O
.	O
With	O
a	O
full	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Setling	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
government	O
there	O
.	O
Together	O
with	O
the	O
Act	O
at	O
Largefor	O
the	O
Establishing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
The	O
safety	O
of	O
France	O
to	O
Moslieur	O
the	O
Dauphins	O
Or	O
the	O
secret	O
History	O
of	O
the	O
French	O
king	O
knowing	O
to	O
his	O
son	O
that	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
other	O
es	O
secure	O
France	O
from	O
approaching	O
Ruin	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
Deposing	O
his	O
Father	O
for	O
a	O
Tyrant	O
and	O
Destroyer	O
of	O
his	O
People	O
.	O
Done	O
into	O
English	O
from	O
the	O
Second	O
Edition	O
of	O
the	O
French	O
Original	O
,	O
printed	O
in	O
Holland	O
.	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
The	O
Braeadocio	O
:	O
or	O
the	O
Baud	O
turn	O
'd	O
Puritan	O
:	O
A	O
new	O
Comedy	O
By	O
a	O
person	O
of	O
Quality	O
.	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
A	O
Collection	O
of	O
many	O
Wonderful	O
Prophesies	O
relating	O
to	O
the	O
English	O
Nation	O
,	O
and	O
happy	O
settlement	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
.	O
His	O
Present	O
Majestice	O
sheerfles	O
in	O
Irleand	O
and	O
particularly	O
his	O
Victory	O
at	O
the	O
Boyne	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Action	O
at	O
Senberwixt	O
both	O
Fleets	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
very	O
Remarkable	O
Things	O
not	O
yet	O
to	O
pass	O
.	O
Written	O
in	O
the	O
Years	O
1623	O
,	O
1628	O
&	O
c.	O
And	O
some	O
never	O
Published	O
before	O
.	O
4	O
last	O
sold	O
by	O
the	O
Salusbary	O
at	O
the	O
Sian	O
of	O
the	O
Temple	O
,	O
near	O
Temple	O
Bar	O
in	O
Fleet	O
street	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
The	O
Young	B-pers
Man	I-pers
's	O
Claim	O
into	O
the	O
Bely	O
sacrament	O
of	O
the	O
Lord	O
's	O
supper	O
,	O
carred	O
by	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
Church	O
of	O
Christ	O
received	O
and	O
accepted	O
by	O
the	O
Pastor	O
and	O
its	O
other	O
Officers	O
.	O
By	O
John	B-pers
Quick	I-pers
,	O
minister	O
of	O
the	O
Gofrel	O
.	O
Price	O
6	O
d.	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
The	O
Anti	O
weesels	O
;	O
a	O
Poem	O
.	O
Price	O
6	O
d.	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
The	O
Wonder	O
of	O
Free	O
Grace	O
:	O
or	O
a	O
compleat	O
History	O
of	O
at	O
the	O
Remarkable	O
Penitents	O
that	O
have	O
been	O
executed	O
at	O
Tyburn	O
and	O
elsewhere	O
for	O
these	O
last	O
thirty	O
years	O
.	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
The	O
third	O
Volume	O
of	O
the	O
Pocket	O
Library	O
(	O
compleatine	O
the	O
two	O
former	O
)	O
containing	O
a	O
further	O
account	O
so	O
the	O
Juvecel	O
Rembles	O
of	O
Dan	B-pers
Kainophtlos	I-pers
,	O
with	O
his	O
first	O
Project	O
of	O
girding	O
the	O
Worla	O
.	O
The	O
whole	O
Work	O
interwixt	O
Essays	O
Historical	O
,	O
Moral	O
and	O
Divine	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
kinds	O
of	O
Learning	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
A	O
Treatise	O
of	O
Formcation	O
;	O
occasioned	O
by	O
the	O
late	O
Earth	O
of	O
several	O
illegitimates	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
-	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
A	O
Penitentiary	O
Sermon	O
preached	O
before	O
the	O
Guilty	O
Person	O
in	O
the	O
publish	O
Congregation	O
upon	O
John	O
8	O
11	O
.	O
Go	O
and	O
sin	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
These	O
four	O
last	O
sold	O
at	O
the	O
Riven	O
in	O
the	O
Poultry	O
.	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
These	O
are	O
10	O
give	O
Notice	O
to	O
all	O
Persons	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
the	O
Publick	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Elmy	O
,	O
Professor	O
of	O
Physick	O
,	O
and	O
Operator	O
,	O
of	O
known	O
Integrity	O
,	O
and	O
above	O
25	O
Years	O
practice	O
,	O
Liveth	O
at	O
the	O
Blue	O
Ball	O
in	O
WhaleBone	O
Court	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Lower	O
End	O
of	O
Bartholomew-lane	O
by	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
who	O
most	O
safely	O
and	O
expeditiously	O
Cures	O
Dearness	O
and	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
Ears	O
in	O
any	O
of	O
what	O
Age	O
soever	O
,	O
(	O
if	O
Cutable	O
)	O
and	O
at	O
first	O
Sight	O
,	O
by	O
Inspection	O
,	O
Resolves	O
the	O
Patient	O
if	O
so	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
as	O
most	O
Eminent	O
Persons	O
of	O
Quality	O
in	O
this	O
City	O
can	O
Testifie	O
.	O
He	O
bath	O
likewise	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Gargarison	O
or	O
MouthWater	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
make	O
black	O
or	O
yellow	O
as	O
white	O
as	O
Ivory	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
few	O
times	O
using	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
will	O
certainly	O
cure	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
Diseases	O
incident	O
to	O
the	O
Month	O
,	O
Teeth	O
and	O
Gums	O
which	O
in	O
many	O
persons	O
caufeth	O
a	O
stinking	O
,	O
Breath	O
,	O
which	O
(	O
by	O
the	O
Blessing	O
of	O
God	O
and	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
this	O
Water	O
)	O
I	O
dare	O
affirm	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
freed	O
from	O
those	O
Maladies	O
beforementioned	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
.	O
His	O
Pills	O
only	O
prepared	O
for	O
the	O
French	O
Disease	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Running	O
of	O
the	O
Reins	O
,	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
in	O
Boxes	O
of	O
several	O
prices	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
Venereal	O
Arcana	O
's	O
,	O
as	O
occasion	O
serves	O
.	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
In	O
Plow-Yard	O
in	O
Grays-Inn-Lane	O
,	O
lives	O
Dr.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kirleus	I-pers
a	O
Collegiate	O
Physician	O
,	O
and	O
Sworn	B-pers
Physician	I-pers
to	O
Charles	B-pers
II	I-pers
until	O
his	O
Death	O
:	O
Who	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Drink	O
and	O
Pill	O
,	O
hindering	O
no	O
Business	O
Cures	O
all	O
Vicers	O
,	O
Scabs	O
,	O
Scarfs	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
or	O
elsewhere	O
;	O
Kings-Evil	O
,	O
Leprofie	O
and	O
Venereal	O
Disease	O
,	O
expecting	O
nothing	O
of	O
he	O
Cures	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
,	O
he	O
both	O
carried	O
above	O
500	O
persons	O
in	O
that	O
City	O
,	O
many	O
after	O
Fluxing	O
.	O
It	O
quickly	O
and	O
safely	O
Cures	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
beginning	O
,	O
which	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
done	O
with	O
Mercury	O
,	O
without	O
danger	O
of	O
Life	O
.	O
The	O
Drink	O
is	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Quars	O
,	O
the	O
she	O
Pill	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
which	O
it	O
two	O
Purges	O
.	O
They	O
excel	O
all	O
Purges	O
,	O
in	O
cleansing	O
all	O
Cruduzes	O
and	O
Impurities	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
prevent	O
and	O
Cure	O
many	O
Diseases	O
,	O
and	O
especially	O
the	O
Gent	O
and	O
stone	O
.	O
In	O
all	O
Diseases	O
he	O
gives	O
his	O
Opinion	O
for	O
nothing	O
.	O
