TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
and	O
Queens	O
Commissions	O
OF	O
THE	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILY	O
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
being	O
the	O
17th	O
,	O
and	O
18th	O
Days	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
1690	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
Second	O
Year	O
of	O
Their	O
MAJESTIES	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
on	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
being	O
the	O
17th	O
,	O
and	O
18th	O
Days	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
1690	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pilkington	I-pers
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Country	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
follow	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Acton	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Speed	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Parrott	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Bromfield	I-pers
Zachary	B-pers
Burrow	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Pyke	I-pers
Peter	B-pers
Hynks	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Maning	I-pers
William	B-pers
Raymont	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Cowes	I-pers
John	B-pers
Northcott	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
Ralph	B-pers
Hutchinson	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Kempion	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Churchill	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Pattle	I-pers
John	B-pers
Howlet	I-pers
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Mynn	I-pers
Bennet	B-pers
Giles	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Hollins	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Awbrey	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
these	O
:	O
Mary	B-pers
Cary	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Painter	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstone	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
2	O
long	O
Black	O
Scarfs	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
2	O
Black	O
Hoods	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Coronet	O
5	O
s.	O
2	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
20	O
s.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Painter	O
to	O
be	O
Hired	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
2	O
hours	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
Entertained	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Painter	O
she	O
stole	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
:	O
and	O
altho	O
'	O
she	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
yet	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
by	O
several	O
Names	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Matter	O
being	O
plain	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Griffeth	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Anthony	B-pers
Chewin	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
Day	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Stays	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
two	O
Petty	O
Coats	O
6	O
l.	O
a	O
Shirt	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
lac	O
'd	O
Smock	O
10	O
s.	O
&	O
c.	O
It	O
happened	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Fire	O
was	O
in	O
Red-Lion	O
street	O
,	O
not	O
long	O
ago	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
a	O
Bible	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
carry	O
several	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Bible	O
and	O
a	O
Trunk	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
thus	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
midst	O
of	O
the	O
Acclamation	O
of	O
Fire	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
called	O
several	O
Evidence	O
who	O
gave	O
a	O
Credible	O
Account	O
of	O
her	O
former	O
behaviour	O
,	O
so	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Adam	B-pers
Voke	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Anne	B-pers
Voke	I-pers
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
and	O
Tryed	O
,	O
for	O
being	O
Accessary	O
to	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
Millicent	B-pers
Blakey	I-pers
:	O
Committed	O
by	O
one	O
George	B-pers
Tavernor	I-pers
since	O
fled	O
.	O
The	O
said	O
Tavernor	O
giving	O
her	O
the	O
said	O
Millicent	B-pers
Blakey	I-pers
,	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
,	O
(	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
day	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
)	O
on	O
the	O
Right	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Belly	O
near	O
the	O
Groine	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
6	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
dyed	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Numerous	O
,	O
who	O
declared	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
George	B-pers
Tavernor	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
2	O
Prisoners	O
had	O
a	O
quarrel	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
the	O
Deceased	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Women	O
,	O
were	O
in	O
Compton-street	B-place
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
designe	O
of	O
the	O
Murther	O
was	O
upon	O
one	O
Stannup	O
,	O
another	O
Woman	O
in	O
the	O
Company	O
:	O
and	O
that	O
Millicent	O
Blakey	O
came	O
there	O
unluckely	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
receiv	O
'd	O
the	O
Wound	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
Intended	O
against	O
Stannup	O
;	O
as	O
the	O
Evidence	O
made	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Anne	B-pers
Voke	I-pers
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
Abbetted	O
the	O
said	O
George	B-pers
Tavernor	I-pers
(	O
he	O
being	O
her	O
Son	O
)	O
who	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
and	O
meeting	O
first	O
with	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
he	O
Cryed	O
out	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Dam	O
you	O
Bitch	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
her	O
that	O
abused	O
my	O
Mother	O
:	O
and	O
presently	O
he	O
thrust	O
the	O
Sword	O
into	O
her	O
Belly	O
;	O
The	O
quarrel	O
at	O
first	O
arose	O
about	O
10	O
s.	O
that	O
Taverner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
to	O
demand	O
of	O
one	O
Ellison	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
much	O
that	O
Affected	O
Adam	O
,	O
only	O
one	O
Evidence	O
Swore	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
the	O
said	O
Tavernor	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Mother	O
was	O
like	O
to	O
be	O
Killed	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
ran	O
to	O
help	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
Committed	O
the	O
Horrid	O
Murther	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
Adam	B-pers
Voke	I-pers
said	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
all	O
he	O
could	O
to	O
keep	O
the	O
Peace	O
.	O
Anne	O
said	O
that	O
She	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
Son	O
that	O
Night	O
the	O
Murther	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
as	O
very	O
Suspicious	O
People	O
and	O
bad	O
livers	O
.	O
Yet	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
somewhat	O
doubtful	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
several	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
were	O
pleased	O
to	O
find	O
them	O
both	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
yards	O
of	O
Bays-Cloth	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
July	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
Robert	B-pers
French	I-pers
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
stopt	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Cloth	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
French	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
Idle	O
Fellow	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
;	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
a	O
Petty-Lacenary	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
Wife	O
of	O
Blanke	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Margarets	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
9	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Shrewsbury	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
Day	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
confess	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Impudence	O
to	O
deny	O
it	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
,	O
yet	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
Rat-catcher	O
,	O
and	O
Susannah	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
were	O
both	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Dr.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gill	I-pers
of	O
Edmonton	B-place
,	O
onthe	O
23d	O
Day	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
4	O
Coach-glasses	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
3	O
Pullets	O
18	O
d.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
Swore	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
to	O
Enquire	O
if	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
troubled	O
with	O
any	O
Rats	O
or	O
Mice	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
Answered	O
in	O
the	O
Negative	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
on	O
the	O
Morrow	O
the	O
Coach-house	O
was	O
found	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Glasses	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
denyed	O
it	O
stifly	O
,	O
and	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
another	O
place	O
when	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
some	O
Evidence	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
prevailed	O
nothing	O
to	O
their	O
advantage	O
,	O
so	O
William	O
Wilson	O
the	O
Ratcatcher	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
Wife	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Drugget-gown	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Pettycoat	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Red	O
Serge	O
Pettycoat	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
Yard	O
of	O
Bone	O
lace	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
Colf	O
3	O
s.	O
three	O
Holland-handkerchiefs	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Sharing	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
July	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
Swore	O
it	O
plain	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
denyed	O
it	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
common	O
Newgate	O
Asseveration	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
as	O
Innocent	O
as	O
the	O
Child	O
unborn	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Kirbey	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Thieves	O
that	O
Robbed	O
Mr.	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bone	I-place
,	O
but	O
was	O
not	O
taken	O
till	O
of	O
late	O
,	O
being	O
amongst	O
the	O
Gang	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
Executed	O
for	O
it	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Sessions	O
ago	O
,	O
was	O
now	O
Tryed	O
for	O
the	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
stealing	O
away	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
two	O
Silver	O
Tankards	O
value	O
12	O
l.	O
two	O
Silver	O
Candlesticks	O
and	O
Salvers	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Plate	O
,	O
besides	O
Money	O
and	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
Watches	O
,	O
and	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
about	O
400	O
l.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
very	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
discovered	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Eleven	O
that	O
Encompassed	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
help	O
to	O
bind	O
the	O
Family	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
it	O
all	O
.	O
But	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Christopher	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Rothery	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Gang	O
that	O
Robbed	O
Mr.	O
Baker	O
of	O
St.	O
Mary	O
le	O
Bone	O
,	O
(	O
but	O
since	O
converted	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
)	O
was	O
now	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
Seven	O
Sheep	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
which	O
he	O
offered	O
to	O
Sale	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
.	O
All	O
which	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
deny	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
immediately	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Deane	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
27	O
Yards	O
of	O
Norwich	O
Stuff	O
value	O
24	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gascoigne	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
Swore	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
cheapen	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
away	O
the	O
piece	O
.	O
All	O
which	O
she	O
denyed	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
one	O
Catherine	B-pers
Knot	I-pers
,	O
and	O
one	O
Chapman	O
,	O
and	O
Rose	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
to	O
vindicate	O
her	O
Reputation	O
;	O
but	O
all	O
did	O
her	O
no	O
Credit	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Goodman	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
,	O
in	O
stealing	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Edward	B-pers
Cork	I-pers
140	O
Yards	O
of	O
Buckram-Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
Swore	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Cork	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
offered	O
them	O
to	O
Sale	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Robbery	O
being	O
committed	O
before	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
within	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
their	O
Majesties	O
most	O
Gracious	O
and	O
Free	O
Pardon	O
,	O
whereupon	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
T	B-pers
-	I-pers
W	I-pers
-	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
Day	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Porringer	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
one	O
Silver	O
Salt-sellar	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
one	O
Roger	B-pers
Pope	I-pers
Gentleman	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
very	O
Circumstantial	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
said	O
Mrs.	O
Pope	O
were	O
always	O
Friends	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
intimate	O
Acquaintance	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
the	O
Evidence	O
could	O
not	O
charge	O
her	O
positively	O
.	O
She	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
brought	O
home	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
offering	O
to	O
call	O
several	O
Persons	O
of	O
good	O
Quality	O
to	O
Vindicate	O
her	O
Reputation	O
;	O
which	O
the	O
Court	O
did	O
not	O
Order	O
,	O
being	O
very	O
well	O
satisfied	O
with	O
her	O
before	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
always	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
an	O
Unblameable	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
Conversation	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
particular	O
defect	O
in	O
so	O
horrid	O
a	O
Crime	O
as	O
Thievery	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
immediately	O
Acquitted	O
by	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Meeres	I-pers
;	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Cock	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Snow	I-pers
Gentleman	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Pitch-Fork	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
upon	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
two	O
Inches	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
Died	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Month	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
Snow	O
was	O
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Field	O
amongst	O
Hay	O
Makers	O
,	O
and	O
Quarrelled	O
about	O
a	O
Gown	O
that	O
was	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
made	O
an	O
Assault	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Pitch-Fork	O
;	O
all	O
which	O
was	O
plainly	O
Evidenced	O
.	O
And	O
Meeres	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
no	O
Affront	O
to	O
Snow	O
,	O
neither	O
did	O
he	O
know	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
some	O
Evidence	O
on	O
his	O
side	O
;	O
so	O
likewise	O
did	O
Cock	O
;	O
so	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Tanner	I-pers
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Carter	B-pers
,	O
on	O
Midsummer	O
Day	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
him	O
two	O
Yards	O
of	O
Tape-Lace	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Pinner	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Looking	O
Glass	O
12	O
d.	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
found	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
the	O
Lace	O
hanging	O
in	O
a	O
Broker	O
's	O
Shop	O
Window	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
further	O
Evidenced	O
against	O
Foster	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Linnen	O
and	O
a	O
Silver-salt	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Breeches	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
charged	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
Tanner	O
was	O
found	O
to	O
offer	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
Sale	O
at	O
a	O
Brokers	O
;	O
the	O
Woman	O
charged	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Man	O
the	O
Woman	O
;	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
end	O
,	O
the	O
Woman	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
but	O
Foster	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
(	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Hodges	I-pers
,	O
)	O
Eleven	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Bason	O
12	O
d.	O
some	O
Plates	O
;	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Pewter	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
good	O
value	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Pewter	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Pick-locks	O
were	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Pewter	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Pick	O
lock	O
Key	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
a	O
many	O
vain	O
Stories	O
to	O
Extenuate	O
the	O
Crime	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
peremptory	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Idle	O
Fellow	O
;	O
so	O
in	O
the	O
conclusion	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
both	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Humphreys	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
Henry	B-pers
Beresford	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
Left	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
near	O
to	O
the	O
Left	O
Pap	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
four	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
Died	O
on	O
the	O
third	O
Instant	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
arose	O
between	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
he	O
giving	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
Lie	O
;	O
which	O
gave	O
occasion	O
for	O
a	O
Battle	O
which	O
was	O
Fought	O
between	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Field	O
by	O
Gray	B-place
's	I-place
Inn	I-place
,	O
in	O
which	O
Battle	O
Mr.	O
Beresford	O
received	O
the	O
Wound	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
Fight	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
gave	O
the	O
first	O
provocation	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
only	O
stood	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Defence	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
So	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Read	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Mare	O
,	O
Coloured	O
Brown	O
,	O
Price	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Fann	I-pers
of	O
Hornesey	B-place
:	O
They	O
were	O
likewise	O
a	O
Second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
breaking	O
theHouse	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Fann	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
a	O
Bridle	O
and	O
Sadle	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pannel	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Girth	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
proof	O
was	O
plain	O
against	O
them	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Mare	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
their	O
custody	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
also	O
plainly	O
arrested	O
,	O
yet	O
they	O
denyed	O
it	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
shifted	O
the	O
matter	O
from	O
one	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
:	O
So	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
Mare	O
,	O
but	O
were	O
acquited	O
of	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
yet	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
for	O
the	O
Sadle	O
and	O
Bridle	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Rebeckah	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Tomson	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Couple	O
of	O
young	O
Girl	O
s	O
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
day	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
50	O
Yards	O
of	O
Silk	O
Stuff	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Chamberlain	I-pers
:	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
one	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Burzey	I-pers
was	O
the	O
Receiver	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
gone	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
sell	O
the	O
Stuff	O
for	O
30	O
s.	O
to	O
one	O
Margaret	B-pers
Woodborne	I-pers
,	O
as	O
their	O
Confessions	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
did	O
testifie	O
,	O
they	O
both	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
however	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
Nine	O
Shillings	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Andrew	B-pers
Ellingburgh	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Martin	B-pers
Tashter	I-pers
,	O
all	O
Foreigners	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
Felony	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
arraignment	O
Tashter	O
Pleaded	O
Guilty	O
:	O
after	O
which	O
Ellingburgh	O
stood	O
mute	O
for	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Court	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
little	O
Respite	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Press	O
and	O
there	O
Threatned	O
to	O
be	O
put	O
to	O
Death	O
,	O
he	O
afterwards	O
Relented	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
Pardon	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
and	O
Bird	O
were	O
tryed	O
upon	O
the	O
Indictment	O
for	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Mony	O
Charged	O
against	O
them	O
was	O
2	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
Value	O
20	O
s.	O
two	O
other	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Coined	O
Gold	O
.	O
22	O
Guines	O
,	O
five	O
pieces	O
of	O
Louis-de	O
ors	O
,	O
value	O
17	O
shillings	O
and	O
six	O
pence	O
,	O
one	O
Linnen	O
bag	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
60	O
l.	O
in	O
Mony	O
Numbered	O
,	O
the	O
Mony	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Bartholomew	I-place
Exchange	I-place
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
plain	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Phillip	B-pers
Oneal	I-pers
in	O
their	O
Company	O
who	O
is	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
Broak	O
open	O
the	O
Locks	O
and	O
Doors	O
to	O
get	O
to	O
the	O
Gold	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
denyed	O
the	O
matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
Gold	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
them	O
was	O
their	O
own	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
had	O
no	O
Evidence	O
on	O
their	O
side	O
:	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
proof	O
against	O
Bird	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Actually	O
at	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
Committed	O
the	O
Robbery	O
:	O
So	O
Ellingburgh	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
but	O
Bird	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Addison	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Counterfeiting	O
a	O
Note	O
to	O
Receive	O
Twenty	O
Shillings	O
of	O
the	O
Commissioners	O
,	O
who	O
are	O
Intrusted	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
the	O
Charity	O
Money	O
to	O
the	O
poor	O
Protestants	O
that	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
Ireland	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Trespass	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Bew	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Beckworth	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Hayes	I-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
Southam	I-place
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
John	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
upon	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
High	O
Way	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Ninth	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
,	O
the	O
Esquire	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
others	O
,	O
who	O
Swore	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
met	O
his	O
Coach	O
upon	O
the	O
High-Way	O
,	O
and	O
caused	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
drawn	O
into	O
a	O
little	O
Lane	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
Rifled	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
taking	O
away	O
a	O
Silver-Hilted-Sword	O
Value	O
Three	O
Pound	O
,	O
Two	O
Pistols	O
Value	O
Thirty	O
Five	O
Shillings	O
,	O
a	O
Coat	O
Value	O
Three	O
Pound	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Breeches	O
Value	O
Forty	O
Shillings	O
,	O
One	O
Embroidered	O
Wast-Coat	O
Value	O
Forty	O
Shillings	O
,	O
Two	O
Holland-Shirts	O
Value	O
Forty	O
Shillings	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Mantua-Gown	O
Value	O
Ten	O
Pound	O
,	O
a	O
Flanders	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Petty-Coat	O
Value	O
Seven	O
Pound	O
,	O
and	O
Five	O
Pound	O
in	O
Money	O
Numbered	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
10	O
Prove	O
this	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
side	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
Three	O
Witnesses	O
swore	O
positively	O
against	O
Bew	O
,	O
and	O
Two	O
others	O
against	O
Becket	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
denyed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
another	O
place	O
when	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
Prove	O
it	O
;	O
Bew	O
being	O
an	O
Old	O
Offender	O
,	O
and	O
Tryed	O
before	O
for	O
great	O
Crimes	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elias	B-pers
Fryar	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Fryar	I-pers
his	O
Son	O
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Gelding	O
,	O
Strawberry	O
Colour	O
,	O
Fifteen	O
Shillings	O
Price	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Eleventh	O
Day	O
of	O
June	O
from	O
Anthony	B-pers
Morton	I-pers
of	O
Harrow	B-place
on	I-place
the	I-place
Hill	I-place
;	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
upon	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
Old	O
Fryar	O
Hired	O
the	O
Horse	O
of	O
Morton	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Colour	O
of	O
Felony	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Woakden	I-pers
,	O
Was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Killing	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Tisdale	I-pers
,	O
his	O
fellow	O
Soldier	O
on	O
the	O
Twenty	O
Fourth	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
by	O
Shooting	O
off	O
his	O
Musquet	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
done	O
through	O
Mischance	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Malice	O
being	O
Premiditated	O
:	O
They	O
having	O
always	O
been	O
Loving	O
Friends	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
acquited	O
and	O
immediately	O
discharged	O
from	O
Newgate	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Leitchfeild	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Daniel	B-pers
Delawny	I-pers
,	O
and	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Goodman	I-pers
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
:	O
Did	O
Steal	O
a	O
Gelding	O
Value	O
Four	O
Pound	O
,	O
a	O
Mare	O
Value	O
Ten	O
Pound	O
,	O
a	O
Saddle	O
Value	O
Forty	O
Shillings	O
,	O
a	O
Bridle	O
Value	O
Twelve	O
Pence	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
he	O
was	O
Acquited	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Everson	I-pers
,	O
Was	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Pettycoat	O
Valued	O
Twenty	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
from	O
one	O
Elinor	B-pers
Lemon	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Sixth	O
of	O
May	O
Last	O
:	O
She	O
did	O
partake	O
of	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
Most	O
Gracious	O
Pardon	O
.	O
The	O
Felony	O
being	O
Committed	O
before	O
the	O
Date	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Sentence	O
as	O
followeth	O
,	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
Four	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Meeres	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Cock	I-pers
.	O
Rebekah	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
Two	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Rothery	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
the	O
Discoverer	O
that	O
Robbed	O
Mr.	O
Baker	O
of	O
St.	O
Mary	O
le	O
Bone	O
.	O
And	O
William	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
Three	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Deane	I-pers
.	O
David	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
And	O
John	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
Eleven	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Cary	I-pers
.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Ellingburgh	I-pers
.	O
Martin	B-pers
Tashter	I-pers
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
James	B-pers
Kerby	I-pers
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Read	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Bew	I-pers
.	O
And	O
Charles	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Beckworth	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Cary	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
Respited	O
after	O
Judgement	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
BALDWIN	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
Committed	O
by	O
the	O
Secretary	O
of	O
State	O
,	O
for	O
Misprision	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
was	O
Ordered	O
to	O
Remain	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Humphreys	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
for	O
Killing	O
Esq	O
;	O
Beresford	O
,	O
was	O
discharged	O
without	O
undergoing	O
the	O
Penalty	O
of	O
a	O
Brand	O
,	O
by	O
Vertue	O
of	O
an	O
Order	O
from	O
the	O
Queens	O
Majesty	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
Giving	O
in	O
Bail	O
to	O
Appear	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
John	O
Addison	O
,	O
for	O
Counterfeiting	O
a	O
Note	O
to	O
Receive	O
Twenty	O
Shillings	O
of	O
the	O
Commissioners	O
appointed	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
the	O
Charity	O
Money	O
given	O
for	O
the	O
Relief	O
of	O
the	O
poor	O
Protestants	O
that	O
were	O
driven	O
out	O
of	O
Ireland	O
,	O
was	O
discharged	O
without	O
paying	O
any	O
Fine	O
,	O
or	O
Fees	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
very	O
Poor	O
,	O
Sick	O
and	O
Lame	O
,	O
Creature	O
,	O
almost	O
in	O
comparison	O
like	O
unto	O
a	O
Skeleton	O
.	O
One	O
William	O
Frowd	O
was	O
called	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
Accused	O
for	O
Speaking	O
Treasonable	O
Words	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
for	O
saying	O
,	O
That	O
King	O
James	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Ireland	O
with	O
Forty	O
Thousand	O
French	O
Men	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
here	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
should	O
have	O
a	O
Brush	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
then	O
who	O
and	O
who	O
was	O
together	O
,	O
or	O
Words	O
to	O
that	O
effect	O
,	O
was	O
Ordered	O
to	O
Remain	O
.	O
Oliver	B-pers
Platt	I-pers
,	O
was	O
accused	O
likewise	O
for	O
saying	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
would	O
Assist	O
King	O
James	O
in	O
his	O
Return	O
into	O
England	O
again	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
last	O
drop	O
of	O
his	O
Blood	O
:	O
Was	O
Ordered	O
to	O
Remain	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Larkin	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Printer	O
,	O
who	O
formerly	O
lived	O
at	O
the	O
Swan	O
and	O
Two	O
Necks	O
without	O
Bishops-gate	O
,	O
but	O
since	O
removed	O
to	O
Charing-Cross	O
,	O
was	O
Accused	O
for	O
Printing	O
a	O
Book	O
Entituled	O
,	O
A	O
Letter	O
to	O
the	O
Lord	O
Bishop	O
of	O
Sarum	O
,	O
in	O
Answer	O
to	O
his	O
Lordships	O
Pastoral	O
Letter	O
;	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
Ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Remanded	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
without	O
a	O
very	O
severe	O
and	O
sharp	O
Repremand	O
from	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
would	O
Inspect	O
very	O
narrowly	O
into	O
such	O
a	O
Crime	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
must	O
not	O
think	O
to	O
put	O
Tricks	O
upon	O
the	O
Government	O
;	O
or	O
to	O
that	O
effect	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
was	O
called	O
up	O
,	O
for	O
suspition	O
of	O
dispersing	O
of	O
Letters	O
that	O
came	O
from	O
King	O
James	O
in	O
Ireland	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
giving	O
him	O
Intelligence	O
of	O
Affairs	O
here	O
in	O
England	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Prosecution	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
Advertisements	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
now	O
Published	O
,	O
The	O
Policks	O
of	O
Europe	O
,	O
or	O
,	O
A	O
Rational	O
Journal	O
concerning	O
the	O
present	O
Affairs	O
;	O
and	O
will	O
for	O
the	O
satisfaction	O
of	O
the	O
Curious	O
,	O
and	O
Ingenious	O
,	O
be	O
continued	O
every	O
Month	O
;	O
and	O
to	O
contain	O
an	O
exact	O
Account	O
of	O
all	O
that	O
passes	O
in	O
Christendom	O
,	O
with	O
Political	O
Reflections	O
upon	O
all	O
Material	O
Events	O
:	O
The	O
First	O
Journal	O
now	O
Published	O
,	O
being	O
Introductory	O
to	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
gives	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
present	O
State	O
of	O
Europe	O
,	O
with	O
regard	O
to	O
its	O
Two	O
most	O
Active	O
Powers	O
,	O
William	O
the	O
Third	O
,	O
and	O
Lewis	O
the	O
Fourteenth	O
.	O
Sold	O
by	O
Langley	O
Curtiss	O
.	O
Iris	O
6	O
d.	O
These	O
are	O
to	O
give	O
Notice	O
,	O
That	O
if	O
any	O
person	O
have	O
occasion	O
to	O
sell	O
any	O
Library	O
,	O
or	O
parcel	O
of	O
Books	O
,	O
either	O
in	O
large	O
or	O
small	O
Quantities	O
,	O
they	O
may	O
receive	O
ready	O
Money	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
upon	O
View	O
thereof	O
,	O
by	O
Langley	O
Curtiss	O
at	O
Sir	O
Edmondbury	O
Godfrey	O
's	O
Head	O
near	O
Fleet-bridge	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
Publish	O
'd	O
a	O
New	O
Play	O
,	O
Entituled	O
,	O
The	O
Royal	O
Voyage	O
,	O
or	O
,	O
The	O
Irish	O
Expedition	O
,	O
a	O
Trags-Comedy	O
,	O
Acted	O
in	O
the	O
Years	O
1689	O
,	O
and	O
90	O
.	O
Sold	O
by	O
most	O
Book-sellers	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
to	O
give	O
Notice	O
to	O
all	O
Persons	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
the	O
Publick	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Elmy	O
,	O
Professor	O
of	O
Physick	O
,	O
and	O
Operator	O
,	O
of	O
known	O
Integrity	O
,	O
and	O
above	O
25	O
Years	O
practice	O
,	O
Liveth	O
at	O
the	O
Blue	O
Ball	O
in	O
Whale-Bone	O
Court	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Lower	O
End	O
of	O
Bartholomew	O
lane	O
by	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
who	O
most	O
safely	O
and	O
expeditiously	O
Cures	O
Deafness	O
and	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
Ears	O
in	O
any	O
of	O
what	O
Age	O
soever	O
,	O
(	O
if	O
Curable	O
)	O
and	O
at	O
first	O
Sight	O
,	O
by	O
Inspection	O
,	O
Resolves	O
the	O
Patient	O
if	O
so	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
as	O
most	O
Eminent	O
Persons	O
of	O
Quality	O
in	O
this	O
City	O
can	O
Testifie	O
.	O
He	O
hath	O
likewise	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Gargarism	O
or	O
Mouth-Water	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
make	O
black	O
or	O
yellow	O
Teeth	O
as	O
white	O
as	O
Ivory	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
times	O
using	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
will	O
certainly	O
cure	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
Diseases	O
incident	O
to	O
the	O
Mouth	O
,	O
Teeth	O
and	O
Gums	O
which	O
in	O
many	O
persons	O
causeth	O
a	O
stinking	O
Breath	O
,	O
which	O
(	O
by	O
the	O
Blessing	O
of	O
God	O
and	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
this	O
Water	O
)	O
I	O
dare	O
affirm	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
freed	O
from	O
those	O
Maladies	O
beforementioned	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
.	O
His	O
Pitls	O
only	O
prepared	O
for	O
the	O
French	O
Disease	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Running	O
of	O
the	O
Reins	O
,	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
in	O
Boxes	O
of	O
several	O
prices	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
Venereal	O
Arcana	O
's	O
,	O
as	O
occasion	O
serves	O
.	O
