TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
and	O
Queens	O
Commissions	O
OF	O
THE	O
Peace	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILY	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
26th	O
,	O
27th	O
,	O
and	O
28th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
1690	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
Second	O
Year	O
of	O
Their	O
MAJESTIES	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
26th	O
,	O
27th	O
,	O
and	O
28th	O
days	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
1690	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pilkington	I-pers
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
follows	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Bland	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Greene	I-pers
William	B-pers
Crouch	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Stanton	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Safferton	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Tayjer	I-pers
Zachariah	B-pers
Heywood	I-pers
John	B-pers
Pettit	I-pers
George	B-pers
Westray	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
Timothy	B-pers
Tyrrell	I-pers
John	B-pers
Fedding	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Bealing	I-pers
Abel	B-pers
Weeks	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
James	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
John	B-pers
Bayley	I-pers
William	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
Michael	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
John	B-pers
Haynes	I-pers
John	B-pers
Partridge	I-pers
John	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Hollin	I-pers
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
these	O
:	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Deacon	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Deacon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
Woodstreet	I-place
Whipmaker	O
,	O
was	O
arraigned	O
and	O
tried	O
for	O
the	O
murther	O
of	O
her	O
Servant	O
maid	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
aged	O
about	O
17	O
years	O
.	O
The	O
Tryal	O
lasted	O
very	O
long	O
,	O
and	O
abundance	O
of	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
called	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
amongst	O
which	O
were	O
two	O
Apprentices	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Newhall	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Albrook	I-pers
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
former	O
of	O
which	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
,	O
on	O
Monday	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
his	O
Mistris	O
found	O
the	O
Maid	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
Shilling	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
?	O
The	O
Maid	O
confest	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
one	O
6d	O
.	O
of	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Baker	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
of	O
one	O
Susannah	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
;	O
which	O
her	O
Mistriss	O
being	O
doubtful	O
of	O
,	O
she	O
ty	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Beds-post	O
,	O
and	O
whipt	O
her	O
very	O
sorely	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
following	O
she	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
,	O
her	O
Mistriss	O
grew	O
extreamly	O
enraged	O
at	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
her	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Blows	O
with	O
a	O
Whip	O
,	O
and	O
proceeded	O
further	O
in	O
her	O
passion	O
,	O
even	O
in	O
causing	O
him	O
to	O
tye	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Beds-post	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
whipt	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
most	O
violent	O
manner	O
,	O
until	O
the	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
Murther	O
.	O
To	O
prevent	O
which	O
,	O
her	O
Mistriss	O
stopt	O
her	O
Mouth	O
with	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
but	O
then	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
following	O
,	O
she	O
tyed	O
her	O
Neck	O
and	O
Heels	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
tyed	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Beds	O
post	O
,	O
burning	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Fire-Poker	O
upon	O
the	O
Neck	O
,	O
Shoulders	O
,	O
and	O
Back	O
,	O
after	O
a	O
most	O
inhuman	O
manner	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Blow	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
with	O
a	O
Hammer	O
,	O
until	O
she	O
made	O
her	O
confess	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
confederate	O
with	O
some	O
Thieves	O
who	O
intended	O
to	O
Rob	O
her	O
Master	O
's	O
House	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
Bristol	O
Fair	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Maid	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
on	O
the	O
next	O
Monday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
she	O
dyed	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
confessed	O
the	O
like	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
After	O
which	O
,	O
her	O
Mistriss	O
grew	O
careless	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
For	O
when	O
she	O
fell	O
sick	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
her	O
have	O
those	O
Accommodations	O
that	O
were	O
fit	O
for	O
a	O
person	O
in	O
that	O
deplorable	O
Condition	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
heard	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
Hang	O
her	O
,	O
Hang	O
her	O
;	O
And	O
that	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
confest	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
kill	O
'd	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
could	O
no	O
ways	O
be	O
prevail	O
'd	O
upon	O
to	O
take	O
any	O
pity	O
upon	O
her	O
Servant	O
,	O
nor	O
give	O
her	O
any	O
sustenance	O
:	O
But	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
Who	O
can	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
for	O
such	O
a	O
Wretch	O
?	O
Telling	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Pox	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Surgeon	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Stripes	O
and	O
Wounds	O
did	O
contribute	O
towards	O
her	O
Death	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
a	O
Surfeit	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
before	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
strived	O
to	O
Extenuate	O
her	O
Crime	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
That	O
her	O
Maid	O
had	O
wronged	O
her	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
by	O
making	O
away	O
her	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
Conversation	O
with	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Thieves	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
a	O
Girl	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
sullen	O
,	O
obstinate	O
,	O
temper	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
reason	O
why	O
she	O
Whipt	O
her	O
,	O
was	O
,	O
for	O
opening	O
her	O
Dressing-Box	O
.	O
She	O
called	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
a	O
favourable	O
account	O
of	O
her	O
former	O
Education	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
that	O
could	O
contradict	O
or	O
invalidate	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Evidence	O
;	O
only	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Maid	O
complained	O
of	O
a	O
stoppage	O
at	O
her	O
stomach	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
pain	O
in	O
her	O
head	O
,	O
before	O
she	O
was	O
so	O
used	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
surfeited	O
her	O
self	O
by	O
eating	O
Ice	O
Cakes	O
,	O
and	O
Apples	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
all	O
which	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
her	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
looking	O
upon	O
the	O
Heinousness	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
brought	O
in	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
wilful	O
Murther	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Page	I-pers
of	O
Harrow	B-place
on	I-place
the	I-place
Hill	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
taking	O
away	O
one	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
7l	O
.	O
and	O
40s	O
.	O
in	O
mony	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Goods	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Seven	O
men	O
that	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
a	O
Field	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
making	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
R	O
try	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
lying	O
in	O
a	O
Hedg	O
near	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
all	O
which	O
he	O
owned	O
,	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
Six	O
Men	O
besides	O
himself	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
dwelt	O
in	O
Drury	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
chance	O
to	O
Harrow	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
a	O
Gun	O
go	O
off	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
help	O
to	O
apprehend	O
the	O
Thieves	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Hillgrave	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Kensington	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Foot	B-pers
Onslow	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
about	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
2	O
Silver	O
Hilted	O
Swords	O
,	O
value	O
3l	O
.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Spurs	O
,	O
value	O
20s	O
.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Salver	O
value	O
5l	O
.	O
4	O
Spoons	O
value	O
40s	O
.	O
2	O
Salts	O
,	O
value	O
30s	O
.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Snuffers	O
,	O
Value	O
15s	O
.	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
Pan	O
,	O
value	O
25s	O
.	O
a	O
Ladle	O
,	O
value	O
40s.	O
,	O
a	O
Camblet	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
3l	O
.	O
a	O
Beaver	O
hat	O
,	O
Value	O
30s	O
.	O
Periwigs	O
value	O
6l	O
.	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
good	O
value	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
Evidenced	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Onslow	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Thieves	O
that	O
Robbed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
Sold	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
produced	O
as	O
a	O
further	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
denyed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Wigs	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
known	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
an	O
Old	O
Thief	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
both	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
of	O
Hackney	B-place
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
(	O
now	O
sick	O
in	O
Newgate	O
)	O
did	O
break	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Katharine	B-pers
Tuncks	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
one	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
3l	O
.	O
10s	O
.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Mugg	O
30s	O
.	O
a	O
Tobacco	O
Box	O
20s	O
a	O
Silver	O
watch	O
3l	O
.	O
a	O
Salt	O
10s	O
.	O
Four	O
Spoons	O
32s	O
.	O
with	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
that	O
came	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
and	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
A	O
Betty	O
was	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
besides	O
Clipt	O
Money	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Pocket	O
.	O
All	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
gain-say	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Floyd	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
upon	O
the	O
Statue	O
of	O
Stabbing	O
;	O
For	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
J	O
-	O
V	O
-	O
and	O
J	O
-	O
E	O
-	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
;	O
did	O
kill	O
and	O
murder	O
one	O
Joseph	B-pers
Burson	I-pers
,	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
upon	O
the	O
right	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Belly	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
six	O
Inches	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
died	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
The	O
Evidence	O
were	O
very	O
numerous	O
,	O
who	O
declared	O
that	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
hapned	O
near	O
the	O
Abby	O
at	O
Westminster	O
about	O
hiring	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
deceased	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
V	O
-	O
and	O
E	O
-	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
the	O
deceased	O
and	O
his	O
Friends	O
resisted	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
Swords	O
drawn	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Scuffle	O
the	O
said	O
Burson	O
was	O
killed	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
pleaded	O
notwithstanding	O
that	O
they	O
knew	O
not	O
who	O
gave	O
the	O
Wound	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
never	O
knew	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
nor	O
had	O
any	O
malice	O
,	O
yet	O
their	O
Swords	O
were	O
drawn	O
,	O
and	O
Jones	O
drew	O
his	O
first	O
.	O
So	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
at	O
Common	O
Law	O
,	O
but	O
were	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Statute	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
On	O
Thursday	O
Morning	O
J	B-pers
-	I-pers
V	I-pers
-	I-pers
and	O
J	B-pers
-	I-pers
E	I-pers
-	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
(	O
who	O
were	O
concern	O
'd	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Floyd	O
,	O
and	O
Richard	O
Jones	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Burson	I-pers
,	O
as	O
is	O
before	O
Incerted	O
,	O
)	O
surrendered	O
themselves	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Indictment	O
being	O
Read	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
much	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
effect	O
,	O
as	O
in	O
Floyd	O
's	O
Tryal	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
how	O
that	O
V	O
-	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
Coach	O
away	O
from	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
Swore	O
at	O
his	O
Servant	O
Jones	O
,	O
commanding	O
him	O
to	O
draw	O
at	O
Burson	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
Cryed	O
out	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
killed	O
,	O
and	O
died	O
with	O
24	O
hours	O
after	O
:	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
flatly	O
that	O
V	O
-	O
gave	O
the	O
mortal	O
Thrust	O
,	O
nor	O
likewise	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Edwards	O
made	O
any	O
Pass	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
had	O
his	O
Sword	O
drawn	O
with	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Coach-side	O
.	O
After	O
a	O
distinct	O
hearing	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
J	O
V	O
:	O
Pardon	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
J	O
E	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jacob	B-pers
Read	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bay	O
Mare	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
Decemb	O
.	O
Price	O
3l	O
.	O
2s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
from	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
of	O
Sommerset	O
Shire	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sold	O
the	O
Mare	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
for	O
3l	O
.	O
odd	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
Bought	O
the	O
Mare	O
of	O
a	O
Welsh-man	O
at	O
Bristol	O
,	O
and	O
produced	O
a	O
Certificate	O
from	O
the	O
Mayor	O
of	O
Bristol	O
,	O
which	O
passed	O
for	O
no	O
Evidence	O
on	O
his	O
account	O
.	O
Yet	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
G	B-pers
-	I-pers
C	I-pers
-	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
36	O
yards	O
of	O
Taffety	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
value	O
16s	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
Instant	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Jordan	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Catherine	B-pers
Jordan	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
were	O
both	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Cragg	B-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
18	O
yards	O
of	O
Silver	O
Fringe	O
,	O
value	O
3l	O
.	O
18s	O
.	O
50	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Gold	O
Fringe	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
l.	O
6s	O
.	O
20	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Gold	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
5l	O
.	O
6s	O
.	O
and	O
10	O
ounces	O
of	O
Silver	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
43s	O
.	O
4d	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Custody	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Lace	O
was	O
found	O
sewed	O
upon	O
the	O
Coat	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Joseph	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
was	O
produced	O
to	O
prove	O
for	O
Burglary	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Law	O
being	O
tender	O
of	O
the	O
Wife	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Man	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ruth	B-pers
Parrot	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Dowlace	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
7s	O
.	O
2	O
Smocks	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Linnen	O
,	O
from	O
George	B-pers
Maddox	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
Instant	O
.	O
Maddox	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
about	O
her	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
of	O
a	O
small	O
value	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Merridy	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Pascall	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
Mortal	O
wound	O
with	O
the	O
Iron	O
Chape	O
of	O
a	O
sword	O
,	O
on	O
his	O
right	O
Eye	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
died	O
the	O
22d	O
Instant	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
Evidenced	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
met	O
the	O
deceased	O
upon	O
the	O
Temple	B-place
Stairs	I-place
,	O
and	O
thrust	O
Pascall	O
into	O
the	O
Eye	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Watchman	O
there	O
in	O
the	O
Christmas	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
further	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Merridy	O
would	O
have	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
Temple	O
,	O
without	O
a	O
Ticket	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
refused	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
deceased	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Wound	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
heard	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
no	O
more	O
Sin	O
to	O
Kill	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Officers	O
,	O
than	O
to	O
Kill	O
a	O
Dog	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
Cat	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
the	O
Blood	O
of	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Exrep	O
ed	O
the	O
Crime	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Case	O
being	O
desperate	O
and	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
wilful	O
Murther	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gelding	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
price	O
7l	O
.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Laye	I-pers
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
offering	O
the	O
Gelding	O
to	O
Sale	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
several	O
Stories	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
how	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Horse	O
at	O
Daintry	O
in	O
Northampton	O
shire	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Horse	O
of	O
2	O
men	O
and	O
a	O
Boy	O
upon	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
no	O
Witness	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
A	O
Dutchman	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
5l	O
.	O
from	O
one	O
Hugh	B-pers
Nufield	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
left	O
a	O
Pewter	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
stead	O
of	O
the	O
Silver	O
one	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
James	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
3	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
20s	O
.	O
4	O
pair	O
of	O
Sleeves	O
,	O
value	O
20s	O
.	O
2	O
Muslin	O
Neckcloths	O
,	O
value	O
3s	O
.	O
5	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
value	O
30s	O
.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
The	O
Evidence	O
put	O
the	O
Woman	O
in	O
trust	O
to	O
keep	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
So	O
the	O
Court	O
was	O
of	O
opinion	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
steal	O
them	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
E	B-pers
-	I-pers
B	I-pers
-	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
400	O
yards	O
of	O
stript	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
40l	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
,	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
immediately	O
acquitted	O
.	O
G	B-pers
-	I-pers
J	I-pers
-	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
small	O
value	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
full	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
not	O
denying	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Earl	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
Swore	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Tankard	O
.	O
All	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
heard	O
to	O
confess	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Vanrosendall	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Gilliart	I-pers
,	O
Dutchmen	O
were	O
all	O
Three	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Lithall	I-pers
,	O
whereupon	O
a	O
Party	O
Jury	O
was	O
Sworn	O
,	O
whose	O
Names	O
are	O
as	O
follows	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Bealing	I-pers
John	B-pers
Shavelier	I-pers
Abel	B-pers
Weeks	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Jolly	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
Daniel	B-pers
Gize	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
Abraham	B-pers
Shauly	I-pers
John	B-pers
Bayly	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Lezeer	I-pers
James	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
James	B-pers
Warrior	I-pers
.	O
After	O
which	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
deceased	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
the	O
way	O
near	O
Chelsey	O
Town	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
was	O
shot	O
by	O
Three	O
men	O
,	O
which	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Vanrosendall	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
confest	O
it	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
Kill	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
gave	O
no	O
reason	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
said	O
Lithall	O
died	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Vanrosendall	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
Lithall	O
had	O
his	O
Sword	O
drawn	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
towards	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
that	O
the	O
Dutch-men	O
were	O
upon	O
any	O
Duty	O
,	O
as	O
Sentinel	O
s.	O
It	O
appeared	O
further	O
,	O
that	O
Lithall	O
was	O
much	O
in	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
Kill	O
the	O
first	O
man	O
he	O
met	O
that	O
should	O
affront	O
him	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
further	O
demonstrated	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Vanrosendall	O
acknowledged	O
that	O
he	O
Kill	O
'd	O
Lithall	O
:	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
affected	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Vanrosendall	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Terry	I-pers
of	O
Fulham	B-place
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barnabey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
one	O
Silver	O
Probe	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
14	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
but	O
single	O
,	O
and	O
spoke	O
very	O
favourable	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
.	O
So	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
Jane	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
with	O
a	O
Bullet	O
shot	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Mustet	O
Barrel	O
fastned	O
in	O
an	O
Engine	O
in	O
the	O
Artillery	B-place
Ground	I-place
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
Slade	O
his	O
man	O
shot	O
off	O
the	O
Piece	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
the	O
Fact	O
about	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Sessions	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
nothing	O
could	O
be	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
design	O
to	O
Kill	O
the	O
said	O
Jane	O
Burton	O
,	O
only	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Misfortune	O
,	O
and	O
done	O
by	O
Chance	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
was	O
Try	O
'd	O
for	O
Killing	O
one	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Hedding	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Wound	O
in	O
the	O
Throat	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
one	O
inch	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
were	O
two	O
Chyrurgeons	O
he	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
deceased	O
was	O
found	O
Buried	O
in	O
a	O
Ditch	O
at	O
Hangmans	O
Acre	O
,	O
near	O
Mile-End	O
Green	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
Throat	O
Cut	O
from	O
Ear	O
to	O
Ear	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Wounds	O
about	O
his	O
Head	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
further	O
made	O
out	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
were	O
in	O
company	O
together	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
the	O
Murther	O
was	O
committed	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
to	O
have	O
Murthered	O
the	O
said	O
Hedding	O
:	O
so	O
the	O
matter	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
of	O
the	O
deceased	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
custody	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
set	O
upon	O
by	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
defence	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
Cut	O
him	O
and	O
mangled	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
not	O
be	O
known	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
available	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
wilful	O
Murther	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
J	B-pers
-	I-pers
L	I-pers
-	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intention	O
to	O
steal	O
her	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
instant	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
3	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
about	O
8	O
or	O
9	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
with	O
a	O
Ripping	O
Chisel	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
being	O
Try	O
'd	O
a	O
Sessions	O
ago	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Burglary	O
.	O
Rowland	B-pers
Tomkins	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Killing	O
William	B-pers
Holding	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
were	O
trying	O
of	O
Guns	O
together	O
,	O
in	O
some	O
other	O
company	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
Gun	O
happened	O
to	O
go	O
off	O
against	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
the	O
deceased	O
having	O
struck	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
little	O
Switch	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
find	O
in	O
his	O
heart	O
to	O
shoot	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Malice	O
appeared	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
formerly	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
Loved	O
as	O
Brothers	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Montague	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Vallens	I-pers
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
break	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Farenbras	B-pers
Styne	I-pers
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
Dean	O
brought	O
some	O
Goods	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
one	O
piece	O
of	O
Stuff	O
Hangings	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Curtains	O
40s	O
.	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Tapstry	O
10l	O
.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
drugget	O
Curtains	O
6l	O
.	O
and	O
other	O
goods	O
,	O
into	O
White-Fryars	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	O
Vallens	O
came	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
seen	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
about	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
;	O
Vallens	O
being	O
entrusted	O
with	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
house	O
,	O
whilst	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
discharged	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Deane	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Montague	O
:	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
at	O
Common	O
Law	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
upon	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
Stabbing	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
wilful	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Marlow	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
outlawed	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
but	O
now	O
Tryed	O
for	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Witness	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
Third	O
Year	O
of	O
King	O
James	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
23d	O
day	O
of	O
June	O
1687	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
Marlow	O
's	O
house	O
at	O
Islington	B-place
drinking	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
Din	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
,	O
upon	O
some	O
slight	O
occasion	O
,	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
prick	O
in	O
the	O
Groin	O
4	O
Inches	O
deep	O
,	O
threatening	O
him	O
before	O
,	O
calling	O
him	O
Son	O
of	O
a	O
Whore	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
(	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
)	O
running	O
away	O
,	O
he	O
owned	O
that	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
Passion	O
,	O
but	O
denyed	O
it	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
how	O
Marlow	O
came	O
by	O
his	O
Death	O
,	O
so	O
after	O
a	O
long	O
Tryal	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
wilful	O
Murther	O
at	O
Common	O
law	O
,	O
but	O
discharged	O
of	O
the	O
Stabbing	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
some	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
from	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Page	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
confest	O
to	O
have	O
let	O
in	O
another	O
Woman	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
Coal	O
hole	O
till	O
towards	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
carried	O
them	O
into	O
Southwark	O
.	O
She	O
not	O
denying	O
it	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Philip	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Boy	O
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Gloves	O
and	O
60	O
Yards	O
of	O
filleting	O
,	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Carlton	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Boy	O
being	O
seen	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
with	O
the	O
Gloves	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
was	O
presently	O
stopt	O
.	O
Notwithstanding	O
his	O
denial	O
of	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Williams	O
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
a	O
dozen	O
of	O
Dowlace	O
Clouts	O
value	O
12s	O
.	O
8	O
Yards	O
of	O
Flanders	O
Lace	O
40s	O
.	O
3	O
Yards	O
of	O
Bone-Lace	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
Edward	B-pers
Harlow	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Day	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Harlow	I-pers
,	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
,	O
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Gown	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
3	O
stuff	O
Peticoats	O
3	O
s.	O
from	O
Matthew	B-pers
Tute	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Boy	O
was	O
an	O
Apprentice	O
near	O
to	O
Tute	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
a	O
Man	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
confest	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
of	O
Peace	O
when	O
apprehended	O
,	O
but	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Fawsey	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
30	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
40s	O
.	O
7	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Thread	O
4s	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
commit	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
taking	O
the	O
Silk	O
off	O
a	O
Shelf	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
.	O
Notwithstanding	O
his	O
denying	O
of	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Bourn	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Youth	O
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Pickard	I-pers
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intention	O
to	O
steal	O
his	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
he	O
broke	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
or	O
took	O
away	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
another	O
Youth	O
,	O
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
fact	O
in	O
kind	O
,	O
(	O
viz	O
.	O
)	O
for	O
breaking	O
Edward	B-pers
Hicks	I-pers
's	O
house	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intention	O
to	O
steal	O
his	O
Goods	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
charging	O
him	O
fully	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Mare	O
,	O
value	O
30s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Gallaway	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
Heyfer	O
,	O
price	O
3l	O
.	O
was	O
owned	O
by	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
West	I-pers
.	O
Galloway	O
lost	O
the	O
Mare	O
out	O
of	O
Berkshire	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Mare	O
of	O
one	O
Boughton	O
,	O
now	O
in	O
Chelmsford	O
Goal	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
West	O
for	O
the	O
Heyfer	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
Heyfer	O
out	O
of	O
Berkshire	O
too	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Custody	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wade	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Gurlington	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
7l	O
.	O
8s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Taster	O
3s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wyn	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
accused	O
maliciously	O
,	O
and	O
proving	O
her	O
Reputation	O
to	O
be	O
honest	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Don	O
Pedro	B-pers
Don	I-pers
Quillo	I-pers
the	O
Spanish	O
Ambassador	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
1688	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
15	O
Guyneas	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
l.	O
2s	O
.	O
and	O
6d	O
.	O
8	O
pieces	O
of	O
other	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
9l	O
.	O
8s	O
.	O
800	O
Guyneas	O
more	O
,	O
value	O
844	O
l.	O
and	O
Fourscore	O
Pound	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
one	O
Jasper	B-pers
Leronso	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
circumstantial	O
,	O
and	O
Leronso	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
the	O
time	O
when	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
Ransackt	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
one	O
could	O
prove	O
any	O
matter	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
Isabella	B-pers
Pardy	I-pers
as	O
principal	O
,	O
and	O
Alice	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
as	O
accessory	O
,	O
were	O
both	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Cecil	I-pers
and	O
stealing	O
goods	O
of	O
great	O
value	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
and	O
Spoons	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
but	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
chief	O
Evidence	O
being	O
absent	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
the	O
Burglary	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
found	O
about	O
Pardy	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
but	O
the	O
Latter	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
J-	B-pers
L	I-pers
-	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
12	O
yards	O
of	O
Sript	O
Lute	O
string	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Humphreys	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
Swore	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Silk	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
one	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
his	O
Father	O
in	O
Law	O
,	O
the	O
Marquess	O
de	O
Bashet	O
,	O
all	O
which	O
being	O
well	O
weigh	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Spegg	I-pers
was	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
20	O
Wether	O
Sheep	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
l.	O
10s	O
.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Fynch	I-pers
,	O
unto	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
all	O
of	O
others	O
within	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
Clergy	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Hebborn	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
and	O
ancient	O
Woman	O
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
,	O
with	O
one	O
Susannah	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Williams	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
Swift	B-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
innocently	O
drawn	O
into	O
the	O
thing	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
abundance	O
of	O
people	O
to	O
prove	O
her	O
Integrity	O
,	O
a	O
good	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
good	O
Christian	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ursula	B-pers
Batters	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
30s	O
.	O
a	O
Cornelion	O
Rings	O
,	O
10s	O
.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Edw	B-pers
.	I-pers
Stanton	I-pers
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
at	O
Stanton	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
Malice	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Read	I-pers
gave	O
in	O
bail	O
to	O
appear	O
next	O
Sessions	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
Ship	O
going	O
to	O
King	O
James	O
,	O
were	O
ordered	O
to	O
remain	O
till	O
further	O
Order	O
.	O
On	O
Fryday	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
Scotch	O
Officers	O
came	O
into	O
Court	O
and	O
pleaded	O
their	O
Majesties	O
most	O
gracious	O
Pardon	O
upon	O
their	O
Knees	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
allowed	O
them	O
accordingly	O
;	O
whose	O
Names	O
are	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
,	O
Mungo	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
,	O
Captains	O
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
David	B-pers
Arnolt	I-pers
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Th	I-pers
k	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Cunningham	I-pers
,	O
Lieutenants	O
,	O
George	B-pers
Chitty	I-pers
,	O
Walter	B-pers
Auchmontey	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Paten	I-pers
,	O
Alexander	B-pers
Innis	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Carr	I-pers
,	O
Patrick	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
Ensigns	O
,	O
Captains	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Peter	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
,	O
received	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
it	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
are	O
since	O
gone	O
into	O
Scotland	O
,	O
in	O
their	O
Majesties	O
Service	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Richard	B-pers
Stafford	I-pers
was	O
Charged	O
to	O
have	O
Written	O
,	O
Composed	O
,	O
and	O
Published	O
,	O
a	O
most	O
scandalous	O
and	O
seditious	O
Libel	O
against	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
Government	O
,	O
intending	O
thereby	O
to	O
raise	O
Dissention	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
breed	O
Disscord	O
between	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
Queen	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
late	O
Parliament	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
he	O
refused	O
to	O
plead	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
only	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
refer	O
himself	O
to	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
William	O
and	O
Mary	O
,	O
which	O
faith	O
,	O
that	O
any	O
thing	O
offered	O
against	O
the	O
Parliament	O
,	O
was	O
Cognizable	O
in	O
Parliament	O
only	O
:	O
and	O
therefore	O
would	O
insist	O
on	O
that	O
plea	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
ought	O
to	O
be	O
Tryed	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
Custody	O
,	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
pleaded	O
not	O
guilty	O
,	O
thereupon	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
remain	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Sentence	O
as	O
followeth	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
Nine	O
.	O
John	O
Williams	O
,	O
John	O
Earle	O
,	O
Henry	O
Floyd	O
,	O
Richard	O
Jones	O
,	O
John	O
Vanrofendall	O
,	O
E	O
-	O
J	O
-	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Spegg	O
,	O
Rowland	O
Tomkins	O
,	O
Henry	O
Deane	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
Eleven	O
.	O
Richard	O
Merridy	O
,	O
George	O
Cox	O
,	O
William	O
Harvey	O
,	O
Robert	O
Hillgrave	O
,	O
John	O
Anderson	O
,	O
(	O
convicted	O
about	O
four	O
sessions	O
ago	O
)	O
Thomas	O
Williams	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Fox	O
,	O
John	O
Longstaffe	O
,	O
Edward	O
Richardson	O
,	O
Jane	O
Smith	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	O
Deacon	O
,	O
who	O
pleading	O
her	O
Belly	O
,	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
were	O
Empannelled	O
,	O
whose	O
Verdict	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
quick	O
Child	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
Two	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Montague	O
,	O
Margaret	O
Jones	O
.	O
Ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Whipt	O
Nine	O
.	O
Joseph	O
Jordan	O
,	O
Philip	O
Clark	O
,	O
Robert	O
Harlow	O
,	O
George	O
Fawsey	O
,	O
Isabella	O
Pardey	O
,	O
Ruth	O
Parrey	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
J	O
-	O
G	O
-	O
C	O
-	O
and	O
John	O
Murray	O
.	O
Those	O
of	O
London-side	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
Whipt	O
from	O
Newgate	O
to	O
Aldgate	O
.	O
Those	O
of	O
Middlesex-side	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
Whipt	O
from	O
Newgate	O
to	O
Holbourn	O
Barn	O
.	O
One	O
Fletcher	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
remain	O
,	O
being	O
suspected	O
to	O
have	O
Cut	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Picture	O
in	O
Guildhall	O
.	O
J	O
-	O
V	O
-	O
Immediately	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
Convicted	O
,	O
pleaded	O
His	O
Majesties	O
most	O
Gracious	O
pardon	O
upon	O
his	O
knees	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
allowed	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
Advertisments	O
These	O
are	O
to	O
give	O
Notice	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
any	O
person	O
should	O
occasion	O
to	O
sell	O
any	O
Library	O
or	O
parcel	O
of	O
Books	O
,	O
either	O
in	O
large	O
or	O
small	O
Quantity	O
,	O
may	O
receive	O
ready	O
Mony	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
upon	O
View	O
thereof	O
,	O
by	O
Langley	O
Curtis	O
at	O
six	O
Edmondbury	O
Godfrey	O
's	O
Head	O
near	O
Fleet-bridge	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
lately	O
publisht	O
a	O
fourth	O
Volume	O
of	O
Cus	O
Morning	O
Excercises	O
,	O
by	O
several	O
Ministers	O
in	O
and	O
about	O
London	O
,	O
preached	O
in	O
October	O
,	O
1689	O
.	O
Sold	O
by	O
John	O
Dunton	O
at	O
the	O
Raven	O
in	O
the	O
Poultry	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
also	O
published	O
a	O
New	O
Play	O
Entituled	O
,	O
The	O
Abdicated	O
Prince	O
;	O
Or	O
,	O
the	O
Adventures	O
of	O
Four	O
Years	O
.	O
A	O
Tragy-Comedy	O
;	O
As	O
it	O
was	O
Lately	O
Acted	O
with	O
great	O
Applause	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Court	O
at	O
Alba	O
Regalia	O
,	O
by	O
several	O
persons	O
of	O
great	O
Quality	O
.	O
Sold	O
by	O
the	O
Book	O
sellers	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
Westminster	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
to	O
give	O
Notice	O
to	O
all	O
Persons	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
the	O
Publick	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Elmy	O
,	O
Prosfessor	O
of	O
Physick	O
,	O
and	O
Operator	O
,	O
of	O
known	O
Integrity	O
,	O
and	O
above	O
25	O
years	O
practice	O
,	O
Liveth	O
at	O
the	O
Blue	O
Ball	O
in	O
Whale-Bone	O
Court	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Lower	O
End	O
of	O
Bartholomew-lane	O
by	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
who	O
most	O
safely	O
and	O
expeditiously	O
Cures	O
Deafness	O
and	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
Ears	O
in	O
any	O
of	O
what	O
Age	O
soever	O
,	O
(	O
if	O
Curable	O
)	O
and	O
at	O
first	O
sight	O
by	O
Inspection	O
,	O
Resolves	O
the	O
Patien	O
if	O
so	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
as	O
most	O
Eminent	O
Persons	O
of	O
Quality	O
in	O
this	O
City	O
can	O
Testifie	O
.	O
He	O
hath	O
likewise	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Gargarism	O
or	O
Mouth	O
Water	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
make	O
black	O
or	O
yellow	O
Teeth	O
as	O
White	O
as	O
Ivory	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
times	O
using	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
will	O
certainly	O
Cure	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
Diseases	O
incident	O
to	O
the	O
Mouth	O
,	O
Teeth	O
and	O
Gums	O
,	O
which	O
in	O
many	O
persons	O
causeth	O
a	O
stinking	O
Breath	O
,	O
which	O
(	O
by	O
the	O
Blessing	O
of	O
God	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
this	O
Water	O
)	O
I	O
dare	O
affirm	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
free	O
from	O
those	O
maladies	O
beforementioned	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
.	O
His	O
Pills	O
only	O
prepared	O
for	O
the	O
French	O
Disease	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Running	O
of	O
the	O
Reins	O
,	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
in	O
Boxes	O
of	O
several	O
Prices	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
Venereal	O
Arcana	O
's	O
as	O
occasion	O
requires	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
.	O
