TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
and	O
Queens	O
Commissions	O
OF	O
THE	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILY	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
9th	O
,	O
10th	O
,	O
11th	O
,	O
and	O
12th	O
Days	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
1691	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
Third	O
Year	O
of	O
Their	O
MAJESTIES	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
9th	O
,	O
10th	O
,	O
11th	O
,	O
and	O
12th	O
Days	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
1691	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pilkington	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Common	O
Sergeant	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
Justice	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
follow	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Mortlock	I-pers
Jonathan	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
James	B-pers
Knapton	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Stretton	I-pers
John	B-pers
Overton	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Green	I-pers
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
Chamberlain	B-pers
Dunn	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Page	I-pers
John	B-pers
Millgate	I-pers
Michael	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
John	B-pers
Tignall	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Farmer	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
Abraham	B-pers
Honour	I-pers
John	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Sawny	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Sawny	I-pers
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
The	O
proceedings	O
were	O
these	O
;	O
Christopher	B-pers
Ashley	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Browne	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Felony	O
,	O
Burglary	O
and	O
Sacriledge	O
,	O
in	O
Robbing	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
Church	I-place
of	I-place
Great	I-place
St.	I-place
Bartholomews	I-place
,	I-place
London	I-place
,	O
in	O
November	O
1689	O
,	O
carrying	O
away	O
the	O
Pulpit	O
Cloth	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
Communion	O
Plate	O
,	O
of	O
very	O
great	O
value	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
confest	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
assisting	O
to	O
Collet	O
,	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
Executed	O
last	O
Sessions	O
)	O
in	O
stealing	O
the	O
plate	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
30l	O
.	O
to	O
his	O
share	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Proof	O
on	O
his	O
side	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sherwin	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Bolton	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
in	O
Black-Fryers	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
.	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
taking	O
away	O
4	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
40s	O
.	O
and	O
30l	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Chest	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
lost	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
presumptuous	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Chester	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
killing	O
one	O
Esther	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Near	O
Wheel	O
of	O
his	O
Cart	O
,	O
in	O
Thames-street	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Cart	O
Wheel	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
run	O
over	O
her	O
Foot	O
,	O
and	O
brusied	O
it	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
she	O
dyed	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
The	O
Chyrurgeons	O
gave	O
their	O
Opinions	O
that	O
it	O
might	O
hasten	O
her	O
Death	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
Ancient	O
Person	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
otherwise	O
Distempered	O
;	O
so	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
and	O
Valentine	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Robbery	O
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
committed	O
upon	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Sir	O
Oliver	B-pers
St.	I-pers
George	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
and	O
Baronet	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
day	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
taking	O
away	O
a	O
Silver	O
Hilted	O
Sword	O
,	O
value	O
40s	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
set	O
upon	O
in	O
St.	B-place
James-street	I-place
,	O
by	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Men	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Sword	O
was	O
snatcht	O
from	O
his	O
Side	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
dark	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
discover	O
the	O
Persons	O
;	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Phillip	B-pers
Harper	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Walton	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
Was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
the	O
wilful	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
David	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Right	O
Pap	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
six	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
dyed	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
arose	O
between	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Publick-House	O
at	O
Charing-Cross	B-place
,	O
and	O
Hughes	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
strike	O
Harper	O
first	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
,	O
Harper	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
to	O
defend	O
himself	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Lewis	B-pers
L'Roach	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Till	O
Box	O
of	O
one	O
Martha	B-pers
Latham	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
15s	O
.	O
The	O
manner	O
thus	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
Shop	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
somewhat	O
,	O
and	O
whilst	O
the	O
Apprentice	O
was	O
busie	O
,	O
he	O
thrust	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Whale-Bone	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
shewed	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
into	O
the	O
Till	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
drest	O
beforehand	O
with	O
Bird-Lyme	O
,	O
brought	O
up	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
In	O
the	O
very	O
Act	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Bernard	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
10	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
value	O
,	O
from	O
Edward	B-pers
Cateret	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictments	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hambleton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Silver	O
Cups	O
value	O
3l	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Sympson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
short	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Cup	O
being	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Custody	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Mayle	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
brought	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
Custody	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Bill	O
of	O
Indictment	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
preferred	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
Tryed	O
,	O
as	O
hereafter	O
may	O
be	O
seen	O
.	O
V	B-pers
-	I-pers
,	I-pers
J-	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
a	O
white	O
Dimmity	O
Counterpane	O
,	O
value	O
9s	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
bundance	O
of	O
small	O
Linnen	O
contained	O
in	O
a	O
Trunk	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Cox	O
's	O
Servants	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
Cox	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
under	O
a	O
pretence	O
of	O
speaking	O
with	O
some	O
Lodgers	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Apron	O
before	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
disprove	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Roger	B-pers
Harry	I-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
5l	O
.	O
from	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ralph	I-pers
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edgerton	B-pers
Brett	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
Was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
killing	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Benbridge	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
,	O
near	O
to	O
the	O
Groyne	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Rapid	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
six	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
dyed	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
Indicted	O
upon	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
stabbing	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Benbridge	O
had	O
no	O
Weapon	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
first	O
Assaulted	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
in	O
the	O
general	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Brett	O
going	O
along	O
by	O
Rose	B-place
and	I-place
Crown-Court	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Grays-Inn-Lane	I-place
,	O
where	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
standing	O
,	O
about	O
10	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
with	O
another	O
man	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
gave	O
a	O
blow	O
with	O
his	O
Gloves	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
unkind	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Brett	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
which	O
aggravated	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
fled	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
lying	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
naked	O
Sword	O
lying	O
by	O
him	O
bloody	O
.	O
The	O
matter	O
was	O
very	O
positively	O
demonstrated	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
wilful	O
Murther	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Stykes	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
40l	O
.	O
two	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
5l	O
.	O
two	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
French	O
Pistol	O
from	O
Lucy	B-pers
Rapely	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Pelling	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
wilful	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
Percy	B-pers
Kinkid	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Wound	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
left	O
Pap	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
six	O
Inches	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
Kinkid	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
the	O
Two	B-place
Loggerheads	I-place
in	I-place
Drury-Lane	I-place
with	O
some	O
others	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
by	O
and	O
threw	O
Flint-stone	O
at	O
him	O
swearing	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
his	O
Butcher	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
a	O
Stone	O
would	O
not	O
kill	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
cut	O
his	O
Throat	O
with	O
a	O
case	O
knife	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
uttered	O
with	O
a	O
Deprecation	O
betwixt	O
them	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
had	O
oftentimes	O
injured	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
by	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
Wife	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
lookt	O
upon	O
as	O
a	O
great	O
Affront	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Swanson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Edward	B-pers
Draynor	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
one	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Fork	O
,	O
value	O
20s	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Draynor	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
them	O
to	O
sale	O
at	O
a	O
Brokers	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
where	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
stopt	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
several	O
Storys	O
there	O
;	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
,	O
she	O
confest	O
to	O
have	O
taken	O
the	O
spoon	O
from	O
her	O
Master	O
aforesaid	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Godfrey	B-pers
Carrick	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Pachy	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Silk	O
Jacquet	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
September	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
one	O
Henry	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
he	O
secretly	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
an	O
Alley	B-place
near	I-place
Dukes	I-place
Place	I-place
,	O
about	O
seven	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
certain	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
He	O
denyed	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
confest	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
the	O
wilful	O
Murther	O
of	O
his	O
Wife	O
Martha	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
numerous	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
in	O
the	O
general	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
Rude	O
behaviour	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
beat	O
his	O
Wife	O
upon	O
the	O
Breast	O
,	O
back	O
and	O
Belly	O
,	O
by	O
kicking	O
and	O
striking	O
her	O
,	O
insomuch	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
Bruised	O
in	O
several	O
parts	O
of	O
her	O
Body	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
complained	O
to	O
her	O
Neighbours	O
when	O
she	O
lay	O
languishing	O
upon	O
her	O
Death-Bed	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
some	O
Ministers	O
that	O
came	O
to	O
visit	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
just	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
departing	O
the	O
World	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
kiss	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
immediately	O
screekt	O
out	O
and	O
refused	O
to	O
Imbrace	O
him	O
:	O
After	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
her	O
wrong	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
chiefly	O
the	O
Devil	O
that	O
put	O
him	O
on	O
;	O
besides	O
this	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
Tore	O
her	O
with	O
some	O
Instrument	O
in	O
her	O
Privy	O
parts	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
most	O
horrid	O
manner	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
died	O
she	O
laid	O
her	O
Death	O
to	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
He	O
oftentimes	O
threatned	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
to	O
do	O
them	O
a	O
mischief	O
whensoever	O
they	O
reproved	O
his	O
Insolency	O
,	O
they	O
witnessed	O
against	O
him	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
alledged	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
Wife	O
had	O
been	O
sick	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
seemed	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
Malice	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
well	O
weighing	O
the	O
Evidence	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Elinor	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Thinn	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Stuff	O
from	O
one	O
George	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
.	O
They	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Shop	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
buying	O
some	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
took	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
Stuff	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
a	O
Petty	O
Lacenary	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Matthew	B-pers
Earsel	I-pers
,	O
Old	B-pers
Mobb	I-pers
,	O
Ruth	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Biggs	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
Indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Whitney	I-pers
,	O
did	O
break	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Joan	B-pers
Flanders	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
Biggs	O
confest	O
the	O
Indictment	O
upon	O
his	O
Arraignment	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
rest	O
was	O
Mrs.	O
Flanders	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
encompassed	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
being	O
Enfield	B-place
Water-Mill	I-place
,	O
and	O
broke	O
it	O
open	O
,	O
about	O
10	O
or	O
11	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
20l	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
with	O
abundance	O
of	O
Plate	O
and	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
of	O
very	O
considerable	O
value	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
300l	O
.	O
They	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
swore	O
great	O
Oaths	O
that	O
they	O
would	O
kill	O
them	O
all	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
shew	O
them	O
where	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
Plate	O
lay	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
forced	O
out	O
of	O
Fear	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
Booty	O
they	O
went	O
off	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
,	O
Earsel	O
was	O
found	O
with	O
Rings	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
in	O
Long	O
Acre	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
owned	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Spoon	O
and	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Hair	O
of	O
Reynolds	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
Wife	O
to	O
one	O
Reynolds	O
who	O
swore	O
against	O
the	O
rest	O
in	O
Custody	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
;	O
but	O
Earsel	O
and	O
Old-Mobb	O
were	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
;	O
Earsel	O
held	O
their	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
whilst	O
the	O
rest	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
25l	O
.	O
for	O
his	O
share	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
especially	O
Old	O
Mobb	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Dadson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
making	O
an	O
Assault	O
upon	O
Thomas	B-pers
Strickland	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
High-way	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
4l	O
.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Brocade	O
Breeches	O
3l.	O
,	O
an	O
Indian	O
Silk	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
40s	O
.	O
a	O
Bevor	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
3l	O
.	O
14	O
Muslin	O
Neckcloths	O
,	O
value	O
3l	O
.	O
10s	O
.	O
10	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
40	O
shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Strickland	O
,	O
who	O
,	O
said	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
set	O
upon	O
near	O
Hounslow	B-place
by	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
Persons	O
,	O
and	O
lost	O
his	O
Goods	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
charge	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
positively	O
;	O
But	O
there	O
was	O
other	O
Evidence	O
produced	O
,	O
that	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
that	O
helpt	O
to	O
commit	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
as	O
Further	O
Evidence	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
urged	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
spightfully	O
sworn	O
against	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
sworn	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Robbery	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Alexander	B-pers
Driver	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
Francis	B-pers
Lepeer	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
1690	O
of	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
14l	O
.	O
Yards	O
of	O
Silk	O
Crimson	O
Damask	O
,	O
value	O
l.	O
25	O
Pud-a-way	O
,	O
Serge	O
,	O
value	O
40s	O
.	O
Lepeer	O
deposed	O
upon	O
Oath	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
him	O
as	O
an	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
being	O
an	O
Upholsterer	O
,	O
for	O
three	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Robbed	O
him	O
as	O
he	O
suspected	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
some	O
Evidence	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
in	O
the	O
general	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
further	O
sworn	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
offered	O
Silk	O
to	O
sale	O
for	O
two	O
Shillings	O
,	O
but	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
him	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
behaved	O
himself	O
honestly	O
in	O
his	O
Service	O
before	O
this	O
time	O
;	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Banks	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Murther	O
,	O
in	O
driving	O
his	O
Coach	O
over	O
the	O
Hand	O
of	O
one	O
Prudence	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
Aged	O
about	O
two	O
Years	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
driving	O
along	O
Bow-street	B-place
in	I-place
Bloomsbury	I-place
,	O
and	O
the	O
Child	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
accidentally	O
run	O
over	O
it	O
;	O
at	O
which	O
the	O
Coachman	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
Consternated	O
and	O
very	O
sorry	O
for	O
so	O
sad	O
a	O
Casualty	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Matter	O
Special	O
,	O
till	O
further	O
considered	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
likewise	O
of	O
one	O
Sarah	B-pers
Smallnick	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Infant	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
driving	O
a	O
Cart	O
over	O
her	O
Short	O
Ribs	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
driving	O
a	O
Brick-Cart	O
along	O
St.	B-place
Giles-street	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
and	O
the	O
child	O
stood	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
did	O
believe	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Child	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confest	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquisition	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
by	O
Misfortune	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
H	B-pers
-	I-pers
M	I-pers
-	I-pers
,	O
B	B-pers
-	I-pers
T	I-pers
-	I-pers
and	O
A	B-pers
-	I-pers
T	I-pers
-	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Clipping	O
the	O
currant	O
Coyn	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
S.	B-place
James	I-place
Clarkenwell	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
M	O
-	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Garret	O
Window	O
,	O
4	O
pieces	O
of	O
Clippings	O
,	O
10	O
Copper	O
Half-Crowns	O
,	O
4	O
Brass	O
Shillings	O
,	O
with	O
Shears	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Implements	O
fit	O
for	O
their	O
Trade	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
all	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
against	O
them	O
:	O
the	O
Shears	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Vault	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Files	O
in	O
another	O
place	O
.	O
They	O
all	O
denyed	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Tryal	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
Repute	O
amongst	O
their	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
no	O
good	O
Defence	O
,	O
so	O
M	O
-	O
and	O
T	O
-	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
but	O
A	O
-	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
B	O
T	O
:	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
H	O
M	O
:	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wanklin	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
of	O
32	O
Guineas	O
,	O
one	O
King	O
James	O
the	O
First	O
's	O
20	O
Shilling	O
piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Wankiln	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
entrusted	O
with	O
the	O
Gold	O
and	O
the	O
Key	O
where	O
it	O
lay	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Indictment	O
being	O
not	O
laid	O
for	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
for	O
a	O
breach	O
of	O
trust	O
,	O
a	O
new	O
Bill	O
was	O
preferred	O
against	O
her	O
at	O
Common	O
Law	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
after	O
a	O
long	O
hearing	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Aldridge	I-pers
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
30s	O
.	O
a	O
Taster	O
,	O
value	O
7s	O
.	O
a	O
thimble	O
,	O
value	O
18d	O
.	O
about	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Hater	I-pers
.	O
She	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
way	O
with	O
the	O
Spoons	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
9s	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Girle	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Alice	B-pers
Merser	I-pers
not	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
Rob	O
one	O
Henry	B-pers
Hartis	I-pers
,	O
about	O
Whitsuntide	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
Camblet	O
Cloak	O
,	O
value	O
4l	O
.	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
40s	O
.	O
a	O
Waistcoat	O
value	O
15s	O
.	O
a	O
Hood	O
,	O
value	O
3s	O
.	O
a	O
Petty-coat	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Merser	O
were	O
Lodging	O
in	O
the	O
prosecutors	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Cloak	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
to	O
a	O
Broker	O
,	O
one	O
Brench	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
having	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
9s	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Adam	B-pers
Mack	I-pers
Affey	I-pers
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
George	B-pers
Cromwell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17	O
of	O
Feb	O
last	O
,	O
taking	O
away	O
one	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
20s	O
.	O
one	O
other	O
Cup	O
30s	O
two	O
Silver	O
Mugs	O
,	O
value	O
3l	O
.	O
a	O
Porringer	O
,	O
value	O
5l	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tumbler	O
,	O
value	O
50s	O
.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Boyle	O
,	O
value	O
22s	O
.	O
a	O
Taster	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
and	O
6d	O
.	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
besides	O
20l	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Cromwell	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
Men	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
at	O
Sunbury	B-place
in	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
and	O
bound	O
him	O
and	O
all	O
his	O
Family	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
horrible	O
Oaths	O
that	O
they	O
must	O
have	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
,	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
afterwards	O
,	O
his	O
House	O
being	O
searcht	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Heard	O
in	O
Crown	O
Court	O
in	O
Chancery-Lane	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Trunk	O
found	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
made	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Pillow-bare	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
denyed	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
further	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
hired	O
Horses	O
,	O
and	O
ingaged	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
pretending	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
Brainford	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
Wedding	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
carry	O
on	O
their	O
design	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
concerned	O
any	O
further	O
than	O
that	O
he	O
past	O
his	O
word	O
for	O
one	O
Horse	O
;	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Neighbours	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
a	O
good	O
Account	O
on	O
't	O
and	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Collins	O
,	O
his	O
Brewer	O
,	O
proved	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
sick	O
all	O
that	O
Day	O
when	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
very	O
well	O
remembered	O
by	O
a	O
good	O
Token	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
received	O
Money	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
made	O
appear	O
by	O
producing	O
his	O
Account	O
Book	O
which	O
was	O
mark	O
'd	O
February	O
the	O
17th	O
,	O
as	O
above	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
last	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Verbeck	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Peter	B-pers
Prince	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
did	O
procure	O
two	O
Persons	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Lord	O
Nottingham	O
's	O
Office	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
false	O
Pass	O
,	O
for	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Arnoll	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Ottall	I-pers
to	O
go	O
to	O
Holland	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Evidence	O
was	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Demott	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Dutchman	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Verbeck	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
pass	O
for	O
two	O
poor	O
Dutchmen	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
beyond	O
Sea	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
John	O
Arnoll	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
five	O
Shillings	O
paid	O
him	O
as	O
a	O
Reward	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
returned	O
half	O
of	O
it	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
This	O
Demott	O
went	O
first	O
to	O
the	O
Spanish	O
Embassador	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Woman	O
who	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
Acquaintance	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
pass	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
went	O
to	O
under	O
Secretary	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
that	O
would	O
be	O
sufficient	O
without	O
another	O
from	O
the	O
Earl	O
of	O
Nottingham	O
,	O
with	O
another	O
Man	O
,	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Mowsal	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Dutchman	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
William	O
Ortall	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
paid	O
him	O
by	O
Verbeck	O
for	O
so	O
doing	O
.	O
Arnoll	O
declared	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
agreed	O
with	O
Verbeck	O
,	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
3	O
Guineas	O
for	O
the	O
Pass	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
part	O
with	O
it	O
under	O
a	O
Luadore	O
more	O
,	O
adding	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
10l	O
.	O
for	O
it	O
before	O
Night	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Arnoll	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Ottall	O
went	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Harwich	O
with	O
the	O
said	O
Pass	O
,	O
but	O
were	O
stopt	O
there	O
by	O
a	O
Messenger	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
back	O
,	O
they	O
being	O
the	O
wrong	O
persons	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
those	O
who	O
went	O
to	O
Whitehall	O
for	O
the	O
Pass	O
.	O
Verbeck	O
made	O
a	O
long	O
Story	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
to	O
no	O
purpose	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
did	O
not	O
so	O
nearly	O
affect	O
Prince	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
but	O
Verbeck	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
a	O
Cheat	O
.	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Bentley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Geldings	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
George	B-place
Inn	I-place
Stable	I-place
in	I-place
Smithfield	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Horses	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Stable	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Bell	O
Inn	O
and	O
no	O
further	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
Difference	O
between	O
them	O
about	O
a	O
Debt	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
owed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
formerly	O
arrested	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Horses	O
were	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
;	O
so	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
found	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
Feloneous	O
Intent	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
black	O
Stone	O
Horse	O
,	O
value	O
5l	O
.	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Gladwell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
made	O
out	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Horse	O
honestly	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
immediately	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
and	O
Daniel	B-pers
Kirkham	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
the	O
Play-House	B-place
in	I-place
Salisbury-Court	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
abundance	O
of	O
Silver	O
and	O
Gold	O
Lace	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
produced	O
that	O
could	O
charge	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
immediately	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
John	B-pers
Kitson	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
confest	O
in	O
Newgate	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Theodore	B-pers
Shevalier	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
,	O
for	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
Cheat	O
one	O
Daniel	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
of	O
5	O
Guineas	O
,	O
thus	O
:	O
Shevalier	O
and	O
Lewis	O
comes	O
to	O
Scott	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
Sadler	O
,	O
and	O
Lewis	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
Shevalier	O
was	O
an	O
Agent	O
under	O
Colonel	O
Cook	O
,	O
and	O
Colonel	O
Bingore	O
in	O
Ireland	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Bill	O
payable	O
in	O
the	O
Treasury	O
for	O
4000l	O
.	O
with	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
buy	O
Accouterments	O
for	O
the	O
Army	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
Sadler	O
,	O
might	O
sell	O
Saddles	O
and	O
Bridles	O
,	O
desiring	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
five	O
Guinneas	O
in	O
hand	O
as	O
a	O
Pledge	O
to	O
incourage	O
him	O
;	O
so	O
also	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Wickin	O
and	O
John	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
and	O
to	O
one	O
Apley	O
,	O
to	O
buy	O
Boots	O
and	O
Shoes	O
,	O
the	O
latter	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
to	O
make	O
all	O
the	O
Boots	O
for	O
the	O
Regiments	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
abovesiad	O
Collonels	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
receive	O
14s	O
.	O
a	O
pair	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
to	O
put	O
a	O
good	O
colour	O
upon	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
prisoners	O
gave	O
the	O
Tradesmen	O
aforesaid	O
an	O
Authority	O
under	O
Shevalier	O
's	O
hand	O
to	O
make	O
up	O
Goods	O
for	O
the	O
Life	O
of	O
the	O
Regiments	O
in	O
Ireland	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
they	O
gave	O
Bond	O
of	O
performance	O
of	O
the	O
Covenants	O
made	O
between	O
them	O
.	O
Lewis	O
declared	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
any	O
Trick	O
in	O
the	O
Matter	O
;	O
Shevalier	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
surprised	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
wherein	O
he	O
would	O
prove	O
himself	O
to	O
be	O
really	O
an	O
Agent	O
to	O
the	O
Persons	O
abovesaid	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
granted	O
.	O
Owen	B-pers
Lavendar	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
In	O
saying	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Ministers	O
of	O
Scotland	O
ought	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
Deprived	O
of	O
their	O
benefices	O
,	O
though	O
they	O
refused	O
to	O
Pray	O
for	O
King	O
William	O
and	O
Queen	O
Mary	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
our	O
lawful	O
King	O
and	O
Queen	O
that	O
the	O
clergy	O
of	O
England	O
deserved	O
to	O
be	O
Hang	O
'd	O
and	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
because	O
they	O
had	O
sworn	O
Fidelity	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
that	O
he	O
spoke	O
the	O
words	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
remember	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
said	O
any	O
such	O
words	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Male	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
Sympson	I-pers
,	O
two	O
Silver	O
Cups	O
,	O
value	O
3l	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
Evidenced	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
one	O
Cup	O
which	O
he	O
bought	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hambleton	I-pers
(	O
before	O
Tryed	O
)	O
and	O
he	O
called	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
honestly	O
by	O
the	O
Cup	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Biggs	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
James	B-pers
Whitney	I-pers
not	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
a	O
Gelding	O
coloured	O
Bay	O
,	O
price	O
8l	O
.	O
from	O
George	B-pers
Barnsley	I-pers
.	O
He	O
confest	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
Horse	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
James	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Earsel	O
and	O
Old	O
Mobb	O
(	O
before	O
Tryed	O
)	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
one	O
Reynolds	O
who	O
swore	O
against	O
him	O
(	O
viz	O
.	O
)	O
that	O
they	O
stole	O
the	O
gelding	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Grounds	O
on	O
the	O
back-side	O
of	O
Newington	B-place
Greene	I-place
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Mare	O
coloured	O
Bay	O
,	O
price	O
4l	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Grounds	O
near	O
Newington	B-place
Green	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
confest	O
before	O
the	O
same	O
Justice	O
abovesaid	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cripps	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Farmer	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
one	O
Smock	O
,	O
value	O
7s	O
.	O
a	O
Silk	O
Pettycoat	O
,	O
value	O
3s	O
.	O
and	O
an	O
Amber	O
Necklace	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
Second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
five	O
Holland	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
40s	O
.	O
two	O
Guineas	O
,	O
some	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
and	O
28l	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
swore	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
lived	O
some	O
time	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
Money	O
oftentimes	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
positively	O
charge	O
it	O
upon	O
her	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
Evidence	O
,	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
only	O
suppositions	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Richowey	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Anne	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
came	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
Discharged	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Sparks	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Downing	I-pers
were	O
both	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Parkinson	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Minories	B-place
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Curtains	O
and	O
Vallens	O
,	O
value	O
30s	O
.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
forty	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Feathers	O
,	O
a	O
Looking	O
glass	O
.	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Chamber	O
was	O
let	O
to	O
them	O
by	O
the	O
Week	O
,	O
for	O
two	O
Shillings	O
per	O
Week	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
;	O
so	O
the	O
Court	O
being	O
divided	O
in	O
their	O
Opinion	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
point	O
of	O
Law	O
,	O
the	O
matter	O
was	O
left	O
to	O
a	O
Special	O
Verdict	O
,	O
till	O
further	O
consideration	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
only	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
taking	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
such	O
another	O
offence	O
,	O
in	O
Robbing	O
Lucy	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Whitechappel	B-place
,	O
of	O
a	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
7s.	O
,	O
two	O
Feather	O
Pillows	O
and	O
a	O
Cubbord	O
cloth	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
They	O
came	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
manner	O
to	O
Pages	O
as	O
they	O
did	O
to	O
Parkinson	O
,	O
and	O
hired	O
a	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
lived	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
likewise	O
left	O
to	O
a	O
Special	O
Verdict	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
6l	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Rowel	I-pers
,	O
which	O
she	O
confest	O
since	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
how	O
that	O
she	O
lodged	O
at	O
Rowels	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
four	O
days	O
time	O
she	O
watched	O
where	O
Mrs.	O
Rowel	O
laid	O
her	O
Key	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
and	O
unlocked	O
the	O
Cupboard	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
away	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Salt	O
,	O
value	O
4l	O
.	O
15s	O
.	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Dimsdale	I-pers
in	O
October	O
last	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
likewise	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
seeing	O
the	O
Salt	O
in	O
the	O
Buttery	O
,	O
said	O
in	O
the	O
hearing	O
of	O
some	O
Persons	O
,	O
That	O
there	O
was	O
but	O
one	O
thing	O
that	O
she	O
likt	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Salt	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
after	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
and	O
made	O
her	O
escape	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
the	O
salt	O
was	O
missing	O
;	O
she	O
owned	O
it	O
when	O
taxed	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
given	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
denyed	O
it	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
looked	O
upon	O
as	O
a	O
very	O
ill	O
Woman	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomasin	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
B	O
,	O
an	O
Old	O
Offender	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Hern	I-pers
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
September	O
,	O
a	O
Serge	O
Mantua	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
6s	O
.	O
a	O
Drugget	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
6s	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
to	O
Cheapen	O
some	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
Blake	O
put	O
the	O
Gown	O
into	O
her	O
Pettycoat	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
denyed	O
stifly	O
so	O
did	O
Williams	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
conclusion	O
,	O
Blake	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
but	O
Williams	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Barret	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Southwood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
of	O
a	O
Serge	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
10d	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
whilst	O
his	O
back	O
was	O
turned	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Coat	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Coat	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
but	O
Southwood	O
was	O
positive	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
his	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
Bower	I-pers
were	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Ingleton	B-pers
Kelson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
7s	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
set	O
upon	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
near	O
the	O
Savoy	B-place
by	O
some	O
Soldiers	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
George	O
Bird	O
Knockt	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Rings	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
so	O
Bird	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
Wife	O
was	O
Discharged	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sha	B-pers
Plum	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
keeping	O
a	O
disorderly	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
harbouring	O
a	O
Thieves	O
.	O
One	O
Reynolds	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Thieves	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Whitney	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
were	O
wont	O
to	O
steal	O
Horses	O
,	O
they	O
carryed	O
them	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
in	O
Chelsey	B-place
,	O
where	O
he	O
would	O
secure	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
private	O
Stable	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
put	O
in	O
the	O
Gazzet	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
owned	O
that	O
they	O
brought	O
horses	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
stole	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
further	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
sit	O
up	O
Nights	O
to	O
receive	O
the	O
Horses	O
when	O
the	O
Robbers	O
came	O
back	O
from	O
Robbing	O
of	O
Wagons	O
and	O
Coaches	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
they	O
gave	O
him	O
forty	O
shillings	O
for	O
sitting	O
up	O
one	O
Night	O
above	O
all	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
liberty	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
choice	O
of	O
the	O
Booty	O
:	O
But	O
after	O
all	O
this	O
,	O
he	O
produced	O
several	O
Substantial	O
and	O
Credible	O
Persons	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
his	O
Neighbours	O
to	O
vindicate	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
which	O
gave	O
the	O
Jury	O
such	O
satisfaction	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Traps	I-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
in	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
born	O
in	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
was	O
made	O
a	O
Seminary	O
Priest	O
of	O
the	O
Authority	O
of	O
the	O
See	O
of	O
Rome	O
,	O
in	O
parts	O
beyond	O
the	O
sea	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
afterwards	O
convey	O
himself	O
over	O
into	O
England	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
did	O
Traiterously	O
abide	O
,	O
contrary	O
to	O
the	O
Laws	O
of	O
the	O
Kingdom	O
of	O
England	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Chamber	O
at	O
a	O
suspected	O
Popish	O
Meeting	O
House	O
in	O
St.	O
James's-street	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
seized	O
with	O
several	O
Latin	O
Books	O
,	O
a	O
Cross	O
with	O
the	O
figure	O
of	O
Christ	O
,	O
several	O
Priestly	O
Vestments	O
and	O
other	O
Trinkets	O
,	O
as	O
Crucifixes	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
seen	O
to	O
officiate	O
as	O
a	O
Priest	O
,	O
so	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
found	O
Guilty	O
upon	O
that	O
Indictment	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
discharged	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Rickowbey	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rickowbey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	O
Himself	O
were	O
Arraigned	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
together	O
with	O
Sarah	B-pers
White	I-pers
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
from	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Goswick	I-pers
a	O
Silver	O
Cane	O
,	O
value	O
20s	O
,	O
and	O
15s	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
:	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
they	O
were	O
discharged	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Stables	O
of	O
one	O
Cundit	B-pers
,	O
near	O
adjoining	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Doctor	O
Cornelius	B-pers
Tilburn	I-pers
in	O
Covent-Garden	B-place
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Cloak	O
,	O
value	O
4l	O
.	O
10s	O
.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
value	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
could	O
not	O
charge	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
particularly	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Westminster	B-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
watch	O
with	O
a	O
Silver	O
Case	O
,	O
from	O
Henry	B-pers
Lankton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
Lodger	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Lankton	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Watch	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
the	O
Cicilian	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
gave	O
her	O
her	O
the	O
watch	O
to	O
pawn	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
:	O
and	O
she	O
confest	O
,	O
when	O
taken	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Ward	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
besides	O
she	O
absented	O
from	O
her	O
Lodging	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
9s	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Thomas	B-pers
Woolley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
.	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
two	O
laced	O
Cornets	O
,	O
value	O
28s	O
.	O
a	O
laced	O
Crevat	O
,	O
value	O
30s	O
.	O
a	O
Smock	O
and	O
a	O
Pinner	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
She	O
,	O
with	O
another	O
Woman	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
Woolleys	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
the	O
Pinner	O
she	O
sold	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Katherine-Wheel-Inn	O
:	O
she	O
had	O
confest	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
but	O
denyed	O
it	O
at	O
her	O
Tryal	O
,	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
that	O
was	O
material	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
of	O
Whitechappel	B-place
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
4l	O
.	O
five	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
value	O
15s	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bowen	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
Bowens	O
House	O
in	O
Goodmans-Fields	B-place
about	O
a	O
Week	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
the	O
Tankard	O
and	O
Dishes	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
Trunk	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
hasp	O
of	O
the	O
Trunk	O
was	O
forced	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Staple	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
alledged	O
that	O
Bowen	O
had	O
several	O
Lodgers	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
besides	O
her	O
who	O
might	O
take	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
contradicted	O
by	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
added	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
Leaden-hall	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
made	O
her	O
escape	O
,	O
being	O
very	O
unwilling	O
to	O
own	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
B	B-pers
-	I-pers
J	I-pers
-	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
Was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
wilful	O
Murther	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
Wife	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
J	I-pers
-	I-pers
on	O
the	O
18th	O
Day	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
before	O
the	O
Tryal	O
proceeded	O
a	O
fresh	O
Jury	O
of	O
Gentlemen	O
were	O
Empannel	O
'd	O
,	O
whose	O
Names	O
are	O
these	O
:	O
Edward	B-pers
Knowls	I-pers
John	B-pers
Milner	I-pers
William	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
William	B-pers
Dinn	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Bealing	I-pers
Gilbert	B-pers
Wharton	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Drumfeild	I-pers
John	B-pers
Outting	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Longland	I-pers
John	B-pers
Burchet	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Young	I-pers
.	O
After	O
the	O
Jury	O
were	O
Sworn	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceded	O
to	O
a	O
distinct	O
Tryal	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
being	O
called	O
on	O
the	O
Kings	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
Sworn	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
at	O
which	O
was	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Godman	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Wife	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
at	O
Kensington	O
for	O
about	O
the	O
space	O
of	O
5	O
Weeks	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
of	O
which	O
time	O
,	O
she	O
observed	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
Melancholy	O
till	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
the	O
Murther	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
Morning	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Dead	O
;	O
she	O
declared	O
to	O
her	O
Landlady	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Godman	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
family	O
after	O
Supper	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
over	O
Night	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
had	O
sent	O
for	O
her	O
into	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
Street	O
,	O
about	O
7	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
should	O
not	O
come	O
home	O
that	O
Night	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
Morrow	O
Morning	O
about	O
Six	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
Men	O
found	O
her	O
lying	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Kensington	B-place
,	I-place
near	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
exposed	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
undecent	O
manner	O
,	O
her	O
Coats	O
turn	O
'd	O
up	O
,	O
her	O
Hand	O
all	O
bloody	O
,	O
lying	O
upon	O
her	O
Thigh	O
,	O
her	O
Throat	O
cut	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
her	O
Breast	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Mortal	O
wound	O
under	O
her	O
left	O
Ear	O
,	O
her	O
Face	O
covered	O
over	O
with	O
Blood	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
a	O
Case	O
knife	O
,	O
valu	O
'd	O
1d	O
.	O
lying	O
betwixt	O
her	O
Face	O
and	O
her	O
Hood	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
most	O
horrible	O
amazing	O
,	O
and	O
most	O
frightful	O
manner	O
,	O
with	O
her	O
Body	O
luke-warm	O
:	O
After	O
the	O
Murther	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
the	O
Woman	O
was	O
found	O
Dead	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
Swore	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
walking	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
a	O
Field	O
in	O
the	O
Grass	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Path-way	O
,	O
near	O
whereto	O
the	O
dead	O
Corps	O
lay	O
,	O
throwing	O
his	O
hands	O
abroad	O
,	O
Sighing	O
,	O
lamenting	O
,	O
and	O
bemoaning	O
himself	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
most	O
distracted	O
manner	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
verily	O
believed	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
matter	O
of	O
15	O
Rood	O
off	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Brother	O
,	O
one	O
Mr	O
Willis	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
found	O
him	O
out	O
acquainted	O
him	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
Wife	O
lay	O
Murthered	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
place	O
,	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
he	O
seemed	O
not	O
so	O
much	O
affected	O
as	O
might	O
be	O
expected	O
,	O
shuffling	O
himself	O
off	O
from	O
them	O
,	O
by	O
pretending	O
earnest	O
Business	O
else-where	O
,	O
desiring	O
his	O
Brother	O
to	O
seek	O
after	O
the	O
Destroyer	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
not	O
willing	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
hard	O
by	O
,	O
where	O
his	O
Mother	O
sending	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
perswaded	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
before-hand	O
ingeniously	O
promising	O
to	O
return	O
immediately	O
again	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
so	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
Justice	O
of	O
Peace	O
's	O
Warrant	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
found	O
him	O
at	O
his	O
Fathers	O
House	O
lock	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
;	O
his	O
Mother	O
denying	O
of	O
him	O
at	O
their	O
first	O
entrance	O
;	O
being	O
apprehended	O
,	O
his	O
Fingers	O
were	O
found	O
cut	O
,	O
his	O
Cravat	O
stained	O
with	O
two	O
spots	O
of	O
Blood	O
,	O
he	O
walking	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
the	O
Room	O
without	O
his	O
Hat	O
:	O
Being	O
brought	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
examined	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Question	O
he	O
could	O
give	O
no	O
satisfactory	O
Answer	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
touching	O
his	O
cut	O
Fingers	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
but	O
a	O
frivolous	O
Account	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
That	O
a	O
Man	O
assaulted	O
him	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
Stairs	O
into	O
his	O
Chamber	O
about	O
Eleven	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
Robbed	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
thought	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
only	O
he	O
called	O
his	O
Fathers	O
Man	O
and	O
Maid	O
to	O
prove	O
what	O
time	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
the	O
Murther	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
Eleven	O
a	O
Clock	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
alone	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Maid	O
had	O
the	O
Key	O
given	O
to	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Man-servant	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
who	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
Room	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
waiting	O
upon	O
his	O
Father	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
some	O
distance	O
from	O
the	O
Chambers	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
Man	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
nor	O
speak	O
to	O
him	O
:	O
He	O
offered	O
also	O
several	O
other	O
frivolous	O
pretences	O
by	O
way	O
of	O
Extenuation	O
,	O
which	O
did	O
not	O
tend	O
at	O
all	O
to	O
his	O
Advantage	O
.	O
So	O
after	O
about	O
Four	O
Hours	O
fair	O
hearing	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
well	O
considered	O
,	O
gave	O
in	O
their	O
Verdict	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Wilfull	O
Murther	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Christian	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Neclace	O
of	O
Pearle	O
,	O
value	O
10l	O
.	O
some	O
Table-Linnen	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
22	O
.	O
Napkings	O
,	O
14	O
Cambrick	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
Septemb	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Pearle	O
Necklace	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Christopher	B-pers
Ashley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Arraigned	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
:	O
The	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
:	O
the	O
second	O
for	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
one	O
Nath	B-pers
.	I-pers
Piggot	I-pers
,	O
to	O
both	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Redman	I-pers
was	O
called	O
to	O
answer	O
to	O
an	O
Indictment	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
committed	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
in	O
printing	O
a	O
Seditious	O
Libel	O
Intituled	O
,	O
An	O
Office	O
for	O
Penitents	O
;	O
or	O
,	O
A	O
Form	O
of	O
Prayer	O
,	O
fit	O
to	O
be	O
used	O
in	O
Sinful	O
and	O
distressed	O
Times	O
.	O
The	O
Book	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
by	O
Robert	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
the	O
King	O
's	O
Messenger	O
,	O
and	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
;	O
being	O
examined	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
him	O
by	O
a	O
Stranger	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
own	O
who	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
Fined	O
100	O
Marks	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Boy	O
,	O
Convicted	O
last	O
Sessions	O
for	O
Publishing	O
the	O
two	O
Libels	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
Intitled	O
The	O
Triming	O
Court	O
Divine	O
;	O
the	O
second	O
about	O
the	O
late	O
Lord	O
Russels	O
's	O
Ghost	O
,	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
set	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
intent	O
of	O
his	O
Sentence	O
last	O
Sessions	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
gave	O
Sentence	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
8	O
.	O
Bernard	O
Clark	O
,	O
Roger	O
Harry	O
Young	O
,	O
Philip	O
Harper	O
,	O
Francis	O
Pelling	O
,	O
Joseph	O
Stykes	O
,	O
alias	O
Smith	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Aldridge	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Smith	O
and	O
Margaret	O
Ellis	O
To	O
be	O
transported	O
1	O
.	O
William	O
Davis	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
12	O
.	O
Christopher	O
Ashley	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Eaton	O
,	O
Edgerton	O
Brett	O
,	O
B-	O
J-	O
,	O
Edward	O
Biggs	O
,	O
Matthew	O
Earsell	O
,	O
Old	O
Mobb	O
,	O
Lawrence	O
Dadson	O
,	O
H	O
-	O
M	O
-	O
,	O
B	O
-	O
T	O
-	O
,	O
George	O
Bird	O
and	O
Elizabeth	O
Jones	O
.	O
B	O
-	O
T	O
-	O
for	O
Clipping	O
,	O
was	O
sentenced	O
to	O
be	O
drawn	O
on	O
a	O
Sledge	O
to	O
Tyburn	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
to	O
be	O
Hanged	O
only	O
and	O
not	O
Quartered	O
.	O
H	O
-	O
M-	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Treasonable	O
Fact	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Burnt	O
.	O
Robert	O
Trumball	O
and	O
Robert	O
Adderton	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
convicted	O
last	O
Sessions	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	O
Thornycroft	O
's	O
Shop	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
were	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Executed	O
with	O
those	O
who	O
are	O
to	O
suffer	O
this	O
Sessions	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
10	O
.	O
Gregory	O
Carrick	O
,	O
Elinor	O
Fox	O
,	O
Mary	O
Thinn	O
,	O
Lewis	O
L'Roach	O
,	O
V-	O
J	O
-	O
,	O
Margaret	O
Swanson	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Cripps	O
,	O
John	O
Williams	O
,	O
Thomasin	O
Blake	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	O
Smith	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Banks	I-pers
gave	O
Bail	O
to	O
bring	O
in	O
his	O
Pardon	O
in	O
course	O
next	O
Sessions	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Boy	O
,	O
Convicted	O
last	O
Sessions	O
for	O
Publishing	O
the	O
two	O
Libels	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
Intitled	O
The	O
Triming	O
Court	O
Divine	O
;	O
the	O
second	O
about	O
the	O
late	O
Lord	O
Russels	O
's	O
Ghost	O
,	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
set	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
intent	O
of	O
his	O
Sentence	O
last	O
Sessions	O
.	O
James	O
Verbeck	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
set	O
by	O
the	O
Pillory	O
,	O
once	O
at	O
Charing-Cross	O
,	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
at	O
the	O
May-Pole	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
pay	O
5l	O
.	O
as	O
a	O
Fine	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
committed	O
till	O
all	O
be	O
performed	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Redman	I-pers
was	O
called	O
to	O
answer	O
to	O
an	O
Indictment	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
committed	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
in	O
printing	O
a	O
Seditious	O
Libel	O
Intituled	O
,	O
An	O
Office	O
for	O
Penitents	O
;	O
or	O
,	O
A	O
Form	O
of	O
Prayer	O
,	O
fit	O
to	O
be	O
used	O
in	O
Sinful	O
and	O
distressed	O
Times	O
.	O
The	O
Book	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
by	O
Robert	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
the	O
King	O
's	O
Messenger	O
,	O
and	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
;	O
being	O
examined	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
him	O
by	O
a	O
Stranger	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
own	O
who	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
Fined	O
100	O
Marks	O
.	O
One	O
Thomas	B-pers
Franks	I-pers
,	O
who	O
at	O
Cambridge	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Father	O
Francis	O
a	O
Priest	O
,	O
moved	O
for	O
a	O
Discharge	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
continued	O
to	O
answer	O
the	O
Charge	O
that	O
shall	O
be	O
brought	O
against	O
him	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
Likewise	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Roe	I-pers
,	O
accused	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
gave	O
sufficient	O
Sureties	O
to	O
appear	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
Philip	O
Harper	O
found	O
Sureties	O
for	O
his	O
Good	O
Behaviour	O
.	O
One	O
Daniel	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
bound	O
over	O
by	O
his	O
Wife	O
for	O
beating	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
was	O
Discharged	O
by	O
his	O
Wives	O
consent	O
,	O
promising	O
in	O
Court	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
kind	O
to	O
her	O
for	O
the	O
time	O
to	O
come	O
.	O
One	O
Richard	B-pers
Cuts	I-pers
,	O
charged	O
upon	O
Suspition	O
of	O
Murthering	O
his	O
Wife	O
in	O
Wiltshire	O
near	O
Malborow	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
found	O
with	O
her	O
Neck	O
and	O
her	O
Arms	O
broken	O
in	O
a	O
most	O
Barbarous	O
manner	O
,	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
thither	O
to	O
be	O
Tryed	O
for	O
the	O
Fact	O
at	O
the	O
next	O
assizes	O
held	O
for	O
that	O
County	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Grabee	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Wilmot	I-pers
,	O
with	O
others	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
Riot	O
lately	O
made	O
in	O
White-Fryers	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
remain	O
till	O
next	O
Sessions	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
on	O
the	O
Kings-side	O
being	O
not	O
all	O
in	O
a	O
readiness	O
to	O
attend	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
.	O
Walter	B-pers
Strickland	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
who	O
were	O
Tryed	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
the	O
Watch-man	O
in	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
Sued	O
their	O
Majesties	O
most	O
Gracious	O
Pardon	O
might	O
be	O
allowed	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
presented	O
in	O
Court	O
;	O
but	O
because	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
obtained	O
a	O
Writ	O
of	O
Allowance	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
obstructed	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
off	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
ensuing	O
Sessions	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
likewise	O
moved	O
to	O
have	O
her	O
Pardon	O
allowed	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
obtain	O
it	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
a	O
Writ	O
of	O
Allowance	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
ADVERTISMENTS	O
The	O
Second	O
Volume	O
of	O
the	O
Athenian	O
Mercury	O
,	O
(	O
is	O
now	O
Published	O
)	O
Resolvinmg	O
all	O
the	O
most	O
Nice	O
and	O
Curious	O
Questions	O
,	O
proposed	O
by	O
the	O
Ingenious	O
of	O
Either	O
Sex	O
,	O
from	O
Saturday	O
,	O
May	O
the	O
30th	O
,	O
to	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
August	O
the	O
18th	O
,	O
1691	O
.	O
Price	O
2s	O
.	O
d.	O
This	O
Second	O
Volume	O
is	O
neatly	O
done	O
in	O
Marble	O
Paper	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
general	O
Title	O
and	O
Index	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Preface	O
,	O
containing	O
Rules	O
for	O
our	O
Quevises	O
constantly	O
to	O
observe	O
in	O
their	O
Writing	O
to	O
us	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
John	O
Dunton	O
at	O
the	O
Raven	O
in	O
the	O
Poultrey	O
,	O
where	O
are	O
to	O
be	O
had	O
and	O
Second	O
Volumes	O
of	O
the	O
Athenian	O
Mercury	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
supplement	O
to	O
beginning	O
March	O
the	O
ust	O
the	O
18	O
th	O
,	O
containing	O
Printed	O
in	O
England	O
Foreign	O
Europe	O
Journal	O
the	O
Affairs	O
with	O
Reflections	O
Maxims	O
of	O
State	O
of	O
Princes	O
and	O
State	O
with	O
reflections	O
on	O
the	O
present	O
War	O
and	O
Confe	O
well	O
approv	O
'd	O
of	O
by	O
the	O
Learned	O
Published	O
every	O
other	O
Saturday	O
in	O
at	O
St.	O
Edmondbury	O
Godfrey	O
's	O
Head	O
The	O
16th	O
Journal	O
will	O
be	O
published	O
on	O
Saturady	O
next	O
.	O
All	O
Gentleman	O
and	O
Ladies	O
that	O
desire	O
to	O
speak	O
Latin	O
or	O
French	O
fluently	O
and	O
that	O
truly	O
and	O
properly	O
according	O
to	O
Grammar	O
Rules	O
,	O
and	O
but	O
spare	O
of	O
hors	O
a	O
Week	O
,	O
may	O
be	O
faithfully	O
taught	O
in	O
one	O
Year	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Switerda	O
,	O
at	O
his	O
Lodging	O
in	O
Clements-Lane	O
,	O
near	O
Canon-street	O
,	O
over	O
against	O
the	O
Church	O
Tuesdays	O
,	O
Thursdays	O
,	O
and	O
Saturdays	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
High-Holbourn	O
,	O
near	O
Little	O
Turn-stile	O
,	O
near	O
to	O
the	O
Falcon	O
,	O
at	O
Mrs	O
Clark	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
Mondays	O
,	O
Wednesdays	O
,	O
and	O
Fridays	O
;	O
where	O
you	O
may	O
have	O
French	O
and	O
Latin	O
,	O
Grammatical	O
and	O
intorical	O
Cards	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
he	O
has	O
taught	O
Children	O
of	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
years	O
old	O
to	O
speak	O
Latin	O
and	O
French	O
:	O
And	O
such	O
as	O
please	O
,	O
may	O
be	O
Attended	O
at	O
their	O
own	O
Habitations	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
to	O
give	O
Notice	O
to	O
all	O
Persons	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
the	O
Publick	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Elmy	O
,	O
Professor	O
of	O
Physick	O
,	O
and	O
Operator	O
of	O
known	O
Integrity	O
,	O
and	O
above	O
25	O
Years	O
Practice	O
,	O
Liveth	O
at	O
the	O
Blue	O
Ball	O
in	O
Whale-Bone-Court	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Lower	O
End	O
of	O
Bartholomew-Lane	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
who	O
most	O
safely	O
,	O
and	O
expeditiously	O
Cures	O
deafness	O
and	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
Ears	O
in	O
any	O
of	O
what	O
Age	O
soever	O
,	O
(	O
if	O
Curable	O
)	O
and	O
at	O
first	O
Sight	O
,	O
by	O
Inspection	O
,	O
Resolves	O
the	O
Patient	O
if	O
so	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
as	O
most	O
Eminent	O
Persons	O
of	O
Quality	O
in	O
this	O
City	O
can	O
Testifie	O
.	O
He	O
hath	O
likewise	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Gargarism	O
or	O
Mouth-Water	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
make	O
black	O
or	O
yellow	O
Teeth	O
as	O
White	O
as	O
Ivory	O
,	O
in	O
few	O
times	O
using	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
will	O
certainly	O
Cure	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
Diseases	O
incident	O
to	O
the	O
Mouth	O
,	O
Teeth	O
and	O
Gums	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
.	O
His	O
Pills	O
only	O
prepared	O
for	O
the	O
French	O
Disease	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Running	O
of	O
the	O
Reins	O
,	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
in	O
Boxes	O
of	O
several	O
Prices	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
Venereal	O
Arcana	O
's	O
as	O
occasion	O
requires	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
.	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
Spitting	O
Drops	O
,	O
that	O
any	O
one	O
may	O
take	O
safely	O
and	O
go	O
abroad	O
after	O
,	O
they	O
powerfully	O
discharge	O
the	O
Head	O
and	O
Stomach	O
of	O
vicious	O
Humours	O
frees	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Grout	O
Dropsie	O
,	O
scurvy	O
,	O
all	O
Infection	O
Venerial	O
or	O
Mercurial	O
Physick	O
,	O
and	O
Cures	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
Pal	O
,	O
Nose	O
,	O
of	O
all	O
ulcers	O
,	O
Scabs	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
it	O
prevents	O
the	O
danger	O
of	O
Fluxing	O
.	O
He	O
hath	O
also	O
those	O
approved	O
drops	O
for	O
Cure	O
of	O
Pistulas	O
,	O
Piles	O
,	O
or	O
Hemorrhoids	O
,	O
several	O
having	O
been	O
cured	O
by	O
once	O
Applying	O
.	O
By	O
Doctor	O
Archer	O
,	O
Author	O
of	O
the	O
Book	O
called	O
Every	O
Man	O
his	O
own	O
Doector	O
:	O
Sworn	O
Physician	O
to	O
King	O
Charles	O
II	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
Spoke	O
with	O
at	O
his	O
Chamber	O
at	O
the	O
Sadlers	O
over	O
against	O
the	O
Muse	O
at	O
Charing-Cross	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Black-Horse	O
,	O
from	O
Noon	O
till	O
5	O
.	O
Evening	O
at	O
other	O
times	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
at	O
Knight	O
's	O
Bridge	O
.	O
He	O
sells	O
not	O
his	O
Drops	O
,	O
but	O
administers	O
them	O
needful	O
.	O
He	O
freely	O
gives	O
his	O
Advice	O
.	O
In	O
Plow-Yard	O
in	O
Grays-Inn-Lane	O
,	O
lives	O
Dr.	O
Thomas	O
Kit	O
a	O
Collegiate	O
Physician	O
,	O
and	O
Sworn	O
Physician	O
to	O
Charles	O
II	O
.	O
Death	O
Who	O
with	O
a	O
Drink	O
and	O
Pill	O
(	O
hindering	O
no	O
Business	O
)	O
and	O
takes	O
to	O
Cure	O
any	O
Ulcers	O
,	O
Sores	O
,	O
swellings	O
in	O
the	O
Nose	O
,	O
Face	O
,	O
or	O
other	O
parts	O
,	O
Scabs	O
,	O
Itch	O
,	O
Scarss	O
,	O
Exprosies	O
,	O
and	O
Venereal	O
Disease	O
,	O
expecting	O
nothing	O
until	O
the	O
cure	O
be	O
finished	O
.	O
Of	O
the	O
last	O
,	O
he	O
hath	O
cured	O
many	O
hundred	O
in	O
this	O
City	O
,	O
many	O
of	O
them	O
after	O
Fluxing	O
,	O
which	O
carries	O
the	O
evil	O
from	O
the	O
lower	O
parts	O
to	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
distress	O
many	O
.	O
The	O
Drink	O
is	O
3s	O
.	O
the	O
Quart	O
,	O
the	O
Pint	O
1s	O
.	O
a	O
Box	O
with	O
Directions	O
,	O
a	O
better	O
purge	O
than	O
which	O
was	O
ever	O
given	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
clense	O
the	O
Body	O
al	O
Impurities	O
,	O
which	O
are	O
the	O
causes	O
of	O
Dropsies	O
,	O
Gouts	O
,	O
Scurvies	O
,	O
or	O
Gravel	O
,	O
Pains	O
in	O
the	O
Head	O
and	O
other	O
parts	O
;	O
with	O
another	O
at	O
1s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
a	O
Quart	O
,	O
he	O
cures	O
all	O
fevers	O
and	O
hot	O
Distempers	O
without	O
bleeding	O
,	O
except	O
in	O
few	O
Bodys	O
.	O
He	O
gives	O
his	O
Opinion	O
to	O
all	O
that	O
writes	O
or	O
comes	O
for	O
nothing	O
.	O
