TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
and	O
Queens	O
Commissions	O
OF	O
THE	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
and	O
Monday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
7th	O
,	O
8th	O
,	O
9th	O
,	O
10th	O
and	O
12th	O
Day	O
of	O
December	O
1692	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
Fourth	O
Year	O
of	O
Their	O
MAJESTIES	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
and	O
Monday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
7th	O
,	O
8th	O
,	O
9th	O
,	O
10th	O
and	O
12th	O
Days	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
1692.	O
before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fleet	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
Salathiel	B-pers
Lovewell	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
follows	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Trentar	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Roome	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Plaisted	I-pers
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
.	O
Nathanael	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Stretton	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Symmons	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Goudge	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Haynes	I-pers
.	O
George	B-pers
Hawson	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Bealing	I-pers
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Fuller	I-pers
.	O
Timothy	B-pers
Thornbury	I-pers
.	O
Simon	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Gerrald	I-pers
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Wade	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lathwell	I-pers
.	O
George	B-pers
Poulfrey	I-pers
.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Cooke	I-pers
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Weckes	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
these	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
in	O
Ironmonger-Lane	B-place
;	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
;	O
The	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
on	O
a	O
Sunday	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
in	O
Sermon-time	O
,	O
whilst	O
Mr.	O
Reynolds	O
's	O
Servants	O
were	O
at	O
Church	O
,	O
and	O
Ransack	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Scarf	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
one	O
Gold	O
Ear-Ring	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
one	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
150	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
seen	O
hovering	O
about	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
Granger	O
,	O
a	O
Criminal	O
,	O
was	O
brought	O
into	O
Court	O
from	O
Newgate	O
,	O
who	O
owned	O
that	O
he	O
himself	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
others	O
concerned	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
about	O
seven	O
;	O
(	O
viz	O
.	O
)	O
one	O
Snelling	O
,	O
one	O
Wood	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Paul	B-pers
Groves	I-pers
,	O
besides	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
White	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
who	O
are	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Davis	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
had	O
5	O
l.	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
to	O
his	O
share	O
;	O
all	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
strived	O
to	O
invalidate	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
no	O
purpose	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Low	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Adderton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
Ralph	B-pers
Springall	I-pers
in	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Cloath-Coat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
met	O
the	O
said	O
Springall	O
in	O
Woodstreet	B-place
with	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
his	O
Mother	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
a	O
Link	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Persons	O
were	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
all	O
drew	O
their	O
Swords	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
snatch	O
'd	O
the	O
Coat	O
off	O
Spingall	O
's	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
along	O
Friday-street	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
stopt	O
by	O
the	O
Watch	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
wounded	O
Springall	O
in	O
the	O
Trunk	O
of	O
his	O
Body	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
desperate	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
the	O
woman	O
thrust	O
the	O
Link	O
in	O
his	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
intention	O
to	O
rob	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Coat	O
was	O
presently	O
found	O
again	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Merridith	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
taking	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Walking-Cane	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Christopher	I-place
's	I-place
Church	I-place
in	O
London	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
presently	O
afterwards	O
;	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
Parnell	B-pers
Brandon	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Crove	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Riggs	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
from	O
Charles	B-pers
Pynches	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Gregories	I-place
Parish	I-place
,	O
London	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
day	O
of	O
November	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
Pynche	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
Drink	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
staid	O
awhile	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Tankard	O
.	O
Brandon	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Brown	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
her	O
self	O
took	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
yet	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Clever	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Head-dress	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
3	O
yards	O
of	O
Bone-Lace	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
Muslin	O
Cornet	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
;	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Washer-woman	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Harper	I-pers
,	O
from	O
whom	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
plainly	O
proved	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Neale	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Soldier	O
of	O
Islington	B-place
,	O
was	O
tried	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Silver	B-pers
Fitz	I-pers
Gerrald	I-pers
,	O
Hugh	B-pers
Bowen	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Crawly	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
rob	O
John	B-pers
Lacey	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
High-way	O
,	O
on	O
Bartholomew	O
Day	O
last	O
,	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
l.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Diamond	O
Pendants	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
l.	O
a	O
Point	O
Crevat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
a	O
Silk	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Flanders-Laced	O
Nightrayle	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
a	O
Strip	O
'd	O
Stuff	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Cloak	O
20	O
s.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Lacy	O
(	O
and	O
others	O
)	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Maid	O
,	O
were	O
passing	O
home	O
in	O
his	O
Coach	O
to	O
Tatnam-high-Cross	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
beyond	O
Islington	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
set	O
upon	O
by	O
several	O
High-way	O
men	O
about	O
eight	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
who	O
stopt	O
his	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Horses	O
,	O
and	O
led	O
them	O
away	O
into	O
a	O
Field	O
adjacent	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
;	O
amongst	O
which	O
Robbers	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
Mackguire	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
transported	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
since	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Fact	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
his	O
ingenuous	O
Confession	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
was	O
at	O
present	O
respited	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
were	O
positive	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Thieves	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Lacey	O
swore	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
more	O
opportunity	O
to	O
observe	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
chiefest	O
amongst	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
personally	O
rob	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
stroke	O
him	O
over	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
some	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
elsewhere	O
when	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
;	O
the	O
matter	O
was	O
very	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Glendon	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement-Danes	I-place
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Rupert	B-pers
Kempthorne	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
wound	O
near	O
the	O
Navel	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
10	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
wound	O
he	O
died	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
in	O
general	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Kempthorne	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
Ship-Tavern	O
at	O
Temple-Bar	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
difference	O
arose	O
betweenthem	O
about	O
Latitude	O
and	O
Longitude	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Kempthorne	O
alledging	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
such	O
word	O
as	O
Longitude	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
further	O
angry	O
words	O
arose	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Glendon	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
5	O
l.	O
Piece	O
for	O
a	O
bite	O
of	O
his	O
Thumb	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
past	O
off	O
for	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
;	O
but	O
immediately	O
after	O
they	O
drew	O
their	O
Swords	O
,	O
and	O
fought	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
said	O
Kempthorne	O
received	O
the	O
wound	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
alledged	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Kempthorne	O
was	O
very	O
severe	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
threatned	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
first	O
but	O
no	O
Witness	O
could	O
confirm	O
that	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
for	O
a	O
bite	O
of	O
the	O
Thumb	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
word	O
that	O
he	O
commonly	O
used	O
in	O
a	O
jesting	O
way	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
premeditated	O
Malice	O
found	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
between	O
them	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
J	B-pers
-	I-pers
K	I-pers
-	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
was	O
likewise	O
tried	O
for	O
killing	O
one	O
Richard	B-pers
Towers	I-pers
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
wound	O
near	O
the	O
Navel	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
6	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
died	O
on	O
the	O
morrow	O
;	O
the	O
deceased	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Angel-Court	B-place
with	O
a	O
Woman	O
accidently	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
supposed	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
lewd	O
Woman	O
;	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Shirt	O
hang	O
out	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
ha	O
n't	O
put	O
up	O
your	O
Shirt	O
,	O
or	O
words	O
to	O
that	O
purpose	O
;	O
at	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
very	O
angry	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
send	O
him	O
far	O
enough	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
immediately	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
wound	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
Towers	O
struck	O
him	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
drew	O
a	O
Sword	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
none	O
could	O
prove	O
it	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
yet	O
it	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
dark	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Witness	O
saw	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
only	O
what	O
the	O
dying	O
man	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
forgave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
came	O
by	O
his	O
own	O
seeking	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
that	O
effect	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
,	O
a	O
blind	O
man	O
,	O
who	O
commonly	O
goes	O
by	O
the	O
Nickname	O
of	O
Diamond	O
Robin	O
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Curtis	I-pers
in	O
Whitechappel	B-place
.	O
He	O
came	O
a	O
begging	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Curtis	O
's	O
door	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
give	O
to	O
every	O
Beggar	O
that	O
came	O
,	O
the	O
Taxes	O
were	O
so	O
great	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
sorry	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
;	O
at	O
which	O
the	O
Beggar	O
was	O
not	O
pleased	O
,	O
but	O
called	O
him	O
Pimp	O
,	O
and	O
old	O
Rogue	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
Begging	O
staff	O
in	O
both	O
his	O
hands	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
him	O
a	O
blow	O
upon	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
near	O
to	O
his	O
left	O
Eye	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
a	O
fracture	O
in	O
the	O
Skull	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Chyrurgion	O
said	O
was	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
his	O
death	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
the	O
Blind	O
man	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
escape	O
down	O
an	O
Alley	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
suddenly	O
taken	O
;	O
other	O
Evidence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
quite	O
blind	O
,	O
but	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
play	O
at	O
Cards	O
oftentimes	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
a	O
kind	O
of	O
a	O
Rustical	O
temper	O
,	O
very	O
apt	O
to	O
abuse	O
any	O
one	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
took	O
a	O
Pen	O
and	O
Ink	O
,	O
and	O
draw	O
'd	O
the	O
form	O
of	O
a	O
Ship	O
;	O
and	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
step	O
from	O
Boat	O
to	O
Boat	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
last	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
's	O
day	O
,	O
without	O
being	O
guided	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
make	O
out	O
nothing	O
to	O
excuse	O
himself	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
very	O
frivolous	O
:	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Murther	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Rhoades	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
Samuel	B-pers
Watkinson	I-pers
of	O
divers	O
Earthen	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
China	O
Ware	O
,	O
of	O
very	O
good	O
value	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shop	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	B-place
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
admitted	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Watkinson	O
's	O
House	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Lodger	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
removing	O
to	O
another	O
Lodging	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
was	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
:	O
She	O
called	O
some	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
declared	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
very	O
careful	O
honest	O
Woman	O
in	O
times	O
past	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
might	O
be	O
mistaken	O
in	O
the	O
Ware	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
one	O
China	O
Dish	O
might	O
be	O
like	O
another	O
.	O
So	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
were	O
pleased	O
to	O
acquit	O
her	O
.	O
Grace	B-pers
Sympson	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Beaver	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Commode	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
from	O
Matthew	B-pers
Wynch	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
;	O
a	O
Crape	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
from	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Chilton	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
in	O
a	O
Blew	O
Apron	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
she	O
dropped	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
;	O
she	O
denied	O
it	O
stifly	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
insolent	O
in	O
urging	O
her	O
Innocency	O
;	O
yet	O
she	O
was	O
known	O
before	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
an	O
Idle	O
secret	O
pilfering	O
Housewife	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Ayers	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
marrying	O
two	O
Wives	O
at	O
the	O
Precinct	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Katherines	I-place
;	O
the	O
first	O
Judith	B-pers
Edmunds	I-pers
,	O
who	O
he	O
married	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
3	O
d.	O
year	O
of	O
the	O
Late	O
King	O
James	O
.	O
The	O
second	O
he	O
married	O
(	O
namely	O
Ann	B-pers
Clare	I-pers
)	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
first	O
Marriage	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
really	O
married	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Judith	O
Edmunds	O
,	O
and	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
one	O
Child	O
by	O
her	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
second	O
Marriage	O
,	O
the	O
Witness	O
swore	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
Clare	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Precinct	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
cohabited	O
together	O
,	O
which	O
Clare	O
deposed	O
in	O
Court	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
former	O
was	O
alive	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
;	O
And	O
it	O
was	O
further	O
offer	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
first	O
Wife	O
was	O
seen	O
but	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
now	O
heard	O
of	O
,	O
which	O
gave	O
great	O
suspicion	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
might	O
be	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
her	O
absconding	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Braggen	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
Tasker	I-pers
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
at	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
.	O
The	O
said	O
Tasker	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
Park	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Woman	O
with	O
another	O
Woman	O
,	O
a	O
Friend	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
Drury-Lane	B-place
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
he	O
mist	O
his	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
suspected	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
sate	O
by	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
lurch	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mark	B-pers
Hybborn	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
own	O
Father	O
James	B-pers
Hybborn	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
set	O
with	O
a	O
Turkey-Stone	O
and	O
four	O
small	O
Diamonds	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
but	O
his	O
Father	O
abovesaid	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
very	O
unwilling	O
to	O
swear	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
being	O
so	O
nearly	O
related	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
at	O
last	O
swore	O
that	O
his	O
Son	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
do	O
it	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Oliver	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
tried	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Southerland	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
day	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
one	O
Black	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
3	O
Cloth	O
Coats	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Green	O
Dragon	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Fleetstreet	O
,	O
under	O
a	O
pretence	O
to	O
drink	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
a	O
while	O
Green	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
with	O
a	O
Candle	O
in	O
a	O
Dark	O
Lanthorn	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
over	O
the	O
Houses	O
,	O
and	O
robbed	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Southerland	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
Goods	O
over	O
the	O
Houses	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Women	O
fetch	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Upon	O
which	O
the	O
Tavern-keeper	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Servants	O
,	O
having	O
suspicion	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
(	O
because	O
some	O
Neighbours	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
before	O
)	O
observed	O
their	O
Motions	O
,	O
and	O
stopping	O
them	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Dark	O
Lanthorn	O
,	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
besides	O
Chissels	O
and	O
Pick	O
lock	O
Keys	O
;	O
Green	O
said	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
given	O
him	O
by	O
a	O
strange	O
man	O
,	O
who	O
he	O
met	O
at	O
Fleet-Bridge	O
,	O
who	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
above	O
said	O
Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
never	O
came	O
:	O
this	O
was	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
fram	O
'd	O
Story	O
;	O
the	O
Woman	O
could	O
say	O
little	O
for	O
themselves	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
plain	O
;	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Green	O
:	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Williams	O
,	O
Oliver	O
:	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
of	O
Christ	B-place
Church	I-place
in	O
London	O
,	O
Taylor	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
and	O
tried	O
for	O
poysoning	O
his	O
Wife	O
Katherine	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
day	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
putting	O
white	O
Mercury	O
into	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
Ale	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
immediately	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
manner	O
of	O
his	O
doing	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
thus	O
;	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
live	O
with	O
his	O
Wife	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
appointed	O
her	O
to	O
meet	O
him	O
to	O
dine	O
together	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
King's-Arms	B-place
in	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
Legrand	I-place
,	O
he	O
would	O
needs	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Hot	O
pot	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
Brandy	O
,	O
Ale	O
,	O
Eggs	O
and	O
Sugar	O
,	O
mix	O
'd	O
together	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
not	O
warm	O
enough	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
his	O
Wife	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
warm	O
half	O
of	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
he	O
might	O
put	O
the	O
Mercury	O
into	O
the	O
remaining	O
half	O
which	O
was	O
left	O
alone	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
drank	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
up	O
Stairs	O
again	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
immediately	O
fell	O
very	O
sick	O
,	O
and	O
vomited	O
,	O
and	O
died	O
within	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
days	O
afterwards	O
;	O
she	O
taxed	O
her	O
Husband	O
with	O
it	O
presently	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
poysoned	O
her	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
replied	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
withal	O
,	O
would	O
not	O
drink	O
any	O
of	O
it	O
himself	O
.	O
The	O
Chyrurgion	O
,	O
who	O
dissectect	O
her	O
,	O
gave	O
his	O
Opinion	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Liver	O
was	O
discoloured	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Stomach	O
expoliated	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
black	O
in	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
places	O
;	O
which	O
discolouration	O
must	O
be	O
effected	O
by	O
some	O
Corrosive	O
Matter	O
thrown	O
into	O
the	O
Stomach	O
,	O
and	O
must	O
proceed	O
from	O
Poyson	O
.	O
Other	O
Witnesses	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
reported	O
to	O
have	O
had	O
more	O
affection	O
for	O
another	O
Woman	O
,	O
than	O
he	O
had	O
for	O
the	O
Deceased	O
Katharine	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
made	O
appear	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
his	O
Wife	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
ill	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
an	O
Evil	O
Tongue	O
,	O
and	O
sought	O
his	O
Ruine	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
live	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
therefore	O
she	O
had	O
out	O
of	O
spight	O
brought	O
this	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
to	O
prove	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
called	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
confirmed	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
debauched	O
woman	O
,	O
given	O
much	O
to	O
drinking	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
troubled	O
with	O
the	O
Foul	O
Disease	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
oftentimes	O
sickly	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
one	O
that	O
see	O
the	O
Poyson	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
Ale	O
;	O
so	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
drawing	O
a	O
Dray-Wheel	O
over	O
the	O
Head	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Infant	O
,	O
aged	O
about	O
8	O
Years	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Witnesses	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Dray	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
Shoe-Lane	B-place
,	O
and	O
went	O
over	O
the	O
Head	O
of	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
bleeding	O
,	O
and	O
died	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
Person	O
that	O
drove	O
the	O
Dray	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
for	O
the	O
Misfortune	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Silk	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
17	O
Pistols	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
l.	O
The	O
ShopWindow	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
about	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Pistols	O
were	O
found	O
afterwards	O
sold	O
to	O
one	O
in	O
Grays-Inn-Lane	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
heard	O
to	O
own	O
(	O
when	O
taken	O
)	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Pistols	O
in	O
Charter-house-lane	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
found	O
them	O
there	O
,	O
left	O
by	O
some	O
Thieves	O
who	O
were	O
pursued	O
upon	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
and	O
fled	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
them	O
behind	O
them	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
last	O
Sessions	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
Executed	O
(	O
viz	O
.	O
)	O
One	O
Richard	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
,	O
&	O
c.	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
tried	O
for	O
Shop-lifting	O
,	O
in	O
stealing	O
18	O
Yards	O
of	O
Muslin	O
,	O
value	O
52	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Peat	I-pers
.	O
They	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Shop	O
to	O
cheapen	O
some	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
put	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
Muslin	O
under	O
her	O
Coats	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Maid	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
stopt	O
,	O
it	O
so	O
appear	O
'd	O
.	O
Jenkins	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Askew	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
for	O
Felony	O
.	O
They	O
both	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
yet	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Earle	I-pers
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Christopher	I-place
's	I-place
Parish	I-place
,	O
London	O
,	O
a	O
Frize	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Neck-cloth	O
18	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
drink	O
at	O
Lucas	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Coat	O
hanging	O
over	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
Door	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
serve	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Star	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Star	I-pers
his	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
Osborne	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Abraham	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
without	B-place
Bishops-gate	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
120	O
Ells	O
of	O
broad	O
Alamode	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
133	O
l.	O
20	O
Ells	O
of	O
Sarsnet	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
l.	O
14	O
Yards	O
of	O
Lute	O
String	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
3	O
Spotted	O
Hoods	O
,	O
value	O
45	O
s.	O
18	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Tippets	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
14	O
s.	O
10	O
White	O
Hoods	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
16	O
other	O
Hoods	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
40	O
Yards	O
of	O
Gloth	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
4	O
Handkerchiefs	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
16	O
Muslin	O
Cornets	O
,	O
120	O
Yards	O
of	O
other	O
Lace	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
consideaable	O
value	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
hole	O
bor	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
big	O
enough	O
to	O
put	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
Hand	O
into	O
;	O
and	O
by	O
that	O
they	O
opened	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
found	O
upon	O
them	O
in	O
their	O
Lodging	O
in	O
Pye-corner	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
Bed	O
together	O
,	O
with	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Pistols	O
loaded	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
known	O
in	O
Court	O
to	O
be	O
old	O
Offenders	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Richard	O
:	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Elizabeth	O
:	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Patrick	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Hardred	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Olaves	I-place
Silver-street	I-place
,	O
one	O
Livery	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
1	O
Hood	O
,	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Bag	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
The	O
Gown	O
was	O
lost	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
,	O
Gown-keeper	O
of	O
Barber-chyrurgeon	O
's	O
Hall	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Lodging	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
Leicester-street	O
in	O
St.	O
Andrew	O
's	O
Parish	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
to	O
have	O
taken	O
the	O
Gown	O
away	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Daniel	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
of	O
White-chappel	B-place
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Tewder	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Goodmansfields	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
third	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
2	O
Silver	O
Tankards	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
1	O
Silver	O
Bowl	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Salt	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
several	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Ladle	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
2	O
Gold	O
Watches	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
240	O
pieces	O
of	O
broad	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
282	O
l.	O
180	O
Guineas	O
,	O
value	O
193	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
80	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Mr.	O
Tewder	O
swore	O
that	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Persons	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Bedside	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
most	O
desperate	O
Oaths	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
they	O
wanted	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
Money	O
they	O
must	O
have	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
particular	O
,	O
stood	O
by	O
his	O
Bed-side	O
,	O
whilest	O
the	O
others	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Doors	O
,	O
and	O
rifled	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
but	O
some	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Tewder	O
's	O
Family	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
hearing	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
cried	O
out	O
Thieves	O
;	O
they	O
made	O
their	O
escape	O
,	O
but	O
left	O
a	O
Hatchet	O
and	O
a	O
Lanthorn	O
behind	O
them	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
Goodmans	O
fields	O
,	O
being	O
dogg	O
'd	O
from	O
place	O
to	O
place	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
lay	O
hands	O
on	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
fell	O
a	O
quaking	O
and	O
trembling	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
much	O
surprized	O
;	O
but	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
and	O
whilest	O
he	O
was	O
waiting	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Constable	O
talking	O
to	O
another	O
man	O
he	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
since	O
that	O
did	O
surrender	O
himself	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
other	O
Evidence	O
that	O
said	O
he	O
went	O
formerly	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Steel	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
committed	O
about	O
four	O
Years	O
ago	O
to	O
Newgate	O
for	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
Pick-lock-keys	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Betty	O
to	O
wrinch	O
open	O
the	O
Doors	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
bail	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Bail	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
appeared	O
afterwards	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
flatly	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
endeavouring	O
by	O
them	O
to	O
invalidate	O
and	O
take	O
off	O
the	O
credit	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Tewder	O
's	O
Prosecution	O
;	O
alledging	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Tewder	O
had	O
a	O
Spite	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
given	O
them	O
Money	O
to	O
assist	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecuting	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
but	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
varied	O
in	O
their	O
Depositions	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
the	O
face	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
look	O
very	O
suspicious	O
:	O
And	O
Mr.	O
Tewder	O
had	O
Persons	O
of	O
honourable	O
Quality	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
who	O
justified	O
his	O
Reputation	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
scorn	O
'd	O
to	O
deal	O
unfair	O
with	O
any	O
Person	O
.	O
The	O
Trial	O
was	O
very	O
long	O
,	O
and	O
distinctly	O
carried	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
:	O
And	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
were	O
so	O
well	O
satisfied	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
,	O
without	O
going	O
from	O
their	O
Seats	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Stafford	I-pers
,	O
Ambrose	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elkana	B-pers
Smewin	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Robbery	O
upon	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
committed	O
upon	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
and	O
others	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
,	O
of	O
South-Mims	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
They	O
met	O
him	O
upon	O
the	O
Road	O
in	O
Mims	B-place
Wash	I-place
,	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
19	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
100	O
Yards	O
of	O
Bone-Lace	O
value	O
31	O
l.	O
which	O
Smith	O
swore	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
;	O
only	O
he	O
said	O
four	O
Men	O
robbed	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
another	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Lace	O
in	O
a	O
Box	O
in	O
Stafford	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
at	O
the	O
Black	O
Horse	O
in	O
Queen-street	O
,	O
which	O
Smith	O
owned	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
,	O
swearing	O
positively	O
to	O
the	O
Marks	O
which	O
was	O
set	O
on	O
with	O
his	O
own	O
hand	O
:	O
It	O
was	O
farther	O
deposed	O
that	O
Stafford	O
fled	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
first	O
searcht	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
escape	O
;	O
but	O
was	O
at	O
last	O
taken	O
in	O
a	O
Garret	O
in	O
Queen-street	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
George	B-pers
Kemble	I-pers
,	O
and	O
one	O
Wilder	O
were	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
are	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
Stafford	O
and	O
Wilder	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
poor	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
they	O
returned	O
again	O
they	O
got	O
all	O
new	O
Cloaths	O
presently	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
full	O
of	O
Money	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
Holland	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
knew	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
his	O
Teeth	O
were	O
out	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
Pock	O
holes	O
in	O
his	O
Face	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
him	O
very	O
well	O
again	O
.	O
Another	O
Witness	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
seven	O
Men	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
White	O
Hart	O
in	O
South	O
Mims	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Flagon	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Carriers	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
coming	O
by	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
no	O
further	O
from	O
London	O
,	O
but	O
returned	O
back	O
with	O
the	O
Carriers	O
;	O
and	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
Mile	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Town	O
they	O
commited	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
kill	O
'd	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Horses	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
700	O
s.	O
from	O
a	O
Carrier	O
out	O
of	O
1500	O
l.	O
and	O
Smewin	O
was	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
Witney	O
the	O
Captain	O
of	O
them	O
all	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
company	O
,	O
who	O
kill	O
'd	O
all	O
the	O
Horses	O
to	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
20	O
but	O
is	O
not	O
as	O
yet	O
taken	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
two	O
Led	O
Horses	O
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
very	O
clear	O
against	O
Holland	O
and	O
Smewin	O
;	O
they	O
all	O
called	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
Holland	O
called	O
a	O
Chyrurgeon	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
wont	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Administer	O
Physick	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
dress	O
a	O
Swelling	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
Breast	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
from	O
the	O
second	O
of	O
November	O
to	O
the	O
17th	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
mistaken	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
Stafford	O
's	O
Witnesses	O
spoke	O
very	O
favourably	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Horse	O
kept	O
in	O
Queen-street	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Brother	O
in	O
Worstershire	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
wont	O
to	O
reside	O
more	O
than	O
in	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
himself	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
civil	O
manner	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
another	O
man	O
Lodged	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
had	O
a	O
Box	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
he	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
Lace	O
might	O
be	O
there	O
,	O
Smewin	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
so	O
positive	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Seven	O
,	O
and	O
rid	O
upon	O
a	O
bright	O
Bay	O
Horse	O
,	O
less	O
than	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Court	O
Summ	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
Evidence	O
exactly	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
directing	O
them	O
to	O
enquire	O
fetiously	O
into	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
bring	O
in	O
a	O
Verdict	O
according	O
as	O
in	O
their	O
consciences	O
they	O
found	O
them	O
deserving	O
and	O
not	O
to	O
forget	O
how	O
pernicious	O
such	O
Offenders	O
were	O
not	O
only	O
to	O
the	O
Right	O
and	O
Property	O
of	O
any	O
particular	O
Person	O
,	O
so	O
robb	O
'd	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
the	O
Kingdom	O
in	O
general	O
.	O
The	O
Trial	O
was	O
very	O
long	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
took	O
,	O
considerable	O
time	O
before	O
they	O
agreed	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
,	O
not	O
being	O
fully	O
satisfied	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Stafford	O
's	O
Box	O
they	O
acquitted	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
Holland	O
and	O
Smewin	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
Holland	O
replied	O
,	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
from	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
dead	O
the	O
Robbery	O
would	O
be	O
discover	O
'd	O
more	O
fully	O
,	O
and	O
who	O
were	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
insinuate	O
into	O
the	O
Credit	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
so	O
far	O
as	O
to	O
make	O
them	O
have	O
a	O
good	O
Opinion	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
although	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
an	O
ill	O
Man	O
formerly	O
yet	O
he	O
was	O
innocent	O
of	O
this	O
robbery	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Harday	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pancrass	I-place
's	I-place
Parish	I-place
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
robbing	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Denzell	B-pers
Lord	I-pers
Hollis	I-pers
at	O
Highgate	B-place
,	O
carrying	O
away	O
15	O
yards	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
a	O
Mohair	O
Cushion	O
,	O
6	O
Silver	O
Forks	O
,	O
8	O
Spoons	O
,	O
one	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
4	O
Salts	O
,	O
one	O
Porringer	O
,	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Curtains	O
and	O
Vallens	O
,	O
an	O
old	O
Camblet	O
Cloke	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
positive	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Thieves	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
three	O
in	O
number	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
running	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
stopt	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
dropt	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Larrymore	I-pers
,	O
Abraham	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
two	O
Boy	O
s	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hutchins	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
another	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
set	O
with	O
a	O
Diamond	O
Stone	O
,	O
value	O
45	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sir	O
Roger	B-pers
Twisden	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Aldgate	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
day	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
;	O
The	O
woman	O
broughtthe	O
Rings	O
to	O
sell	O
at	O
a	O
Goldsmiths	O
in	O
East-Smithfield	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
stopt	O
,	O
with	O
Larrymore	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Boy	O
;	O
Turner	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
Hutchins	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
sworn	O
that	O
the	O
woman	O
was	O
a	O
person	O
of	O
ill	O
same	O
;	O
but	O
however	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
none	O
could	O
say	O
the	O
Rings	O
were	O
Mr.	O
Twisden	O
's	O
;	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
was	O
arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
from	O
Hugh	B-pers
Daniel	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Gregory	I-place
's	I-place
Parish	I-place
London	I-place
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
;	O
and	O
to	O
all	O
others	O
within	O
benefit	O
of	O
the	O
Clergy	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Rowland	B-pers
Cadman	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Cadman	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Dominico	B-pers
Burley	I-pers
of	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
one	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Crevat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
one	O
half	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
l	O
10	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
;	O
the	O
Witness	O
was	O
Burly	O
himself	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
woman	O
enticed	O
him	O
to	O
her	O
Lodging	O
in	O
Ragged-Staff	B-place
Court	I-place
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
said	O
Rowland	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
she	O
made	O
fast	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
her	O
Husband	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
seized	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
him	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
almost	O
strangled	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
pickt	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
but	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
hand	O
,	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
Burley	O
did	O
,	O
or	O
would	O
have	O
lain	O
with	O
the	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
violence	O
to	O
her	O
in	O
that	O
kind	O
;	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Ray	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
was	O
arraigned	O
for	O
robbing	O
one	O
William	B-pers
James	I-pers
in	O
St.	B-place
Bridget	I-place
's	I-place
Parish	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
two	O
Silver	O
Tankards	O
,	O
value	O
19	O
l.	O
one	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
6	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
another	O
little	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
was	O
arraigned	O
upon	O
another	O
Indictment	O
,	O
for	O
robbing	O
Edward	B-pers
Trotman	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Seat	O
of	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Nott	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Launder	I-pers
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
from	O
Symon	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bennet	I-place
Fink	I-place
;	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
valued	O
at	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
woman	O
came	O
to	O
drink	O
at	O
Brooks	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
's	O
time	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Tankard	O
;	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Latham	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
being	O
Accessary	O
to	O
Ann	B-pers
Ducker	I-pers
in	O
robbing	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Fodey	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Undershaft	I-place
,	O
of	O
4	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
28	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
;	O
which	O
Indictment	O
Ducker	O
confest	O
,	O
as	O
may	O
be	O
seen	O
in	O
this	O
Account	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
could	O
prove	O
her	O
concern	O
'd	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Rich	B-pers
.	I-pers
Blackham	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Allhallows	I-place
Barkin	I-place
,	O
60	O
yards	O
of	O
Broad	O
Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
l.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
remnant	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
List	O
found	O
at	O
a	O
Dyers	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
carried	O
some	O
Cloth	O
to	O
be	O
dy	O
'd	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
it	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Blackham	O
's	O
Remnant	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
was	O
arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Rob	B-pers
.	I-pers
Hatton	I-pers
of	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
Ludgate	O
,	O
four	O
20	O
s.	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
privily	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
coming	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wale	I-pers
of	O
Fullham	B-place
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Lympany	I-pers
in	O
the	O
same	O
Town	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
October	O
1688	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
2	O
s.	O
Mr.	O
Lympany	O
's	O
Evidence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
jump	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Lympany	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Box	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
mist	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Doors	O
were	O
fast	O
shut	O
when	O
the	O
Family	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
supposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
disturbed	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
taken	O
other	O
Goods	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Witness	O
could	O
swear	O
only	O
to	O
his	O
Voice	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
midnight	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
discharged	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
by	O
vertue	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
most	O
Gracious	O
Pardon	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Prick	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Bunworth	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Weather	O
Sheep	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Crislow	I-pers
of	O
Islington	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
;	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
that	O
the	O
Sheep	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
stopt	O
,	O
they	O
threw	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
Ditch	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Prick	O
said	O
that	O
Bunworth	O
stumbled	O
at	O
the	O
Sheep	O
in	O
the	O
Field	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
Islington	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
and	O
drank	O
a	O
Flagon	O
of	O
Beer	O
at	O
a	O
House	O
of	O
Good-fellowship	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
Story	O
availing	O
them	O
nothing	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
,	O
one	O
for	O
robbing	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
High-way	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
November	O
;	O
the	O
second	O
for	O
robbing	O
John	B-pers
Clayton	I-pers
in	O
the	O
same	O
manner	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
day	O
of	O
December	O
instant	O
:	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
met	O
Vaughan	O
between	O
High-gate	O
and	O
Islington	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Cane	O
and	O
Peruke	O
,	O
and	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
;	O
Clayton	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
robbed	O
him	O
presently	O
after	O
of	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
meeting	O
accidentally	O
with	O
Vaughan	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
his	O
Case	O
known	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
pursu	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
near	O
Pancras	O
Church	O
;	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
very	O
positive	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
robb	O
'd	O
them	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
afterwards	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
upon	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Pepper	I-pers
of	O
Chiswick	B-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Susannah	B-pers
Adshead	I-pers
in	O
the	O
day	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
two	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
27	O
s.	O
10	O
Guineas	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
7	O
half	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
French	O
Pistoles	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Adshead	O
said	O
she	O
lost	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
16	O
l.	O
and	O
upwards	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Lock	O
was	O
took	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
hung	O
upon	O
the	O
Hatch	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
shut	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
born	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
spent	O
all	O
the	O
Money	O
before	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
except	O
8	O
s.	O
4	O
d.	O
halfpenny	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
within	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
after	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
the	O
Trunk	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
Money	O
lie	O
there	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Frances	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Banister	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
tried	O
for	O
robbing	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Lawrenson	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
(	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Henry	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
of	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
3	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
2	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
17	O
s.	O
one	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
15	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
but	O
Mrs.	O
Lawrenson	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
charge	O
them	O
positively	O
;	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Chandlor	I-pers
,	O
were	O
tried	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Robert	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
not	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
from	O
Faith	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
a	O
Quilted	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
an	O
Alamode	O
Scarf	O
,	O
a	O
Muff	O
,	O
7	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Sowing	O
Silk	O
,	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
Callicoe	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
small	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
confest	O
before	O
Justice	O
Marshall	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
they	O
had	O
pawned	O
at	O
one	O
Reads	O
a	O
Broker	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
;	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
broken	O
open	O
in	O
the	O
day-time	O
,	O
whilst	O
the	O
Family	O
was	O
abroad	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Morgan	O
,	O
alias	O
Jones	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
tried	O
singly	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
valued	O
4	O
s.	O
from	O
George	B-pers
Young	I-pers
of	O
Covent	B-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
which	O
she	O
confest	O
,	O
when	O
taken	O
;	O
and	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
at	O
one	O
Hills	O
's	O
a	O
Broker	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Morgan	O
:	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Bampford	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Houses	O
of	O
one	O
Robert	B-pers
Metcalfe	I-pers
,	O
one	O
Senses	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
and	O
one	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gamball	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
Parish	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
:	O
Metcalfe	O
's	O
Lock	O
was	O
shot	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Kettle	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
which	O
Metcalfe	O
owned	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
positive	O
proof	O
was	O
found	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Kettle	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Gamball	O
swore	O
that	O
she	O
found	O
a	O
Rug	O
,	O
a	O
Blanket	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pillow	O
of	O
hers	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Key	O
would	O
unlock	O
the	O
said	O
Gamball	O
's	O
Door	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
her	O
own	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
Parsons	O
said	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
shut	O
on	O
the	O
over-night	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
it	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Lock	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
24	O
pair	O
of	O
Stokins	O
,	O
and	O
42	O
Skeins	O
of	O
Yarn	O
and	O
Worsted	O
;	O
the	O
Stockins	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Apron	O
by	O
the	O
Watch	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elinor	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pancras	I-place
Parish	I-place
was	O
tried	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
,	O
with	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Gilly	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
Rob	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hackaridge	I-pers
in	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
her	O
(	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Grays-Inn-Lane	B-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
)	O
one	O
Stuff	O
Mantua	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
small	O
Goods	O
;	O
The	O
said	O
Hackeridge	O
was	O
coming	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
a	O
Soldier	O
met	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
under	O
her	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
under	O
a	O
pretence	O
of	O
helping	O
her	O
to	O
a	O
Lodging	O
,	O
the	O
Soldier	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
with	O
a	O
Shift	O
of	O
Hackeridges	O
upon	O
her	O
back	O
;	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
several	O
Goods	O
from	O
Henry	B-pers
Gore	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
a	O
Morning	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
a	O
Doe-skin	O
Wastecoat	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
&	O
c.	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
positive	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Gillet	I-pers
a	O
Boy	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Nozy	O
,	O
was	O
Tried	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Walter	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
from	O
Henry	B-pers
Gore	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
Monday	O
was	O
Seven-night	O
last	O
,	O
1	O
Silk	O
Morning	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
1	O
Coat	O
with	O
Silver	O
Buttons	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
a	O
Wastecoat	O
8	O
l.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
40	O
s.	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
50	O
s.	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
brought	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Porter	O
set	O
it	O
upon	O
a	O
Shop	O
Window	O
,	O
whilest	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
deliver	O
a	O
Letter	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
the	O
Trunk	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
could	O
charge	O
the	O
Boy	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cary	I-pers
the	O
Elder	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
Capt	B-pers
.	I-pers
Conley	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
day	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
2	O
Silver	O
Tankards	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
l.	O
1	O
Porringer	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
1	O
Pot	O
50	O
s.	O
6	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
7	O
Silver	O
Forks	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Cup	O
10	O
s.	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
Sleeves	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
ofgood	O
value	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Daughter	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cary	I-pers
the	O
Younger	O
,	O
was	O
arraigned	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
confest	O
the	O
Indictment	O
:	O
And	O
Mr.	O
Conleys	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Daughter	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Connyer	O
's	O
Door	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Fork	O
and	O
Spoon	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
an	O
accessary	O
to	O
her	O
Daughter	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
Clipping	O
Sheers	O
and	O
Scales	O
found	O
in	O
their	O
Custody	O
,	O
which	O
gave	O
suspicion	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
an	O
ill	O
Woman	O
before	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Catling	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
making	O
an	O
Assault	O
upon	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Welsborne	I-pers
,	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
Bruise	O
upon	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
died	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
after	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
struck	O
him	O
over	O
the	O
Head	O
with	O
a	O
Broom-stick	O
;	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
a	O
going	O
down	O
White-cross-street	B-place
,	O
being	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
November	O
was	O
12	O
Month	O
last	O
,	O
some	O
Boys	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
Hallowing	O
,	O
stopt	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
make	O
him	O
Hallow	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
refusing	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
with	O
the	O
Broomstick	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
provocation	O
given	O
by	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
the	O
Skull	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
afterwards	O
Trepan	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Chyrurgeons	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
open	O
by	O
a	O
circular	O
Incision	O
,	O
yet	O
could	O
not	O
save	O
his	O
Life	O
;	O
but	O
was	O
really	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
several	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
always	O
carried	O
himself	O
honestly	O
and	O
fairly	O
amongst	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
was	O
given	O
to	O
quarrelling	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
New	I-place
Fish-street	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
breaking	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wayte	I-pers
there	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
day	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
lost	O
were	O
,	O
1	O
Gold	O
Chain	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
1	O
Pearl	O
Necklace	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
l.	O
2	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
2	O
Silver	O
Watches	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
1	O
Porringer	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
29	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
1	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Ladle	O
,	O
and	O
abundance	O
of	O
more	O
Plate	O
,	O
besides	O
113	O
Guineas	O
,	O
42	O
pieces	O
of	O
Broad	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Gold	O
,	O
besides	O
100	O
l.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
catch	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Locks	O
were	O
broken	O
,	O
whilest	O
the	O
Family	O
were	O
at	O
Church	O
;	O
and	O
several	O
Pick-lock-keys	O
and	O
a	O
Betty	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
that	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
say	O
nothing	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
Burglary	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
day-time	O
.	O
Hyllary	B-pers
Tulley	I-pers
was	O
Tried	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
,	O
one	O
for	O
stealing	O
of	O
a	O
Sword	O
with	O
a	O
Handle	O
inlaid	O
with	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
from	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Philboy	I-pers
:	O
And	O
and	O
another	O
for	O
stealing	O
several	O
pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
from	O
Matthew	B-pers
Philboy	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
declared	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
pawned	O
a	O
Sword	O
at	O
a	O
Goldsmiths	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
such	O
Sword	O
as	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
only	O
a	O
Silver	O
Hilted	O
one	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
sworn	O
positively	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Cold	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
one	O
was	O
very	O
ill	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
.	O
The	O
Trial	O
was	O
long	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
distinctly	O
handled	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
were	O
directed	O
to	O
be	O
careful	O
in	O
their	O
Verdict	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
having	O
well	O
considered	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
finding	O
no	O
full	O
proof	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sufficient	O
enough	O
to	O
find	O
him	O
guilty	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
charge	O
laid	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
in	O
respect	O
to	O
both	O
parts	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Phillip	B-pers
Street	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Daering	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Hempen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
from	O
Margaret	B-pers
Jacket	I-pers
of	O
Harrow	B-place
on	I-place
the	I-place
Hill	I-place
;	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
stood	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
in	O
a	O
Tub	O
,	O
and	O
1	O
Sheet	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
Street	O
's	O
Yard	O
,	O
which	O
Jacket	O
said	O
was	O
hers	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
brought	O
good	O
Evidence	O
for	O
their	O
Reputation	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
sufficient	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
14	O
l.	O
a	O
year	O
free	O
;	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Sympson	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Dempley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Grace	B-pers
Sympson	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
Tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
black	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Wastecoat	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Snuff-box	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
from	O
David	B-pers
Serah	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
day	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
that	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
confest	O
the	O
Robbery	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
had	O
been	O
Branded	O
before	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Edward	O
:	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Grace	O
:	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Wakeman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
high	O
Treason	O
,	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
,	O
One	O
for	O
Counterfeiting	O
and	O
Coyning	O
the	O
Currant	O
Money	O
of	O
England	O
;	O
The	O
Second	O
for	O
Clipping	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
:	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
Women	O
only	O
Evidence	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
First	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
very	O
unwilling	O
to	O
declare	O
their	O
knowledge	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
although	O
they	O
were	O
suspected	O
to	O
be	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
false	O
Money	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
For	O
the	O
Proof	O
of	O
the	O
Second	O
Indictment	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
Sheers	O
and	O
other	O
Clipping	O
Conveniencies	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
besides	O
some	O
Clipt	O
Money	O
and	O
Clippings	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
shut	O
the	O
Door	O
against	O
the	O
Constable	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
double	O
lockt	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
they	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
did	O
upon	O
the	O
Trial	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
for	O
his	O
shutting	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
Bailiffs	O
:	O
withal	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
his	O
Wife	O
did	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
much	O
abroad	O
about	O
publick	O
Business	O
;	O
his	O
Wife	O
is	O
not	O
yet	O
found	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
discharged	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Gawhon	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Pierce	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
in	O
Drury	B-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
day	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Thimble	O
and	O
a	O
6	O
d.	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
positive	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gold	I-pers
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Coach-Seat	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Coney	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
worth	O
40	O
s.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
stopt	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
in	O
the	O
dark	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Coach-Seat	O
in	O
his	O
custody	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
take	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
in	O
Gravell	B-place
Street	I-place
and	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
at	O
Brooks-street	O
End	O
;	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Everton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
Robbing	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
without	B-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
an	O
Ivory	O
handle	O
Cane	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
Napkin	O
,	O
a	O
Knife	O
and	O
Fork	O
;	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
Clark	O
's	O
House	O
and	O
whilst	O
he	O
was	O
abroad	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
the	O
Knife	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Cane	O
was	O
pawn	O
'd	O
in	O
Houndsditch	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
gave	O
him	O
leave	O
to	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
the	O
Cane	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
drinking	O
at	O
an	O
Ale	O
house	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
Cane	O
to	O
pay	O
his	O
Reckoning	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Fell	I-pers
a	O
High-Dutchman	O
,	O
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Bullock	I-pers
in	O
the	O
night-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
48	O
Pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Beef	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
confest	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
:	O
and	O
Bullock	O
swore	O
that	O
his	O
Window	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
but	O
was	O
shut	O
on	O
the	O
over-night	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
mistaken	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Ducker	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Duckworth	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Arraigned	O
upon	O
an	O
Indictment	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
14	O
Guineas	O
and	O
28	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
from	O
James	B-pers
Fodey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Undershaft	I-place
;	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Humphrey	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
of	O
White-chappel	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
4	O
Hempen	O
Sacks	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
2	O
Pillowbaers	O
18	O
d.	O
a	O
Peck	O
of	O
Wheat	O
Flour	O
;	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Journey	O
man	O
to	O
Humphrey	O
Watts	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
carry	O
some	O
Flour	O
home	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Sacks	O
were	O
found	O
under	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Bed	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
carried	O
Oats	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
Sacks	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
put	O
them	O
under	O
the	O
Bed	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
forgot	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
home	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Piliowbear	O
Watts	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Flour	O
he	O
had	O
liberty	O
to	O
take	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Seager	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Staples	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Coat	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
stopt	O
,	O
he	O
dropt	O
the	O
Coat	O
and	O
got	O
away	O
and	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
was	O
quickly	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dupeer	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
Eight	O
and	O
Ten	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Dupeer	O
about	O
a	O
Twelvemonth	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Dupeer	O
's	O
Chamber	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
naked	O
Sword	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
gilt	O
Pistole	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Dupeer	O
owned	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
;	O
the	O
Window	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pane	O
of	O
Glass	O
took	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
drink	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
allowed	O
of	O
by	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Evidence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
and	O
tried	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
in	O
clipping	O
the	O
currant	O
Money	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22th	O
day	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
upon	O
Oath	O
.	O
That	O
Cook	O
was	O
searcht	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
his	O
Working	O
Room	O
was	O
found	O
some	O
Clippings	O
,	O
and	O
Sheers	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Implements	O
fit	O
for	O
Clipping	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
which	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
to	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
;	O
but	O
Cook	O
himself	O
was	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
happily	O
left	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
his	O
Door	O
behind	O
him	O
(	O
he	O
being	O
gone	O
abroad	O
)	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
thing	O
;	O
but	O
rather	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Butt	I-pers
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
Tried	O
for	O
Felony	O
in	O
Robbing	O
one	O
Charles	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
black	O
Strip	O
'd	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
adorn	O
'd	O
with	O
a	O
Silver	O
Fringe	O
,	O
value	O
34	O
s.	O
another	O
Petticoat	O
value	O
36	O
s.	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
black	O
Moe-hair	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Good	O
value	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
were	O
other	O
Lodgers	O
besides	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
none	O
could	O
charge	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
particularly	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Wythe	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
Robbing	O
John	B-pers
Hanchman	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
of	O
3	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
58	O
s.	O
6	O
pair	O
of	O
Diaper	O
Child-bed	O
Clouts	O
.	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Pillowbear	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
visit	O
Mrs.	O
Hanchman	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
by	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
plainly	O
swore	O
.	O
She	O
confest	O
it	O
when	O
taken	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
pleaded	O
guilty	O
to	O
an	O
Indictment	O
brought	O
against	O
her	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Stretton	I-pers
of	O
White-chappel	B-place
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Sheet	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Muslin	O
Lace	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
One	O
Samuel	B-pers
Kendrick	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
going	O
into	O
France	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
holding	O
correspondence	O
with	O
the	O
Enemies	O
of	O
our	O
present	O
King	O
and	O
Queen	O
,	O
and	O
returning	O
again	O
into	O
England	O
contrary	O
to	O
the	O
Act	O
of	O
Parliament	O
in	O
that	O
case	O
made	O
and	O
provided	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
heard	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
French	O
King	O
did	O
not	O
want	O
men	O
;	O
for	O
he	O
could	O
raise	O
17000	O
men	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
raised	O
but	O
one	O
in	O
a	O
Parish	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
witness	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
over	O
within	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Act	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
One	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wyllan	I-pers
.	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Writing	O
and	O
Printing	O
a	O
Book	O
in	O
vIndication	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Harison	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
who	O
was	O
lately	O
Executed	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Dr.	O
Andrew	O
Clench	O
;	O
in	O
which	O
Book	O
are	O
several	O
scandalous	O
Expressions	O
against	O
the	O
Proceedings	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
at	O
his	O
Trial	O
;	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
fin	O
'd	O
100	O
Marks	O
for	O
the	O
Offence	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Lunsden	I-pers
,	O
for	O
Writing	O
and	O
Composing	O
a	O
certain	O
False	O
,	O
Scandalous	O
and	O
Seditious	O
Libel	O
against	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
Queen	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
favour	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
King	O
James	O
,	O
gave	O
Bail	O
to	O
answer	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
Hugh	B-pers
Ridley	I-pers
,	O
for	O
Composing	O
and	O
Printing	O
a	O
Mock	O
Speech	O
,	O
by	O
way	O
of	O
a	O
Ridicule	O
to	O
our	O
present	O
King	O
William	O
's	O
last	O
Speech	O
to	O
the	O
Parliament	O
at	O
Westminster	O
,	O
gave	O
Sureties	O
to	O
appear	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Canning	I-pers
,	O
was	O
called	O
to	O
answer	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
suspected	O
to	O
have	O
printed	O
the	O
late	O
King	O
James	O
's	O
Declaration	O
,	O
and	O
entred	O
into	O
a	O
Recognizance	O
to	O
appear	O
next	O
Sessions	O
,	O
to	O
answer	O
the	O
charge	O
that	O
shall	O
be	O
brought	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
&	O
c.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
the	O
10th	O
instant	O
,	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Charles	O
Lord	O
Banbury	O
,	O
was	O
brought	O
into	O
Court	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
committed	O
lately	O
for	O
killing	O
of	O
one	O
Capt	O
.	O
Dawson	O
;	O
he	O
pleaded	O
his	O
Right	O
of	O
Peerage	O
by	O
his	O
Patent	O
which	O
was	O
openly	O
Read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
he	O
moved	O
for	O
Bail	O
;	O
but	O
was	O
told	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
granted	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
matter	O
was	O
referred	O
till	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
The	O
Gentlmen	O
of	O
the	O
Grand	O
Jury	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
did	O
this	O
Sessions	O
bring	O
in	O
a	O
Presentment	O
into	O
Court	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
openly	O
Read	O
;	O
the	O
Contents	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
to	O
this	O
effect	O
.	O
THAT	O
whereas	O
divers	O
good	O
wholesome	O
Laws	O
and	O
Orders	O
have	O
been	O
lately	O
made	O
in	O
this	O
City	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
strict	O
Observation	O
of	O
the	O
Lords-Day	O
and	O
for	O
the	O
Restriction	O
of	O
all	O
such	O
as	O
offend	O
in	O
that	O
case	O
:	O
yet	O
notwithstanding	O
several	O
Persons	O
in	O
and	O
about	O
the	O
City	O
and	O
Subburbs	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
do	O
still	O
persist	O
and	O
go	O
on	O
in	O
the	O
Violation	O
and	O
Contempt	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
by	O
way	O
of	O
prophaning	O
of	O
the	O
Lord	O
Day	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
displeasure	O
and	O
dishonour	O
of	O
Almighty	O
God	O
,	O
the	O
discouraging	O
of	O
Vertue	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
increase	O
of	O
Vice	O
and	O
Wickedness	O
;	O
and	O
to	O
the	O
disparagement	O
of	O
this	O
Honourable	O
City	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Therefore	O
they	O
did	O
humbly	O
entreat	O
this	O
Honourble	O
Court	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
severe	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
put	O
the	O
Laws	O
in	O
due	O
Execution	O
against	O
;	O
First	O
,	O
All	O
such	O
as	O
sit	O
Tipling	O
and	O
Drinking	O
in	O
Taverns	O
and	O
Ale-houses	O
on	O
the	O
Lords	O
Day	O
.	O
Secondly	O
,	O
Against	O
all	O
those	O
who	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
Reformed	O
,	O
but	O
do	O
Sell	O
Drink	O
in	O
Silver	O
Tankards	O
;	O
because	O
it	O
occasions	O
great	O
trouble	O
to	O
this	O
Honourable	O
Court	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
that	O
so	O
many	O
Offenders	O
in	O
that	O
kind	O
are	O
committed	O
to	O
Prison	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Thirdly	O
,	O
Against	O
all	O
Pedlars	O
and	O
Hawkers	O
,	O
or	O
such	O
as	O
sit	O
Selling	O
of	O
Fruit	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
the	O
streets	O
on	O
the	O
Sabbath-Day	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
intent	O
that	O
all	O
such	O
as	O
offend	O
herein	O
may	O
be	O
brought	O
to	O
condign	O
punishment	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Anne	B-pers
Merriweather	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Arraigned	O
upon	O
an	O
Indictment	O
of	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
for	O
printing	O
the	O
late	O
King	O
James	O
's	O
Declaration	O
,	O
unto	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
not	O
guilty	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
remain	O
a	O
Prisoner	O
till	O
next	O
Sessions	O
,	O
to	O
answer	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
gave	O
Sentence	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
20	O
.	O
John	O
Glendon	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Allen	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Catlin	O
,	O
Anne	O
Ducker	O
,	O
Parnel	O
Brandon	O
,	O
Anne	O
Brown	O
,	O
Anne	O
Ray	O
,	O
Anne	O
Jenkins	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Greene	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Cary	O
Senior	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Cary	O
Junior	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Knott	O
,	O
Edward	O
Ayers	O
,	O
Edward	O
Prick	O
,	O
John	O
Bunworth	O
,	O
John	O
Gold	O
,	O
Lawrence	O
Fell	O
,	O
George	O
Seagor	O
,	O
Anne	O
Wythe	O
,	O
Alice	O
Chamberlain	O
,	O
a	O
former	O
convict	O
.	O
R.	O
-	O
J.	O
was	O
Respited	O
from	O
the	O
Burning	O
till	O
further	O
Order	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
Mary	O
Clever	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Young	O
.	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
21	O
.	O
Richard	O
Star	O
,	O
Edward	O
Sympson	O
,	O
Phillip	O
Davies	O
,	O
James	O
Greene	O
,	O
Mary	O
Williams	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Harris	O
,	O
alias	O
Oliver	O
George	O
Wood	O
,	O
John	O
Neale	O
,	O
Robert	O
Marshall	O
the	O
Blind	O
man	O
,	O
Daniel	O
Jones	O
,	O
Ambrose	O
Holland	O
,	O
Eikana	O
Smewin	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Harding	O
,	O
Robert	O
Wright	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Pepper	O
Elizabeth	O
Morgan	O
,	O
Sarah	O
Chandlor	O
,	O
Mary	O
Bampford	O
,	O
Elinor	O
Jones	O
,	O
Phillip	O
Maguire	O
a	O
former	O
convict	O
,	O
and	O
Henry	O
Tankard	O
,	O
for	O
killing	O
Mr.	O
Burton	O
Grace	O
Sympson	O
respited	O
before	O
Judgment	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Starr	O
.	O
Robert	O
Earle	O
,	O
and	O
Patrick	O
Gilbert	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
into	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
Service	O
,	O
and	O
respited	O
from	O
the	O
Penalty	O
due	O
to	O
them	O
for	O
a	O
Petty	O
Larcenary	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Gibson	O
delivered	O
of	O
a	O
Child	O
since	O
her	O
Arraignment	O
.	O
John	O
Adderton	O
,	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
and	O
Wounding	O
Ralph	O
Springall	O
,	O
Fin	O
'd	O
40	O
l.	O
And	O
for	O
running	O
one	O
Remington	O
through	O
the	O
Arms	O
,	O
Fin	O
'd	O
20	O
l.	O
and	O
to	O
find	O
Sureties	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
for	O
12	O
Months	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
rest	O
in	O
custody	O
till	O
all	O
be	O
performed	O
.	O
Mary	O
William	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Harris	O
,	O
alias	O
Oliver	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Pepper	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Morgan	O
,	O
Elinor	O
Jones	O
,	O
pleaded	O
their	O
Bellies	O
,	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
were	O
sworn	O
to	O
enquire	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
all	O
quick	O
with	O
child	O
.	O
Sarah	O
Chandlor	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	O
Bamford	O
,	O
an	O
old	O
Woman	O
,	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
with	O
child	O
,	O
but	O
were	O
not	O
found	O
so	O
.	O
Clippers	O
and	O
Coiners	O
left	O
to	O
be	O
tried	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
Richard	O
Cox	O
,	O
Richard	O
Tapping	O
,	O
Mary	O
Cartwright	O
,	O
Anne	O
Matthews	O
,	O
Edward	O
Jeavon	O
,	O
Katherine	O
Jeavon	O
,	O
William	O
Turner	O
,	O
William	O
Baily	O
,	O
and	O
Bethia	O
Evans	O
.	O
John	O
Stafford	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
tried	O
with	O
Ambrose	O
Holland	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
,	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
remain	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
further	O
suspicion	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Benjamin	O
Kallow	O
,	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
to	O
Kent	O
Affizes	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
Robbery	O
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
committed	O
upon	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Thomas	O
Janson	O
Baronet	O
,	O
near	O
Tunbridge	O
,	O
in	O
company	O
of	O
Whitney	O
and	O
other	O
High-way-men	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Blackford	O
,	O
Brother	O
to	O
William	O
Blackford	O
,	O
lately	O
executed	O
for	O
Clipping	O
,	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Sea	O
in	O
the	O
Service	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
Queen	O
.	O
Daniel	O
Brett	O
,	O
and	O
Giles	O
Wilcox	O
,	O
were	O
continued	O
upon	O
their	O
former	O
Recognizance	O
.	O
Adam	O
Banks	O
Travers	O
'd	O
his	O
Indictment	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENT	O
These	O
are	O
to	O
give	O
notice	O
to	O
all	O
Persons	O
for	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
this	O
Publick	O
That	O
W.	O
Elmy	O
Professor	O
of	O
Physick	O
,	O
and	O
Operator	O
,	O
of	O
known	O
Integrity	O
,	O
and	O
above	O
25	O
Years	O
Practice	O
,	O
liveth	O
at	O
the	O
Blew-Ball	O
in	O
Whale-Bone-Court	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
lower	O
end	O
of	O
Bartholomew-Lane	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Royal-Exchange	O
:	O
Who	O
most	O
safely	O
and	O
expeditiously	O
cures	O
Deafness	O
,	O
and	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
Ears	O
,	O
in	O
any	O
,	O
of	O
what	O
Age	O
soever	O
,	O
(	O
if	O
curable	O
)	O
and	O
at	O
first	O
sight	O
by	O
inspection	O
resolves	O
the	O
Patient	O
,	O
if	O
so	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
as	O
most	O
eminent	O
Persons	O
of	O
Quality	O
in	O
this	O
City	O
can	O
testifie	O
.	O
He	O
hath	O
likewise	O
a	O
Sovereign	O
Head-Pill	O
,	O
which	O
infallibly	O
cures	O
all	O
Pains	O
in	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
whether	O
old	O
or	O
newly	O
contracted	O
;	O
Speedily	O
taking	O
only	O
all	O
Swimmings	O
and	O
Giddiness	O
,	O
preventing	O
the	O
dangerous	O
consequence	O
of	O
Apoplectical	O
Fits	O
;	O
preserves	O
the	O
Sight	O
,	O
and	O
takes	O
away	O
all	O
Accidents	O
offending	O
the	O
Eyes	O
.	O
strengthens	O
the	O
Memory	O
,	O
and	O
dishurthens	O
the	O
Brain	O
of	O
all	O
offensive	O
Humours	O
,	O
thereby	O
rendring	O
the	O
Understanding	O
more	O
clear	O
and	O
vigorous	O
.	O
These	O
Pills	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
.	O
He	O
heath	O
also	O
Pills	O
only	O
prepared	O
for	O
the	O
French	O
Disease	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Running	O
of	O
the	O
Reins	O
,	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
six	O
Boxes	O
of	O
several	O
Prizes	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
Vetnerial	O
Arcanaes	O
,	O
as	O
occasion	O
requires	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
He	O
bath	O
likewise	O
an	O
expeditious	O
way	O
in	O
curing	O
all	O
pains	O
in	O
the	O
Teeth	O
without	O
drawing	O
He	O
hath	O
likewise	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Gargarisme	O
or	O
Month-Water	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
make	O
black	O
or	O
yellow	O
Teeth	O
as	O
white	O
as	O
Ivory	O
in	O
few	O
times	O
using	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
will	O
certainly	O
cure	O
the	O
Scurvey	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
Diseases	O
,	O
incident	O
to	O
the	O
Mouth	O
,	O
Teeth	O
and	O
Gums	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
.	O
