TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
and	O
Queens	O
Commissions	O
OF	O
THE	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
,	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
Wednesday	O
and	O
Thursday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
16th	O
,	O
17th	O
,	O
18th	O
,	O
and	O
19th	O
Days	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
1692	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
Fourth	O
Year	O
of	O
Their	O
MAJESTIES	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
on	O
Monday	O
,	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
Wednesday	O
and	O
Thursday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
16th	O
,	O
17th	O
,	O
18th	O
,	O
and	O
19th	O
Days	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
1692.	O
before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fleet	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
Salathiel	B-pers
Lovell	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
follows	O
,	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Marlow	I-pers
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Marks	I-pers
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Carpenter	I-pers
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Bathue	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Hollyhawk	I-pers
.	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Layton	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wharton	I-pers
.	O
Hugh	B-pers
Granger	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Lavender	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Partridge	I-pers
.	O
James	B-pers
Fearn	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Parkinson	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Preston	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilks	I-pers
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Hutchinson	I-pers
.	O
Moses	B-pers
Colewell	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Preston	I-pers
of	O
Westminster	O
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
these	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Wayte	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Copper	O
Cover	O
of	O
a	O
Pan	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
from	O
one	O
Daniel	B-pers
Ower	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Barber	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dionis	I-place
Back-church	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Ower	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
stopt	O
in	O
Column-street	O
,	O
he	O
dropp	O
'd	O
the	O
Cover	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
fully	O
sworn	O
,	O
besides	O
his	O
own	O
Confession	O
,	O
when	O
taken	O
;	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Norris	I-pers
as	O
principal	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
,	O
as	O
accessary	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
tried	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Sherman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Parish	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
away	O
was	O
a	O
Frize	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
Serge	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Sherman	O
aforesaid	O
;	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
a	O
Latin	O
Bible	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Gascon	I-pers
,	O
his	O
Servant	O
;	O
two	O
Coats	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
a	O
Broker	O
's	O
in	O
Thieving	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
owned	O
to	O
have	O
received	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Son	O
of	O
hers	O
that	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Sea	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Coat	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
Norris	O
's	O
back	O
;	O
but	O
none	O
could	O
swear	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
broke	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
or	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
Norris	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Coat	O
for	O
10	O
s.	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
,	O
Son	O
of	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
but	O
the	O
Woman	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Brunkhurst	I-pers
,	O
Garret	B-pers
Van-Owen	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Dennis	I-pers
,	O
all	O
three	O
Dutchmen	O
,	O
were	O
tried	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
David	B-pers
Van-Ferny	I-pers
not	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
kill	O
and	O
murther	O
one	O
Walter	B-pers
Van-Riel	I-pers
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
January	O
instant	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Dutchmen	O
were	O
drinking	O
at	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
in	O
Sohoe	B-place
about	O
Eight	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
words	O
arose	O
about	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Van-Riel	O
was	O
kill	O
'd	O
,	O
having	O
a	O
wound	O
given	O
him	O
near	O
the	O
left	O
Pap	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
four	O
Inches	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
proof	O
was	O
made	O
that	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
gave	O
the	O
wound	O
,	O
but	O
rather	O
that	O
Van-ferny	O
kill	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
fled	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
besides	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
above	O
20	O
Dutchmen	O
in	O
company	O
,	O
being	O
met	O
together	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
New-years	O
Gift	O
which	O
was	O
given	O
them	O
by	O
their	O
Captain	O
,	O
so	O
there	O
might	O
be	O
others	O
concerned	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
said	O
(	O
by	O
an	O
Interpreter	O
)	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
no	O
ways	O
abetting	O
to	O
the	O
Murther	O
;	O
So	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Pulford	I-pers
,	O
a	O
very	O
ancient	O
man	O
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Bellinger	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Clements-Inn	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intention	O
to	O
steal	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
standing	O
upon	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Window	O
was	O
opened	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Chamber	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Cord	O
like	O
a	O
Ship-Rope	O
,	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
custody	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
he	O
got	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
presently	O
taken	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
took	O
nothing	O
away	O
;	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
without	O
great	O
suspicion	O
of	O
being	O
a	O
very	O
ill	O
man	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Webster	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Kettle	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
at	O
Westminster	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
day	O
of	O
December	O
;	O
the	O
Kettle	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
another	O
Woman	O
employ	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
Kettle	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
produce	O
her	O
;	O
yet	O
no	O
one	O
was	O
found	O
to	O
own	O
the	O
Kettle	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
(	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
from	O
Alice	B-pers
Scroggs	I-pers
)	O
a	O
Bible	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
Dowlace	O
Smock	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
Violin	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
to	O
have	O
taken	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
stole	O
them	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
a	O
young	O
Girl	O
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Jeve	I-pers
in	O
Hosyer	B-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
London	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
5	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
Pewter	O
Pots	O
,	O
three	O
Spoons	O
,	O
two	O
Flaxen	O
Tablecloths	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
;	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
an	O
empty	O
House	O
in	O
Moor-fields	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
to	O
have	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
when	O
taken	O
;	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
broken	O
open	O
about	O
four	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
tried	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
branded	O
;	O
yet	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
was	O
so	O
kind	O
as	O
to	O
quit	O
her	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
and	O
only	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mabel	B-pers
Symonds	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
Instant	O
,	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Womens	O
Shoes	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
from	O
her	O
Master	O
one	O
Daniel	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
of	O
Bishopsgate-street	B-place
,	O
she	O
confest	O
it	O
before	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stamp	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
and	O
and	O
that	O
some	O
evil-disposed	O
Persons	O
tempted	O
her	O
to	O
commit	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
all	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
at	O
the	O
Trial	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
very	O
pensive	O
and	O
sorrowful	O
for	O
her	O
fact	O
;	O
So	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
a	O
Petty-Larcenary	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Belcher	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
four	O
Damask	O
Napkins	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Pillowbear	O
,	O
from	O
Abel	B-pers
Bradley	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolph	I-place
's	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Bradley	O
to	O
nurse	O
her	O
Children	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
suspected	O
her	O
to	O
have	O
stolen	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
sold	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
a	O
Broker	O
in	O
Hounsditch	O
for	O
9	O
s.	O
which	O
the	O
said	O
Bradly	O
owned	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
:	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Pabworth	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
hundred	O
weight	O
of	O
Logwood	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s	O
from	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Knap	I-pers
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Logwood	O
off	O
Dice	B-place
Key	I-place
,	O
but	O
was	O
presently	O
stopt	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
burn	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
the	O
Wood	O
;	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Cartwright	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
in	O
that	O
she	O
intending	O
to	O
deceive	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
People	O
,	O
did	O
clip	O
,	O
file	O
,	O
and	O
diminish	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
England	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
search	O
made	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
in	O
Soho	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
Chamber	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
Leather	O
and	O
Canvas	O
of	O
the	O
Chairs	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
some	O
Clipt	O
Money	O
.	O
Clippings	O
,	O
Files	O
and	O
Shears	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
which	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
as	O
Corroborating	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
;	O
But	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
produced	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
one	O
Young	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
Lodged	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
who	O
are	O
gone	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
proof	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
actually	O
concerned	O
;	O
She	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Coates	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Pullene	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Salter	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Iron	O
Anchor	O
from	O
one	O
Joseph	B-pers
Sandwell	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
Instant	O
;	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
took	O
away	O
his	O
Anchor	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dock	O
,	O
and	O
Salter	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
30	O
s.	O
to	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
near	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
which	O
very	O
evidently	O
appeared	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Jeavon	I-pers
,	O
Catherine	B-pers
Jeavon	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Dunton	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
tried	O
for	O
Counterfeiting	O
and	O
Coining	O
false	O
Money	O
;	O
there	O
being	O
search	O
made	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
upon	O
suspicion	O
,	O
(	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Sellinger	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Dunn	O
,	O
who	O
are	O
Persons	O
that	O
have	O
been	O
very	O
industrious	O
and	O
careful	O
of	O
late	O
to	O
discover	O
all	O
such	O
Offenders	O
)	O
in	O
their	O
House	O
was	O
found	O
several	O
Stamps	O
,	O
and	O
Crucibles	O
,	O
and	O
Shears	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
pieces	O
of	O
false	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
Utensils	O
fit	O
for	O
the	O
work	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
brought	O
into	O
Court	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
Coverly	B-place
's	I-place
Fields	I-place
in	I-place
Mile-End	I-place
New	I-place
Town	I-place
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
but	O
lately	O
come	O
to	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
lived	O
but	O
5	O
days	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
before	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
Shakesby	O
had	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
before	O
them	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
an	O
ill	O
name	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
Ralph	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
the	O
like	O
Offence	O
of	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
in	O
Counterfeiting	O
and	O
making	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
false	O
Money	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
at	O
Westminster	B-place
two	O
false	O
half	O
Crowns	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Mill	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
useful	O
to	O
make	O
Money	O
,	O
besides	O
several	O
Stamps	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
all	O
which	O
was	O
brought	O
into	O
Court	O
,	O
as	O
confirming	O
Evidence	O
:	O
But	O
none	O
could	O
charge	O
her	O
positively	O
to	O
be	O
concerned	O
,	O
but	O
rather	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
absconded	O
.	O
So	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
B	B-pers
-	I-pers
J	I-pers
-	I-pers
of	O
Covent-Garden	B-place
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Caudle-Cup	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
three	O
Spoons	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
value	O
,	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Joanna	B-pers
Bowden	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
Instant	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Bowden	O
went	O
to	O
prayers	O
to	O
the	O
Church	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
her	O
return	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
her	O
House	O
rifled	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Spoons	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
his	O
Room	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
the	O
Cup	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
othes	O
Goods	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
only	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
on	O
purpose	O
to	O
surprize	O
Mrs	O
Bowden	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
contradicted	O
;	O
So	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gelding	O
,	O
price	O
10	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
Saddle	O
and	O
Bridle	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
on	O
the	O
22d	O
.	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Cox	O
was	O
riding	O
into	O
Bedfordshire	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Horse	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
near	O
Dunstable	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
charge	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
dark	O
;	O
but	O
other	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
Horse	O
to	O
an	O
Inn	O
at	O
Westminster	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
further	O
corroborated	O
by	O
a	O
Witness	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Phillips	O
when	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
done	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hynton	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
40	O
pair	O
of	O
Yarn	O
Stockins	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
on	O
the	O
27th	O
day	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
out	O
of	O
Shoreditch	B-place
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
men	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
Hynton	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Stockins	O
off	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
out	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
immediatly	O
stopt	O
:	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
let	O
fall	O
the	O
Stockins	O
in	O
the	O
dirt	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
got	O
away	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Oswin	I-pers
was	O
arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
seven	O
Quarter	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Oates	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
fifteen	O
Sacks	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Prentice	I-pers
,	O
unto	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ruth	B-pers
Plovell	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
32	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
of	O
Westminster	B-place
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Howard	O
's	O
Servant	O
when	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
lost	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
positively	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Gross	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nolthrope	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Saddle	O
and	O
Bridle	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Cloath	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Carolina	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
8	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
5	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
two	O
more	O
met	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
persons	O
about	O
seven	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
near	O
Pancrass	B-place
Church	I-place
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
their	O
Money	O
and	O
Goods	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
on	O
Horseback	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
they	O
bid	O
them	O
stand	O
,	O
and	O
holding	O
a	O
Blunderbuss	O
to	O
their	O
Breast	O
,	O
swore	O
damn	O
you	O
if	O
you	O
stir	O
you	O
are	O
dead	O
Men	O
:	O
The	O
Coat	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
Westminster	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
the	O
matter	O
was	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
deserted	O
his	O
Lodging	O
after	O
the	O
Robery	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
nothing	O
material	O
to	O
offer	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Wilder	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
Katherine	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lurcock	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Lacey	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Blathwait	I-pers
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
from	O
George	B-pers
Bromly	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
of	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Child	O
's	O
Morning	O
Gown	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Point	O
Cravat	O
,	O
two	O
yards	O
of	O
Flanders	O
Lace	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
small	O
Goods	O
:	O
Catherine	O
Davis	O
took	O
a	O
Lodging	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
following	O
,	O
Wilder	O
and	O
Lurcock	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
having	O
drank	O
a	O
while	O
,	O
they	O
assaulted	O
Martha	O
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Bromly	O
,	O
tying	O
her	O
Legs	O
and	O
Hands	O
together	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
pinn	O
'd	O
her	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Blanket	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
her	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
Davis	O
telling	O
her	O
(	O
if	O
she	O
made	O
a	O
noise	O
)	O
she	O
would	O
cut	O
her	O
Throat	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
found	O
guilty	O
except	O
Magaret	O
Lacey	O
.	O
[	O
Wilder	O
,	O
Davis	O
:	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Lurcock	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Boyle	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Walsh	I-pers
Knt	O
.	O
and	O
Baronet	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
King	O
Charles	O
I	O
.	O
Gold	O
Medals	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
Flowerd	O
Muslin	O
Cravats	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
13	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
;	O
the	O
Woman	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
where	O
Sir	O
Robert	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
Chamber	O
under	O
a	O
pretence	O
to	O
fetch	O
away	O
aSnuff	O
of	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Medal	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
which	O
Sir	O
Robert	O
found	O
at	O
pawn	O
at	O
a	O
Brokers	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
charge	O
her	O
positively	O
:	O
She	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Beames	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
2900	O
weight	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
value	O
80	O
l.	O
40	O
Canvas	O
Bags	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Esther	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
of	O
Stepny	B-place
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Jarvis	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
lay	O
in	O
a	O
Celler	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
offering	O
four	O
of	O
the	O
Bags	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
to	O
sale	O
,	O
which	O
Jarvis	O
owned	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Goods	O
;	O
none	O
could	O
swear	O
he	O
broke	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
tho	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
very	O
ill	O
Fame	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
James	B-pers
Tilney	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
of	O
25	O
yards	O
of	O
Lutestring	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
another	O
piece	O
of	O
Grasset	O
Silk	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
unto	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bagly	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Bethia	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
were	O
tryed	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
for	O
Forging	O
and	O
Counterfeiting	O
the	O
lawful	O
Coyn	O
of	O
England	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
Turner	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
Swallowstreet	B-place
,	O
several	O
Stamps	O
,	O
Files	O
,	O
Melting-Pots	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Half-Crowns	O
and	O
Shillings	O
made	O
of	O
False	O
Metal	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
shewed	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
and	O
Turner	O
hid	O
himself	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
soon	O
fetch	O
'd	O
out	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Dunn	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
that	O
affected	O
the	O
Woman	O
and	O
Bagly	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
,	O
but	O
Turner	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Whitney	I-pers
the	O
Captain	O
of	O
the	O
High-way	O
Men	O
,	O
who	O
hath	O
so	O
much	O
infested	O
the	O
Roads	O
of	O
late	O
years	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
about	O
England	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
much	O
talked	O
of	O
abroad	O
for	O
his	O
great	O
Exploits	O
,	O
in	O
committing	O
several	O
Rapines	O
upon	O
the	O
High-way	O
)	O
was	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
17th	O
Instant	O
arraigned	O
and	O
tryed	O
for	O
a	O
Burglary	O
committed	O
upon	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Flanders	I-pers
of	O
Enfield	B-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
was	O
Twelvemonth	O
;	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
beset	O
by	O
Old	O
Mobb	O
.	O
since	O
executed	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
open	O
about	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Money	O
and	O
Plate	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
of	O
very	O
great	O
value	O
;	O
one	O
Witness	O
swore	O
that	O
Morning	O
before	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
Whitney	O
and	O
another	O
Man	O
was	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
at	O
Cheston	O
,	O
(	O
being	O
an	O
Inn	O
)	O
but	O
went	O
away	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
could	O
swear	O
that	O
Whitney	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
denied	O
the	O
Matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
this	O
first	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Delawny	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Pestle	O
and	O
Morter	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Pot	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Christian	B-pers
West	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Bartholomew	I-place
Exchange	I-place
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
about	O
her	O
;	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Ayres	I-pers
and	O
Nathanel	B-pers
Hattrell	I-pers
were	O
tryed	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Rew	I-pers
an	O
ancient	O
Woman	O
by	O
driving	O
the	O
Wheel	O
of	O
a	O
Dray	O
loaden	O
with	O
three	O
Barels	O
of	O
Small	O
Beer	O
over	O
her	O
Body	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
died	O
the	O
19th	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
her	O
Death	O
she	O
declared	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
crush	O
'd	O
up	O
against	O
a	O
Stall	O
in	O
Pye-Corner	B-place
by	O
a	O
Dray	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Men	O
that	O
drove	O
it	O
curst	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
her	O
stand	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
Men	O
,	O
neither	O
did	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
swear	O
positively	O
;	O
but	O
Ayers	O
owned	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
wilfully	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
but	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Hattrell	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
was	O
arraigned	O
and	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Samuel	B-pers
Tavernor	I-pers
of	O
Great	B-place
St.	I-place
Bartholomew	I-place
's	I-place
two	O
Silk	O
Scarves	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
three	O
Hoods	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
Black	O
Scarf	O
,	O
several	O
Linnen	O
and	O
Woollen	O
Cloths	O
,	O
besides	O
9	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
between	O
the	O
Matt	O
and	O
the	O
Bed	O
lying	O
hid	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
tyed	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Blanket	O
ready	O
to	O
carry	O
away	O
;	O
she	O
could	O
say	O
nothing	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Alice	B-pers
Page	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Fryar	I-pers
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Scarf	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
three	O
Silver	O
Tankards	O
,	O
15	O
l.	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
from	O
Judith	B-pers
Gordon	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
one	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
from	O
Elisha	B-pers
Whitton	I-pers
;	O
she	O
came	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
to	O
live	O
(	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
)	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Gordon	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
she	O
robbed	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
about	O
10	O
a	O
Clock	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
to	O
have	O
disposed	O
of	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Tankards	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
again	O
;	O
She	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
:	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Ingram	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
six	O
Holland	O
Shifts	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
five	O
Smocks	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
seven	O
pair	O
of	O
Lace	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
two	O
Nightroils	O
,	O
four	O
Neckcloaths	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
one	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Peacock	I-pers
:	O
Mrs.	O
Ingram	O
's	O
Window	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
the	O
Glass	O
being	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
in	O
Goodman	B-place
's	I-place
Fields	I-place
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
gone	O
;	O
but	O
none	O
could	O
charge	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
another	O
Robbery	O
upon	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
committed	O
upon	O
Roger	B-pers
Clynton	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Duncombe	I-pers
s	O
Servant	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
near	O
Harrow	B-place
on	I-place
the	I-place
Hill	I-place
;	O
Mr.	O
Stacy	O
met	O
him	O
,	O
bid	O
him	O
stand	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
and	O
Stacy	O
stab	O
'd	O
his	O
own	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
Gelding	O
from	O
him	O
priz	O
'd	O
10	O
l	O
and	O
Philips	O
to	O
make	O
sure	O
work	O
of	O
Stacy	O
's	O
Horse	O
,	O
shot	O
him	O
through	O
the	O
Head	O
;	O
the	O
Witness	O
swore	O
home	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
not	O
contradict	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
dozen	O
pair	O
of	O
Mens	O
Norway	O
Gloves	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
several	O
other	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
value	O
32	O
s.	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Grantham	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
left	O
alone	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
mist	O
after	O
she	O
has	O
gone	O
;	O
She	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Ezembergh	I-pers
in	O
Dukes-Court	B-place
in	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
Parish	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
Instant	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
16	O
pair	O
of	O
Mens	O
Shoes	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Breeches	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
Sea-boy	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
vain	O
Excuse	O
;	O
the	O
Shop	O
being	O
no	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Mansion-house	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Ferguson	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Ferguson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
robbing	O
Archibald	B-pers
Robbinson	I-pers
of	O
two	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Pinners	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
three	O
Sutes	O
of	O
Cambrick	O
lac	O
'd	O
Head-cloths	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
small	O
value	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
Bed	O
alone	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
confest	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
Goods	O
for	O
about	O
15	O
s.	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hewin	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Giles	B-pers
Millet	I-pers
of	O
Fulham	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
nine	O
Coives	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
some	O
Neckcloths	O
and	O
Stockings	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
She	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
Millet	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
who	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
was	O
her	O
Cozen	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
her	O
Master	O
's	O
leave	O
she	O
lay	O
all	O
night	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
the	O
pretended	O
Cozen	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Newgate	O
;	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
upon	O
an	O
Indictment	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
for	O
Clipping	O
Money	O
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
Queen	O
swore	O
that	O
he	O
clipt	O
six	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
7th	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Shears	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Witness	O
was	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
familiar	O
Friend	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
unwilling	O
to	O
continue	O
his	O
wonted	O
Courtship	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
sworn	O
against	O
him	O
merely	O
out	O
of	O
Revenge	O
and	O
pure	O
Malice	O
,	O
as	O
was	O
confirmed	O
by	O
Evidence	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
behalf	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
did	O
not	O
discover	O
it	O
,	O
till	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
after	O
;	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Avery	I-pers
was	O
arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
200	O
l.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Poor	O
's	O
Box	O
at	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
positively	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
S	B-pers
-	I-pers
J	I-pers
-	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
two	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
two	O
Muslin	O
Night-royles	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Scarf	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
wearing	O
Apparrel	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Fones	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
carrying	O
to	O
a	O
Country	O
Coach	O
in	O
a	O
Trunk	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Trunk	O
off	O
the	O
Coach-side	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elinor	B-pers
Scriven	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Lancaster	I-pers
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Watch	O
with	O
a	O
Silver	O
Case	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Katharine	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
from	O
one	O
George	B-pers
Dutton	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Nurse	O
,	O
(	O
he	O
being	O
sick	O
)	O
and	O
whilst	O
he	O
was	O
asleep	O
,	O
his	O
Breeches	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
confest	O
to	O
have	O
taken	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
the	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
about	O
four	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Doors	O
open	O
;	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Katharine	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
tried	O
for	O
robbing	O
John	B-pers
Petrey	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
two	O
other	O
Silver	O
Cups	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
two	O
other	O
Cups	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Bottle	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
eight	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
eight	O
Forks	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
other	O
sorts	O
of	O
Plate	O
of	O
a	O
considerable	O
value	O
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sold	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Plate	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Rowley	O
a	O
Broker	O
;	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Mackerish	I-pers
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Mackerish	I-pers
,	O
were	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Gloves	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
another	O
pair	O
of	O
half-handed	O
Gloves	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jenks	I-pers
the	O
18th	O
day	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shop	O
at	O
Enfield	B-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
upon	O
the	O
Woman	O
's	O
hands	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
about	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
mistaken	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Gloves	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Peregrin	B-pers
Barret	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
in	O
Goodman	B-place
's	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
January	O
instant	O
,	O
and	O
carrying	O
away	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Linnen	O
of	O
good	O
value	O
;	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
about	O
Three	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Cooper	O
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
Burglary	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
at	O
Charing-Cross	B-place
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
January	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
by	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
with	O
three	O
Princes	O
Mettal	O
Rings	O
set	O
with	O
Bristol	O
Stones	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
a	O
Brass	O
Bottle	O
,	O
an	O
Iron	O
Bodkin	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
d.	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
small	O
Goods	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Whitney	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
called	O
Captain	O
Whitney	O
,	O
Butcher	O
,	O
the	O
great	O
Highway-man	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Kallow	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
,	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
at	O
South-Mims-wash	B-place
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
100	O
yards	O
of	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
l.	O
Neither	O
of	O
them	O
made	O
any	O
Exceptions	O
against	O
the	O
Jury	O
;	O
only	O
Mr.	O
Whitney	O
desired	O
none	O
might	O
be	O
sworn	O
amongst	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
were	O
of	O
the	O
Hundred	O
where	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
granted	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
call	O
'd	O
and	O
sworn	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
;	O
The	O
first	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
Robbed	O
by	O
seven	O
Men	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
them	O
:	O
The	O
next	O
Witness	O
swore	O
flatly	O
against	O
Mr.	O
Whitney	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
Robbed	O
him	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
afterward	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
and	O
Robbed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
stob	O
'd	O
several	O
Carriers	O
Horses	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
could	O
charge	O
Kallow	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Whitney	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
;	O
answered	O
in	O
short	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Man	O
was	O
hard-mouth	O
'd	O
.	O
But	O
was	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
mouth	O
was	O
soft	O
enough	O
to	O
do	O
his	O
business	O
.	O
And	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Stafford	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
tryed	O
last	O
Sessions	O
for	O
Robbing	O
John	O
Smith	O
the	O
Lace-man	O
at	O
South	B-place
Mims-wash	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
then	O
acquitted	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
was	O
now	O
singly	O
tried	O
again	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Lyndsey	I-pers
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
and	O
Place	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
charge	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
Stafford	O
ride	O
into	O
South-Mims	O
Town	O
,	O
in	O
Company	O
of	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
more	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
called	O
several	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
account	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
another	O
Place	O
when	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
had	O
such	O
good	O
fortune	O
as	O
to	O
be	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Rowley	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
being	O
accessary	O
to	O
Catharine	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Felony	O
she	O
committed	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
her	O
Master	O
,	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Petrey	I-pers
;	O
it	O
was	O
witnessed	O
that	O
Rowley	O
bought	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
;	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Poor	I-pers
,	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Nealand	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Fetherstone	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
tried	O
;	O
first	O
for	O
robbing	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Paul	I-pers
of	O
St.	O
Mary	O
Islington	O
,	O
of	O
three	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
22	O
s.	O
and	O
8	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
secondly	O
for	O
robbing	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Richard	B-pers
Parrot	I-pers
of	O
15	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Hanger	O
,	O
Belt	O
and	O
Cane	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Paul	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
against	O
any	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
positively	O
,	O
only	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
Poor	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Parrot	O
said	O
that	O
six	O
of	O
them	O
met	O
them	O
between	O
Kingsland	O
and	O
Islington	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
them	O
off	O
their	O
Horses	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
kill	O
'd	O
one	O
Horse	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
more	O
kind	O
than	O
the	O
rest	O
;	O
Stacey	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
rob	O
the	O
two	O
above	O
mentioned	O
Persons	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
before	O
they	O
had	O
robbed	O
several	O
Merchants	O
of	O
40	O
l.	O
coming	O
from	O
Essex	O
towards	O
London	O
;	O
they	O
all	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
Nealand	O
called	O
some	O
Persons	O
who	O
were	O
his	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
for	O
his	O
Reputation	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
company	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
mistaken	O
;	O
Fetherstone	O
called	O
a	O
cloud	O
of	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
a	O
fair	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Poor	O
,	O
Nealand	O
,	O
and	O
Fetherstone	O
,	O
were	O
all	O
taken	O
at	O
the	O
Cheshire	O
Cheese	O
at	O
Chelsey	O
;	O
and	O
Poor	O
said	O
then	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
man	O
;	O
Philips	O
complained	O
against	O
Stacey	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
swore	O
against	O
them	O
to	O
save	O
his	O
own	O
life	O
;	O
but	O
yet	O
nothing	O
availed	O
them	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
four	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susan	B-pers
Norris	I-pers
for	O
clipping	O
the	O
currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
England	O
;	O
she	O
brought	O
a	O
Trunk	O
to	O
a	O
New	O
Lodging	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
a	O
File	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Clipt	O
Money	O
;	O
but	O
none	O
could	O
swear	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
how	O
the	O
Money	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
cut	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
Making	O
,	O
Coining	O
,	O
and	O
Counterfeiting	O
False	O
Money	O
;	O
It	O
was	O
sworn	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
some	O
false	O
Money	O
to	O
one	O
Ratsford	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
28	O
half	O
Crowns	O
for	O
20	O
,	O
by	O
way	O
of	O
encouragement	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
Ratsford	O
is	O
since	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
found	O
Melting-pots	O
,	O
Stamps	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Necessaries	O
fit	O
for	O
the	O
trade	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
False	O
Money	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Capell	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Joshua	B-pers
Granger	I-pers
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Flanders	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
24	O
s.	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
Granger	O
,	O
and	O
within	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
days	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Lace	O
was	O
missing	O
;	O
but	O
nothing	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
her	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Adlam	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Stable	O
of	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gurnet	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
four	O
small	O
Pigs	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Saddle	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
Pig	O
roasting	O
upon	O
the	O
Spit	O
at	O
a	O
Cook	O
's	O
Shop	O
near	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
Pig	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Chamber-pot	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Singleton	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
on	O
the	O
7th	O
day	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
;	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
found	O
the	O
Chamber-pot	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
she	O
lodged	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
Woman	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
drinking	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
might	O
as	O
well	O
take	O
it	O
;	O
She	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Holman	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
10	O
Quarter	O
of	O
Oates	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Prentice	I-pers
in	O
Milford-Lane	B-place
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
and	O
20	O
Sacks	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
there	O
were	O
20	O
empty	O
Sacks	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Corn	O
and	O
Sacks	O
were	O
lost	O
off	O
the	O
Wharf	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Corn	O
of	O
one	O
Richard	B-pers
Brome	I-pers
a	O
Lighter-man	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
was	O
arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Lace	O
Crevat	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
from	O
Joseph	B-pers
Barns	I-pers
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
coming	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
immediately	O
acquitted	O
.	O
ANN	B-pers
MERRYWEATHER	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
and	O
Tried	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
for	O
Composing	O
,	O
Printing	O
,	O
and	O
Publishing	O
the	O
late	O
King	O
James	O
's	O
Declaration	O
:	O
The	O
Gentlemen	O
who	O
were	O
summoned	O
to	O
Try	O
her	O
were	O
called	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
liberty	O
to	O
make	O
Exceptions	O
against	O
whom	O
she	O
pleased	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Prescription	O
of	O
Law	O
;	O
she	O
Challenged	O
to	O
the	O
Number	O
of	O
about	O
Thirty	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
who	O
were	O
sworn	O
are	O
those	O
whose	O
Names	O
follow	O
;	O
George	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Bateman	I-pers
.	O
Tanner	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Awbrey	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lathwell	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Burnel	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Ingram	I-pers
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Billing	I-pers
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Longland	I-pers
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Indictment	O
was	O
read	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
set	O
forth	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
being	O
a	O
person	O
of	O
a	O
turbulent	O
spirit	O
,	O
and	O
instigated	O
andseduced	O
by	O
the	O
Devil	O
,	O
and	O
minding	O
and	O
intending	O
to	O
Depose	O
and	O
put	O
to	O
Death	O
Their	O
most	O
Sacred	O
Majesties	O
King	O
William	O
and	O
Queen	O
Mary	O
;	O
and	O
to	O
subvert	O
and	O
alter	O
the	O
Government	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
;	O
and	O
to	O
draw	O
away	O
the	O
hearts	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
Subjects	O
from	O
their	O
Duty	O
and	O
Allegiance	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
incline	O
them	O
to	O
adhere	O
to	O
the	O
Interest	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
King	O
James	O
and	O
the	O
French	O
King	O
;	O
did	O
on	O
the	O
Seventh	O
day	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
past	O
,	O
Compose	O
,	O
Print	O
,	O
and	O
Publish	O
,	O
a	O
most	O
False	O
,	O
Pernicious	O
,	O
Traiterous	O
,	O
and	O
Scandalous	O
Libel	O
,	O
Signed	O
J.	O
R.	O
and	O
entituled	O
,	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
most	O
Gracious	O
Declaration	O
to	O
all	O
his	O
Loving	O
Subjects	O
;	O
commanding	O
their	O
Assistance	O
against	O
the	O
Prince	O
of	O
Orange	O
and	O
his	O
Adherents	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
the	O
Council	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
Queen	O
opened	O
the	O
Indictment	O
to	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
;	O
telling	O
of	O
what	O
bad	O
Consequence	O
and	O
evil	O
Example	O
such	O
Libels	O
were	O
;	O
and	O
how	O
it	O
tended	O
to	O
raise	O
a	O
Disaffection	O
in	O
the	O
hearts	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
Subjects	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
had	O
done	O
all	O
that	O
lay	O
in	O
her	O
power	O
to	O
promote	O
the	O
Interest	O
of	O
the	O
French	O
King	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
late	O
King	O
James	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
Levy	O
War	O
and	O
Rebellion	O
against	O
our	O
present	O
King	O
and	O
Queen	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
Restore	O
the	O
late	O
King	O
James	O
.	O
Several	O
Hundreds	O
of	O
the	O
Declarations	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
in	O
Covent-Garden	B-place
,	O
besides	O
other	O
Seditious	O
Pamphlets	O
,	O
entituled	O
,	O
The	O
Dear	O
Bargain	O
;	O
and	O
Just	O
Weights	O
and	O
Measures	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
To	O
prove	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
were	O
called	O
and	O
Sworn	O
:	O
The	O
first	O
of	O
which	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
having	O
Information	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
an	O
Ill	O
Woman	O
,	O
a	O
Warrant	O
was	O
obtained	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
under	O
a	O
pretence	O
of	O
her	O
being	O
a	O
Clipper	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
Constable	O
came	O
there	O
with	O
his	O
Assistants	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
searching	O
in	O
the	O
Garret	O
,	O
in	O
an	O
old	O
Trunk	O
was	O
found	O
a	O
great	O
Number	O
of	O
the	O
Declarations	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
Thousand	O
or	O
more	O
besides	O
other	O
Pamphlets	O
,	O
entituled	O
,	O
The	O
Dear	O
Bargain	O
;	O
Just	O
Weights	O
and	O
Measures	O
;	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
called	O
Hodge-Podge	O
as	O
before-mentioned	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
seemed	O
very	O
much	O
surprized	O
at	O
their	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
Papers	O
;	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
Searchers	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
Clipp	O
'd	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
what	O
had	O
they	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
Papers	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
?	O
They	O
seized	O
the	O
Pamphlets	O
and	O
the	O
Declarations	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
her	O
before	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
who	O
committed	O
her	O
to	O
Newgate	O
for	O
the	O
Offence	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
concurring	O
Evidence	O
to	O
the	O
Matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
;	O
especially	O
two	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
owned	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Papers	O
from	O
Westminster	O
,	O
brought	O
to	O
her	O
by	O
a	O
Boy	O
who	O
she	O
called	O
Black	O
or	O
Jack	O
;	O
but	O
would	O
not	O
acknowledge	O
who	O
was	O
the	O
Author	O
or	O
Printer	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
sate	O
up	O
all	O
night	O
to	O
dry	O
the	O
Declarations	O
,	O
being	O
newly	O
brought	O
from	O
the	O
Press	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
bundled	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
in	O
Coaches	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
Confess	O
'd	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
disposed	O
of	O
several	O
of	O
them	O
amongst	O
her	O
Friends	O
,	O
(	O
but	O
she	O
lookt	O
upon	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
Waste	O
Paper	O
)	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Papers	O
were	O
to	O
be	O
brought	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
received	O
them	O
she	O
promised	O
the	O
Witness	O
that	O
she	O
should	O
have	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
some	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
an	O
ingenuous	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
her	O
self	O
well	O
in	O
times	O
past	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
general	O
Conversation	O
.	O
After	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
withdrew	O
to	O
Consider	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
half	O
an	O
hours	O
time	O
they	O
brought	O
in	O
a	O
Verdict	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Guilty	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
.	O
After	O
which	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Condemned	O
to	O
be	O
Burnt	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Ambrose	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
after	O
the	O
Condemnation	O
was	O
past	O
,	O
was	O
brought	O
into	O
Court	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
charged	O
upon	O
the	O
Jury	O
upon	O
Oath	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
to	O
satisfie	O
all	O
people	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
Company	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
and	O
one	O
Aldgood	O
High-Way	O
Men	O
,	O
stole	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
Horses	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Grounds	O
near	O
Tatnum	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
Horses	O
of	O
Major	O
Langstone	O
:	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
plead	O
to	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
but	O
Aldgood	O
proved	O
it	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
notice	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
but	O
a	O
feign	O
'd	O
Excuse	O
;	O
He	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
executed	O
this	O
Sessions	O
.	O
NOtwithstanding	O
the	O
great	O
Indulgence	O
that	O
hath	O
been	O
shewed	O
to	O
several	O
great	O
and	O
wicked	O
Offenders	O
,	O
who	O
have	O
(	O
since	O
the	O
Corronation	O
of	O
our	O
most	O
Gracious	O
King	O
and	O
Queen	O
that	O
now	O
is	O
)	O
been	O
Committed	O
to	O
Newgate	O
for	O
their	O
Enormous	O
and	O
Mischievous	O
Faults	O
;	O
yet	O
how	O
many	O
are	O
there	O
(	O
that	O
tho	O
their	O
Eyes	O
are	O
open	O
)	O
do	O
blind	O
themselves	O
,	O
and	O
will	O
not	O
see	O
into	O
the	O
Abyss	O
and	O
Depth	O
of	O
that	O
Misery	O
wherein	O
they	O
involve	O
themselves	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
of	O
their	O
perverse	O
and	O
unreformable	O
Lives	O
?	O
But	O
will	O
still	O
go	O
on	O
in	O
the	O
pursuit	O
of	O
their	O
premeditated	O
and	O
base	O
Designs	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
great	O
Loss	O
and	O
Destruction	O
(	O
not	O
only	O
)	O
of	O
honest	O
Mens	O
Rights	O
but	O
to	O
the	O
utter	O
Ruin	O
(	O
many	O
times	O
)	O
of	O
their	O
own	O
Souls	O
and	O
Bodies	O
;	O
yet	O
for	O
all	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
purpose	O
to	O
shew	O
Mercy	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
extend	O
Their	O
Royal	O
Favour	O
and	O
Bounty	O
,	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
Queen	O
did	O
at	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
of	O
this	O
Session	O
,	O
Grant	O
a	O
Pardon	O
to	O
those	O
Persons	O
whose	O
Names	O
follow	O
,	O
who	O
all	O
pleaded	O
the	O
same	O
on	O
their	O
Knees	O
in	O
open	O
Court	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Dixy	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Kallaway	I-pers
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
.	O
James	B-pers
Forbes	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Pledwell	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Abel	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Demey	I-pers
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Scofield	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Overton	I-pers
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Mead	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
.	O
Joanna	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Margaret	I-pers
Moor	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tovey	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Page	I-pers
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Thursfield	I-pers
.	O
James	B-pers
Duncomb	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Child	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Aldgood	I-pers
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
.	O
George	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Warrington	I-pers
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Welsh	I-pers
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Chandler	I-pers
.	O
After	O
they	O
had	O
all	O
kneeled	O
down	O
,	O
the	O
Pardon	O
was	O
read	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Convicts	O
were	O
all	O
advised	O
to	O
take	O
due	O
warning	O
by	O
such	O
and	O
so	O
great	O
Clemency	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
lead	O
better	O
Lives	O
for	O
the	O
future	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
they	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
much	O
affected	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
remanded	O
to	O
the	O
Goal	O
.	O
THe	O
Grand	O
Jury	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
did	O
this	O
Sessions	O
bring	O
a	O
Presentment	O
into	O
Court	O
against	O
several	O
Abuses	O
and	O
Misdemeanors	O
committed	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Displeasure	O
of	O
Almighty	O
God	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Dishonour	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
First	O
,	O
Against	O
Ale-houses	O
and	O
Taverns	O
,	O
who	O
suffer	O
lewd	O
and	O
evil-disposed	O
Persons	O
,	O
to	O
fit	O
Tipling	O
and	O
Drinking	O
on	O
the	O
Lords	O
Day	O
.	O
Secondly	O
,	O
Against	O
all	O
such	O
who	O
lay	O
Unnecessary	O
and	O
Impertinent	O
Wagers	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
several	O
Offices	O
kept	O
about	O
the	O
Town	O
to	O
encourage	O
Persons	O
so	O
to	O
do	O
.	O
Thirdly	O
,	O
Against	O
all	O
Lotteries	O
and	O
Gaming-houses	O
,	O
especially	O
against	O
the	O
Royal-Oak	O
Lottery	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
of	O
bad	O
Consequence	O
to	O
the	O
Youth	O
,	O
and	O
Apprentices	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
.	O
Fourthly	O
,	O
Against	O
all	O
Persons	O
who	O
entertain	O
such	O
Persons	O
who	O
pick	O
up	O
each	O
other	O
in	O
the	O
Streets	O
.	O
To	O
this	O
the	O
Court	O
was	O
pleased	O
to	O
Answer	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
had	O
made	O
a	O
very	O
Grave	O
and	O
Sober	O
Presentment	O
;	O
and	O
Order	O
'd	O
that	O
Processes	O
should	O
be	O
made	O
out	O
against	O
several	O
particular	O
Houses	O
in	O
and	O
about	O
the	O
City	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
the	O
Suppression	O
of	O
all	O
such	O
Offenders	O
;	O
it	O
being	O
of	O
very	O
evil	O
Example	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
great	O
Mischief	O
to	O
the	O
Interest	O
of	O
all	O
Men	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Sentence	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
11	O
.	O
John	O
Ayers	O
.	O
S	O
-	O
J	O
-	O
Elizabeth	O
Jones	O
.	O
Alice	O
Page	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Bird	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Oswin	O
.	O
Daniel	O
Hopkins	O
.	O
Richard	O
Holman	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Lurcock	O
.	O
Katherine	O
Jones	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Gibson	O
,	O
Convicted	O
last	O
Sessions	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
10	O
James	O
Whitney	O
.	O
James	O
Phillips	O
.	O
Edward	O
Poor	O
.	O
Nicholas	O
Nealand	O
John	O
Fetherstone	O
.	O
Nathanael	O
Gross	O
,	O
all	O
Highway-men	O
.	O
William	O
Turner	O
.	O
Ann	O
Merryweather	O
.	O
Mary	O
Wilder	O
.	O
Katherine	O
Davis	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
latter	O
were	O
found	O
quick	O
with	O
Child	O
.	O
Ambrose	O
Holland	O
and	O
Elkana	O
Smewin	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
Convicted	O
last	O
Session	O
for	O
a	O
Robbery	O
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
(	O
at	O
South-Mims	O
)	O
were	O
called	O
to	O
their	O
former	O
Judgment	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
to	O
make	O
themselves	O
ready	O
for	O
their	O
Execution	O
with	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
,	O
9	O
Robert	O
Wayt	O
.	O
Mabell	O
Symons	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Belcher	O
.	O
John	O
Pabworth	O
.	O
Sarah	O
Delawny	O
.	O
John	O
Norris	O
.	O
Sarah	O
Stephens	O
.	O
Ann	O
Ferguson	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Hewin	O
.	O
Persons	O
Respitted	O
from	O
Branding	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
into	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
Service	O
by	O
Sea	O
or	O
Land	O
,	O
by	O
their	O
own	O
free	O
Consent	O
.	O
John	O
Coates	O
.	O
John	O
Pullen	O
.	O
John	O
Salter	O
.	O
B	O
-	O
J	O
-	O
Thomas	O
Hynton	O
.	O
Robert	O
Beames	O
.	O
Richard	O
Ford	O
.	O
Peregrin	O
Barret	O
.	O
Francis	O
Wheeler	O
.	O
NOtwithstanding	O
the	O
great	O
Indulgence	O
that	O
hath	O
been	O
shewed	O
to	O
several	O
great	O
and	O
wicked	O
Offenders	O
,	O
who	O
have	O
(	O
since	O
the	O
Corronation	O
of	O
our	O
most	O
Gracious	O
King	O
and	O
Queen	O
that	O
now	O
is	O
)	O
been	O
Committed	O
to	O
Newgate	O
for	O
their	O
Enormous	O
and	O
Mischievous	O
Faults	O
;	O
yet	O
how	O
many	O
are	O
there	O
(	O
that	O
tho	O
their	O
Eyes	O
are	O
open	O
)	O
do	O
blind	O
themselves	O
,	O
and	O
will	O
not	O
see	O
into	O
the	O
Abyss	O
and	O
Depth	O
of	O
that	O
Misery	O
wherein	O
they	O
involve	O
themselves	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
of	O
their	O
perverse	O
and	O
unreformable	O
Lives	O
?	O
But	O
will	O
still	O
go	O
on	O
in	O
the	O
pursuit	O
of	O
their	O
premeditated	O
and	O
base	O
Designs	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
great	O
Loss	O
and	O
Destruction	O
(	O
not	O
only	O
)	O
of	O
honest	O
Mens	O
Rights	O
but	O
to	O
the	O
utter	O
Ruin	O
(	O
many	O
times	O
)	O
of	O
their	O
own	O
Souls	O
and	O
Bodies	O
;	O
yet	O
for	O
all	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
purpose	O
to	O
shew	O
Mercy	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
extend	O
Their	O
Royal	O
Favour	O
and	O
Bounty	O
,	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
Queen	O
did	O
at	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
of	O
this	O
Session	O
,	O
Grant	O
a	O
Pardon	O
to	O
those	O
Persons	O
whose	O
Names	O
follow	O
,	O
who	O
all	O
pleaded	O
the	O
same	O
on	O
their	O
Knees	O
in	O
open	O
Court	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Dixy	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Kallaway	I-pers
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
.	O
James	B-pers
Forbes	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Pledwell	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Abel	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Demey	I-pers
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Scofield	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Overton	I-pers
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Mead	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
.	O
Joanna	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Margaret	I-pers
Moor	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tovey	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Page	I-pers
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Thursfield	I-pers
.	O
James	B-pers
Duncomb	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Child	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Aldgood	I-pers
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
.	O
George	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Warrington	I-pers
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Welsh	I-pers
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Chandler	I-pers
.	O
After	O
they	O
had	O
all	O
kneeled	O
down	O
,	O
the	O
Pardon	O
was	O
read	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Convicts	O
were	O
all	O
advised	O
to	O
take	O
due	O
warning	O
by	O
such	O
and	O
so	O
great	O
Clemency	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
lead	O
better	O
Lives	O
for	O
the	O
future	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
they	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
much	O
affected	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
remanded	O
to	O
the	O
Goal	O
.	O
Ben	B-pers
.	I-pers
Kellow	I-pers
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
to	O
Kent	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
tryed	O
at	O
the	O
next	O
Assizes	O
held	O
there	O
for	O
a	O
Robbery	O
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Stafford	I-pers
,	O
for	O
suspicion	O
of	O
being	O
a	O
High-way	O
Man	O
,	O
sent	O
into	O
Barkshire	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Brett	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Giles	B-pers
Wilcox	I-pers
were	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
continued	O
till	O
next	O
Sessions	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
peremptorily	O
to	O
be	O
tried	O
or	O
discharged	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Canning	I-pers
continued	O
.	O
Adam	B-pers
Banks	I-pers
brought	O
a	O
Certe	O
Orars	O
to	O
remove	O
his	O
Cause	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Lumsden	I-pers
for	O
publishing	O
a	O
Scandalous	O
Libel	O
,	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
try	O
'd	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
The	O
Lord	O
Banbury	O
to	O
rest	O
till	O
further	O
Order	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
The	O
Fourth	O
Edition	O
of	O
the	O
New	O
Martyrology	O
or	O
Bloody	O
Assizes	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Concerning	O
several	O
Speeches	O
,	O
Letters	O
,	O
Elegies	O
,	O
and	O
New	O
Discoveries	O
,	O
(	O
sent	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
WEST	O
)	O
never	O
printed	O
before	O
:	O
As	O
also	O
many	O
large	O
and	O
Private	O
Memoirs	O
sent	O
from	O
other	O
places	O
,	O
which	O
renders	O
this	O
Fourth	O
Edition	O
A	O
New	O
SECRET	O
HISTORY	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
Times	O
:	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
the	O
Effigies	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
Eminent	O
Sufferers	O
,	O
with	O
many	O
New	O
Poems	O
on	O
their	O
Deaths	O
,	O
not	O
printed	O
before	O
;	O
as	O
also	O
a	O
much	O
larger	O
Account	O
than	O
has	O
yet	O
been	O
given	O
of	O
the	O
LIFE	O
and	O
DEATH	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
Lord	O
JEFFERIES	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
whole	O
Work	O
is	O
now	O
Compleat	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
ALPHABETICAL	O
TABLE	O
annext	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Published	O
by	O
Thomas	O
Pitts	O
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
Printed	O
(	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Original	O
Copies	O
)	O
for	O
John	O
Dunton	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Raven	O
in	O
the	O
Poultrey	O
.	O
A	O
Succinct	O
and	O
Seasonable	O
Discourse	O
of	O
the	O
Occasions	O
,	O
Causes	O
,	O
Nature	O
,	O
Rise	O
,	O
Growth	O
,	O
and	O
Remedies	O
of	O
Mental	O
Errors	O
:	O
Whereunto	O
are	O
subjoyned	O
,	O
by	O
way	O
of	O
Appendix	O
,	O
I.	O
Vindiciarum	O
Vindex	O
,	O
Being	O
a	O
Succinct	O
,	O
but	O
full	O
Answer	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Philip	O
Cary	O
's	O
Weak	O
and	O
Impertinent	O
Exceptions	O
to	O
my	O
Vindiciae	O
Legis	O
&	O
Foederis	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
A	O
Sinopsis	O
of	O
Ancient	O
and	O
Modern	O
Antinomian	O
Errors	O
,	O
with	O
Scriptural	O
Arguments	O
and	O
Reasons	O
against	O
them	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
A	O
Sermon	O
composed	O
for	O
preventing	O
and	O
healing	O
of	O
Rents	O
and	O
Divisions	O
in	O
the	O
Churches	O
of	O
Christ	O
;	O
with	O
an	O
Epistle	O
by	O
several	O
Divines	O
,	O
relating	O
to	O
Dr	O
.	O
Crisp	O
's	O
Works	O
.	O
The	O
Reasonableness	O
of	O
Personal	O
Reformation	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Necessity	O
of	O
Conversion	O
:	O
The	O
true	O
Methods	O
of	O
making	O
all	O
men	O
happy	O
in	O
this	O
world	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
to	O
come	O
;	O
seasonably	O
discoursed	O
,	O
and	O
expresly	O
pressed	O
,	O
upon	O
this	O
licentious	O
Age	O
.	O
Mr.	O
John	O
Flavell	O
's	O
Remains	O
:	O
Being	O
two	O
Sermons	O
composed	O
by	O
that	O
Reverend	O
and	O
Learned	O
Divine	O
;	O
the	O
former	O
preached	O
at	O
Dartmouth	O
in	O
Devon	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
happy	O
Coronation	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
,	O
King	O
William	O
and	O
Queen	O
Mary	O
,	O
the	O
latter	O
intended	O
to	O
be	O
preached	O
at	O
Taunton	O
in	O
Somerset	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Meeting	O
of	O
the	O
United	O
Ministers	O
of	O
several	O
Counties	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
held	O
there	O
,	O
Sept	O
2	O
.	O
1691	O
.	O
With	O
a	O
brief	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Life	O
and	O
Death	O
of	O
that	O
Reverend	O
Author	O
.	O
An	O
Explanation	O
of	O
the	O
Assemblies	O
Catechism	O
,	O
with	O
Practical	O
Inferences	O
from	O
each	O
Question	O
.	O
All	O
by	O
Mr.	O
John	O
Flavell	O
.	O
A	O
Sermon	O
at	O
the	O
Funeral	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
Reverend	O
Divine	O
Mr.	O
Edward	O
West	O
.	O
A	O
Discourse	O
of	O
Regeneration	O
,	O
Faith	O
and	O
Repentance	O
.	O
A	O
Discourse	O
of	O
Christian	O
Religion	O
on	O
sundry	O
Points	O
.	O
The	O
Incomprehensibleness	O
of	O
Imputed	O
Righteousness	O
for	O
Justification	O
,	O
by	O
human	O
Reason	O
,	O
till	O
enlightened	O
by	O
the	O
Spirit	O
of	O
God	O
.	O
These	O
four	O
published	O
by	O
the	O
Reverend	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	O
Cole	O
.	O
Love	O
to	O
Christ	O
necessary	O
to	O
Escape	O
the	O
Curse	O
at	O
his	O
Coming	O
.	O
By	O
Thomas	O
Doolitle	O
,	O
M.	O
A.	O
Geography	O
Anatomized	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
A	O
Compleat	O
Geographical	O
Grammar	O
.	O
Being	O
a	O
Short	O
and	O
Exact	O
Analysis	O
of	O
the	O
whole	O
Body	O
of	O
Modern	O
Geography	O
,	O
after	O
a	O
New	O
,	O
Plain	O
and	O
Easie	O
Method	O
,	O
whereby	O
any	O
Person	O
may	O
in	O
a	O
short	O
time	O
attain	O
to	O
the	O
knowledge	O
of	O
that	O
most	O
noble	O
and	O
useful	O
Science	O
.	O
Comprehending	O
a	O
most	O
Compendious	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Continents	O
,	O
Islands	O
,	O
Peninsula	O
's	O
,	O
Isthmus	O
,	O
Promontories	O
,	O
Mountains	O
,	O
Oceans	O
,	O
Seas	O
,	O
Gulphs	O
,	O
Straits	O
,	O
Lakes	O
Rivers	O
and	O
chief	O
Towns	O
of	O
the	O
whole	O
Earth	O
.	O
As	O
also	O
the	O
Divisions	O
,	O
Subdivisions	O
,	O
Scituation	O
,	O
Extent	O
,	O
Air	O
,	O
Soil	O
,	O
Commodities	O
,	O
Manners	O
,	O
Government	O
,	O
Religion	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
Countries	O
of	O
the	O
World	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
subjoin	O
'd	O
the	O
present	O
State	O
of	O
the	O
European	O
Plantations	O
in	O
the	O
East	O
and	O
West	O
Indies	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Reasonable	O
Proposal	O
for	O
the	O
Propagation	O
of	O
the	O
Bleffed	O
Gospel	O
in	O
all	O
Pagan	O
Countries	O
.	O
The	O
whole	O
Work	O
carefully	O
performed	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
exactest	O
and	O
latest	O
Discoveries	O
.	O
Illustrated	O
with	O
divers	O
Maps	O
.	O
By	O
Pat	O
.	O
Gordon	O
,	O
M.	O
A	O
.	O
All	O
sold	O
by	O
Thomas	O
Cockerill	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Leggs	O
in	O
the	O
Poultrey	O
.	O
The	O
Tragedies	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
Age	O
,	O
consider	O
'd	O
and	O
examin	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Practice	O
of	O
the	O
Ancients	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
common	O
Sense	O
of	O
all	O
Ages	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
Letter	O
to	O
Fleetwood	O
Shepheard	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Part	O
.	O
I	O
.	O
The	O
Second	O
Edition	O
.	O
A	O
short	O
View	O
of	O
Tragedy	O
;	O
Its	O
Original	O
,	O
Excellency	O
,	O
and	O
Corruption	O
.	O
With	O
some	O
Reflections	O
on	O
Shakespear	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Practitioners	O
for	O
the	O
Stage	O
.	O
Both	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Rymer	O
,	O
Servant	O
to	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
.	O
State	O
Tracts	O
:	O
Being	O
a	O
farther	O
Collection	O
of	O
several	O
Choice	O
Treatises	O
relating	O
to	O
the	O
Government	O
from	O
the	O
Year	O
1660.	O
to	O
1689	O
.	O
Now	O
published	O
in	O
a	O
body	O
to	O
shew	O
the	O
Necessity	O
,	O
and	O
clear	O
the	O
Legality	O
of	O
the	O
Late	O
Revolution	O
,	O
and	O
our	O
present	O
Happy	O
Settlement	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
Auspicious	O
Reign	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
,	O
King	O
William	O
and	O
Queen	O
Mary	O
Mathematical	O
Magick	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
The	O
Wonders	O
that	O
may	O
be	O
performed	O
by	O
Mechanical	O
Geometry	O
.	O
In	O
Two	O
Books	O
.	O
Concerning	O
Mechanical	O
Powers	O
,	O
and	O
Motions	O
.	O
Being	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
Easie	O
,	O
Pleasant	O
,	O
Useful	O
,	O
(	O
and	O
yet	O
most	O
neglected	O
)	O
part	O
of	O
Mathematicks	O
.	O
Not	O
before	O
treated	O
of	O
in	O
this	O
Language	O
.	O
By	O
J.	O
Wilkins	O
,	O
late	O
Lord	O
Bishop	O
of	O
Chester	O
.	O
The	O
Fourth	O
Edition	O
.	O
Truth	O
brought	O
to	O
Light	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
The	O
History	O
of	O
the	O
First	O
14	O
Years	O
of	O
King	O
James	O
the	O
1st	O
.	O
In	O
Four	O
Parts	O
.	O
I	O
.	O
The	O
Happy	O
State	O
of	O
England	O
at	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Entrance	O
;	O
The	O
Corruption	O
of	O
it	O
afterwards	O
.	O
With	O
the	O
Rise	O
of	O
particular	O
Favourites	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Divisions	O
between	O
this	O
and	O
other	O
States	O
abroad	O
.	O
II	O
The	O
Divorce	O
betwixt	O
the	O
Lady	O
Frances	O
Howard	O
and	O
Robert	O
Earl	O
of	O
Essex	O
before	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Delegates	O
,	O
authorized	O
under	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Broad	O
Seal	O
As	O
also	O
the	O
Arraignment	O
of	O
Sir	O
Jervis	O
Yelvis	O
,	O
Lieutenant	O
of	O
the	O
Tower	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
about	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Sir	O
Thomas	O
Overbury	O
,	O
with	O
all	O
Proceedings	O
thereupon	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Gracious	O
Pardon	O
and	O
Favour	O
to	O
the	O
Countess	O
.	O
III	O
.	O
A	O
Declaration	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Revenue	O
since	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Crown	O
of	O
England	O
;	O
with	O
the	O
Annual	O
Issues	O
,	O
Gifts	O
,	O
Pensions	O
,	O
and	O
Extraordinary	O
Disbursements	O
.	O
IV	O
.	O
The	O
Commissions	O
and	O
Warrants	O
for	O
burning	O
two	O
Hereticks	O
,	O
newly	O
revived	O
with	O
two	O
Pardons	O
,	O
one	O
for	O
Theophilus	O
Higgons	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
Sir	O
Eustace	O
Hart	O
.	O
All	O
Printed	O
for	O
Richard	O
Baldwin	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
to	O
give	O
notice	O
to	O
all	O
Persons	O
for	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
the	O
Publick	O
That	O
W.	O
Elmy	O
Professor	O
of	O
Physick	O
,	O
and	O
Operator	O
,	O
of	O
known	O
Integrity	O
,	O
and	O
above	O
25	O
Years	O
Practice	O
,	O
liveth	O
at	O
the	O
Blew-Ball	O
in	O
Whale-Bone-Court	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
lower	O
end	O
of	O
Bartholomew-Lane	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Royal-Exchange	O
.	O
:	O
Who	O
most	O
safely	O
and	O
expenditiously	O
cures	O
Deafness	O
,	O
and	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
Ears	O
,	O
in	O
any	O
,	O
of	O
what	O
Age	O
soever	O
,	O
(	O
if	O
curable	O
)	O
and	O
as	O
first	O
sight	O
by	O
inspection	O
resolves	O
the	O
Patient	O
,	O
if	O
so	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
as	O
most	O
eminent	O
Persons	O
of	O
Quality	O
in	O
this	O
City	O
can	O
testifie	O
.	O
He	O
hath	O
likewise	O
a	O
Sovereign	O
Head-Pill	O
,	O
which	O
infallibly	O
cures	O
all	O
Pains	O
in	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
whether	O
old	O
or	O
newly	O
contracted	O
;	O
Speedily	O
taking	O
away	O
all	O
Swimmings	O
and	O
Giddiness	O
,	O
preventing	O
the	O
dangerous	O
consequence	O
of	O
Apoplectical	O
Fits	O
;	O
preserves	O
the	O
Sight	O
,	O
and	O
takes	O
away	O
all	O
Accidents	O
offending	O
the	O
Eyes	O
.	O
strengthens	O
the	O
Memory	O
,	O
and	O
disburthens	O
the	O
Brain	O
of	O
all	O
offensive	O
Humours	O
,	O
thereby	O
rendring	O
the	O
Understanding	O
more	O
clear	O
and	O
vigorous	O
.	O
These	O
Pills	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
.	O
He	O
bath	O
also	O
Pills	O
only	O
prepared	O
for	O
the	O
French	O
Disease	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Running	O
of	O
the	O
Reins	O
,	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
in	O
Boxes	O
of	O
several	O
Prizes	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
Venerial	O
Arcanaes	O
,	O
as	O
occasion	O
requires	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
He	O
bath	O
likewise	O
an	O
expeditious	O
way	O
in	O
curing	O
all	O
pains	O
in	O
the	O
Teeth	O
without	O
drawing	O
He	O
hath	O
likewise	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Gargarisme	O
or	O
Mouth-Water	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
make	O
black	O
or	O
yellow	O
Teeth	O
as	O
white	O
as	O
Ivory	O
in	O
few	O
times	O
using	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
will	O
certainly	O
cure	O
the	O
Scurvey	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
Diseases	O
incident	O
to	O
the	O
Mouth	O
,	O
Teeth	O
and	O
Gums	O
;	O
with	O
Directions	O
.	O
In	O
Grays-Inn-Lane	O
in	O
Plow-Yard	O
,	O
the	O
third	O
Door	O
,	O
lives	O
Dr.	O
Thomas	O
Kirleus	O
,	O
a	O
Collegiate	O
Physician	O
,	O
and	O
Sworn	O
Physician	O
in	O
Ordinary	O
to	O
King	O
Charles	O
II	O
until	O
his	O
Death	O
,	O
who	O
with	O
a	O
Drink	O
and	O
Pill	O
(	O
hindring	O
no	O
Business	O
)	O
undertakes	O
to	O
Care	O
any	O
Uicers	O
,	O
Sores	O
,	O
Swellings	O
in	O
the	O
Nose	O
,	O
Face	O
,	O
or	O
other	O
Parts	O
;	O
Scabes	O
,	O
Itch	O
,	O
Scurfs	O
,	O
Leprosies	O
,	O
and	O
Veneral	O
Disease	O
expecting	O
nothing	O
until	O
the	O
Cure	O
be	O
finished	O
:	O
Of	O
the	O
Last	O
he	O
bath	O
cured	O
many	O
hundred	O
in	O
this	O
City	O
,	O
many	O
of	O
them	O
after	O
Fuxing	O
,	O
which	O
carries	O
the	O
Evil	O
from	O
the	O
Lower	O
Parts	O
to	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
destroys	O
many	O
.	O
The	O
Drink	O
is	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Quart	O
,	O
the	O
Pill	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
Box	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
;	O
a	O
better	O
Purger	O
than	O
which	O
was	O
never	O
given	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
cleanse	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
all	O
Impurities	O
,	O
which	O
are	O
the	O
Causes	O
of	O
Dropsies	O
,	O
Gout	O
,	O
Scurvies	O
,	O
Stone	O
or	O
Grawel	O
.	O
Pains	O
in	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Parts	O
.	O
With	O
another	O
Drink	O
at	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Quart	O
.	O
He	O
cure	O
all	O
Fevers	O
and	O
hot	O
Distempers	O
without	O
Bleeding	O
,	O
except	O
in	O
few	O
Bodies	O
.	O
He	O
gives	O
his	O
Opinion	O
to	O
all	O
that	O
writes	O
or	O
comes	O
for	O
nothing	O
.	O
