TOKEN	NE
The	O
Proceedings	O
of	O
the	O
KING	O
and	O
QUEEN	O
'S	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bayly	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
6th	O
,	O
7th	O
,	O
8th	O
and	O
9th	O
Days	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
1693	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
Fifth	O
Year	O
of	O
Their	O
MAJESTIES	O
Reign	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
6th	O
,	O
7th	O
,	O
8th	O
and	O
9th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
1693.	O
before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fleet	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
Salathiel	B-pers
Lovell	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
follow	O
,	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Stroud	I-pers
.	O
Archibald	B-pers
Willson	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Wynkle	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Langbridge	I-pers
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nutt	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Fryar	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bayly	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Hitch	I-pers
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Sherlock	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Edmund	B-pers
Salter	I-pers
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Biscoe	I-pers
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
Morgain	B-pers
Hynde	I-pers
.	O
Peter	B-pers
King	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Wade	I-pers
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pattle	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Henley	I-pers
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Rufford	I-pers
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
these	O
,	O
Prudence	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
divers	O
small	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
6	O
s.	O
from	O
Edward	B-pers
Styles	I-pers
,	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susanna	B-pers
Tanner	I-pers
,	O
was	O
arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Cloth	O
from	O
Tobias	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
value	O
16	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
fifth	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
confessed	O
upon	O
her	O
Arraignment	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Trapps	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Maculley	I-pers
Wife	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Maculley	I-pers
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
past	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Evidence	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
riding	O
a	O
Horse-back	O
along	O
Leaden	B-place
hall-street	I-place
;	O
the	O
said	O
Mrs.	O
Maculley	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
walking	O
along	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Horse	O
being	O
too	O
strong	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
against	O
the	O
two	O
Women	O
and	O
struck	O
them	O
down	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
said	O
Mrs.	O
Maculley	O
received	O
a	O
mortal	O
Bruise	O
near	O
her	O
left	O
Ear	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
died	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
received	O
little	O
hurt	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
declared	O
that	O
his	O
Horse	O
stumbled	O
and	O
fell	O
on	O
his	O
Knees	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
spur	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Horse	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
what	O
he	O
could	O
to	O
stop	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
was	O
evidenced	O
by	O
several	O
Persons	O
that	O
he	O
produced	O
on	O
his	O
behalf	O
,	O
that	O
saw	O
the	O
matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
nine	O
Yards	O
of	O
Bone-lace	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Lawse	I-pers
on	O
the	O
8th	O
day	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Emsworth	I-pers
in	O
Loathbury	B-place
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
one	O
Watch	O
with	O
a	O
Silver	O
case	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
another	O
Watch	O
value	O
20	O
s	O
upon	O
evidence	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
about	O
eleven	O
a	O
clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
pick	O
'd	O
the	O
Lock	O
of	O
the	O
Hatch	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
got	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
from	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
immediately	O
stopt	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
dropt	O
the	O
Watches	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
;	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Adam	B-pers
Martyn	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Norman	I-pers
Carmen	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
tried	O
for	O
killing	O
one	O
Jane	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
a	O
Child	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
July	O
in	O
Cannon-street	B-place
;	O
they	O
were	O
driving	O
their	O
Carts	O
hastily	O
along	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
striving	O
which	O
should	O
get	O
formost	O
;	O
and	O
Martin	O
's	O
Cart	O
drove	O
Norman	O
's	O
Cart	O
upon	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
squeezed	O
it	O
to	O
death	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
driving	O
in	O
haste	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
to	O
do	O
any	O
hurt	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
the	O
fault	O
one	O
upon	O
another	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
directed	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
telling	O
them	O
,	O
That	O
tho	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
about	O
their	O
lawful	O
Imployment	O
,	O
yet	O
they	O
ought	O
to	O
be	O
careful	O
how	O
they	O
drive	O
their	O
Carts	O
;	O
and	O
altho	O
the	O
Fact	O
could	O
not	O
reach	O
their	O
Lives	O
,	O
yet	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
a	O
warning	O
to	O
others	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
must	O
not	O
think	O
to	O
escape	O
:	O
So	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Daniel	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
and	O
Francis	B-pers
Herring	I-pers
were	O
both	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
black	O
Mare	O
price	O
20	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
William	B-pers
Lord	I-pers
Sey	I-pers
and	I-pers
Sign	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
the	O
Mare	O
in	O
Gloucestershire	O
by	O
two	O
men	O
on	O
the	O
High	O
way	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
the	O
men	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
declared	O
that	O
the	O
Mare	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Mairmaid	O
in	O
Carter-lane	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
kept	O
by	O
a	O
Porter	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
her	O
being	O
stolen	O
:	O
So	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
Gent	O
.	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Strowd	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
near	O
to	O
his	O
right	O
Pap	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
six	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
immediately	O
died	O
Upon	O
the	O
Evidence	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
were	O
Fellow	O
Soldiers	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
drinking	O
together	O
in	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
,	O
some	O
difference	O
arose	O
betwixt	O
them	O
about	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
and	O
sought	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
kill	O
Strowd	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
had	O
some	O
difference	O
about	O
their	O
Horses	O
some	O
small	O
time	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
Friends	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
alledged	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
Strowd	O
began	O
the	O
Quarrel	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Reckoning	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
willing	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Strowd	O
did	O
provoke	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
his	O
Blood	O
;	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
very	O
urging	O
Language	O
,	O
swearing	O
God	O
Damn	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
his	O
Blood	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
and	O
cut	O
Mr.	O
Francis	O
over	O
the	O
Head	O
first	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
confirmed	O
by	O
good	O
Evidence	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
side	O
:	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Boy	O
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Quarterman	I-pers
Widow	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
in	O
the	O
day-time	O
about	O
three	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
without	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Fellow	O
within	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
catcht	O
in	O
the	O
pursuit	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Matthew	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Ounce	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
of	O
Hair	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
from	O
Frances	B-pers
Hicks	I-pers
Widow	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Hicks	O
's	O
House	O
about	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
sell	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
the	O
Hair	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Hicks	O
;	O
and	O
before	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
went	O
away	O
they	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Hair	O
:	O
He	O
had	O
very	O
credible	O
Evidence	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tavernour	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Mare	O
coloured	O
gray	O
from	O
Edward	B-pers
Henderson	I-pers
,	O
price	O
4	O
l.	O
which	O
he	O
lost	O
off	O
Epping	B-place
Forrest	I-place
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
swopt	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
one	O
Robert	B-pers
Symmons	I-pers
of	O
South-Lambeth	O
,	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
which	O
Mare	O
was	O
owned	O
by	O
Henderson	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
confest	O
it	O
in	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
tho	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Trial	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Cammell	I-pers
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
laced	O
Pinner	O
and	O
a	O
Coif	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
from	O
one	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Smithergill	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
third	O
of	O
August	O
:	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
to	O
a	O
Broker	O
in	O
East-Smithfield	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
little	O
Girl	O
she	O
met	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Essington	I-pers
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
his	O
Goods	O
.	O
He	O
having	O
leave	O
to	O
lye	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
did	O
attempt	O
first	O
to	O
get	O
Mrs.	O
Dorcas	O
Essington	O
's	O
Rings	O
of	O
her	O
Finger	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
;	O
andhe	O
put	O
her	O
in	O
bodily	O
fear	O
,	O
as	O
was	O
sworn	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Mrs.	O
Essington	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
quartered	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Dorcas	O
and	O
he	O
lived	O
as	O
Man	O
and	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
one	O
Pocket	O
and	O
one	O
Bed	O
.	O
It	O
seemed	O
to	O
favour	O
of	O
Malice	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
several	O
Soldiers	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
account	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
more	O
than	O
ordinary	O
Familiarity	O
betwixt	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
wont	O
to	O
be	O
naught	O
together	O
:	O
And	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Ogle	I-pers
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
from	O
Mr.	O
William	B-pers
Burrowes	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
;	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Tankard	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
telling	O
the	O
Boy	O
that	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
was	O
coming	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
induced	O
the	O
Boy	O
to	O
draw	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
so	O
whilst	O
the	O
Boy	O
went	O
to	O
draw	O
some	O
other	O
Drink	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Tankard	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Boy	O
was	O
positive	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
Burrowes	O
House	O
for	O
another	O
Theft	O
about	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
laid	O
to	O
his	O
Charge	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
and	O
Anne	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
were	O
both	O
tried	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
for	O
Clipping	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Constables	O
going	O
about	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
private	O
Search	O
,	O
the	O
Woman	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
Chandlers	O
Shop	O
in	O
Long-Acre	O
,	O
and	O
under	O
her	O
Petticoat	O
was	O
found	O
a	O
Glove	O
of	O
Clippings	O
tyed	O
round	O
her	O
middle	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
her	O
Lodgings	O
at	O
the	O
Half	B-place
Moon	I-place
in	I-place
Drury-lane	I-place
,	O
in	O
a	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
5	O
l.	O
of	O
broad	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Money	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
newly	O
Clipt	O
:	O
In	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
her	O
Husband	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
began	O
to	O
examine	O
the	O
Constables	O
what	O
they	O
wanted	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
soon	O
satisfied	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
searcht	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
10	O
s.	O
found	O
newly	O
clipt	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Woman	O
said	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
Clippings	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
excused	O
her	O
Husband	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
:	O
She	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
clipt	O
Money	O
,	O
nor	O
the	O
5	O
l.	O
of	O
broad	O
Money	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
,	O
but	O
her	O
Husband	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
,	O
Elinor	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
and	O
Anne	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
three	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Lord	I-pers
who	O
was	O
bail	O
'd	O
,	O
did	O
Cut	O
,	O
Clip	O
,	O
File	O
and	O
Diminish	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Barker	O
,	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
change	O
fourscore	O
Guineas	O
at	O
a	O
Goldsmiths	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
suspicion	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
set	O
the	O
Beadle	O
to	O
dog	O
her	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Mashomes	B-place
street	I-place
at	I-place
Westminster	I-place
;	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
search	O
was	O
made	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
were	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
with	O
the	O
said	O
,	O
Lord	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
farther	O
search	O
there	O
was	O
found	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Clippings	O
,	O
clipt	O
Money	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shears	O
,	O
Finger	O
Leathers	O
,	O
Files	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
necessary	O
Implements	O
fit	O
for	O
Clipping	O
.	O
Elinor	O
Wilkinson	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
did	O
they	O
all	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
other	O
Lodgers	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
knew	O
not	O
how	O
such	O
things	O
came	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
not	O
full	O
though	O
against	O
the	O
two	O
Daughters	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Barker	O
and	O
Anne	O
Wilkinson	O
,	O
but	O
Elinor	O
Wilkinson	O
the	O
Mother	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Child	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Child	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
Susannah	B-pers
Price	I-pers
Wife	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
indicted	O
for	O
Clipping	O
the	O
Currant	O
Money	O
of	O
England	O
:	O
There	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
Child	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
Whitechappel	B-place
an	O
Ingot	O
Mold	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
John	O
Child	O
lodged	O
there	O
was	O
found	O
Clippings	O
and	O
clipt	O
Money	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Window	O
and	O
below	O
Stairs	O
was	O
found	O
several	O
Crucibles	O
and	O
melting	O
Pots	O
,	O
and	O
Files	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
was	O
found	O
a	O
large	O
paper	O
of	O
Clippings	O
&	O
c.	O
When	O
the	O
Searchers	O
came	O
first	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
Child	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
escape	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
soon	O
seized	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
in	O
making	O
false	O
and	O
counterfeit	O
Money	O
,	O
to	O
prove	O
which	O
there	O
were	O
divers	O
sorts	O
of	O
Stamps	O
,	O
as	O
half	O
Crown	O
Stamps	O
,	O
and	O
Shilling	O
Stamps	O
,	O
besides	O
a	O
great	O
quantity	O
of	O
counterfeit	O
Money	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
agreed	O
with	O
the	O
Stamp	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
John	O
Child	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
always	O
been	O
a	O
Labouring	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
understood	O
nothing	O
of	O
,	O
Clipping	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
another	O
man	O
brought	O
the	O
things	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
to	O
no	O
effect	O
,	O
for	O
both	O
himself	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
that	O
affected	O
Susannah	O
Price	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
only	O
was	O
barely	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
as	O
a	O
Guest	O
that	O
came	O
to	O
visit	O
Child	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Bryan	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Arthur	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bayly	I-pers
Wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bayly	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Avery	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
arraigned	O
upon	O
an	O
Indictment	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Mary	B-pers
Widnes	I-pers
one	O
Yard	O
of	O
Bone-lace	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
6	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
they	O
both	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Naylor	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Hambleton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
black	O
Hood	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Webster	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
Parish	I-place
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
was	O
arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
seven	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
14	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Fork	O
,	O
value	O
23	O
s.	O
two	O
Tumblers	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Springall	I-pers
;	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Babb	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Freezby	I-pers
were	O
both	O
tried	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Foukes	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
one	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
one	O
Spoon	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
Forks	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
five	O
Napkins	O
and	O
two	O
Sutes	O
of	O
Child-bed	O
Linnen	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Hatch	O
was	O
opened	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
carried	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
Babb	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
Freezby	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
immediately	O
taken	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
the	O
Goods	O
by	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
fully	O
made	O
appear	O
upon	O
Oath	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
could	O
prove	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Bundle	O
that	O
Freezby	O
had	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
Muslin	O
in	O
her	O
Bundle	O
which	O
she	O
sold	O
.	O
Babb	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
offer	O
Muslin	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
the	O
Plate	O
was	O
presently	O
mist	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
Freezby	O
had	O
in	O
all	O
probability	O
carried	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Jury	O
were	O
not	O
satisfied	O
that	O
Babb	O
opened	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Evidence	O
did	O
affect	O
Freezby	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
Wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
Wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
30	O
Yards	O
of	O
Indian	O
Sattin	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
.	O
Three	O
Women	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Knight	O
's	O
Shop	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
whereof	O
Knight	O
was	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
pincht	O
away	O
the	O
Silk	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
a	O
Broker	O
's	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
at	O
one	O
Cropley	O
's	O
Shop	O
in	O
Long-Acre	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
denied	O
the	O
matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
;	O
and	O
all	O
were	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
ill	O
Women	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
often	O
in	O
Newgate	O
before	O
.	O
Knight	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
killing	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Macklin	I-pers
;	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
upon	O
the	O
right	O
Pap	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
four	O
Inches	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
value	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
.	O
The	O
matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
happened	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
day	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
;	O
they	O
fell	O
out	O
about	O
a	O
Groat	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
run	O
upon	O
Macklin	O
's	O
Score	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
Corporal	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
called	O
each	O
other	O
evil	O
names	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
old	O
Quarrel	O
betwixt	O
them	O
;	O
so	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
assaulted	O
by	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
he	O
happened	O
to	O
kill	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
done	O
upon	O
a	O
sudden	O
Heat	O
of	O
Passion	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Cary	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
,	O
in	O
marrying	O
two	O
Wives	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
named	O
Ann	B-pers
Cleer	I-pers
,	O
who	O
she	O
married	O
in	O
the	O
33d	O
.	O
Year	O
of	O
King	O
Charles	O
II	O
.	O
the	O
other	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Serjeant	I-pers
whom	O
he	O
married	O
in	O
the	O
fifth	O
Year	O
of	O
King	O
William	O
and	O
Queen	O
Mary	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
upon	O
Oath	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
confess	O
to	O
have	O
married	O
Ann	O
Cleer	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
her	O
as	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
besides	O
the	O
Church-book	O
proved	O
it	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
which	O
a	O
Certificate	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
marriage	O
of	O
the	O
second	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Mary	O
Serjeant	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
that	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
Wife	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
steal	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
day	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
threescore	O
Pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Tallow	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
Pound	O
weight	O
and	O
an	O
Ounce	O
of	O
Cotton	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
pewter	O
Pot	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
the	O
Watch	O
late	O
at	O
night	O
with	O
the	O
Tallow	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
give	O
any	O
account	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
Tallow	O
;	O
and	O
none	O
had	O
claim	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
because	O
none	O
could	O
swear	O
that	O
she	O
stole	O
it	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Roane	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Abigail	B-pers
White	I-pers
of	O
a	O
flower	O
'd	O
Silk	O
Petticoat	O
with	O
a	O
Silver	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
one	O
Callico	O
one	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
She	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Moor	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Salter	I-pers
were	O
both	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
34	O
Ells	O
of	O
Holland	O
Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
35	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Morden	I-pers
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
they	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Katharine	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
was	O
arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Silk	O
Hoods	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
Silk	O
Tippet	O
,	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
a	O
laced	O
Cornet	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
small	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
Barbara	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Osborn	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Dowlace	O
Shirt	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Smock	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
sorts	O
of	O
small	O
Linnen	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
one	O
Henry	B-pers
Osborn	I-pers
:	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
put	O
to	O
a	O
Washerwoman	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Custody	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Butcher	O
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Wether	O
Sheep	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Mastin	I-pers
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
Mastin	O
swore	O
that	O
he	O
sold	O
three	O
Sheep	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
lost	O
two	O
more	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
proved	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
Sheep	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Gilington	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
one	O
Richard	B-pers
Pollar	I-pers
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
a	O
Coral	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
laced	O
Cornet	O
and	O
a	O
Crevat	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
of	O
Clarkenwell	B-place
in	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
laced	O
Cornet	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
Neckcloth	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
and	O
other	O
small	O
Linnen	O
;	O
the	O
Witness	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Cloths	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
by	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
offered	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
Petticoat	O
in	O
satisfaction	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
was	O
arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Quilt	O
,	O
value	O
21	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
34	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
Pillow-bears	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Katharine	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
and	O
arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
a	O
twisted	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
Silver	O
Fringes	O
45	O
s.	O
a	O
laced	O
Cornet	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
,	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
Clipping	O
the	O
lawful	O
Money	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
viz	O
20	O
half	O
Crowns	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
Shillings	O
,	O
diminishing	O
from	O
each	O
piece	O
Silver	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
2	O
d	O
There	O
were	O
a	O
small	O
parcel	O
of	O
Clippings	O
,	O
a	O
File	O
,	O
Scales	O
and	O
Weights	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Lodging	O
in	O
Fleet-lane	B-place
,	O
which	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
to	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
File	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Clippings	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
Band-box	O
in	O
the	O
Closet	O
in	O
a	O
paper	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
most	O
strongly	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
ill	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
company	O
with	O
another	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
might	O
put	O
the	O
Clippings	O
in	O
the	O
Closet	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
She	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Barnet	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
Dennis	B-pers
Bonsellers	I-pers
as	O
Principal	O
,	O
Judith	B-pers
Bonsellers	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Dyamond	I-pers
as	O
Accessaries	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
Felony	O
committed	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Saveridgeworth	I-pers
a	O
Salesman	O
in	O
Hounsditch	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
:	O
Mrs.	O
Saveridgworth	O
swore	O
that	O
the	O
Window	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
altho	O
nailed	O
with	O
ten	O
Ten-penny	O
Nails	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
lost	O
was	O
79	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
l.	O
140	O
Yards	O
of	O
Serge	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
80	O
Yards	O
of	O
Serge	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
l.	O
60	O
Yards	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
six	O
Serge	O
Waistcoats	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
13	O
Calamanco	O
Waistcoats	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
l.	O
16	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
besides	O
30	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Barnet	O
offered	O
some	O
Breeches	O
to	O
sale	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
Carter	O
:	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Dennis	O
Bonsellers	O
nor	O
Judith	O
,	O
but	O
Dyamond	O
came	O
along	O
with	O
Barnet	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
Carter	O
bought	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
of	O
Mrs	O
Saveridge	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
,	O
which	O
might	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
;	O
so	O
no	O
Evidence	O
affecting	O
any	O
besides	O
Barnet	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
rest	O
were	O
all	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Cule	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
and	O
tried	O
for	O
killing	O
one	O
Richard	B-pers
Key	I-pers
,	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
near	O
to	O
his	O
short	O
Ribs	O
with	O
a	O
Bullet	O
which	O
past	O
quite	O
through	O
his	O
Body	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
with	O
two	O
Pistols	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
discharged	O
,	O
and	O
Key	O
being	O
near	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
came	O
towards	O
him	O
,	O
having	O
heard	O
one	O
Pistol	O
go	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bid	O
him	O
stand	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
Key	O
clapt	O
his	O
hand	O
upon	O
his	O
Belly	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
O	O
Lord	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
done	O
;	O
and	O
died	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
presently	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
but	O
paper	O
in	O
the	O
Pistol	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
care	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
always	O
been	O
very	O
good	O
Friends	O
,	O
and	O
loved	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
alledged	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
desired	O
by	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
to	O
discharge	O
the	O
Pistols	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
misfortune	O
to	O
shoot	O
the	O
said	O
Key	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
nothing	O
of	O
Malice	O
found	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
nor	O
that	O
he	O
designed	O
to	O
do	O
Key	O
any	O
harm	O
;	O
so	O
in	O
the	O
end	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
from	O
Joseph	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Dolphin	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
September	O
instant	O
,	O
50	O
Yards	O
of	O
painted	O
Callicoe	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
50	O
Yards	O
of	O
flaxen	O
Cloth	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
were	O
put	O
to	O
Dying	O
at	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Battins	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
stole	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
He	O
made	O
a	O
feigned	O
Story	O
,	O
how	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
hired	O
by	O
a	O
strange	O
Man	O
to	O
carty	O
the	O
Cloth	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
produce	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
M	B-pers
-	I-pers
S	I-pers
-	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
23	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Bees-Wax	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
on	O
the	O
fifth	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
:	O
He	O
took	O
it	O
off	O
the	O
Shop-window	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
pursued	O
he	O
threw	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
plain	O
proof	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Colston	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
from	O
George	B-pers
Ranton	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Parish	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
The	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
the	O
Chamber	O
where	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
lockt	O
up	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
but	O
the	O
Key	O
was	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
left	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
all	O
upon	O
his	O
Trial	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Witness	O
could	O
not	O
Swear	O
positively	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Ogle	I-pers
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
38	O
Fitchows	O
Skins	O
,	O
value	O
48	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
tenth	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Pigney	I-pers
,	O
and	O
cheapned	O
some	O
Skins	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Art	O
of	O
Legerdem	O
in	O
he	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Skins	O
:	O
He	O
denied	O
that	O
ever	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
and	I-pers
Ann	I-pers
his	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
and	O
Ann	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
were	O
tried	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
for	O
Clipping	O
the	O
lawful	O
Coin	O
of	O
the	O
Kingdom	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
was	O
searcht	O
in	O
Barden	B-place
's	I-place
Gardens	I-place
,	O
and	O
in	O
his	O
Chamber	O
was	O
found	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Clippings	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shears	O
and	O
a	O
File	O
;	O
the	O
Shears	O
were	O
found	O
lying	O
upon	O
the	O
Sacking	O
of	O
the	O
Bed	O
between	O
that	O
and	O
the	O
Bed	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
urged	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
more	O
Lodgers	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
knew	O
nothing	O
how	O
the	O
things	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
never	O
shut	O
their	O
Door	O
.	O
And	O
their	O
Witness	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
Walker	O
himself	O
was	O
a	O
Person	O
that	O
dealt	O
in	O
Brandy	O
and	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
always	O
abroad	O
in	O
the	O
any-time	O
;	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
was	O
a	O
Sempstress	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
They	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Widdowes	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Roan	O
Gelding	O
,	O
price	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Rouse	I-pers
:	O
The	O
Gelding	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
Horse	O
on	O
a	O
Thursday	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
Market	O
day	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
two	O
men	O
were	O
Vouchers	O
which	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
found	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
proved	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
altho	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
privy	O
to	O
the	O
stealing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
yet	O
that	O
could	O
not	O
reach	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dwarras	I-pers
and	O
Ann	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
were	O
both	O
tried	O
for	O
being	O
Accessary	O
afterwards	O
to	O
the	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
committed	O
by	O
G	O
-	O
V	O
-	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
True	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
G	O
-	O
V	O
-	O
stole	O
away	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
Fork	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
Looking	O
glass	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
three	O
pieces	O
of	O
Ribboning	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
G	O
-	O
V	O
-	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
opposed	O
by	O
a	O
Stranger	O
that	O
stood	O
upon	O
the	O
Stairs	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dwarras	I-pers
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
notice	O
to	O
get	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
said	O
G	O
-	O
V	O
-	O
being	O
found	O
guilty	O
only	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
the	O
good	O
Fortune	O
to	O
be	O
acquitted	O
from	O
being	O
Accessaries	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
from	O
Rice	B-pers
Saywell	I-pers
at	O
the	B-place
Rose	I-place
in	I-place
Newgate-street	I-place
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Tankard	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
slipt	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
as	O
was	O
sworn	O
by	O
the	O
Tapster	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
pursued	O
he	O
was	O
stopt	O
in	O
the	O
Market	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Tankard	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
got	O
away	O
:	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
but	O
the	O
Tapster	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
mistaken	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
Face	O
,	O
having	O
staid	O
so	O
little	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
:	O
He	O
had	O
good	O
Witness	O
,	O
viz	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Piggot	O
,	O
with	O
whom	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
a	O
very	O
credible	O
account	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
very	O
Faithful	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
entrusted	O
him	O
with	O
all	O
his	O
richest	O
things	O
:	O
Others	O
gave	O
the	O
like	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
Behaviour	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
18	O
Yards	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
3	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
and	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Wise	I-pers
near	O
Ludgate	B-place
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
with	O
one	O
Jane	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
who	O
confest	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
that	O
Lee	O
was	O
her	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
wanted	O
some	O
Silk	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
so	O
pincht	O
it	O
away	O
between	O
them	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
presently	O
stopt	O
:	O
She	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Smocks	O
and	O
other	O
Linnen	O
,	O
from	O
Francis	B-pers
Emmerson	I-pers
on	O
the	O
second	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pierce	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Deane	I-pers
in	O
Chancery-lane	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
seen	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
when	O
the	O
Cup	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
rusht	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
on	O
a	O
sudden	O
,	O
and	O
therewas	O
no	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
but	O
him	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
But	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samuel	B-pers
Mitchell	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Midgley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Springer	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Springhall	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
in	O
Clipping	O
the	O
lawful	O
Money	O
of	O
the	O
Kingdom	O
of	O
England	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
being	O
searcht	O
in	O
Katharine-Wheel-Alley	B-place
in	I-place
White-Chappel	I-place
,	O
there	O
was	O
found	O
there	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shears	O
,	O
a	O
File	O
and	O
a	O
Rubbing	O
Leather	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Clipping	O
of	O
a	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Taylor	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
used	O
the	O
Shears	O
about	O
his	O
Trade	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Brufford	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
likewise	O
for	O
Coining	O
of	O
False	O
Money	O
;	O
several	O
pieces	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Pocket	O
,	O
cut	O
out	O
ready	O
to	O
be	O
coined	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
desired	O
the	O
Constables	O
to	O
be	O
kind	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
tell	O
them	O
all	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
at	O
last	O
:	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Money	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
coined	O
by	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
however	O
he	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
kept	O
in	O
Custody	O
till	O
he	O
find	O
good	O
Sureties	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Redshaw	I-pers
was	O
arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Parchment	O
Writings	O
,	O
value	O
200	O
l.	O
from	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Day	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
High-way	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
coming	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
Moneys	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
Henry	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
of	O
Hanwell	B-place
,	O
who	O
declared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Fellow-Servant	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
he	O
suspected	O
him	O
to	O
have	O
taken	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
full	O
of	O
Money	O
afterwards	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
an	O
evil	O
Character	O
given	O
of	O
him	O
by	O
his	O
former	O
Master	O
;	O
yet	O
all	O
was	O
but	O
a	O
bare	O
Presumption	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ashmoll	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Ashmoll	I-pers
were	O
tried	O
for	O
Clipping	O
200	O
half	O
Crowns	O
,	O
100	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
100	O
Six-pences	O
:	O
The	O
King	O
's	O
Witness	O
declared	O
upon	O
Oath	O
.	O
That	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Garret	O
in	O
Kings-street	B-place
at	I-place
Tower-hill	I-place
,	O
were	O
found	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shears	O
fixt	O
,	O
and	O
above	O
32	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Clippings	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
as	O
farther	O
corroborating	O
Evidence	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
some	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Silver-Smith	O
by	O
his	O
Trade	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
any	O
way	O
Suspicious	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
Reputation	O
:	O
And	O
the	O
Jury	O
were	O
not	O
well	O
satisfied	O
with	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stanes	I-pers
was	O
arraigned	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
putting	O
off	O
False	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Florendine	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
likewise	O
,	O
in	O
getting	O
and	O
procuring	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
Iron	O
Shears	O
into	O
her	O
custody	O
,	O
fit	O
for	O
Clipping	O
,	O
which	O
Shears	O
were	O
found	O
under	O
the	O
Stair-case	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
else	O
was	O
found	O
that	O
was	O
Suspicious	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Husband	O
that	O
is	O
not	O
yet	O
found	O
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Circumstantial	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
May	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Randall	I-pers
and	O
Christian	B-pers
Cossey	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
indicted	O
,	O
and	O
tried	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Joan	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
in	O
Green-Dragon	B-place
Court	I-place
in	I-place
Grays-Inn	I-place
lane	I-place
,	O
on	O
Bartholomew	O
day	O
at	O
night	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
lost	O
were	O
4	O
Smocks	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
4	O
Stuff	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
15	O
Aprons	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
Short	O
's	O
Gardens	O
a	O
Drinking	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Smock	O
of	O
Ellis	O
's	O
upon	O
Costey	O
's	O
Back	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
Thomasin	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
in	O
their	O
company	O
,	O
commonly	O
called	O
Ruff	O
and	O
Ugly	O
,	O
a	O
noted	O
Thief	O
:	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
that	O
affected	O
May	O
and	O
Randall	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
,	O
but	O
Cossey	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Luth	I-pers
was	O
arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
three	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
13	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
Michael	B-pers
Lamprier	I-pers
,	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
,	O
after	O
much	O
deliberation	O
,	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Esther	B-pers
Evanes	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
Felony	O
,	O
in	O
taking	O
for	O
her	O
Husband	O
first	O
one	O
Richard	B-pers
Evanes	I-pers
,	O
which	O
was	O
presently	O
proved	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
Evanes	O
about	O
three	O
Years	O
ago	O
:	O
And	O
that	O
she	O
married	O
one	O
David	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
since	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
in	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
both	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Grace	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
two	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
day	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
break	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Nehemiah	B-pers
Buzkil	I-pers
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
ten	O
pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
pewter	O
Dish	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Pewter	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
proof	O
on	O
her	O
side	O
,	O
nor	O
no	O
witness	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Wootton	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Perkway	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Clipping	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
England	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
person	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
him	O
from	O
one	O
Mrs	O
Stanes	O
for	O
some	O
Money	O
that	O
was	O
Clipt	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
him	O
at	O
work	O
with	O
the	O
Shears	O
fixt	O
to	O
the	O
Bed-side	O
,	O
and	O
broad	O
Money	O
lying	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
narrow	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
desired	O
the	O
messenger	O
,	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
to	O
stay	O
and	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
quite	O
wrought	O
it	O
off	O
:	O
He	O
being	O
told	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
hanged	O
for	O
it	O
:	O
He	O
answered	O
,	O
What	O
signifies	O
at	O
,	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
but	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hours	O
squeek	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
urged	O
Malice	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
called	O
some	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
a	O
favourable	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
Reputation	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stanes	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
buying	O
of	O
Clipt	O
Money	O
at	O
under	O
rates	O
,	O
and	O
uttering	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
Payments	O
:	O
She	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Wheat-sheaf	B-place
on	I-place
Ludgate-hill	I-place
,	O
and	O
changed	O
several	O
Guineas	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
could	O
swear	O
that	O
she	O
put	O
away	O
any	O
false	O
Money	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Emanes	I-pers
and	O
Peter	B-pers
Higham	I-pers
were	O
both	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
and	O
a	O
Salt	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
l.	O
from	O
Henry	B-pers
Lickborrow	I-pers
at	O
the	B-place
Bell	I-place
in	I-place
Warwick-lane	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
ask	O
for	O
a	O
Carrier	O
at	O
the	O
abovesaid	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
drank	O
where	O
the	O
Plate	O
was	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
private	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Plate	O
was	O
there	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
it	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
one	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
besides	O
them	O
:	O
This	O
was	O
sworn	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Emanes	O
went	O
by	O
another	O
Name	O
,	O
viz	O
,	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Bartlet	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
alledged	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
other	O
Carriers	O
and	O
Companies	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
besides	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
three	O
hours	O
afterwards	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
one	O
charged	O
them	O
with	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Plate	O
was	O
not	O
missing	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
could	O
not	O
fix	O
the	O
matter	O
home	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
without	O
great	O
Suspicion	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Jingen	I-pers
was	O
arraigned	O
for	O
privily	O
stealing	O
12	O
s.	O
from	O
Ann	B-pers
Rutt	I-pers
Wife	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Rutt	I-pers
:	O
Ann	O
Rutt	O
swore	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
coming	O
through	O
the	O
Fair	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pickt	O
her	O
Pocket	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
her	O
hand	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Purse	O
dropt	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
plain	O
Evidence	O
:	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Fairbank	I-pers
Widow	O
was	O
accused	O
and	O
tried	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
in	O
Clipping	O
the	O
Currant	O
Money	O
of	O
England	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
but	O
one	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
altho	O
some	O
Clippings	O
&	O
c.	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
yet	O
the	O
Room	O
was	O
her	O
Lodgers	O
that	O
was	O
gone	O
:	O
So	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
L	B-pers
-	I-pers
J	I-pers
-	I-pers
a	O
Refiner	O
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
a	O
dishonest	O
Conversation	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
the	O
great	O
Encouragement	O
of	O
the	O
Clipping	O
Trade	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
buy	O
Clippings	O
:	O
His	O
House	O
being	O
searcht	O
in	O
Aldersgate-street	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
found	O
two	O
papers	O
of	O
Clippings	O
weighing	O
about	O
60	O
Ounces	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
heard	O
to	O
confess	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
buy	O
Clippings	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
5	O
s.	O
1	O
d.	O
an	O
Ounce	O
for	O
them	O
:	O
This	O
was	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
urged	O
by	O
his	O
Counsel	O
,	O
That	O
a	O
Woman	O
brought	O
the	O
Clippings	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
to	O
offer	O
them	O
to	O
sale	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
her	O
bring	O
more	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
discover	O
her	O
:	O
But	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Witness	O
to	O
discover	O
his	O
Intention	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
several	O
Neighbours	O
appeared	O
in	O
his	O
behalf	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
a	O
favourable	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
Conversation	O
in	O
the	O
general	O
,	O
yet	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Purchase	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
were	O
both	O
tried	O
for	O
making	O
an	O
Assault	O
upon	O
Mr.	O
William	B-pers
Chalinor	I-pers
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
Kill	O
and	O
Murder	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Witness	O
against	O
William	B-pers
Newbolt	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Farr	I-pers
:	O
Mr.	O
Chalinor	O
gave	O
in	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
and	O
one	O
Captain	O
Webb	O
,	O
being	O
at	O
Bartholomew-Fair	O
,	O
they	O
observed	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
more	O
Persons	O
to	O
dog	O
them	O
for	O
several	O
hours	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
Mr.	O
Chalinor	O
,	O
fearing	O
that	O
they	O
sought	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
advised	O
with	O
Captain	O
Webb	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
for	O
shelter	O
;	O
The	O
Men	O
followed	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
being	O
above	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
perceiving	O
that	O
they	O
whispered	O
together	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Chalinor	O
sent	O
down	O
his	O
Foot	O
boy	O
a	O
Black	O
,	O
to	O
hearken	O
what	O
they	O
said	O
:	O
And	O
when	O
he	O
returned	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
to	O
another	O
,	O
Jack	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
seize	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
come	O
up	O
and	O
do	O
his	O
business	O
.	O
The	O
Woman	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
advised	O
them	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
at	O
a	O
back-door	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
thought	O
it	O
not	O
convenient	O
,	O
so	O
continued	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
:	O
At	O
last	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
People	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Prize	O
worth	O
500	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
greatest	O
Rogue	O
in	O
England	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
would	O
endeavour	O
todo	O
what	O
they	O
could	O
to	O
execute	O
their	O
Design	O
(	O
or	O
words	O
to	O
that	O
effect	O
,	O
)	O
at	O
last	O
Captain	O
Webb	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Chalinor	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Street	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
went	O
off	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
themselves	O
,	O
but	O
pleaded	O
they	O
had	O
no	O
design	O
against	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
very	O
Poor	O
men	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
from	O
Islington	O
to	O
the	O
Fair	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
They	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
Clip	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
England	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Shears	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
vast	O
quantity	O
of	O
Clippings	O
:	O
And	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
Women	O
tried	O
before	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Witness	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
neither	O
could	O
they	O
charge	O
her	O
with	O
Clipping	O
.	O
This	O
Fact	O
was	O
done	O
about	O
a	O
Twelvemonth	O
ago	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
Epsom	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
only	O
Circumstantial	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Not	O
guilty	O
John	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Dishonest	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
an	O
evil	O
Principle	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
receive	O
,	O
harbour	O
,	O
and	O
comfort	O
several	O
Thieves	O
and	O
Highway-men	O
,	O
particularly	O
one	O
Christopher	B-pers
Pickering	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Vicars	I-pers
,	O
a	O
great	O
and	O
notorious	O
Highway-man	O
and	O
Robber	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
opened	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
account	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Wilkinson	O
did	O
entertain	O
the	O
said	O
Pickering	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Highway-men	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
over	O
against	O
Thieving	B-place
lane	I-place
.	O
Pickering	O
was	O
called	O
,	O
and	O
declared	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
whither	O
Mr.	O
Wilkinson	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Thief	O
or	O
no	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
receive	O
him	O
into	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
received	O
stolen	O
Goods	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
did	O
his	O
Wife	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
Lodgings	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
persuaded	O
the	O
said	O
Pickering	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
and	O
make	O
his	O
escape	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
when	O
one	O
Gross	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Highwaymen	O
were	O
taken	O
at	O
Westminster	O
.	O
Furthermore	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
to	O
one	O
Mr	O
.	O
Kitchen	O
a	O
Counsellor	O
of	O
the	O
Temple	O
for	O
Advice	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
bid	O
him	O
make	O
over	O
his	O
Goods	O
to	O
some	O
Friend	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
safe	O
:	O
And	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Mr	O
Kitchen	O
made	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
Bill	O
of	O
Charges	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
Bill	O
he	O
set	O
down	O
paid	O
the	O
Recorder	O
of	O
London	O
20	O
l.	O
and	O
his	O
Son	O
a	O
Fee	O
,	O
and	O
treating	O
the	O
Grand-Jury	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Sums	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
which	O
was	O
not	O
true	O
;	O
and	O
was	O
made	O
appear	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
in	O
Court	O
:	O
Yet	O
the	O
Jury	O
looking	O
upon	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
sufficient	O
proof	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
though	O
the	O
Court	O
was	O
of	O
opinion	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
Ill	O
man	O
,	O
they	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
James	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
five	O
Shirts	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
but	O
Mrs.	O
James	O
leaving	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
in	O
trust	O
by	O
her	O
own	O
consent	O
,	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
made	O
a	O
Robbery	O
;	O
so	O
the	O
Indictment	O
was	O
quash	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Discharged	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Sheldon	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
clipping	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
England	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shears	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
small	O
parcel	O
of	O
Clippings	O
found	O
under	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Bed	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
but	O
a	O
Lodger	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
Broad	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
found	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
owned	O
by	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Watson	O
,	O
who	O
the	O
Constable	O
said	O
he	O
thought	O
to	O
be	O
more	O
guilty	O
than	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
alledged	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
another	O
Woman	O
lodged	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
might	O
put	O
them	O
there	O
:	O
So	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
J	B-pers
-	I-pers
C	I-pers
-	I-pers
of	O
Shoreditch	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
whereas	O
John	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
stands	O
convicted	O
of	O
Felony	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Mary	B-pers
Quarterman	I-pers
;	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
C	O
-	O
did	O
abett	O
the	O
said	O
Jennings	O
to	O
commit	O
the	O
said	O
Robbery	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Datby	B-pers
Lary	I-pers
and	O
Frances	B-pers
Lary	I-pers
were	O
tryed	O
for	O
robbing	O
neIzzabella	B-pers
Boddenham	I-pers
of	O
an	O
Ear-Ring	O
in	O
the	O
Open-street	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
which	O
proceeded	O
to	O
Blows	O
amongst	O
the	O
Rabble	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Witness	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
robbed	O
her	O
;	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Oliver	B-pers
Dubree	I-pers
a	O
Parson	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
perswading	O
one	O
Katherine	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Jersey	O
and	O
Guernsey	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
the	O
French	O
King	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
King	O
James	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Stephens	O
was	O
sworn	O
and	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Islands	O
,	O
and	O
posses	O
himself	O
of	O
divers	O
Castles	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
afterwards	O
he	O
would	O
deliver	O
them	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
French	O
King	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
bring	O
him	O
to	O
St.	O
Germains	O
to	O
King	O
James	O
,	O
to	O
consult	O
him	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
King	O
James	O
was	O
to	O
help	O
him	O
to	O
Ships	O
to	O
carry	O
on	O
this	O
Design	O
;	O
the	O
Court	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
why	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
it	O
convenient	O
.	O
(	O
Court	O
)	O
How	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
it	O
?	O
(	O
Witness	O
)	O
Why	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
those	O
Ships	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
Jarsey	O
and	O
Guernsy	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
tell	O
them	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
driven	O
in	O
thither	O
by	O
the	O
French	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
all	O
this	O
was	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
but	O
as	O
a	O
frivolous	O
Story	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
credited	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
:	O
This	O
Mrs.	O
Stephens	O
being	O
asked	O
what	O
Countrey	O
and	O
Religion	O
she	O
was	O
off	O
,	O
she	O
answered	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Scotch-woman	O
and	O
a	O
Jacobite	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
a	O
Jacobite	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
Nature	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
no	O
Answer	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
the	O
Parson	O
had	O
instructed	O
her	O
better	O
,	O
she	O
might	O
have	O
been	O
better	O
provided	O
:	O
The	O
Parson	O
declared	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
abetted	O
to	O
swear	O
against	O
him	O
in	O
this	O
matter	O
by	O
two	O
Jesuit	O
Converts	O
,	O
who	O
turn	O
their	O
Religion	O
any	O
way	O
to	O
serve	O
their	O
own	O
turns	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
do	O
by	O
Mental	O
Reservation	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Court	O
directed	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
but	O
a	O
frivolous	O
and	O
a	O
groundless	O
Indictment	O
:	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Collet	I-pers
was	O
arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
15	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cloath	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Silk	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
from	O
George	B-pers
Hungerford	I-pers
;	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Dyllon	I-pers
a	O
French	O
Minister	O
,	O
was	O
arraigned	O
this	O
Sessions	O
upon	O
an	O
Indictment	O
of	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Sermon-Oration	O
at	O
the	O
Parish	O
Church	O
of	O
St.	O
Matthew	O
's	O
Friday	O
street	O
,	O
express	O
several	O
dangerous	O
and	O
Treasonable	O
Words	O
and	O
Sentences	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
these	O
;	O
The	O
Text	O
says	O
,	O
That	O
none	O
but	O
Devils	O
will	O
lay	O
a	O
Sacrilegious	O
Hand	O
upon	O
the	O
Lord	O
's	O
Anointed	O
.	O
Some	O
will	O
fight	O
for	O
a	O
Whore	O
,	O
but	O
who	O
will	O
fight	O
to	O
vindicate	O
the	O
King	O
(	O
James	O
the	O
late	O
King	O
of	O
England	O
meaning	O
;	O
)	O
then	O
and	O
no	O
soonner	O
will	O
I	O
have	O
mercy	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
them	O
happy	O
;	O
and	O
indeed	O
the	O
happiness	O
of	O
us	O
all	O
depends	O
upon	O
the	O
said	O
King	O
James	O
's	O
coming	O
again	O
And	O
on	O
the	O
said	O
20th	O
day	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
presence	O
and	O
heating	O
of	O
divers	O
of	O
their	O
Present	O
Majestys	O
Subjects	O
,	O
those	O
Treasonable	O
Sentences	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Libellous	O
Oration	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
Dyllon	O
did	O
openly	O
speak	O
,	O
preach	O
and	O
set	O
forth	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
not	O
guilty	O
;	O
and	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
remain	O
in	O
Prison	O
till	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
The	O
Tryal	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Newbolt	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
Printers	O
,	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
in	O
composing	O
and	O
imagining	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
their	O
Most	O
Sacred	O
Majesties	O
,	O
King	O
William	O
,	O
and	O
Queen	O
Mary	O
.	O
ON	O
Friday	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
September	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
3d	O
Day	O
of	O
this	O
Sessions	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
arraigned	O
upon	O
an	O
Indictment	O
of	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
for	O
composing	O
,	O
printing	O
and	O
publishing	O
a	O
libellous	O
and	O
traiterous	O
Paper	O
,	O
Entituled	O
,	O
The	O
late	O
King	O
James	O
's	O
Declaration	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
they	O
both	O
pleaded	O
Not	O
guilty	O
:	O
And	O
then	O
the	O
Jury	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
having	O
made	O
their	O
Challenge	O
to	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
26	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
upon	O
their	O
Tryal	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
sworn	O
to	O
try	O
the	O
Issue	O
,	O
were	O
these	O
whose	O
Names	O
follow	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Underhill	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
William	B-pers
Withers	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Francis	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Bradberry	I-pers
.	O
Edmond	B-pers
Salter	I-pers
.	O
Gent	O
.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Skynner	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Bowler	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Richman	I-pers
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lynn	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Preston	I-pers
.	O
Gent	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
desired	O
they	O
might	O
have	O
Pen	O
,	O
Ink	O
and	O
Paper	O
allow	O
'd	O
them	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
granted	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Indictment	O
was	O
read	O
again	O
,	O
which	O
set	O
forth	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
stood	O
indicted	O
by	O
the	O
Names	O
of	O
William	O
Newbolt	O
,	O
and	O
Edward	O
Butler	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
Gentlemen	O
;	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
not	O
having	O
God	O
before	O
their	O
eyes	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
moved	O
and	O
instigated	O
by	O
the	O
power	O
of	O
the	O
Devil	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
Enemies	O
of	O
our	O
Sovereign	O
Lord	O
and	O
Lady	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
Queen	O
,	O
and	O
minding	O
and	O
intending	O
to	O
raise	O
War	O
and	O
Rebellion	O
in	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Government	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
wholly	O
to	O
subvert	O
,	O
alter	O
and	O
change	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
miserable	O
Slaughter	O
amongst	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
Subjects	O
to	O
make	O
;	O
and	O
to	O
depose	O
and	O
put	O
to	O
death	O
Their	O
Most	O
Sacred	O
Majesties	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
Day	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
past	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
times	O
as	O
well	O
before	O
as	O
after	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
compose	O
,	O
print	O
and	O
publish	O
,	O
or	O
cause	O
to	O
be	O
compos	O
'd	O
,	O
printed	O
,	O
and	O
publish	O
'd	O
a	O
most	O
false	O
and	O
scandalous	O
,	O
malicious	O
and	O
Traiterous	O
Libel	O
,	O
Entituled	O
,	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Most	O
Gracious	O
Declaration	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
which	O
was	O
publickly	O
read	O
at	O
large	O
:	O
And	O
their	O
Majestys	O
Counsel	O
having	O
very	O
fully	O
and	O
learnedly	O
opened	O
the	O
Matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
that	O
would	O
be	O
fully	O
proved	O
by	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
against	O
the	O
said	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
Queen	O
were	O
called	O
and	O
sworn	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
which	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
about	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
Ship	O
in	O
Charles-street	O
in	O
Covent-Garden	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
Dined	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
Dinner	O
the	O
man	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
brought	O
up	O
word	O
that	O
one	O
Capt	O
.	O
Griffis	O
was	O
below	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Newbolt	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
the	O
Company	O
that	O
Capt	O
.	O
Griffis	O
wanted	O
10000	O
of	O
the	O
Declarations	O
for	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
15	O
l.	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
about	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
days	O
afterwards	O
he	O
being	O
there	O
again	O
,	O
Mr	O
Butler	O
pulled	O
a	O
Declaration	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Farr	O
being	O
there	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
lookt	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
it	O
wanted	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Letters	O
,	O
God	O
save	O
the	O
King	O
;	O
so	O
Farr	O
said	O
at	O
last	O
,	O
Come	O
,	O
we	O
will	O
go	O
to	O
my	O
Lords	O
and	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
(	O
meaning	O
at	O
Douglass	O
's	O
where	O
the	O
Printing-Press	O
stood	O
)	O
which	O
was	O
to	O
set	O
the	O
Declaration	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
June	O
following	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
Butler	O
in	O
Charles-street	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
had	O
some	O
Declarations	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
heart	O
failed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
this	O
Witness	O
;	O
soon	O
after	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
apprehended	O
with	O
those	O
Declarations	O
wet	O
in	O
their	O
custody	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
carried	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Trenchard	I-pers
,	O
where	O
they	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
and	O
thirty	O
of	O
them	O
found	O
upon	O
Butler	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
had	O
a	O
Printing-Press	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
was	O
kept	O
at	O
one	O
Douglosses	O
at	O
Westminster	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
they	O
printed	O
the	O
Declarations	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
both	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
concerned	O
equally	O
in	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
seen	O
to	O
compose	O
the	O
Press	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Frame	O
so	O
set	O
by	O
their	O
hands	O
was	O
brought	O
into	O
Court	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
the	O
Declaration	O
had	O
been	O
printed	O
,	O
and	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
set	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
All	O
this	O
was	O
fully	O
and	O
clearly	O
sworn	O
against	O
them	O
by	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Evidence	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
once	O
made	O
their	O
escape	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
nor	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
Print	O
this	O
Declaration	O
,	O
but	O
alledged	O
that	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
Treason	O
to	O
Print	O
;	O
for	O
nothing	O
could	O
be	O
accounted	O
Treason	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
contained	O
in	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
Ed	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
And	O
Printing	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
that	O
Statute	O
,	O
therefore	O
Printing	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
an	O
Overt-Act	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
but	O
Servants	O
,	O
and	O
hired	O
to	O
work	O
for	O
their	O
Livelihood	O
,	O
the	O
Press	O
not	O
theirs	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
therefore	O
they	O
hoped	O
that	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Treason	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
never	O
known	O
,	O
that	O
Servants	O
did	O
suffer	O
for	O
their	O
Masters	O
Faults	O
.	O
But	O
they	O
were	O
answered	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
That	O
Servants	O
and	O
Masters	O
too	O
were	O
equally	O
principals	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Matter	O
contain	O
'd	O
in	O
that	O
Paper	O
was	O
Treason	O
of	O
the	O
highest	O
rate	O
,	O
designing	O
to	O
change	O
the	O
Government	O
,	O
depose	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
,	O
and	O
raise	O
open	O
War	O
in	O
these	O
Nations	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Design	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
ignorant	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
Composers	O
and	O
Printers	O
thereof	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
done	O
with	O
setled	O
purpose	O
and	O
intent	O
to	O
be	O
published	O
throughout	O
the	O
Nation	O
,	O
to	O
accomplish	O
and	O
effect	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Jury	O
having	O
considered	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
after	O
about	O
an	O
hours	O
time	O
they	O
brought	O
this	O
Verdict	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
Guilty	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
received	O
Sentence	O
,	O
they	O
desired	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
favourable	O
Report	O
of	O
their	O
Circumstances	O
to	O
the	O
Queen	O
;	O
And	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
Poor	O
men	O
,	O
and	O
only	O
work	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Living	O
.	O
Who	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
would	O
report	O
to	O
their	O
Majesties	O
nothing	O
but	O
what	O
should	O
be	O
just	O
and	O
true	O
,	O
and	O
advised	O
them	O
to	O
repent	O
of	O
their	O
wicked	O
and	O
evil	O
Purposes	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
thank	O
Almighty	O
God	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
prevented	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
Nations	O
blessed	O
in	O
the	O
safety	O
and	O
preservation	O
of	O
the	O
best	O
and	O
most	O
religious	O
King	O
and	O
Queen	O
that	O
ever	O
did	O
rule	O
and	O
govern	O
these	O
Realms	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Lord	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
Clipping	O
the	O
Currant	O
Money	O
of	O
England	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
their	O
Majesties	O
were	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
were	O
against	O
Barber	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
Wilkinsons	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
like	O
Case	O
as	O
you	O
may	O
see	O
in	O
their	O
Trials	O
aforesaid	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
Dinner	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Court	O
finding	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bringing	O
his	O
Trial	O
so	O
suddenly	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Evidence	O
being	O
somewhat	O
unprepared	O
,	O
there	O
might	O
be	O
some	O
Trick	O
in	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
remain	O
in	O
Custody	O
till	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
Wife	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Alice	B-pers
Sebbin	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Dimblebey	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
tried	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
together	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
not	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
first	O
Coin	O
the	O
Currant	O
Money	O
of	O
England	O
;	O
secondly	O
for	O
Clipping	O
of	O
it	O
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
Jones	O
the	O
owner	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
all	O
manner	O
of	O
Instruments	O
for	O
both	O
Trades	O
;	O
but	O
Jones	O
being	O
gone	O
away	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
set	O
aside	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
bound	O
over	O
to	O
appear	O
next	O
Sessions	O
to	O
prosecute	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
diligent	O
search	O
is	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Jones	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Sherwood	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
were	O
tryed	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
in	O
coining	O
false	O
Money	O
:	O
There	O
was	O
18	O
new	O
false	O
Half	O
Crowns	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Witness	O
not	O
being	O
ready	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
bound	O
in	O
a	O
Recognizance	O
to	O
prosecute	O
them	O
next	O
Sessions	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
ordered	O
to	O
remain	O
in	O
custody	O
till	O
then	O
:	O
So	O
this	O
Jury	O
was	O
discharged	O
from	O
any	O
farther	O
enquiry	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Sentence	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
29	O
.	O
Richard	O
Norman	O
,	O
Adam	O
Martin	O
,	O
John	O
Parker	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Jackson	O
,	O
Susannah	O
Tanner	O
,	O
Prudence	O
Johnson	O
,	O
Mary	O
Moor	O
,	O
Mary	O
Salter	O
,	O
Hannah	O
Roan	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Nayler	O
,	O
Sarah	O
Bayly	O
,	O
Ann	O
Avery	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Knight	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Martyn	O
,	O
Ann	O
Collet	O
,	O
Ann	O
Luthe	O
,	O
Jane	O
Lee	O
,	O
Mary	O
Shaw	O
,	O
Margaret	O
Denham	O
,	O
William	O
Ogle	O
,	O
William	O
Ford	O
,	O
William	O
Cule	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Pierce	O
,	O
Mary	O
Bryan	O
,	O
Katharine	O
Mason	O
,	O
Ann	O
Ward	O
,	O
Ann	O
Knight	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Ward	O
,	O
and	O
Esther	O
Evanes	O
William	O
Francis	O
was	O
respited	O
from	O
the	O
Penalty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
Bail	O
to	O
appear	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
15	O
.	O
John	O
Williams	O
,	O
Joseph	O
Barnet	O
,	O
Mary	O
Jingen	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Tavernor	O
,	O
Ann	O
Davis	O
,	O
Elinor	O
Wilkinson	O
,	O
John	O
Child	O
,	O
Mary	O
Child	O
,	O
Christian	O
Cossey	O
,	O
Grace	O
Butler	O
,	O
Robert	O
Wooten	O
alias	O
Perkway	O
,	O
William	O
Newbolt	O
,	O
Edward	O
Butler	O
,	O
James	O
Cary	O
,	O
John	O
Jennings	O
.	O
Ordered	O
into	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
Service	O
,	O
3	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Clark	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Browne	O
,	O
M	O
-	O
S	O
-	O
Fined	O
,	O
L	O
-	O
J	O
-	O
500	O
Mark	O
and	O
to	O
find	O
good	O
Sureties	O
for	O
a	O
Year	O
.	O
John	O
Herbert	O
and	O
William	O
Purchase	O
fined	O
20	O
Mark	O
each	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
considering	O
their	O
Poverty	O
.	O
G	O
-	O
t	O
-	O
was	O
respited	O
from	O
being	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
by	O
vertue	O
of	O
a	O
Warrant	O
from	O
Her	O
Majesty	O
.	O
Ann	O
Davis	O
,	O
Elinor	O
Wilkinson	O
and	O
Christian	O
Cossey	O
pleaded	O
their	O
Bellies	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Women	O
being	O
Sworn	O
to	O
enquire	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
found	O
quick	O
with	O
Child	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Farr	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
is	O
to	O
remain	O
till	O
farther	O
order	O
.	O
Ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Whipt	O
,	O
3	O
.	O
Mary	O
Smith	O
,	O
Mary	O
Osborne	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Williams	O
.	O
These	O
Persons	O
following	O
having	O
been	O
formerly	O
convicted	O
,	O
were	O
this	O
Sessions	O
called	O
down	O
to	O
their	O
former	O
Judgment	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Executed	O
.	O
Susannah	O
Lucas	O
,	O
Susannah	O
Martin	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Gardner	O
,	O
Sarah	O
Sheldon	O
,	O
Mary	O
Brown	O
,	O
all	O
five	O
for	O
Clipping	O
:	O
Margaret	O
Williams	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Pepper	O
,	O
for	O
Burglary	O
:	O
Elizabeth	O
Harris	O
alias	O
Oliver	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Morgan	O
,	O
for	O
Felony	O
;	O
and	O
Elizabeth	O
Jones	O
for	O
a	O
Robbery	O
on	O
the	O
High	O
way	O
.	O
The	O
Midwife	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Crompton	I-pers
,	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
tried	O
till	O
next	O
Sessions	O
,	O
being	O
very	O
Sick	O
.	O
THe	O
Necessary	O
and	O
Advantage	O
of	O
an	O
Early	O
Victory	O
over	O
Satan	O
;	O
with	O
some	O
Rules	O
for	O
obtaining	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
Sermon	O
preached	O
to	O
an	O
Auditory	O
in	O
London	O
.	O
By	O
T.	O
Cruso	O
.	O
4to	O
.	O
A	O
Discourse	O
of	O
Christian	O
Religion	O
in	O
sundry	O
Points	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Christ	O
the	O
Hope	O
of	O
Glory	O
.	O
The	O
Knowledg	O
of	O
God	O
in	O
Christ	O
.	O
Christ	O
the	O
only	O
Saviour	O
.	O
The	O
Great	O
Redeemer	O
.	O
The	O
only	O
Mediator	O
.	O
The	O
Foundation	O
of	O
our	O
Adoption	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Necessity	O
of	O
preaching	O
Christ	O
.	O
Preached	O
at	O
the	O
Merchants	O
Lecture	O
in	O
Broad-street	O
.	O
By	O
Thomas	O
Cole	O
.	O
8vo	O
.	O
A	O
Practical	O
Discourse	O
of	O
God	O
's	O
Sovereignty	O
;	O
with	O
other	O
material	O
Points	O
deriving	O
thence	O
.	O
8vo	O
.	O
The	O
Righteous	O
Man	O
's	O
Hope	O
at	O
Death	O
:	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
Death-Bed	O
Reflections	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
proper	O
for	O
a	O
Righteous	O
Man	O
in	O
his	O
Last	O
Sickness	O
.	O
By	O
Samuel	O
Doolittel	O
.	O
8vo	O
.	O
These	O
four	O
Printed	O
for	O
Thomas	O
Cockerill	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Leggs	O
in	O
the	O
Poultrey	O
.	O
A	O
True	O
and	O
Exact	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Retaking	O
a	O
Ship	O
called	O
The	O
Friend	O
's	O
Adventure	O
of	O
Topsham	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
French	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
Taken	O
six	O
Days	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
upon	O
the	O
Coasts	O
of	O
France	O
with	O
it	O
four	O
Days	O
;	O
where	O
one	O
Englishman	O
and	O
a	O
Boy	O
set	O
upon	O
Seven	O
Frenchmen	O
,	O
killed	O
Two	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
other	O
Five	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
Ship	O
and	O
them	O
safe	O
to	O
England	O
.	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
Customs	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Ship	O
amounted	O
to	O
1000	O
l.	O
and	O
upwards	O
.	O
Performed	O
and	O
written	O
by	O
Robert	O
Lyde	O
,	O
Mate	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Ship	O
.	O
State-Tracts	O
.	O
In	O
Two	O
Parts	O
.	O
The	O
First	O
Part	O
being	O
a	O
Collection	O
of	O
several	O
Treatises	O
relating	O
to	O
the	O
Government	O
.	O
Privately	O
printed	O
in	O
the	O
Reign	O
of	O
King	O
Charles	O
II	O
The	O
Second	O
Part	O
consisting	O
of	O
a	O
farther	O
Collection	O
of	O
several	O
Choice	O
Treatises	O
relating	O
to	O
the	O
Government	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Year	O
1660.	O
to	O
1689	O
.	O
Now	O
published	O
in	O
a	O
Body	O
,	O
to	O
shew	O
the	O
Necessity	O
,	O
and	O
clear	O
the	O
Legality	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
Revolution	O
and	O
our	O
Happy	O
Settlement	O
under	O
the	O
Auspicious	O
Reign	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
King	O
William	O
and	O
Queen	O
Mary	O
.	O
Both	O
Printed	O
for	O
Richard	O
Baldwin	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
to	O
give	O
notice	O
to	O
all	O
Persons	O
for	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
the	O
Publick	O
,	O
That	O
W.	O
Elmy	O
,	O
Professor	O
of	O
Physick	O
,	O
and	O
Operator	O
,	O
of	O
known	O
Integrity	O
,	O
and	O
above	O
25	O
Years	O
Practice	O
,	O
liveth	O
at	O
the	O
Blue	O
Ball	O
in	O
Whale-Bone-Court	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
lower	O
end	O
of	O
Bartholomew-Lane	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Royal-Exchange	O
.	O
Who	O
most	O
safely	O
and	O
expeditiously	O
cures	O
Deafness	O
,	O
and	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
Ears	O
,	O
in	O
any	O
,	O
of	O
what	O
Age	O
soever	O
,	O
(	O
if	O
curable	O
)	O
and	O
at	O
first	O
sight	O
by	O
inspection	O
resolves	O
the	O
Patient	O
,	O
if	O
so	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
as	O
most	O
eminent	O
Persons	O
of	O
Quality	O
in	O
this	O
City	O
can	O
testify	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
Remedies	O
ready	O
prepared	O
for	O
the	O
preservation	O
of	O
the	O
Hearing	O
in	O
those	O
who	O
through	O
some	O
great	O
defects	O
in	O
the	O
Sounding	O
Membrane	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Impediments	O
in	O
the	O
Auditory	O
Passages	O
are	O
not	O
perfectly	O
curable	O
,	O
which	O
Remedies	O
preserves	O
them	O
from	O
ever	O
growing	O
worse	O
,	O
and	O
improves	O
their	O
Hearing	O
to	O
Old	O
Age	O
.	O
That	O
you	O
may	O
not	O
mistake	O
and	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
false	O
Pretender	O
,	O
my	O
House	O
is	O
at	O
the	O
Blue-Ball	O
,	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
see	O
it	O
as	O
you	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
