TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
and	O
Queens	O
Commissions	O
ON	O
THE	O
Peace	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
,	O
On	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
24th	O
,	O
25th	O
and	O
26th	O
Days	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
1694	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
Sixth	O
Year	O
of	O
Their	O
MAJESTIES	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bayly	O
,	O
on	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
24th	O
,	O
25th	O
and	O
26th	O
days	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
1694	O
before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Ashurst	I-pers
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
Salathiel	B-pers
Lovell	I-pers
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
follows	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
[	B-pers
Text	I-pers
unreadable	I-pers
in	I-pers
original	I-pers
.	I-pers
]	I-pers
Hutchinson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Warden	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Raffold	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Walsh	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wyldman	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Everingham	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Daniel	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Boyce	I-pers
,	O
Obadiah	B-pers
Hickman	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Adames	I-pers
,	O
Giles	B-pers
Stretton	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Partridge	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Bolthey	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hooper	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Collson	I-pers
James	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Cliffton	I-pers
,	O
Moses	B-pers
Golwell	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Greaves	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Hull	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Longland	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Norton	I-pers
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stafford	I-pers
was	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
35s	O
.	O
from	O
one	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Dockeray	I-pers
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
:	O
To	O
which	O
she	O
immediately	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
robbing	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
a	O
Child	O
,	O
aged	O
four	O
years	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Seige	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
The	O
Child	O
was	O
at	O
play	O
about	O
one	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
day-time	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
parents	O
missing	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
made	O
search	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
Tenter-Ally	O
stript	O
of	O
the	O
Coat	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
afterwards	O
at	O
a	O
Broker	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
by	O
the	O
Father	O
of	O
the	O
Child	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
Coat	O
;	O
but	O
none	O
could	O
swear	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
Child	O
.	O
She	O
denying	O
the	O
fact	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
was	O
arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Chain	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Locket	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
14l	O
.	O
a	O
Watch	O
40s	O
.	O
3	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
6l	O
.	O
5	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
30s	O
.	O
a	O
Box	O
30s	O
.	O
20	O
Guineas	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
one	O
Walter	B-pers
Manning	I-pers
.	O
She	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Lucia	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
was	O
arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
6000	O
Pins	O
,	O
value	O
3s	O
.	O
7	O
yards	O
of	O
Tape	O
2s	O
.	O
and	O
7l	O
.	O
10s	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
;	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Philip	B-pers
Martyn	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
killing	O
one	O
Josiah	B-pers
Yarley	I-pers
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
bruise	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
died	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
was	O
sworn	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
Yarley	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
about	O
10	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
some	O
Night-work	O
,	O
and	O
first	O
struck	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
with	O
a	O
stick	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
goes	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
gives	O
him	O
several	O
blows	O
,	O
which	O
relished	O
so	O
ill	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
struck	O
the	O
Deceased	O
with	O
a	O
Raking	O
Shovel	O
over	O
the	O
head	O
;	O
of	O
which	O
blow	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
afterwards	O
found	O
bleeding	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
Yarley	O
struck	O
him	O
several	O
blows	O
,	O
and	O
drove	O
him	O
up	O
against	O
a	O
Wall	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
one	O
blow	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
forc	O
'd	O
to	O
do	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
defence	O
;	O
adding	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
to	O
hurt	O
Yarley	O
.	O
Mr	O
Bateman	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
swore	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Fracture	O
in	O
the	O
Skull	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
his	O
death	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Malice	O
proved	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Witness	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
said	O
Yarley	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
matter	O
upon	O
himself	O
:	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Holland	O
Shifts	O
,	O
value	O
40s	O
.	O
six	O
Neckcloths	O
,	O
16s	O
.	O
a	O
dozen	O
of	O
Napkins	O
,	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Linen	O
of	O
good	O
value	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
Alice	B-pers
Bassett	I-pers
Widow	O
.	O
The	O
Cloaths	O
were	O
stole	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Field	O
in	O
Southwark	B-place
near	I-place
St.	I-place
Savory	I-place
's	I-place
Dock	I-place
;	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
as	O
she	O
landed	O
with	O
them	O
at	O
Blackfryers	O
Stairs	O
,	O
being	O
stopt	O
by	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
which	O
Goods	O
were	O
owned	O
by	O
Alice	O
Bassett	O
to	O
be	O
hers	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
11	O
Napkins	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
by	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Dunn	O
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Dunn	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
were	O
given	O
her	O
by	O
another	O
Woman	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
and	O
branded	O
before	O
,	O
whereupon	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
One	O
Katherine	B-pers
Salsbury	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
of	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
for	O
forging	O
a	O
Ticket	O
to	O
receive	O
money	O
from	O
the	O
Navy-Office	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
discharg	O
'd	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Diana	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Girl	O
about	O
twelve	O
years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
40s	O
.	O
privily	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
one	O
Sarah	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
Ben	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Honey-lane	B-place
Market	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
Instant	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Foster	O
was	O
hearing	O
a	O
Ballad	O
sung	O
in	O
the	O
Market	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Pocket	O
was	O
pickt	O
immediately	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
telling	O
the	O
money	O
in	O
a	O
corner	O
,	O
which	O
money	O
was	O
owned	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Foster	O
,	O
she	O
swearing	O
it	O
was	O
hers	O
that	O
she	O
then	O
lost	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
strongly	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Market	O
:	O
But	O
that	O
was	O
lookt	O
upon	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
old	O
Newgate	O
shift	O
,	O
and	O
groundless	O
Excuse	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
old	O
Gamester	O
in	O
the	O
Art	O
of	O
Legerdemain	O
,	O
tho	O
but	O
a	O
young	O
Girl	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
thereupon	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Agatha	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
28	O
Yards	O
of	O
Wosted	O
Camblet	O
,	O
value	O
28s	O
.	O
and	O
35	O
Yards	O
of	O
Sarsnet	O
,	O
35s	O
.	O
from	O
Mr.	O
James	B-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
.	O
Mr.	O
Bradshaw	O
lost	O
his	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
pawn	O
'd	O
at	O
a	O
Brokers	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
for	O
17s	O
.	O
She	O
urged	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
bought	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
certain	O
Woman	O
she	O
met	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
who	O
confirmed	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
lent	O
her	O
10s	O
.	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
Goods	O
:	O
others	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
repute	O
.	O
So	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
good	O
Fortune	O
to	O
be	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elinor	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
and	O
Christian	B-pers
Bourne	I-pers
,	O
two	O
Scotch	O
Women	O
,	O
were	O
both	O
Tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
9s	O
.	O
They	O
came	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wilcoxe	I-pers
s	O
's	O
Shop	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
in	O
the	O
Little	B-place
Minories	I-place
,	O
and	O
under	O
a	O
Pretence	O
of	O
buying	O
a	O
Ring	O
,	O
they	O
pinch	O
'd	O
it	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
stopt	O
,	O
Jackson	O
threw	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
into	O
a	O
Kennel	O
.	O
They	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
appear	O
'd	O
:	O
So	O
Jackson	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
,	O
but	O
Bourne	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Osborne	I-pers
of	O
Whitechappel	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
and	O
Tried	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Wayman	I-pers
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
break	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Peterson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
away	O
two	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
8s	O
.	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockins	O
,	O
9s	O
.	O
four	O
Yards	O
of	O
Serge	O
,	O
6s	O
.	O
two	O
Smocks	O
,	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
nine	O
Guinea	O
's	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Peterson	O
swore	O
that	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Goods	O
took	O
away	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
never	O
had	O
again	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
have	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Wayman	O
and	O
Clark	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
Shirt	O
and	O
a	O
Smock	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Confederate	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
one	O
could	O
charge	O
her	O
with	O
Burglary	O
,	O
nor	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
the	O
said	O
Petersons	O
;	O
and	O
indeed	O
the	O
grand	O
Thieves	O
were	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
thereupon	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
robbing	O
her	O
Master	O
,	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Gill	I-pers
of	O
Wapping	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
Instant	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Bag	O
,	O
value	O
1d	O
.	O
40	O
Guinea	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
10l	O
.	O
in	O
money	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
confessed	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
stole	O
7l	O
.	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pistole	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Master	O
's	O
Trunk	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
300	O
Guinea	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
broad	O
Pieces	O
in	O
the	O
Bag	O
besides	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
spar	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
upon	O
her	O
Trial	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
away	O
7l	O
.	O
as	O
also	O
a	O
Pistole	O
and	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
but	O
medled	O
with	O
nothing	O
more	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
,	O
in	O
forging	O
a	O
false	O
Note	O
in	O
the	O
Names	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Holles	I-pers
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Martlin	I-pers
,	O
to	O
receive	O
5l	O
.	O
17s	O
.	O
and	O
4d	O
.	O
from	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Israel	B-pers
Lock	I-pers
;	O
which	O
Offence	O
he	O
immediately	O
confest	O
upon	O
his	O
Arraignment	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Blewet	I-pers
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
a	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
Key	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
being	O
the	B-place
Cross-Keys	I-place
in	I-place
Gracious-street	I-place
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
away	O
one	O
Bever	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
3l	O
.	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
10s	O
.	O
one	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
7s	O
.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
moneys	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
Mrs.	O
Keys	O
Dwelling-house	O
.	O
The	O
Casement	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
which	O
was	O
fast	O
shut	O
on	O
the	O
over-night	O
,	O
a	O
Quorrel	O
being	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
way	O
to	O
get	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
stopt	O
by	O
the	O
Servants	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
Another	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
got	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
,	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lay'n	O
in	O
the	O
Hayloft	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pocket-Book	O
was	O
found	O
dropt	O
upon	O
the	O
Leads	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
that	O
way	O
late	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
made	O
bold	O
to	O
lie	O
there	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
but	O
a	O
feigned	O
Excuse	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
an	O
Offender	O
before	O
this	O
time	O
,	O
yet	O
the	O
Evidence	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
nothing	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
that	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Lee	O
;	O
thereupon	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
good	O
Fortune	O
to	O
be	O
acquitted	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
was	O
Arraigned	O
and	O
Tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
Napkins	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
one	O
Table-cloth	O
5s	O
.	O
and	O
two	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
,	O
when	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
person	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
fell	O
a	O
crying	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
taxed	O
with	O
the	O
Thefts	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
compounded	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
She	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
Mrs.	O
Bishop	O
's	O
Daughter	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
all	O
the	O
day	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
very	O
circumstantial	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
called	O
good	O
Witnesses	O
for	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Katherine	B-pers
Desseens	I-pers
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
9	O
Yards	O
of	O
Ribboning	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
from	O
one	O
Titford	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
to	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Titford	I-pers
's	O
Shop	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Ribbons	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Ribboning	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
knowing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sent	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
taxt	O
her	O
with	O
stealing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
deni	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
satisfaction	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
if	O
Mrs.	O
Titford	O
would	O
swear	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
some	O
good	O
Witnesses	O
for	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
declared	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
careful	O
industrious	O
Woman	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
arrest	O
Mr.	O
Titford	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
in	O
a	O
Joint	O
Action	O
of	O
40l	O
.	O
for	O
scandalizing	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
might	O
raise	O
some	O
Animosity	O
betwixt	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Titford	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
trusted	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Ribboning	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
;	O
for	O
she	O
had	O
dealt	O
with	O
her	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
of	O
her	O
Trade	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
Milliner	O
s.	O
She	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Bainbrigg	I-pers
was	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
Andrew	B-pers
Bourne	I-pers
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Laced	O
Pinner	O
,	O
a	O
Blanket	O
,	O
4	O
Plates	O
,	O
a	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Muslin	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
value	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Northorp	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
for	O
two	O
several	O
Robberies	O
upon	O
the	O
Hig-way	O
:	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
Jehudah	B-pers
Stenet	I-pers
,	O
the	O
second	O
for	O
robbing	O
one	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
who	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
four	O
High-way	O
men	O
met	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
Lane	O
near	O
Honslow	B-place
Heath	I-place
,	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
their	O
Horses	O
Bridle	O
and	O
clapt	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
threatened	O
them	O
with	O
death	O
;	O
so	O
carried	O
them	O
into	O
a	O
little	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
robb	O
'd	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
of	O
40s	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
their	O
Swords	O
and	O
Pistols	O
;	O
afterwards	O
the	O
Waggons	O
coming	O
by	O
,	O
they	O
fell	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
them	O
;	O
causing	O
the	O
said	O
Webb	O
and	O
Stenet	O
to	O
lie	O
still	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
whilst	O
they	O
committed	O
the	O
Robbery	O
:	O
then	O
the	O
Town	O
of	O
Honslow	O
was	O
raised	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
High-way	O
men	O
pursued	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
all	O
got	O
away	O
except	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
shot	O
in	O
the	O
Leg	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Countrey	O
men	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Horse	O
also	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
though	O
with	O
great	O
difficulty	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Pistol	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
owned	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Webb	O
:	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Countrey	O
Boy	O
about	O
16	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
sworn	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
him	O
hold	O
their	O
Horses	O
whilst	O
they	O
committed	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
threatening	O
to	O
shoot	O
him	O
through	O
the	O
head	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
discharge	O
his	O
Office	O
;	O
the	O
Boy	O
being	O
askt	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
afraid	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
made	O
him	O
shake	O
a	O
little	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
so	O
much	O
daunted	O
:	O
Other	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
upon	O
Oath	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
Vizard-Mask	O
on	O
,	O
so	O
had	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
;	O
all	O
this	O
was	O
fully	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Witnesses	O
.	O
All	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
other	O
three	O
upon	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
forced	O
him	O
to	O
ingage	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
improbable	O
Story	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
believed	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
:	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Cusack	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
killing	O
one	O
Robert	B-pers
Salisbury	I-pers
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
at	O
Grays-Inn	B-place
Lane-end	I-place
in	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
upon	O
his	O
breast	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
8	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
Mr.	O
Salisbury	O
,	O
were	O
in	O
company	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Salisbury	O
,	O
where	O
Mr.	O
Cusack	O
was	O
saying	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lately	O
recommended	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
a	O
certain	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
a	O
particular	O
Friend	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
done	O
him	O
great	O
kindnesses	O
,	O
therefore	O
hop't	O
the	O
Servant	O
would	O
prove	O
well	O
,	O
or	O
words	O
to	O
that	O
effect	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
his	O
Pimp	O
,	O
or	O
do	O
you	O
procure	O
for	O
him	O
?	O
Upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
grew	O
angry	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
scorn	O
'd	O
any	O
such	O
Action	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
further	O
words	O
arose	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Deceased	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
overtook	O
him	O
just	O
at	O
Grays-Inn	O
Lane-end	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
further	O
words	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
strike	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
his	O
Cane	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
shake	O
Mr.	O
Cusack	O
upon	O
the	O
Breast	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
shake	O
him	O
to	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
challenging	O
him	O
to	O
box	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Cusack	O
refusing	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Salisbury	O
would	O
have	O
struck	O
him	O
again	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Cusack	O
drew	O
his	O
sword	O
and	O
unfortunately	O
ran	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Body	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
;	O
adding	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
all	O
he	O
could	O
to	O
evade	O
the	O
Quarrel	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
always	O
been	O
loving	O
Friends	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
to	O
have	O
kill	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
being	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
allowed	O
:	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Law	O
requires	O
in	O
all	O
such	O
sudden	O
Quarrels	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mustapha	B-pers
Pochowachett	I-pers
a	O
Turk	O
,	O
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
committing	O
the	O
most	O
Unnatural	O
and	O
Horrid	O
Sin	O
of	O
Buggery	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
so	O
detestable	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
fit	O
to	O
be	O
named	O
among	O
Christians	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
one	O
Anthony	B-pers
Bassa	I-pers
,	O
Dutch	O
Boy	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
age	O
of	O
14	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
upwards	O
.	O
Bassa	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
lay	O
together	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
assaulted	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
forced	O
his	O
Yard	O
into	O
his	O
Body	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Boy	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
to	O
prevent	O
which	O
he	O
stopt	O
his	O
Mouth	O
with	O
the	O
Pillow	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
unnatural	O
manner	O
.	O
The	O
Surgeon	O
swore	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
the	O
said	O
Bassa	O
the	O
Venereal	O
Distemper	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Boy	O
was	O
very	O
ill	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
What	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
say	O
?	O
which	O
was	O
done	O
by	O
an	O
Interpreter	O
sworn	O
for	O
that	O
purpose	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
did	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
,	O
only	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
But	O
then	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
further	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
order	O
'd	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
Boy	O
,	O
found	O
two	O
great	O
Ulcers	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
his	O
Fundament	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
dangerous	O
condition	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Turk	O
's	O
Members	O
were	O
shanker	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
much	O
bloody	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
hole	O
upon	O
the	O
fleshly	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
Yard	O
.	O
The	O
Turk	O
said	O
by	O
the	O
Interpreter	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
do	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
stand	O
the	O
Search	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
done	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
believ	O
'd	O
the	O
Boy	O
's	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
thing	O
appeared	O
very	O
very	O
foul	O
and	O
detestable	O
before	O
the	O
Face	O
of	O
Christians	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
Crime	O
so	O
grievous	O
in	O
the	O
sight	O
of	O
God	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
having	O
maturely	O
consider	O
'd	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
Buggery	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Peter	B-pers
Whittingham	I-pers
,	O
S	B-pers
-	I-pers
H	I-pers
-	I-pers
and	O
A	B-pers
-	I-pers
H	I-pers
-	I-pers
were	O
all	O
Tried	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
in	O
Cutting	O
,	O
Clipping	O
,	O
Filing	O
,	O
and	O
Diminishing	O
the	O
Currant	O
Money	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
10	O
Half-Crowns	O
,	O
20	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
Six-pences	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
Queen	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
seen	O
at	O
work	O
;	O
Whittingham	O
clipping	O
money	O
,	O
S	O
-	O
H	O
-	O
Filing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
A	O
-	O
H	O
-	O
rubbing	O
it	O
upon	O
a	O
Leather	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
smooth	O
.	O
They	O
made	O
their	O
Escape	O
once	O
from	O
the	O
Officers	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
were	O
taken	O
sometime	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Peter	O
Whittingham	O
was	O
taken	O
at	O
the	O
Salmon	O
and	O
Ball	O
in	O
Moorfields	O
,	O
and	O
H	O
-	O
and	O
A	O
-	O
in	O
Mugwell-street	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
very	O
clearly	O
proved	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
clipt	O
money	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
as	O
corroborating	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
shewed	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
divers	O
of	O
their	O
Neighbours	O
to	O
justify	O
their	O
Reputation	O
,	O
urging	O
,	O
That	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
had	O
malice	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
prosecute	O
,	O
till	O
they	O
had	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
with	O
a	O
Warrant	O
for	O
suspicion	O
of	O
robbing	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
of	O
50l	O
.	O
But	O
yet	O
the	O
Court	O
directed	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
That	O
People	O
that	O
are	O
Clippers	O
,	O
are	O
commonly	O
of	O
good	O
Repute	O
,	O
because	O
they	O
get	O
their	O
money	O
easier	O
than	O
other	O
men	O
,	O
therefore	O
acted	O
fairly	O
with	O
their	O
Neighbours	O
;	O
that	O
a	O
man	O
might	O
have	O
a	O
fair	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
yet	O
be	O
an	O
Offender	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Case	O
;	O
yet	O
it	O
was	O
left	O
to	O
their	O
Consciences	O
,	O
whether	O
they	O
did	O
believe	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
;	O
if	O
they	O
did	O
,	O
they	O
must	O
find	O
them	O
guilty	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
otherwise	O
acquit	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
having	O
well	O
weighed	O
the	O
Case	O
,	O
brought	O
them	O
in	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
James	I-pers
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
Francis	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Blow	O
with	O
a	O
Broomstick	O
upon	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
of	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
which	O
gave	O
him	O
such	O
a	O
Bruise	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
died	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
May	O
following	O
.	O
A	O
Quarrel	O
hapned	O
betwixt	O
them	O
about	O
striking	O
a	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
James	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
fling	O
the	O
Stick	O
at	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
his	O
head	O
being	O
search	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
depression	O
was	O
made	O
upon	O
the	O
Scull	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
and	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Stick	O
was	O
but	O
a	O
small	O
Stick	O
,	O
and	O
probably	O
he	O
might	O
receive	O
the	O
wound	O
by	O
the	O
Fall	O
;	O
for	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
(	O
his	O
Foot	O
slipping	O
)	O
against	O
a	O
Stair-Case	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
one	O
saw	O
the	O
Stick	O
cut	O
his	O
Head	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Pryor	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Coachman	O
,	O
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
driving	O
his	O
Coach-wheel	O
over	O
the	O
Leg	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Hewetson	I-pers
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
by	O
Chance	O
,	O
not	O
wilfully	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
standing	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
.	O
So	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
by	O
misfortune	O
,	O
therefore	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Nathanael	B-pers
Peck	I-pers
of	O
London	O
,	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
in	O
Counterfeiting	O
,	O
Forging	O
,	O
and	O
making	O
one	O
hundred	O
false	O
Guineas	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Witness	O
swore	O
that	O
Peck	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
Guineas	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
21s	O
.	O
8d	O
.	O
a	O
piece	O
for	O
24	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
which	O
when	O
weighed	O
,	O
proved	O
too	O
light	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
they	O
were	O
false	O
ones	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
suffering	O
Sir	O
James	B-pers
Montgomery	I-pers
to	O
make	O
his	O
Escape	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hands	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
delivered	O
into	O
his	O
Custody	O
(	O
being	O
a	O
Messenger	O
)	O
charged	O
upon	O
suspicion	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
before	O
the	O
Secretary	O
of	O
State	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
swore	O
that	O
Sir	O
James	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
Sutton	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Centinels	O
being	O
set	O
over	O
him	O
to	O
keep	O
him	O
safe	O
;	O
they	O
gave	O
him	O
leave	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Sutton	O
was	O
privy	O
to	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
nor	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Lock	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
which	O
could	O
be	O
done	O
by	O
none	O
but	O
the	O
two	O
Centinels	O
that	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
:	O
And	O
Sutton	O
proved	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
abroad	O
to	O
execute	O
a	O
Warrant	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
concerning	O
the	O
Government	O
;	O
and	O
this	O
Witness	O
swore	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
Sutton	O
was	O
a	O
person	O
very	O
well	O
affected	O
to	O
the	O
present	O
Government	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
always	O
very	O
careful	O
in	O
his	O
business	O
;	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Drury	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
near	O
Bloomsbury	O
,	O
by	O
shooting	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Pistol-Bullet	O
into	O
the	O
Thigh	O
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
suspected	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
persons	O
that	O
Robbed	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Pigget	I-pers
of	O
Woodford	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
pursued	O
by	O
some	O
persons	O
into	O
the	O
Field	O
behind	O
Montague	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
apprehend	O
him	O
,	O
crying	O
out	O
a	O
Highway-man	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Field	O
,	O
a	O
great	O
Rabble	O
was	O
running	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
throwing	O
Brick-Batts	O
at	O
him	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
the	O
Constable	O
coming	O
along	O
the	O
Field	O
,	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Constable	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
surrender	O
himself	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
preserve	O
him	O
from	O
the	O
Insolencies	O
of	O
the	O
Mobb	O
:	O
But	O
he	O
refused	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
swearing	O
he	O
would	O
kill	O
any	O
man	O
that	O
should	O
come	O
near	O
him	O
,	O
bidding	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
keep	O
off	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
(	O
he	O
swore	O
)	O
God	O
Damn	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
shoot	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
Pass	O
at	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
put	O
by	O
with	O
his	O
Staff	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
man	O
.	O
Closed	O
in	O
with	O
hi	O
,	O
and	O
clasped	O
him	O
about	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
his	O
Constables	O
Staff	O
in	O
his	O
Left	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pistol	O
in	O
the	O
Right	O
,	O
he	O
immediately	O
discharged	O
his	O
Pistol	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
directing	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
might	O
not	O
hurt	O
him	O
.	O
After	O
which	O
,	O
Mr.	O
W.	O
shot	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
into	O
the	O
Thigh	O
,	O
who	O
fell	O
back	O
and	O
Cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
Rogue	O
has	O
kill	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
proved	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
shewed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
his	O
Authority	O
as	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
by	O
producing	O
his	O
Staff	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
mildly	O
desired	O
him	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Name	O
,	O
to	O
yield	O
and	O
surrender	O
himself	O
quietly	O
to	O
his	O
power	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
protect	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
yield	O
,	O
swearing	O
he	O
would	O
shoot	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
And	O
if	O
the	O
Constable	O
had	O
not	O
put	O
the	O
said	O
W	O
's	O
Pistol	O
downwards	O
towards	O
the	O
earth	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
shot	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Belly	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
who	O
all	O
agreed	O
in	O
the	O
matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
,	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Mr.	O
W.	O
declared	O
in	O
his	O
Behalf	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
Bayliffs	O
arresting	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
made	O
that	O
defence	O
for	O
himself	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
came	O
without	O
a	O
Staff	O
or	O
Warrant	O
to	O
seize	O
him	O
,	O
therefore	O
he	O
thought	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Field	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
the	O
Murder	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
who	O
could	O
not	O
confirm	O
what	O
he	O
asserted	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
declared	O
in	O
the	O
general	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
struggling	O
together	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
Pistols	O
shot	O
off	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
W.	O
went	O
off	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Witness	O
against	O
him	O
further	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
desired	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
inform	O
the	O
Court	O
at	O
the	O
Trial	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
Society	O
with	O
Bernard	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
that	O
Robbed	O
Sir	O
Richard	O
Pigget	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
might	O
be	O
a	O
prejudice	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
urged	O
further	O
,	O
That	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
defence	O
:	O
But	O
was	O
told	O
that	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
for	O
all	O
the	O
Evidence	O
agreed	O
viva	O
voce	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
killed	O
him	O
maliciously	O
and	O
basely	O
,	O
being	O
unwilling	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
,	O
lest	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
prosecuted	O
for	O
the	O
Burglary	O
at	O
Sir	O
Richard	O
Piggets	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
full	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Murther	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
watch	O
value	O
8l	O
.	O
and	O
45s	O
.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
from	O
George	B-pers
Duch	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
positive	O
that	O
she	O
stole	O
the	O
watch	O
or	O
money	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Susan	B-pers
Tills	I-pers
,	O
Katharine	B-pers
Dodd	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Barber	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Gayler	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Tried	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
in	O
Clipping	O
the	O
Currant	O
Money	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
Queen	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
Maid	O
that	O
lived	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Tills	O
,	O
who	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
her	O
Mistris	O
Clip	O
and	O
her	O
Master	O
both	O
in	O
Bed	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
but	O
Tills	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
himself	O
,	O
being	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
She	O
swore	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
Gayler	O
clip	O
money	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
say	O
nothing	O
against	O
Dodd	O
.	O
Another	O
Witness	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
change	O
narrow	O
money	O
for	O
broad	O
money	O
oftentimes	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
money	O
that	O
was	O
newly	O
clipt	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Tills	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
Gang	O
of	O
them	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
carrying	O
on	O
the	O
Trade	O
;	O
particularly	O
one	O
Ann	B-pers
Auguish	I-pers
and	O
Moll	B-pers
Rowley	I-pers
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
wont	O
to	O
procure	O
the	O
money	O
for	O
the	O
Clippers	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shears	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
Crown	O
that	O
was	O
brass	O
,	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Tills	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Shears	O
were	O
useful	O
to	O
her	O
Husband	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
of	O
his	O
Trade	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Watchmaker	O
.	O
Dodd	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
so	O
did	O
Gayler	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
several	O
of	O
their	O
Neighbours	O
who	O
gave	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Tills	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
known	O
her	O
20	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
found	O
that	O
she	O
clipt	O
any	O
money	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
bad	O
sort	O
of	O
people	O
did	O
resort	O
to	O
Till	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
others	O
said	O
that	O
Gayler	O
was	O
a	O
Woman	O
that	O
works	O
hard	O
for	O
her	O
living	O
at	O
washing	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Servant	O
Sarah	B-pers
Jyn	I-pers
was	O
an	O
ill	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
frequented	O
Bawdy-houses	O
in	O
White-Fryers	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Tills	O
and	O
Jyn	O
us't	O
to	O
fall	O
out	O
;	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
that	O
Dodd	O
had	O
been	O
whipt	O
in	O
Bridewell	O
several	O
times	O
for	O
picking	O
Pockets	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
heard	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
help	O
an	O
old	O
Gentlewoman	O
to	O
a	O
Maidenhead	O
for	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
common	O
Report	O
of	O
the	O
Women	O
of	O
the	O
Town	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
the	O
Trade	O
of	O
Pocket-picking	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
now	O
turned	O
Niggler	O
,	O
(	O
that	O
is	O
to	O
say	O
)	O
a	O
Clipper	O
of	O
money	O
;	O
all	O
this	O
was	O
not	O
enough	O
to	O
convict	O
them	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
but	O
one	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
a	O
doubtful	O
one	O
too	O
;	O
So	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Blundevill	I-pers
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
being	O
a	O
Common	O
Defrauder	O
and	O
Cheater	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
Subjects	O
of	O
their	O
monies	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
by	O
Forging	O
and	O
Counterfeiting	O
Letters	O
signed	O
with	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Post-Office	O
General	O
;	O
particularly	O
,	O
he	O
delivered	O
two	O
Letters	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Robert	B-pers
Tempest	I-pers
,	O
supposed	O
to	O
come	O
from	O
Ireland	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Tempest	O
paid	O
10d	O
.	O
a	O
piece	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
such	O
Letters	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
Gentleman	O
Swore	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
practice	O
such	O
doings	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
delivered	O
several	O
Letters	O
to	O
other	O
persons	O
besides	O
Major	O
Tempest	O
,	O
which	O
agreed	O
with	O
his	O
own	O
hand	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
write	O
before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
;	O
one	O
Letter	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
sent	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Dodd	O
from	O
the	O
Poultrey	O
Comter	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
discover	O
other	O
People	O
that	O
were	O
Accomplices	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
provided	O
Mr.	O
Dodd	O
would	O
be	O
favourable	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
him	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
such	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
impeach	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
never	O
did	O
act	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
Person	O
in	O
Court	O
who	O
produced	O
12	O
Letters	O
that	O
were	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
stamp	O
and	O
Character	O
:	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
a	O
Cheat	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
C	B-pers
-	I-pers
B	I-pers
-	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
29	O
Yards	O
of	O
Stuff	O
,	O
value	O
4l	O
.	O
7s	O
.	O
from	O
Francis	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
Witness	O
that	O
saw	O
him	O
buy	O
the	O
Stuff	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Hulk	I-pers
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
100	O
Weight	O
of	O
melted	O
tallow	O
,	O
value	O
42s	O
.	O
from	O
Michael	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
clear	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
not	O
being	O
indicted	O
for	O
Burglary	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Cobham	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Forging	O
a	O
False	O
Ticket	O
of	O
the	O
Navy	O
Office	O
,	O
prtending	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Seaman	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
get	O
money	O
from	O
the	O
Treasurer	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
in	O
course	O
.	O
W	B-pers
-	I-pers
H	I-pers
-	I-pers
and	O
W	B-pers
-	I-pers
C	I-pers
-	I-pers
who	O
were	O
Evidence	O
in	O
the	O
Trial	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Whittingham	I-pers
and	O
the	O
rest	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
were	O
now	O
Arraigned	O
and	O
Tried	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
said	O
Peter	O
Whittingham	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bag	O
value	O
1d	O
.	O
53l	O
.	O
10s	O
.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
S	B-pers
-	I-pers
H	I-pers
-	I-pers
.	O
There	O
was	O
only	O
Whittingham	O
's	O
single	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
and	O
Elinor	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
as	O
Accessary	O
were	O
Tried	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Deane	I-pers
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
watch	O
value	O
7l	O
.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Pistols	O
40s	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
not	O
positive	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Woodcock	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Spence	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
Three	O
Tried	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mr.	O
William	B-pers
Fitz-Harrold	I-pers
;	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
10s	O
.	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
There	O
appearing	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
malice	O
in	O
the	O
Trial	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
done	O
in	O
the	O
day-time	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
Not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Tobin	I-pers
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
killing	O
one	O
David	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
wound	O
in	O
his	O
throat	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
five	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
died	O
the	O
22d	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
one	O
Rhodes	O
and	O
Powel	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
were	O
drinking	O
in	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
Somerset	B-place
Yard	I-place
,	O
where	O
the	O
deceased	O
Hughes	O
was	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
threw	O
the	O
Pot	O
of	O
Drink	O
in	O
his	O
face	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
provocation	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Swords	O
were	O
drawn	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
was	O
a	O
top	O
of	O
Hughes	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
drawn	O
,	O
having	O
a	O
wound	O
given	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
Neck	O
as	O
abovesaid	O
,	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
swore	O
that	O
he	O
died	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Evidence	O
pro	O
&	O
con	O
,	O
but	O
Hughes	O
,	O
as	O
appeared	O
by	O
a	O
Witness	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
which	O
of	O
the	O
Three	O
killed	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Dakers	I-pers
was	O
Tried	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
,	O
with	O
Mary	B-pers
Westcomb	I-pers
,	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
break	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
,	O
and	O
did	O
steal	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Child-bed	O
Linen	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
value	O
.	O
She	O
confest	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
but	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Trial	O
.	O
It	O
being	O
proved	O
she	O
broke	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
York	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Edge	I-pers
were	O
Tried	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barloe	I-pers
now	O
sick	O
in	O
Jail	O
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
not	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
Rob	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hosey	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Highway	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
day	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Gelding	O
coloured	O
black	O
,	O
value	O
16l	O
.	O
with	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
value	O
.	O
Hosey	O
swore	O
he	O
was	O
Robb	O
'd	O
by	O
Six	O
men	O
upon	O
Honslow-heath	B-place
,	O
but	O
they	O
having	O
Vizard-Masks	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
discern	O
their	O
Faces	O
.	O
But	O
one	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
swore	O
that	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
actually	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Robbery	O
.	O
They	O
having	O
nothing	O
material	O
to	O
offer	O
,	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
One	O
Richard	B-pers
Cokley	I-pers
an	O
Irish	O
Papist	O
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
falsly	O
pretending	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Snow	O
under	O
his	O
Feet	O
the	O
12th	O
day	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
near	O
the	O
Temple-gate	O
,	O
a	O
Green	O
Vellum	O
Pocket-book	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
some	O
writing	O
and	O
several	O
Papers	O
,	O
importing	O
a	O
Design	O
against	O
the	O
Lives	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
;	O
whereas	O
in	O
truth	O
the	O
Book	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
long	O
before	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
design	O
was	O
to	O
impose	O
upon	O
the	O
Secretary	O
of	O
State	O
by	O
bringing	O
it	O
as	O
a	O
Discovery	O
of	O
Consequence	O
to	O
raise	O
a	O
merit	O
to	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
sham	O
the	O
Real	O
Design	O
against	O
the	O
Government	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
,	O
in	O
respect	O
of	O
his	O
Poverty	O
,	O
impos	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
the	O
Fine	O
of	O
100l	O
.	O
and	O
Three	O
times	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
,	O
and	O
find	O
Sureties	O
for	O
his	O
Good	O
behaviour	O
for	O
a	O
Twelvemonth	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
,	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
under	O
Bail	O
,	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
day	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1689	O
,	O
being	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
Lodging	O
of	O
Dr.	B-pers
Littleton	I-pers
of	O
Doctors	B-place
Commons	I-place
,	O
London	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
before	O
been	O
Clerk	O
,	O
did	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
Doctor	O
's	O
going	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
take	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Doctor	O
's	O
Study	O
,	O
and	O
unlock	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Gold	O
and	O
Silver	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
200l	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
that	O
swore	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
were	O
Dr.	O
Littleton	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
then	O
a	O
Footman	O
to	O
the	O
Doctor	O
.	O
Johnson	O
swore	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Bradshaw	O
ordered	O
him	O
the	O
time	O
aforesaid	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
fetch	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
Doctor	O
's	O
Study	O
that	O
then	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
in	O
the	O
Doctor	O
's	O
Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
bring	O
it	O
down	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
therewith	O
the	O
said	O
Bradshaw	O
unlockt	O
the	O
Study	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
7l	O
.	O
in	O
Silver	O
and	O
two	O
Guineas	O
in	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
be	O
gone	O
into	O
his	O
own	O
Countrey	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
accordingly	O
did	O
.	O
The	O
Doctor	O
swore	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
aforesaid	O
of	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
Two	O
hundred	O
Pound	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
always	O
suspected	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
alledged	O
,	O
That	O
Johnson	O
immediately	O
upon	O
the	O
committing	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
fled	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
Gazette	O
by	O
Dr.	O
Littleton	O
with	O
a	O
Reward	O
of	O
20l	O
.	O
to	O
any	O
Person	O
that	O
should	O
take	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
Bradshaw	O
never	O
remov	O
'd	O
from	O
his	O
Business	O
,	O
but	O
took	O
all	O
possible	O
care	O
to	O
have	O
Johnson	O
apprehended	O
;	O
and	O
proved	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
caused	O
2000	O
Bills	O
to	O
be	O
printed	O
,	O
described	O
the	O
said	O
Johnson	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
distributed	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
all	O
Watches	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
also	O
caused	O
Hue	O
and	O
Cries	O
to	O
be	O
be	O
made	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
to	O
all	O
parts	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
for	O
taking	O
the	O
said	O
Johnson	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Reward	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Doctor	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
afterwards	O
Johnson	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
said	O
Johnson	O
for	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
did	O
testify	O
,	O
That	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
by	O
Johnson	O
's	O
confession	O
,	O
a	O
Correspondence	O
between	O
the	O
Doctor	O
and	O
the	O
said	O
Johnson	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Doctor	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
the	O
Doctor	O
(	O
whose	O
Hand	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
very	O
well	O
)	O
wherein	O
the	O
Doctor	O
had	O
promised	O
a	O
Pardon	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Johnson	O
in	O
case	O
he	O
would	O
swear	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Johnson	O
declared	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Doctor	O
's	O
whole	O
Design	O
to	O
lay	O
the	O
matter	O
upon	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Bradshaw	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
condition	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Sum	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
;	O
but	O
saith	O
Johnson	O
,	O
this	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
,	O
nor	O
will	O
not	O
do	O
,	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Bradshaw	O
is	O
innocent	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
is	O
as	O
honest	O
a	O
man	O
as	O
any	O
one	O
living	O
;	O
further	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
testify	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Johnson	O
had	O
been	O
seen	O
to	O
have	O
100	O
or	O
more	O
Guineas	O
at	O
one	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
since	O
the	O
Robbery	O
he	O
had	O
paid	O
several	O
Debts	O
,	O
particularly	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Tax	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
12l	O
.	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Johnson	O
had	O
built	O
a	O
House	O
that	O
cost	O
20l	O
.	O
or	O
more	O
.	O
Further	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
testified	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
said	O
Johnson	O
had	O
committed	O
several	O
Robberies	O
by	O
several	O
Names	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
on	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
of	O
100l	O
.	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
fled	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
never	O
heard	O
of	O
till	O
this	O
time	O
;	O
others	O
testified	O
,	O
that	O
Johnson	O
was	O
a	O
common	O
Gaol-bird	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
burnt	O
in	O
the	O
hand	O
,	O
which	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
off	O
the	O
suspicion	O
the	O
Doctor	O
had	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
proved	O
by	O
the	O
Doctor	O
's	O
Confession	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
employed	O
him	O
in	O
all	O
,	O
or	O
most	O
of	O
his	O
Affairs	O
,	O
since	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
committed	O
;	O
and	O
by	O
his	O
Letters	O
,	O
not	O
only	O
with	O
his	O
moneys	O
,	O
but	O
with	O
his	O
Mistress	O
also	O
;	O
which	O
Letters	O
were	O
produced	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lost	O
20l	O
.	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
money	O
.	O
So	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
finding	O
the	O
said	O
Johnson	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
notorious	O
Rogue	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sworn	O
one	O
thing	O
to	O
the	O
Grand	O
Jury	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
;	O
the	O
Grand	O
Jury	O
happening	O
to	O
hear	O
it	O
,	O
desired	O
leave	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
information	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
accordingly	O
did	O
,	O
looking	O
upon	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
:	O
And	O
that	O
Dr.	O
Littleton	O
's	O
only	O
using	O
very	O
reflecting	O
Language	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
nothing	O
to	O
the	O
purpose	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
person	O
of	O
undoubted	O
honesty	O
and	O
Reputation	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
Court	O
was	O
well	O
satisfied	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
upon	O
the	O
matter	O
to	O
be	O
rather	O
malice	O
than	O
fact	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Johnson	O
taken	O
into	O
custody	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Wilmore	I-pers
was	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Tippet	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
a	O
Hood	O
,	O
2s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
a	O
Scarf	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Ell	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Connel	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Connel	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
were	O
both	O
Tried	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Edward	B-pers
Poor	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Thorp	I-pers
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
rob	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wyng	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
12s	O
.	O
and	O
17l	O
.	O
in	O
money	O
-	O
Connel	O
producing	O
a	O
Warrant	O
in	O
Court	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
evil	O
persons	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
not	O
to	O
search	O
with	O
any	O
Felonious	O
Intent	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
May	I-pers
was	O
Tried	O
upon	O
two	O
indictments	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Richard	B-pers
Hutton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
breaking	O
his	O
House	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
stealing	O
a	O
Beaver	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
30s	O
.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
besides	O
Guinea	O
's	O
and	O
Silver	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
near	O
100l	O
.	O
The	O
matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
Indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Tuckeley	I-pers
,	O
taking	O
away	O
several	O
Swords	O
with	O
Silver	O
and	O
steel	O
Hilts	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
great	O
value	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rush	I-pers
a	O
Sword-Cutter	O
.	O
The	O
Burglary	O
being	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
thereupon	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
York	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Edge	I-pers
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Eason	I-pers
of	O
3l	O
.	O
in	O
money	O
.	O
Richard	O
Jenkins	O
shot	O
Mr.	O
Eason	O
upon	O
the	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
bruised	O
his	O
Arm	O
.	O
The	O
King	O
's	O
Witness	O
swore	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
there	O
at	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
Barloe	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
one	O
C	O
-	O
all	O
which	O
was	O
believed	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
Indicted	O
by	O
the	O
same	O
Names	O
together	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Newin	I-pers
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Emanuel	B-pers
Colony	I-pers
Marquess	O
of	O
Cavalis	O
,	O
the	O
Spanish	O
Ambassador	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
taking	O
away	O
a	O
Silver	O
Chalice	O
,	O
value	O
8l	O
.	O
three	O
Holland	O
Surplices	O
30s	O
.	O
three	O
Stuff-Gowns	O
4l	O
.	O
10s	O
.	O
&	O
c.	O
about	O
12	O
a	O
clock	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
positively	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
thereupon	O
they	O
were	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Adam	B-pers
Lynn	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Drummer	O
,	O
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
wound	O
near	O
the	O
Right	O
pap	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
12	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Witness	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
in	O
Newgate	O
that	O
he	O
killed	O
the	O
said	O
Richardsson	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
that	O
Lynn	O
pusht	O
with	O
a	O
good	O
will	O
,	O
and	O
killed	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
alledged	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
all	O
day	O
with	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
because	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
Bawdy-house	O
,	O
Richardson	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
drew	O
their	O
Swords	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
threatening	O
to	O
kill	O
him	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
draw	O
his	O
Sword	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
defence	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
killed	O
him	O
.	O
Having	O
no	O
Witness	O
to	O
prove	O
any	O
thing	O
he	O
alledged	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
positive	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
only	O
,	O
considering	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
done	O
in	O
a	O
sudden	O
heat	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Mark	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
October	O
lost	O
,	O
a	O
Serge	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
20s	O
.	O
also	O
another	O
Gown	O
12s	O
.	O
She	O
confessing	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
offering	O
to	O
compound	O
it	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
York	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Tovey	I-pers
were	O
Tried	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Jekyll	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
stealing	O
several	O
Goods	O
to	O
a	O
very	O
considerable	O
value	O
,	O
besides	O
60	O
Guinea	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
25l	O
.	O
in	O
Silver	O
numbered	O
.	O
Though	O
the	O
Witness	O
affirmed	O
that	O
Tovey	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
York	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
behaving	O
himself	O
undecently	O
in	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
The	O
Witness	O
was	O
a	O
Rogue	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
Gallows	O
in	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
hoped	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Notwithstanding	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
full	O
against	O
them	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Humphrey	B-pers
Woodman	I-pers
and	O
W	B-pers
-	I-pers
C	I-pers
-	I-pers
were	O
Tried	O
for	O
robbing	O
Major	B-pers
Belloe	I-pers
in	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
(	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
)	O
a	O
Gelding	O
,	O
coloured	O
White	O
,	O
price	O
12l	O
.	O
with	O
a	O
Saddle	O
and	O
Bridle	O
,	O
value	O
14s	O
.	O
The	O
Robbery	O
was	O
done	O
on	O
Fulmore	B-place
Heath	I-place
,	O
and	O
they	O
being	O
pursued	O
by	O
the	O
Country	O
men	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
taken	O
at	O
Uxbridge	O
Townsend	O
,	O
but	O
Major	O
Belloe	O
was	O
not	O
present	O
in	O
Court	O
to	O
prosecute	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
at	O
present	O
,	O
but	O
order	O
'd	O
to	O
find	O
Bail	O
to	O
appear	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Groves	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Groves	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Scarf	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
value	O
12s	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
Knight	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
Wedding	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
fold	O
up	O
the	O
Scarf	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
the	O
Skirt	O
of	O
her	O
Wastcoat	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
20l	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
Feathers	O
,	O
value	O
20s	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
reaching	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
White	I-pers
was	O
Tried	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Beckham	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
Rob	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Besouth	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Goods	O
to	O
an	O
extraordinary	O
value	O
.	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
Long-Ford	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
at	O
Tumble-down	O
Dicks	O
at	O
Brentford	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
the	O
Fact	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
the	O
Trial	O
deni	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
having	O
no	O
Witness	O
to	O
contradict	O
what	O
was	O
alledg	O
'd	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
was	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Gold	O
Ear-Rings	O
set	O
with	O
Pearls	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
30s	O
.	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
did	O
appear	O
against	O
her	O
:	O
So	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Loe	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
,	O
two	O
young	O
Youth	O
s	O
,	O
were	O
Tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Copper	O
Pot	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4s	O
.	O
a	O
Brass	O
Kettle	O
2s	O
.	O
from	O
Francis	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
;	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
but	O
a	O
made	O
Excuse	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Jinn	I-pers
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
divers	O
Goods	O
from	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Gayler	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
;	O
She	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Katherine	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
a	O
French	O
Woman	O
,	O
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
in	O
the	O
day-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
of	O
value	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
by	O
her	O
direction	O
at	O
a	O
Brokers	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
charge	O
her	O
to	O
have	O
stolen	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Whelpley	I-pers
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
several	O
Goods	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Abratha	I-pers
on	O
the	O
14th	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
full	O
and	O
clear	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susan	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Holden	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Glass	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Rebekah	B-pers
Randale	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
Tried	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
for	O
Clipping	O
the	O
Currant	O
money	O
of	O
England	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Dunn	O
and	O
Mr.	O
St.	O
Leger	O
proved	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
upon	O
search	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
altogether	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Paper	O
of	O
Clippings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
quantity	O
of	O
Clipt	O
money	O
,	O
both	O
Half-Crowns	O
and	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
Shears	O
and	O
Files	O
and	O
melting	O
Pots	O
,	O
and	O
Scissers	O
and	O
Scales	O
;	O
Mary	O
Williams	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
kind	O
to	O
her	O
Mother	O
Susan	O
Powell	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
discover	O
all	O
;	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
produced	O
the	O
Clipt	O
money	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Bosom	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	O
Williams	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Clippings	O
were	O
hid	O
under	O
a	O
Washing	O
Tub	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Old	O
Woman	O
Susan	O
Powell	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
Escape	O
out	O
at	O
a	O
Window	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
all	O
found	O
in	O
one	O
Room	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
Randale	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
came	O
there	O
for	O
a	O
Hood	O
as	O
she	O
alledged	O
:	O
So	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
High	O
Treason	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Sentence	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
11	O
.	O
Edward	O
Tobin	O
Nicholas	O
Northorp	O
Mustapha	O
Pochowachett	O
Drury	O
Wake	O
William	O
York	O
Thomas	O
Edge	O
Thomas	O
Maye	O
Susan	O
Powell	O
Mary	O
Williams	O
Thomas	O
Newin	O
Richard	O
Tovey	O
,	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
16	O
.	O
Phillip	O
Martin	O
Lusia	O
Walker	O
Mary	O
Davis	O
Elizabeth	O
Stafford	O
Sarah	O
Jones	O
John	O
Cusack	O
Thomas	O
White	O
Andrew	O
Whelpley	O
Adam	O
Lynn	O
Elinor	O
Jackson	O
Sarah	O
Anderson	O
Mary	O
Bambrigg	O
Sarah	O
Wilmore	O
Ann	O
Dakers	O
Rebekah	O
Taylor	O
Isaac	O
Skellome	O
Who	O
was	O
Convicted	O
last	O
Sessions	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
4	O
.	O
Ann	O
Hulk	O
Elizabeth	O
Groves	O
John	O
Loe	O
John	O
Barnes	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
Dyanah	O
Lawrence	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Adams	O
was	O
Fined	O
6s	O
.	O
8	O
d.	O
being	O
poor	O
;	O
and	O
ordered	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
Three	O
times	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Blundervill	O
was	O
Fined	O
40l	O
.	O
and	O
ordered	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
Three	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
find	O
good	O
Sureties	O
.	O
Richard	O
Cokely	O
was	O
Fined	O
100l	O
.	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
3	O
Times	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
.	O
Susan	O
Powell	O
and	O
Mary	O
Williams	O
were	O
found	O
with	O
Quick	O
Child	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
Whereas	O
it	O
was	O
design	O
'd	O
at	O
first	O
to	O
print	O
the	O
Englaish	O
Translation	O
of	O
Malbranche	O
's	O
Search	O
after	O
Truth	O
,	O
in	O
Folio	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
to	O
give	O
Notice	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Undertakers	O
,	O
John	O
Dunton	O
,	O
and	O
Samuel	O
Manslip	O
,	O
(	O
what	O
they	O
may	O
sooner	O
gratify	O
the	O
Expectation	O
of	O
the	O
Learned	O
World	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
so	O
useful	O
a	O
Work	O
may	O
be	O
every	O
Bodies	O
Money	O
)	O
design	O
to	O
print	O
it	O
in	O
Two	O
Volumes	O
,	O
(	O
as	O
't	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
Original	O
)	O
upon	O
a	O
very	O
Fair	O
Letters	O
,	O
and	O
Extraordinary	O
Paper	O
,	O
without	O
Subscriptions	O
.	O
Done	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
French	O
from	O
the	O
Paris	O
4th	O
Edition	O
,	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Sault	O
,	O
Math	O
.	O
Of	O
the	O
whose	O
Abilities	O
in	O
performing	O
so	O
Nice	O
and	O
Learned	O
a	O
Work	O
,	O
John	O
Norris	O
,	O
M.A	O
.	O
is	O
very	O
well	O
satisfi	O
'd	O
,	O
after	O
some	O
Converse	O
with	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Sault	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
has	O
express	O
'd	O
himself	O
by	O
Letter	O
to	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Acquaintance	O
in	O
Town	O
;	O
and	O
therefore	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
for	O
some	O
other	O
Reasons	O
,	O
has	O
desired	O
to	O
be	O
excus	O
'd	O
from	O
his	O
Promise	O
of	O
the	O
Revisal	O
.	O
The	O
First	O
Volume	O
will	O
be	O
publisht	O
in	O
Two	O
months	O
,	O
being	O
now	O
in	O
the	O
Press	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Second	O
soon	O
after	O
:	O
The	O
Translator	O
having	O
began	O
the	O
Work	O
above	O
Twelve	O
Months	O
since	O
.	O
A	O
discourse	O
of	O
Christian	O
Religion	O
in	O
Sundry	O
Points	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Christ	O
the	O
Hope	O
of	O
Glory	O
,	O
the	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
God	O
in	O
Christ	O
,	O
Christ	O
the	O
saviour	O
of	O
the	O
People	O
,	O
the	O
only	O
Mediator	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Preached	O
at	O
the	O
Merchants	O
Lecture	O
.	O
By	O
Tho	O
.	O
Cole	O
,	O
8	O
vo	O
.	O
A	O
Succinct	O
and	O
Seasonable	O
Discourse	O
of	O
the	O
Occasions	O
,	O
causes	O
,	O
Natures	O
,	O
Rise	O
,	O
Growth	O
and	O
Remedies	O
if	O
Mental	O
Errors	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
(	O
1	O
.	O
)	O
An	O
Answer	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Cary	O
against	O
Instant	O
Baptism	O
.	O
(	O
2	O
.	O
)	O
An	O
Answer	O
to	O
some	O
Antinomian	O
Errors	O
.	O
(	O
3	O
.	O
)	O
Sermon	O
about	O
Union	O
.	O
By	O
John	O
Flavel	O
.	O
Mr.	O
John	O
Flavel'sv	O
Remains	O
,	O
being	O
two	O
Sermons	O
:	O
The	O
one	O
preached	O
at	O
Dartmouth	O
in	O
Devon	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
Coronation	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
.	O
The	O
latter	O
intended	O
to	O
be	O
preached	O
at	O
a	O
Meeting	O
of	O
the	O
United	O
Ministers	O
of	O
several	O
Counties	O
.	O
With	O
some	O
Account	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
.	O
The	O
Reasonableness	O
of	O
Personal	O
Reformation	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Necessity	O
of	O
Conversion	O
.	O
The	O
true	O
methods	O
of	O
making	O
all	O
men	O
happy	O
in	O
this	O
world	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
to	O
come	O
.	O
By	O
J.	O
Flavell	O
.	O
Instructions	O
about	O
Heart-work	O
,	O
what	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
on	O
God	O
's	O
part	O
and	O
ours	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Cure	O
and	O
keeping	O
of	O
the	O
Heart	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
by	O
that	O
Eminent	O
Gospel-Minister	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Richard	O
Alleyn	O
.	O
With	O
a	O
Preface	O
by	O
Dr.	O
Annesley	O
.	O
The	O
2d	O
.	O
Edition	O
.	O
These	O
Printed	O
for	O
Thomas	O
Cockerill	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Legs	O
in	O
the	O
Poultrey	O
.	O
About	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
of	O
may	O
will	O
be	O
publisht	O
the	O
Third	O
and	O
last	O
Volume	O
of	O
the	O
Works	O
of	O
Francis	O
Rabelais	O
M.	O
D.	O
containing	O
the	O
Fourth	O
and	O
Fifth	O
Books	O
of	O
the	O
Heroick	O
Deeds	O
and	O
sayings	O
of	O
Gargantua	O
and	O
Pantagruel	O
;	O
which	O
two	O
Books	O
are	O
the	O
whole	O
Voyage	O
to	O
the	O
Holy-Bottle	O
.	O
The	O
Pantagruelian	O
Prognostication	O
.	O
Enciclopidee	O
Questions	O
.	O
Three	O
Epistles	O
in	O
Verse	O
.	O
Historical	O
Letters	O
written	O
in	O
by	O
the	O
Doctor	O
during	O
his	O
stay	O
in	O
Italy	O
.	O
This	O
Volume	O
,	O
which	O
compleats	O
all	O
his	O
Works	O
,	O
was	O
never	O
before	O
published	O
in	O
English	O
;	O
and	O
is	O
also	O
to	O
contain	O
a	O
Key	O
to	O
the	O
Voyage	O
,	O
and	O
large	O
Explanations	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
difficult	O
Passages	O
,	O
never	O
before	O
published	O
in	O
any	O
Language	O
.	O
Bibliotheca	O
Politica	O
,	O
Compleat	O
in	O
Thirteen	O
Dialogues	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
a	O
large	O
Table	O
to	O
the	O
whole	O
Work	O
Both	O
printed	O
for	O
Rich	O
.	O
Baldwin	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
to	O
give	O
notice	O
to	O
all	O
Persons	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
the	O
Publick	O
,	O
That	O
W.	O
Elmy	O
,	O
Prosfessor	O
of	O
Physick	O
,	O
and	O
Operator	O
,	O
of	O
known	O
Integrity	O
,	O
and	O
above	O
25	O
Years	O
Practice	O
,	O
liveth	O
at	O
the	O
Blue	O
Ball	O
in	O
Whale-Bone-Court	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
lower	O
end	O
of	O
Bartholomew-Lane	O
by	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
:	O
Who	O
most	O
safely	O
and	O
expeditiously	O
cures	O
Deafness	O
,	O
and	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
Ears	O
,	O
in	O
any	O
,	O
of	O
what	O
Age	O
soever	O
,	O
(	O
if	O
Curable	O
)	O
and	O
at	O
first	O
sight	O
,	O
by	O
Inspection	O
,	O
Resolves	O
the	O
Patient	O
,	O
if	O
so	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
as	O
most	O
eminent	O
Persons	O
of	O
Quality	O
in	O
this	O
City	O
can	O
testifie	O
.	O
His	O
Pills	O
only	O
prepared	O
for	O
the	O
French	O
Disease	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Running	O
of	O
the	O
Reins	O
,	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
in	O
Boxes	O
of	O
several	O
Prices	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
Venereal	O
Arcana	O
's	O
as	O
occasion	O
requires	O
.	O
Price	O
from	O
1s	O
6d	O
.	O
to	O
3s	O
.	O
And	O
from	O
3s	O
.	O
to	O
6s	O
.	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
.	O
These	O
Pills	O
are	O
free	O
from	O
Mercury	O
:	O
They	O
are	O
proper	O
in	O
all	O
Diseases	O
,	O
where	O
Purging	O
is	O
Requisite	O
.	O
He	O
hath	O
likewise	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Gargarism	O
or	O
Mouth	O
Water	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
make	O
Black	O
or	O
Yellow	O
Teeth	O
as	O
White	O
as	O
Ivory	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
times	O
using	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
will	O
certainly	O
Cure	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
Diseases	O
incident	O
to	O
the	O
Mouth	O
,	O
Teeth	O
and	O
Gums	O
.	O
The	O
Glasses	O
are	O
of	O
several	O
Prices	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
.	O
That	O
you	O
may	O
not	O
mistake	O
,	O
my	O
House	O
is	O
at	O
the	O
Blue-Ball	O
,	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
see	O
it	O
as	O
you	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
On	O
Ludgate-Hill	O
,	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
the	O
King's-Arms	O
Tavern	O
near	O
Fleet-Bridge	O
,	O
any	O
person	O
may	O
be	O
furnished	O
with	O
a	O
Water	O
for	O
taking	O
away	O
the	O
Freckles	O
,	O
Pimples	O
,	O
Worms	O
and	O
Morphew	O
in	O
the	O
face	O
,	O
Elixir	O
Salutis	O
,	O
Balsamum	O
Vitae	O
,	O
Tinctura	O
Vitae	O
,	O
An	O
excellent	O
Water	O
and	O
Ointment	O
for	O
the	O
Eyes	O
.	O
Ointments	O
for	O
the	O
Eyes	O
.	O
Ointments	O
for	O
the	O
Rickets	O
,	O
Burns	O
,	O
Scalds	O
,	O
Wounds	O
,	O
Aches	O
,	O
Sprians	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Powders	O
,	O
Dentrifices	O
,	O
Elixirs	O
,	O
Essences	O
,	O
Oils	O
,	O
Spirits	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
For	O
the	O
easing	O
and	O
curing	O
of	O
most	O
Distempers	O
incident	O
to	O
humane	O
Bodies	O
.	O
Prepared	O
and	O
Sold	O
by	O
B	O
L	O
In	O
Grays	O
Inn-Lane	O
in	O
Plow-Yard	O
,	O
the	O
third	O
Door	O
,	O
lives	O
Doctor	O
Thomas	O
Kirleus	O
,	O
a	O
Collegiate	O
Physician	O
,	O
and	O
Sworn	O
Physician	O
in	O
Ordinary	O
to	O
King	O
Charles	O
II	O
until	O
his	O
Death	O
;	O
who	O
with	O
a	O
Drink	O
and	O
Pill	O
(	O
hindring	O
no	O
Business	O
)	O
undertakes	O
to	O
Cure	O
any	O
Ulcers	O
,	O
Sores	O
,	O
Swellings	O
in	O
the	O
Nose	O
,	O
Face	O
,	O
or	O
other	O
Parts	O
;	O
Scabs	O
,	O
Itch	O
,	O
Scurfs	O
,	O
Leprosies	O
,	O
and	O
Venereal	O
Diseases	O
,	O
expecting	O
nothing	O
until	O
the	O
Cure	O
be	O
finished	O
:	O
Of	O
the	O
last	O
he	O
hath	O
cured	O
many	O
hundred	O
in	O
this	O
City	O
,	O
many	O
of	O
them	O
after	O
Fluxing	O
,	O
which	O
carries	O
the	O
Evil	O
from	O
the	O
Lower	O
Parts	O
to	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
destroys	O
many	O
.	O
The	O
Drink	O
is	O
3s	O
.	O
the	O
Quart	O
,	O
the	O
Pill	O
1s	O
.	O
a	O
Box	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
;	O
a	O
better	O
Purger	O
than	O
which	O
was	O
never	O
given	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
cleanse	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
all	O
Impurities	O
,	O
which	O
are	O
the	O
causes	O
of	O
Dropsies	O
,	O
Gout	O
,	O
Scurvies	O
,	O
Stone	O
or	O
Gravel	O
,	O
pains	O
in	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Parts	O
.	O
Take	O
heed	O
whom	O
you	O
trust	O
in	O
Physick	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
's	O
become	O
a	O
Common	O
Cheat	O
to	O
profess	O
it	O
He	O
gives	O
his	O
Opinion	O
to	O
all	O
that	O
writes	O
or	O
comes	O
,	O
for	O
Nothing	O
He	O
hath	O
a	O
Chamber	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
at	O
the	O
first	O
House	O
in	O
Vine-street	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
or	O
his	O
Son	O
,	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
from	O
1	O
till	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
.	O
