TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
OF	O
THE	O
King	O
and	O
Queens	O
Commissions	O
ON	O
THE	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
21st	O
,	O
22d	O
,	O
and	O
23d	O
Days	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
1693/4	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
Fifth	O
Year	O
of	O
Their	O
MAJESTIES	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice	O
Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bayly	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
21st	O
,	O
22d	O
,	O
and	O
23d	O
Days	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
1693/4	O
.	O
before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Ashhurst	I-pers
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
Salathiel	B-pers
Lovell	I-pers
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
:	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
follow	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pitts	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
East	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Roove	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Strudwick	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Mardook	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Long	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Church	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Blackwell	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Stretton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Overton	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Bradbury	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Moody	I-pers
,	O
Andrew	B-pers
Cooke	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Caquick	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Brian	B-pers
Turbervill	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hollins	I-pers
.	O
James	B-pers
Nayland	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Dayllou	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
for	O
preaching	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Matthews	I-place
Friday	I-place
street	I-place
several	O
Treasonable	O
Words	O
and	O
Sentences	O
;	O
who	O
,	O
after	O
a	O
long	O
Debate	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Councel	O
,	O
was	O
at	O
last	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
being	O
ordered	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
to	O
give	O
Sureties	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
for	O
a	O
Twelvemonth	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
one	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
of	O
one	O
Guinea	O
in	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Silver	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
being	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
between	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Legs	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Salter	I-pers
,	O
Tried	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Pendulum	O
Watch	O
from	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Barton	I-pers
.	O
The	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Barton	O
coming	O
from	O
Bagshott	B-place
,	O
was	O
Set	O
upon	O
by	O
three	O
Highway-Men	O
,	O
who	O
Robbed	O
him	O
of	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Monies	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
taken	O
at	O
St.	O
Sepulchres	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
searched	O
,	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Breeches	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
three	O
Men	O
at	O
Kensington	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kerton	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Trunk	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
were	O
seven	O
Holland	O
Shifts	O
,	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
from	O
Abigall	B-pers
Hathorne	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Rabbet	O
got	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
run	O
up	O
her	O
Stairs	O
:	O
But	O
whilst	O
they	O
were	O
busy	O
about	O
seeking	O
for	O
this	O
pretended	O
Rabbet	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
bold	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
the	O
Trunk	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Page	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Hendon	B-place
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Sheep	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
tied	O
the	O
Sheep	O
,	O
and	O
covered	O
them	O
over	O
with	O
Wheat-straw	O
,	O
and	O
Beanstraw	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
fetch	O
them	O
away	O
the	O
next	O
Evening	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
.	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Moor	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Edmonton	B-place
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
20	O
Weather	O
Sheep	O
,	O
three	O
Ewe-Sheep	O
,	O
from	O
Henry	B-pers
Hawkin	I-pers
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Beale	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Billing	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
's	O
Glass	O
,	O
on	O
December	O
29	O
.	O
from	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Ashfield	I-pers
;	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
three	O
Diamond	O
Stone	O
Rings	O
,	O
four	O
Turky	O
Stone	O
Rings	O
,	O
with	O
Diamonds	O
,	O
30	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
22	O
l.	O
in	O
Monies	O
numbred	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
great	O
value	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Beale	O
alledged	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
her	O
Husband	O
;	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Carash	I-pers
,	O
a	O
French	O
man	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Anns	O
Westminster	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
murdering	O
John	B-pers
Bertillin	I-pers
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
value	O
5	O
s	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
Right	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Right	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Wound	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
struck	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Cane	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
draw	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
deceased	O
having	O
his	O
Sword	O
drawn	O
,	O
made	O
several	O
Passes	O
prisoner	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
defend	O
himself	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
as	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
fell	O
upon	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
had	O
no	O
former	O
Malice	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Daniel	B-pers
White	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Matfellon	I-place
,	I-place
alias	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Robbery	O
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
committed	O
upon	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Delaphont	I-pers
,	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Castor	O
Hat	O
a	O
Laced	O
Crevat	O
,	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
two	O
Boxes	O
of	O
Surgeons	O
Instruments	O
,	O
and	O
50	O
s.	O
in	O
Monies	O
numbred	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
could	O
not	O
positively	O
swear	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
Robbed	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Joane	B-pers
King	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Goddard	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Edd	I-pers
four	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Child	O
bed	O
Linen	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
they	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
whereupon	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Grace	B-pers
Denby	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Dane	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Nathanael	B-pers
Rosewell	I-pers
four	O
Pewter	O
Pots	O
,	O
and	O
six	O
Draper	O
Napkins	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
thirteen	O
Shillings	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Morris	O
persuaded	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Denby	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
same	O
at	O
the	O
Ditch	O
side	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
stopt	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
guilty	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Matfellon	I-place
,	I-place
alias	I-place
White	I-place
Chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
Barn	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bocock	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
one	O
Bushel	O
of	O
Wheat	O
and	O
Rye	O
,	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
Horse-	O
etters	O
,	O
two	O
Ropes	O
,	O
two	O
Hatchets	O
,	O
a	O
Bill	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
tried	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Pinnace	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
in	O
stealing	O
four	O
Fretted	O
Stuff-Curtains	O
printed	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Sinus	I-pers
;	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
J	B-pers
-	I-pers
S	I-pers
-	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Colehampton	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
forty	O
yards	O
of	O
White	O
Broad	O
Cloth	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
day	O
of	O
January	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Edwards	O
alledged	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
was	O
left	O
him	O
by	O
one	O
Henry	B-pers
Oxton	I-pers
,	O
who	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
Service	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
so	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
;	O
and	O
J	O
-	O
S	O
-	O
and	O
Richard	O
Colehampton	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Sorrell	I-pers
,	O
together	O
with	O
Mary	B-pers
Cornwall	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
nine	O
yards	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
35	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
February	O
from	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Maynard	I-pers
,	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Sorrell	O
:	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Cornwall	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Linney	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Five	O
and	O
twenty	O
yards	O
of	O
Calamanca	O
,	O
Nineteen	O
yards	O
of	O
Serge	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shag	O
Breeches	O
,	O
an	O
Ounce	O
of	O
Gold	O
Thread	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Price	I-pers
:	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Lorriman	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Paul	B-pers
Peregrine	I-pers
of	O
5	O
l	O
18	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Palmer	O
and	O
Lorriman	O
being	O
together	O
near	O
Bow-Church	B-place
,	O
they	O
jostled	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
presently	O
finding	O
his	O
Pocket	O
lighter	O
,	O
was	O
told	O
by	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
the	O
persons	O
that	O
picked	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
pursuit	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
Lorriman	O
's	O
Pocket	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
given	O
him	O
by	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
,	O
and	O
Palmer	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Gillet	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
February	O
six	O
Black	O
Castor	O
Hats	O
from	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Bostell	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
alledged	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Hats	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
man	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Percivall	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Forgery	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Bilton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
in	O
stealing	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
one	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Stays	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
of	O
value	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Simon	B-pers
Betts	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
in	O
stealing	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Finney	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Lawrence	I-place
Jury	I-place
,	O
one	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
one	O
Necklace	O
of	O
Pearl	O
,	O
one	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
,	O
two	O
Lockets	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Girdle	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Buckle	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
Lodgings	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
Box	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
advantage	O
to	O
carry	O
away	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
Simon	O
Betts	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
December	O
three	O
Silver	O
Cups	O
,	O
two	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
one	O
Flute	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Walter	B-pers
Floyd	I-pers
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
Lodgings	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
for	O
Beer	O
one	O
morning	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
occasion	O
to	O
send	O
the	O
Maid	O
up	O
stairs	O
for	O
to	O
fetch	O
some	O
Powder	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
pretended	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
taking	O
his	O
opportunity	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
the	O
Maid	O
,	O
telling	O
her	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
he	O
desiring	O
the	O
Maid	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
carried	O
away	O
the	O
things	O
aforesaid	O
;	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Davenport	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
in	O
Clipping	O
the	O
Current	O
Coyn	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
(	O
that	O
is	O
to	O
say	O
)	O
20	O
pieces	O
of	O
Silver	O
call	O
'd	O
Half-Crowns	O
,	O
10	O
other	O
pieces	O
of	O
Silver	O
call	O
'd	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
other	O
pieces	O
of	O
Silver	O
call	O
'd	O
Six-pences	O
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
having	O
Information	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
Clippers	O
at	O
Davenport	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
search	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Shears	O
,	O
Files	O
,	O
Rubbing	O
leathers	O
,	O
Clippings	O
,	O
Filings	O
and	O
clipt	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
Davenport	O
's	O
Pockets	O
clipt	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
making	O
the	O
Search	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
thrown	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Garret	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
clipt	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
seen	O
a	O
womans	O
hand	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
which	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
hang	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shears	O
on	O
a	O
nail	O
;	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
brought	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
testify	O
on	O
their	O
behalfs	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
a	O
very	O
favourable	O
account	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Ward	I-place
of	I-place
Farringdon	I-place
without	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
;	O
For	O
that	O
she	O
on	O
the	O
seven	O
and	O
twentieth	O
day	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
did	O
clip	O
20	O
Half-crowns	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
Shillings	O
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
having	O
Intelligence	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
clip	O
in	O
this	O
Kempe	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
search	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
Melting-Pot	O
,	O
Shears	O
,	O
Files	O
,	O
Clippings	O
,	O
Rubbin-leather	O
,	O
Scales	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
lump	O
of	O
melted	O
Silver	O
was	O
found	O
between	O
the	O
Bed	O
and	O
the	O
Matt	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
alledg	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
lodg	O
'd	O
long	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
suppose	O
that	O
theywere	O
left	O
there	O
by	O
some	O
other	O
persons	O
that	O
lodg	O
'd	O
there	O
before	O
she	O
came	O
;	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
justify	O
her	O
Honesty	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Achust	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
Ludgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
for	O
clipping	O
the	O
Current	O
Coyn	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
(	O
that	O
is	O
to	O
say	O
)	O
20	O
pieces	O
of	O
Silver	O
call	O
'd	O
Half-Crowns	O
,	O
20	O
other	O
pieces	O
call	O
'd	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
other	O
pieces	O
call	O
'd	O
Six-pences	O
,	O
with	O
Shears	O
and	O
other	O
Iron	O
Instruments	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
having	O
Information	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
Clippers	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
House	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
search	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
found	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shears	O
in	O
the	O
Sleeve	O
of	O
an	O
old	O
Coat	O
that	O
hung	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Closet	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
found	O
between	O
the	O
sleeve	O
and	O
the	O
lining	O
,	O
four	O
and	O
twenty	O
half	O
Crowns	O
of	O
a	O
mixed	O
sort	O
of	O
Mettal	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Coat	O
was	O
left	O
there	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
since	O
;	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
justify	O
his	O
Honesty	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
Pains-taker	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Smithfield	O
to	O
sell	O
Cattle	O
for	O
other	O
people	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Boucher	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Somerset	I-place
Queen-Hithe	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Mault	O
and	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Bagg	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Raven	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
same	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Lighter	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
into	O
Ware	O
Barge	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
Escape	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
hid	O
in	O
the	O
Sail	O
:	O
he	O
brough	O
several	O
people	O
to	O
speak	O
in	O
the	O
behalf	O
of	O
his	O
Honesty	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Deborah	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Southern	I-pers
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolph	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
without	I-place
,	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
Murther	O
,	O
for	O
whipping	O
one	O
Greatricke	B-pers
on	O
the	O
two	O
and	O
twentieth	O
of	O
January	O
with	O
a	O
Birchen	O
Rod	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
farthing	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
immoderate	O
Correction	O
the	O
said	O
Greatrick	O
instantly	O
dyed	O
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
deceased	O
was	O
very	O
sickly	O
,	O
and	O
troubled	O
with	O
an	O
Agne	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
Looseness	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
proved	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Deborah	O
King	O
was	O
asleep	O
in	O
her	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
to	O
charge	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Murther	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
thereupon	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Joan	B-pers
Shore	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Steward	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolph	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Philip	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
on	O
the	O
twentieth	O
day	O
of	O
January	O
four	O
yards	O
of	O
Bone	O
Lace	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
and	O
another	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Lace-Chamber	O
at	O
the	O
White	B-place
Hart	I-place
in	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
Street	I-place
,	O
and	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
Lace	O
,	O
she	O
privately	O
conveyed	O
the	O
Lace	O
under	O
her	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
tip	O
of	O
her	O
Stays	O
;	O
Freeman	O
missing	O
his	O
Lace	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
to	O
stop	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
searched	O
by	O
a	O
young	O
Gentlewoman	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
give	O
no	O
account	O
of	O
her	O
Life	O
and	O
Conversation	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Peter	B-pers
Testes	I-pers
on	O
the	O
five	O
and	O
twentieth	O
day	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
a	O
yard	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
of	O
Scotch	O
Cloth	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
Arraigned	O
,	O
to	O
her	O
indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Haines	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Tuller	I-pers
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
on	O
the	O
eleventh	O
day	O
of	O
February	O
at	O
Stoake	B-place
Newington	I-place
,	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
at	O
night	O
were	O
found	O
under	O
a	O
Hay-Cock	O
cover	O
'd	O
with	O
Hay	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
design	O
'd	O
to	O
break	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pickett	I-pers
,	O
but	O
being	O
taken	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
found	O
a	O
Sack	O
and	O
Cords	O
for	O
to	O
bind	O
folks	O
with	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
poor	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
pay	O
for	O
a	O
Lodging	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
by	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
Moneys	O
sufficient	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Misdemeanour	O
.	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
and	O
Leonard	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Peter	B-pers
Briggins	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Tottenham	B-place
High	I-place
Cross	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
thirteenth	O
of	O
October	O
a	O
black	O
Gelding	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Briggins	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
Gelding	O
was	O
stole	O
out	O
of	O
grounds	O
called	O
Freehold	B-place
Field	I-place
near	I-place
Green	I-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
offered	O
it	O
to	O
sale	O
:	O
William	O
Evans	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
given	O
him	O
by	O
his	O
Father	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
could	O
give	O
no	O
account	O
of	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
,	O
and	O
Leonard	O
Evans	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Hooper	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
black	O
Gelding	O
on	O
the	O
fourth	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
from	O
Sir	O
Edward	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
at	O
South	B-place
Picnam	I-place
in	I-place
Norfolk	I-place
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Gelding	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
stable	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
put	O
in	O
the	O
Gazette	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
Grays-Inn-Lane	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Custody	O
,	O
who	O
offered	O
it	O
to	O
sale	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
alledged	O
that	O
he	O
changed	O
a	O
Horse	O
with	O
a	O
man	O
called	O
Jeffery	B-pers
Land	I-pers
of	O
Luddington	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
for	O
this	O
Gelding	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tayler	I-pers
the	O
Elder	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Hays	B-place
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Trespass	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
of	O
the	O
Gate	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Vannam	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
an	O
Iron	O
Gardner	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Trespass	O
and	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Peter	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepny	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Cupboard	O
of	O
one	O
George	B-pers
Leeds	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
one	O
Linnen-bag	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d	O
:	O
and	O
11	O
l.	O
numbred	O
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Leeds	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
that	O
advantage	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
absented	O
himself	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
apprehended	O
and	O
brought	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
several	O
Goods	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
but	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Paleing	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
High	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
for	O
speaking	O
and	O
uttering	O
most	O
hainous	O
and	O
dangerous	O
Words	O
against	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
,	O
King	O
William	O
and	O
Queen	O
Mary	O
,	O
their	O
Crown	O
and	O
Dignity	O
.	O
It	O
happen	O
'd	O
that	O
one	O
Oliver	B-pers
Mace	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Watchman	O
,	O
being	O
in	O
Discourse	O
with	O
the	O
said	O
Francis	O
Paleing	O
,	O
Paleing	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
that	O
King	O
James	O
will	O
come	O
again	O
.	O
Mace	O
answered	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
not	O
.	O
And	O
Paleing	O
said	O
,	O
By	O
God	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
he	O
will	O
.	O
Then	O
Paleing	O
went	O
to	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Giveme	O
a	O
Mugg	O
of	O
Ale	O
,	O
to	O
Drink	O
to	O
William	O
and	O
Mary	O
,	O
George	O
and	O
Ann	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Four	O
such	O
Children	O
the	O
Devil	O
never	O
had	O
.	O
The	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
moved	O
the	O
Court	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
most	O
audacious	O
Fellow	O
,	O
and	O
behaving	O
himself	O
not	O
seemly	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
took	O
it	O
into	O
Consideration	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
High	O
Misdemeanour	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Lancelot	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
9	O
Silver	O
Plates	O
from	O
his	O
Grace	O
,	O
Maynard	B-pers
,	I-pers
Duke	I-pers
of	I-pers
Scomberg	I-pers
and	I-pers
Leinster	I-pers
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
Lee	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
But	O
James	O
made	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
Plates	O
;	O
the	O
Plates	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Top	O
of	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
a	O
Gutter	O
in	O
White-Fryers	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
home	O
to	O
charge	O
James	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
R	B-pers
-	I-pers
C	I-pers
-	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
Felony	O
,	O
for	O
Marrying	O
of	O
Two	O
Wives	O
,	O
(	O
that	O
is	O
to	O
say	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Greaves	I-pers
his	O
first	O
Wife	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	O
James	O
Dukes	O
Place	O
;	O
and	O
Judith	B-pers
Abbot	I-pers
his	O
second	O
Wife	O
,	O
at	O
Knights-Bridge	B-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Liberty	I-place
of	I-place
Westminster	I-place
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
within	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
most	O
Gracious	O
Pardon	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Skidmore	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
for	O
Erecting	O
a	O
private	O
Printing-Press	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
printed	O
a	O
Seditious	O
Libel	O
,	O
called	O
,	O
A	O
new	O
Scotch-Whim	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
,	O
in	O
stealing	O
a	O
Saddle	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Red-Bays	O
Saddle-Cloath	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Stable	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Red-Lyon	B-place
in	I-place
Grays-Inn-Lane	I-place
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
denied	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
imployed	O
by	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Three	O
Cups	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
but	O
a	O
very	O
slender	O
Account	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
and	O
Conversation	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
and	O
40	O
yards	O
of	O
Norwich	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Woosted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Yarn	O
Stockings	O
,	O
36	O
yards	O
of	O
Taffety	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Scarlet	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
in	O
searching	O
for	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Norwich	O
Stuff	O
on	O
her	O
Back	O
;	O
and	O
whilst	O
the	O
Constable	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
busy	O
a	O
searching	O
,	O
she	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
slipt	O
it	O
of	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
He	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Liberty	I-place
of	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
day	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
Three	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Kid-Leather	O
Gloves	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Collis	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Collis	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
several	O
Nights	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
between	O
Eight	O
and	O
Nine	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
drew	O
back	O
the	O
Bolt	O
of	O
the	O
Hatch	O
that	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
them	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Hewit	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Varner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepny	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Ann	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
5	O
Linnen	O
Smocks	O
,	O
5	O
Laced	O
Hankerchifs	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Value	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susan	B-pers
Wrothwell	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Rothwell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
Thompson	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
set	O
upon	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
there	O
came	O
Riding	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
ten	O
or	O
twelve	O
Horsemen	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
her	O
ways	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
missing	O
:	O
But	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
charge	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
fully	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Riggs	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Ricks	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Smeaton	I-pers
at	O
Seven	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
31st	O
day	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
one	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
,	O
one	O
Cloath	O
Gown	O
,	O
Two	O
Holland	O
Smocks	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
with	O
an	O
Iron-Betty	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
Pass	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
very	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
behalf	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Breed	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Buckingham	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Field	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Stable	O
of	O
Sir	O
George	B-pers
Rivers	I-pers
,	O
and	O
removing	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Trunk	O
,	O
6	O
Yards	O
of	O
Woollen	O
Cloath	O
,	O
4	O
Hempen	O
Shirts	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
32	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
lockt	O
the	O
Stable-door	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
a	O
Chissel	O
into	O
a	O
Seller-window	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
behalf	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Osborn	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Osborn	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Osborn	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
were	O
tried	O
for	O
taking	O
from	O
Job	B-pers
Higginbottom	I-pers
a	O
Spit	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Andirons	O
,	O
a	O
Turkey-work	O
Carpet	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
value	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
being	O
called	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
Bell-man	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
their	O
Cellar	O
Door	O
open	O
about	O
four	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
found	O
two	O
Pewter	O
Porringers	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
pieces	O
of	O
Beef	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
very	O
poor	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Meat	O
was	O
given	O
them	O
by	O
a	O
man	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Cellar	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
having	O
compassion	O
on	O
them	O
,	O
found	O
Margaret	O
Osborn	O
,	O
and	O
Richard	O
Osborn	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	O
Palmer	O
,	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
Elizabeth	O
Osborn	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomasin	B-pers
Deakin	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Meakin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Marmaduke	B-pers
Grimston	I-pers
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Doe-skin	O
Breeches	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Stays	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Meakin	O
:	O
They	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
T	B-pers
-	I-pers
G	I-pers
-	I-pers
alias	I-pers
G	I-pers
-	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
four	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
value	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
sold	O
to	O
one	O
Meadow	O
of	O
Redriff	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Carman	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Feather-bolster	O
,	O
a	O
Rug	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Grates	O
,	O
a	O
Bible	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
;	O
these	O
Goods	O
were	O
sold	O
to	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Mathew	O
likewise	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Second	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Simon	B-pers
Betts	I-pers
was	O
also	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
Indicted	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Richard	B-pers
Betts	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mitchell	I-pers
,	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
one	O
Silver	O
Porringer	O
,	O
one	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
eleven	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Bristol	O
Stone	O
,	O
and	O
100	O
l.	O
in	O
monies	O
numbred	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
monies	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
Maid	O
,	O
If	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Harrison	O
lived	O
not	O
there	O
?	O
The	O
Maid	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
Yes	O
:	O
They	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
bound	O
the	O
Maid	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Winstead	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Holland	O
Shifts	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
She	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
James	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Hempen	O
Sheet	O
,	O
one	O
Holland	O
Pillowber	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Hempen	O
Pillowber	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
.	O
She	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Person	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Seat	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Callash	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
yards	O
of	O
Flowered	O
Velvet	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
Firkin	O
in	O
the	O
Closet	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susanna	B-pers
Ley	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
33	O
s.	O
in	O
monies	O
numbred	O
,	O
from	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
positive	O
of	O
her	O
taking	O
the	O
monies	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
for	O
putting	O
Dorcas	O
,	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
William	O
Townsend	O
in	O
bodily	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
rob	O
the	O
said	O
William	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Court	O
lookt	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
malicious	O
Indictment	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Free	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Carkass	O
of	O
Mutton	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Maynard	I-pers
,	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Frances	B-pers
Wroth	I-pers
,	O
Margery	B-pers
Townley	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hilliard	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Beale	I-pers
,	O
together	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Townley	I-pers
sick	O
in	O
Prison	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
in	O
clipping	O
the	O
Current	O
Coyn	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
(	O
that	O
is	O
to	O
say	O
)	O
20	O
Half	O
Crowns	O
,	O
30	O
other	O
pieces	O
called	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
40	O
other	O
pieces	O
called	O
Six-pences	O
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Pump-House	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
adjoyning	O
to	O
the	O
Pump-House	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
the	O
Keys	O
of	O
the	O
Pump-House	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
body	O
within	O
;	O
but	O
going	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
,	O
he	O
chanced	O
to	O
push	O
with	O
his	O
stick	O
against	O
a	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
discover	O
'd	O
Wroth	O
and	O
Townley	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
open	O
the	O
doors	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shears	O
in	O
the	O
floor	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
paper	O
of	O
Clippings	O
and	O
other	O
Instruments	O
:	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
Frances	O
Wroth	O
and	O
Margery	O
Townley	O
Guilty	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	O
Hilliard	O
and	O
Mary	O
Beale	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Wroth	O
:	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Townley	O
:	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
and	O
Jasper	B-pers
Marrey	I-pers
a	O
French	O
man	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Holt	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
6	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
of	O
value	O
;	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
about	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
bound	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
in	O
his	O
Bed	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Porteine	I-pers
at	O
Westminster	B-place
,	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Porteine	O
having	O
notice	O
given	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Waterman	O
of	O
their	O
coming	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
prevented	O
of	O
their	O
design	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
Sessions	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgement	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
16	O
.	O
John	O
Salter	O
Richard	O
Loriman	O
Robert	O
Lewis	O
Jasper	O
Murrey	O
William	O
Evans	O
Henry	O
Hooper	O
Samuel	O
Smith	O
T	O
-	O
G	O
-	O
alias	O
G	O
John	O
Edwards	O
John	O
Riggs	O
,	O
al	O
.	O
Ricks	O
Simon	O
Betts	O
Richard	O
Betts	O
Thomas	O
Mitchell	O
Thomas	O
Breed	O
To	O
be	O
Burnt	O
,	O
Frances	O
Wroth	O
Margery	O
Townley	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
2	O
l.	O
Mary	O
Cornwall	O
Mary	O
Finnace	O
Joan	O
Shore	O
John	O
Moore	O
John	O
Carrash	O
Thomas	O
Limney	O
Peter	O
Jackson	O
Richard	O
Ley	O
Henry	O
Hawkins	O
Mary	O
Warkins	O
Sarah	O
Childe	O
Elizabeth	O
Jones	O
Ann	O
Belton	O
Mary	O
Peale	O
,	O
al	O
Lidel	O
Mary	O
Hewitt	O
,	O
al	O
.	O
Varnant	O
.	O
Thomasin	O
Deakin	O
Mary	O
Meakin	O
Sarah	O
Shepley	O
Mary	O
Chapman	O
Martha	O
Free	O
Mary	O
Person	O
Ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Whipt	O
7	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Morris	O
Grace	O
'	O
Denby	O
Jane	O
Turner	O
Margaret	O
Osborne	O
Richard	O
Osborne	O
Mary	O
Palmer	O
Jane	O
Sorrell	O
Edward	O
Haynes	O
,	O
Benjamin	O
Watkins	O
,	O
and	O
Henry	O
Tuller	O
,	O
ordered	O
into	O
Then	O
Majesties	O
Service	O
.	O
Jacob	O
Percivall	O
Fined	O
20	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
at	O
Charing-Cross	O
,	O
Westminster-Hall	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Maypols	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
Frances	O
Faling	O
Fined	O
100	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
with	O
Percivall	O
.	O
Conyers	O
to	O
remain	O
in	O
Prison	O
for	O
a	O
Twelvemonth	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Statute	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Taylor	O
Fined	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
8	O
d.	O
Margery	O
Townley	O
pleaded	O
her	O
Belly	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
Child	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
A	O
Discourse	O
of	O
Regeneration	O
,	O
Faith	O
,	O
and	O
Repentance	O
,	O
Preached	O
at	O
the	O
Merchants	O
Lecture	O
in	O
Broad	O
street	O
.	O
By	O
The	O
Cale	O
.	O
Minister	O
of	O
the	O
Gospel	O
.	O
A	O
Discourse	O
of	O
the	O
Christian	O
Religion	O
in	O
sundry	O
Points	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Christ	O
the	O
Hope	O
of	O
Glory	O
,	O
the	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
God	O
in	O
Christ	O
,	O
Christ	O
the	O
only	O
Savlour	O
of	O
his	O
People	O
from	O
Sin	O
,	O
Christ	O
the	O
only	O
Mediator	O
,	O
the	O
Foundation	O
of	O
our	O
Adoption	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Necessity	O
of	O
preaching	O
Christ	O
Preached	O
at	O
the	O
Merchants	O
Lecture	O
.	O
By	O
The	O
Cote	O
,	O
8	O
to	O
,	O
The	O
Incomprehensibleness	O
of	O
Imputed	O
Righteousness	O
for	O
Justification	O
by	O
Humane	O
Reason	O
,	O
till	O
inlightned	O
by	O
the	O
Spirit	O
of	O
God	O
,	O
in	O
two	O
Sermons	O
,	O
preached	O
at	O
the	O
Merchants	O
Lecture	O
in	O
Broad-street	O
.	O
By	O
Tho	O
.	O
Cole	O
A	O
Succinct	O
and	O
Seasonable	O
Discourse	O
of	O
the	O
Occasions	O
,	O
Causes	O
,	O
Natures	O
,	O
Rise	O
,	O
Growth	O
and	O
Remedies	O
of	O
Mental	O
Errors	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
(	O
1	O
.	O
)	O
An	O
Answer	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Cary	O
against	O
Insant	O
Baptism	O
.	O
(	O
2	O
.	O
)	O
An	O
Answer	O
to	O
some	O
Antinormian	O
Errors	O
.	O
(	O
3	O
.	O
)	O
A	O
Sermon	O
about	O
Union	O
.	O
By	O
John	O
Flavel	O
.	O
Mr.	O
John	O
Flavel	O
's	O
Remains	O
,	O
being	O
two	O
Sermons	O
:	O
The	O
one	O
preached	O
at	O
Dartmouth	O
in	O
Devon	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
Coronation	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
.	O
The	O
latter	O
intended	O
to	O
be	O
preached	O
at	O
a	O
Meeting	O
of	O
the	O
United	O
Ministers	O
of	O
several	O
Counties	O
.	O
With	O
some	O
Account	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
.	O
An	O
Exposition	O
of	O
the	O
Assemblies	O
Shorter	O
Catechism	O
,	O
with	O
Practical	O
Inferences	O
from	O
each	O
Question	O
.	O
By	O
John	O
Flavel	O
,	O
late	O
Minister	O
of	O
the	O
Gospel	O
at	O
Dartmouth	O
in	O
Devon	O
.	O
A	O
Discourse	O
of	O
the	O
Reasonableness	O
of	O
Personal	O
Reformation	O
,	O
and	O
Necessity	O
of	O
Conversion	O
,	O
the	O
true	O
method	O
of	O
making	O
all	O
men	O
happy	O
in	O
this	O
World	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
to	O
come	O
:	O
Seasonably	O
discoursed	O
,	O
and	O
earnestly	O
pressed	O
on	O
this	O
liceutious	O
Age	O
.	O
By	O
John	O
Flavel	O
,	O
a	O
sincere	O
Lover	O
of	O
his	O
Native	O
Country	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Souls	O
of	O
men	O
.	O
Love	O
to	O
Christ	O
,	O
necessary	O
for	O
all	O
to	O
escape	O
the	O
Curse	O
at	O
his	O
coming	O
.	O
By	O
The	O
Doolittle	O
M.	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
Mourners	O
Directory	O
,	O
guiding	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
middle	O
way	O
betwixt	O
the	O
two	O
Extremes	O
,	O
Defect	O
and	O
Excess	O
of	O
Sorrow	O
for	O
his	O
Dead	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
The	O
Mourners	O
Soliloquy	O
.	O
By	O
Thomas	O
Doolittle	O
M.	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
Righteous	O
Man	O
's	O
Hope	O
at	O
Death	O
considered	O
and	O
improved	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Comfort	O
of	O
dying	O
Christians	O
,	O
and	O
Support	O
of	O
reviving	O
Relations	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
Death	O
bed	O
Reflections	O
proper	O
for	O
a	O
Righreous	O
Man	O
in	O
his	O
last	O
Sickness	O
.	O
By	O
Sam	O
.	O
Doolittle	O
A	O
Discourse	O
of	O
secret	O
Prayer	O
,	O
first	O
preached	O
and	O
now	O
published	O
at	O
the	O
Request	O
of	O
those	O
that	O
heard	O
it	O
.	O
By	O
Samuel	O
Slater	O
Minister	O
of	O
the	O
Gospel	O
.	O
The	O
Future	O
State	O
:	O
Or	O
a	O
Discourse	O
attempting	O
some	O
Display	O
of	O
the	O
Soul	O
's	O
Happiness	O
,	O
in	O
regard	O
to	O
that	O
eternally	O
progressive	O
Knowledge	O
,	O
or	O
eternal	O
increase	O
of	O
Knowledge	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Cousequences	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
among	O
the	O
blessed	O
in	O
Heaven	O
.	O
By	O
a	O
Country	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
a	O
Worshipper	O
of	O
God	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
of	O
England	O
.	O
Instructions	O
about	O
Heart	O
Work	O
,	O
what	O
it	O
to	O
besides	O
on	O
God	O
's	O
part	O
and	O
ours	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Cure	O
and	O
keeping	O
of	O
the	O
Heart	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
By	O
that	O
Eminent	O
Gospel	O
Minister	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Richard	O
Alleyn	O
.	O
With	O
a	O
Preface	O
by	O
Dr	O
Annestey	O
.	O
The	O
2d	O
Edition	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
of	O
Things	O
not	O
seen	O
:	O
Or	O
divers	O
Spiritual	O
and	O
Philosophical	O
Discourses	O
,	O
concerning	O
the	O
state	O
of	O
Holy	O
Men	O
after	O
Death	O
:	O
By	O
that	O
eminemly	O
learned	O
Diving	O
horses	O
bought	O
dust	O
.	O
Translated	O
Four	O
of	O
the	O
French	O
,	O
Tongue	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
Minister	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
of	O
England	O
.	O
A	O
Discourse	O
of	O
Schism	O
:	O
By	O
Edward	O
Pollhill	O
Esq	O
;	O
A	O
short	O
Introduction	O
into	O
Orthography	O
;	O
or	O
the	O
method	O
of	O
true	O
Spelling	O
,	O
published	O
for	O
the	O
Common	O
Good	O
,	O
but	O
especially	O
for	O
the	O
Use	O
of	O
a	O
private	O
Grammar	O
and	O
Writing	O
School	O
in	O
Whitecross-street	O
:	O
By	O
Richard	O
Morther	O
Schoolmaster	O
.	O
Sermens	O
on	O
several	O
Occasions	O
;	O
By	O
John	O
Canant	O
D.	O
D.	O
gvo	O
.	O
The	O
Almost	O
Christian	O
discovered	O
,	O
in	O
some	O
Sermons	O
on	O
Acts	O
26	O
.	O
28	O
.	O
By	O
Ezekrel	O
Hopkins	O
Lord	O
Bishop	O
of	O
Londondarry	O
,	O
12	O
There	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
the	O
Press	O
,	O
and	O
will	O
be	O
suddenly	O
,	O
published	O
a	O
Book	O
Intituled	O
,	O
A	O
Remedy	O
against	O
Trouble	O
:	O
In	O
a	O
Discourse	O
on	O
John	O
4	O
Wherein	O
something	O
to	O
also	O
briefly	O
attempted	O
for	O
clearing	O
the	O
N	O
of	O
Fifth	O
,	O
of	O
Jusitification	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Covenant	O
of	O
Grace	O
,	O
Assurance	O
;	O
the	O
Witness	O
,	O
Seal	O
and	O
Earnest	O
of	O
the	O
Spirit	O
:	O
By	O
H.	O
Lubin	O
There	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
the	O
Press	O
,	O
and	O
will	O
be	O
suddenly	O
published	O
,	O
a	O
Book	O
Intituled	O
Eutropii	O
Breviarium	O
Histot	O
.	O
Romance	O
ab	O
urbe	O
condita	O
ad	O
Annum	O
ejusdem	O
urbis	O
M	O
C	O
XIX	O
ex	O
recensione	O
&	O
cum	O
Notulis	O
T.	O
Fabri	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
These	O
Printed	O
for	O
Thomas	O
Cockerill	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Legs	O
in	O
the	O
Poultrey	O
.	O
RAblau	O
's	O
Works	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
large	O
Key	O
,	O
explaining	O
the	O
most	O
difficult	O
Passages	O
Bibltotheca	O
Politica	O
,	O
Compleat	O
in	O
Thirteen	O
Dialogues	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
a	O
large	O
Table	O
to	O
the	O
whole	O
Work	O
.	O
Barault	O
's	O
French	O
Grammar	O
A	O
Collection	O
of	O
several	O
Speeches	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Henry	O
late	O
Earl	O
of	O
Warrington	O
The	O
Antiquity	O
and	O
Justice	O
of	O
an	O
Oath	O
of	O
Abjuration	O
Bishop	O
Wilkin	O
's	O
Mathematical	O
Works	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
Secret	O
and	O
swift	O
Messengers	O
2	O
Mathematical	O
Magick	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
World	O
in	O
the	O
Moon	O
Mr	O
Rymer	O
of	O
Tragedy	O
,	O
in	O
Two	O
Books	O
.	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Journal	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Year	O
1692	O
,	O
and	O
1693	O
.	O
An	O
Answer	O
to	O
the	O
Late	O
King	O
James	O
's	O
last	O
Declaration	O
,	O
dated	O
at	O
St.	O
Germains	O
,	O
April	O
17	O
S	O
N	O
1693	O
An	O
Essay	O
concerning	O
Obedience	O
to	O
the	O
Supreme	O
Powers	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Duty	O
of	O
Subjects	O
in	O
all	O
Revolutions	O
.	O
With	O
some	O
Considerations	O
touching	O
the	O
present	O
Juncture	O
of	O
Affairs	O
.	O
An	O
Essay	O
concerning	O
the	O
Laws	O
of	O
Nations	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Rights	O
of	O
Soveraigns	O
With	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
what	O
was	O
said	O
at	O
the	O
Council-Board	O
by	O
the	O
Civilians	O
upon	O
the	O
Question	O
,	O
Whether	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
Subjects	O
taken	O
at	O
Sea	O
acting	O
by	O
the	O
late	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
,	O
might	O
not	O
be	O
looked	O
on	O
as	O
Pirates	O
?	O
With	O
Reflections	O
upon	O
the	O
Arguments	O
of	O
Sir	O
T	O
P	O
and	O
Dr	O
Ol	O
By	O
Mat	O
Trudull	O
,	O
Doctor	O
of	O
Laws	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
R.	O
Baldwin	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
to	O
give	O
notice	O
to	O
all	O
Persons	O
for	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
the	O
Publick	O
,	O
That	O
W.	O
Elmy	O
,	O
Professor	O
of	O
Physick	O
,	O
and	O
Operator	O
,	O
of	O
known	O
Integrity	O
,	O
and	O
above	O
26	O
Years	O
Practice	O
,	O
truth	O
at	O
the	O
Blue-Hall	O
in	O
Whale-Bone-Court	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
lower	O
end	O
of	O
Bartholemew-lane	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
:	O
Win	O
wast	O
suspected	O
expoditiously	O
Deafness	O
,	O
and	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
Ears	O
,	O
in	O
any	O
,	O
of	O
what	O
Age	O
they	O
a	O
(	O
if	O
Curable	O
)	O
and	O
at	O
first	O
sight	O
,	O
by	O
Inspection	O
,	O
resolves	O
the	O
Pations	O
,	O
if	O
so	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
as	O
most	O
reminent	O
Persons	O
of	O
Quality	O
in	O
this	O
City	O
can	O
testifie	O
.	O
His	O
Pills	O
only	O
prepared	O
for	O
the	O
French	O
Disease	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Running	O
of	O
the	O
Reins	O
,	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
in	O
Boxes	O
of	O
several	O
Pri	O
or	O
a	O
with	O
other	O
Venereal	O
Arcana	O
's	O
,	O
as	O
occasion	O
requires	O
.	O
Price	O
from	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
to	O
3	O
s.	O
And	O
from	O
3	O
s.	O
to	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
.	O
These	O
Pills	O
are	O
free	O
from	O
Mercury	O
;	O
They	O
are	O
proper	O
in	O
all	O
Diseases	O
,	O
where	O
Purging	O
is	O
Requisite	O
.	O
He	O
hath	O
likewise	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Gorgarison	O
on	O
Mauth-Water	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
make	O
Black	O
or	O
Yellow	O
Teeth	O
as	O
White	O
i	O
as	O
Ivory	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
times	O
using	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
will	O
certainly	O
cure	O
the	O
Scurary	O
,	O
s	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
Defenses	O
incident	O
to	O
the	O
Mouth	O
,	O
Teeth	O
and	O
Gums	O
.	O
The	O
Glasses	O
are	O
of	O
several	O
Prices	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
.	O
That	O
you	O
may	O
not	O
mistake	O
,	O
my	O
House	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Blue-Ball	O
,	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
see	O
it	O
as	O
you	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
In	O
Grays	O
Inn-Lane	O
in	O
Plow-Yard	O
,	O
the	O
third	O
Door	O
,	O
lives	O
Doctor	O
Thomas	O
Kirleus	O
,	O
a	O
Collegiate	O
Physician	O
,	O
and	O
Sworn	O
Physician	O
in	O
Ordinary	O
to	O
King	O
Charles	O
II	O
until	O
his	O
Death	O
;	O
who	O
with	O
a	O
Drink	O
and	O
Pill	O
(	O
hindering	O
no	O
Business	O
)	O
undertakes	O
to	O
Cure	O
any	O
Ulcers	O
,	O
Sores	O
,	O
Swellings	O
in	O
the	O
Nose	O
,	O
Face	O
,	O
or	O
other	O
Parts	O
;	O
Scabs	O
,	O
Itch	O
,	O
Scurfs	O
,	O
Leprofiet	O
,	O
and	O
Venereal	O
Diseases	O
,	O
expecting	O
nothing	O
until	O
the	O
Cure	O
be	O
finished	O
:	O
Of	O
the	O
last	O
be	O
bath	O
cared	O
many	O
hundreds	O
in	O
this	O
City	O
,	O
many	O
of	O
them	O
after	O
Fluxing	O
,	O
which	O
carries	O
the	O
Evil	O
from	O
the	O
Lower	O
Parts	O
to	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
destroys	O
many	O
.	O
The	O
Drink	O
is	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Quart	O
,	O
the	O
Pill	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
Box	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
;	O
a	O
better	O
Purger	O
theem	O
which	O
was	O
never	O
gives	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
cleanse	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
all	O
Impurities	O
,	O
which	O
are	O
the	O
Causes	O
of	O
Dropsies	O
,	O
Gout	O
,	O
Scurvies	O
,	O
Stone	O
or	O
Gravel	O
,	O
Palms	O
in	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Parts	O
.	O
Take	O
need	O
whom	O
you	O
trust	O
in	O
Physitk	O
;	O
for	O
it	O
's	O
become	O
a	O
Common	O
Cheat	O
to	O
profess	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
gives	O
his	O
Opinion	O
to	O
all	O
th7at	O
writes	O
or	O
comes	O
,	O
for	O
Nothing	O
.	O
On	O
Ludgate-Hill	O
,	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms	O
Tavern	O
,	O
near	O
Fleet-Bridge	O
,	O
any	O
person	O
may	O
be	O
furnished	O
with	O
a	O
Water	O
for	O
taking	O
away	O
the	O
Frockles	O
,	O
Pimples	O
,	O
Worms	O
and	O
Morphew	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
Elixir	O
Saluns	O
,	O
Balsamum	O
Vite	O
,	O
Tinctura	O
Vice	O
.	O
An	O
excellent	O
Water	O
and	O
Ointment	O
for	O
the	O
Eyes	O
.	O
Ointments	O
for	O
the	O
Rickets	O
,	O
Burns	O
;	O
Donalds	O
,	O
Wounds	O
Aahar	O
,	O
Sprains	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Powders	O
,	O
Dtutrifice	O
,	O
Elixira	O
,	O
Essopotes	O
,	O
Oils	O
,	O
Spitita	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
For	O
the	O
casing	O
and	O
curing	O
of	O
most	O
Distrumpers	O
incident	O
to	O
humant	O
Bodies	O
.	O
Prepared	O
and	O
Sold	O
by	O
B	O
L	O
.	O
