TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
OF	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
on	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
20th	O
,	O
21st	O
and	O
22d	O
Days	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
1694/5	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
Seventh	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTIES	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
Held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bayly	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
20th	O
,	O
21st	O
and	O
22d	O
Days	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
1694/5	O
.	O
before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
Salathiel	B-pers
Lovell	I-pers
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
follow	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lambert	I-pers
John	B-pers
Hammond	I-pers
John	B-pers
Pettit	I-pers
Paul	B-pers
Derby	I-pers
Caleb	B-pers
Hook	I-pers
Josias	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Ewers	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Thare	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Kane	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Chettingham	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Mawle	I-pers
Ebenezer	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Dynn	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Peter	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
Bryant	B-pers
Turbevill	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
Peter	B-pers
King	I-pers
George	B-pers
Polfrey	I-pers
John	B-pers
Preston	I-pers
Paul	B-pers
Winkle	I-pers
Bennet	B-pers
Giles	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
William	B-pers
Tomson	I-pers
Ambrose	B-pers
Henborrow	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
are	O
as	O
follow	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Talent	I-pers
was	O
arraigned	O
and	O
tried	O
for	O
Picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Edward	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
;	O
who	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
February	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
Temple	B-place
Bar	I-place
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
stop	O
with	O
the	O
Coaches	O
,	O
caused	O
a	O
great	O
Crowd	O
,	O
amongst	O
which	O
his	O
Pocket	O
was	O
pickt	O
of	O
6l	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
;	O
he	O
seized	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
could	O
give	O
but	O
little	O
account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
there	O
or	O
what	O
was	O
his	O
business	O
;	O
and	O
was	O
deemed	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
old	O
pick-pocket	O
,	O
yet	O
the	O
Evidence	O
did	O
not	O
touch	O
him	O
home	O
enough	O
to	O
find	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elinor	B-pers
Griffeth	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
from	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hawkes	I-pers
,	O
value	O
16s	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
Instant	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hawkes	O
's	O
Shop	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
difficult	O
to	O
be	O
pleased	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
handling	O
the	O
Rings	O
she	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
a	O
Brass	O
Ring	O
amongst	O
the	O
Gold	O
ones	O
into	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
Mrs	O
Hawkes	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
call	O
the	O
Man	O
to	O
whom	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
married	O
,	O
and	O
come	O
again	O
to	O
fetch	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
went	O
a	O
little	O
distance	O
from	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs	O
Hawkes	O
finding	O
the	O
Brass	O
Ring	O
in	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
presently	O
sent	O
her	O
Apprentice	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
who	O
with	O
some	O
kind	O
of	O
force	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
where	O
she	O
dropt	O
the	O
Ring	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
owned	O
by	O
Samuel	O
Hawkes	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
offer	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
So	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hitch	I-pers
was	O
arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Weather	O
Sheep	O
,	O
value	O
16s	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
;	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Priscilla	B-pers
Hamar	I-pers
was	O
arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
Ten	O
pair	O
of	O
mens	O
Wosted-stockings	O
,	O
value	O
3l	O
.	O
from	O
Abraham	B-pers
Wilmot	I-pers
;	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Martha	B-pers
Free	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jefforson	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Legs	O
of	O
Mutton	O
,	O
value	O
6s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
a	O
Shoulder	O
of	O
Mutton	O
18d	O
.	O
5	O
Quarters	O
of	O
Lamb	O
10s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
a	O
Lambs	O
head	O
6d	O
.	O
a	O
Hind-quarter	O
of	O
Veal	O
6s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Lauson	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Butcher	O
,	O
in	O
Newgate-market	B-place
.	O
Jefforson	O
immediately	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
Free	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
and	O
Lauson	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
meat	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shop	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
February	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
Jefferson	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Free	O
had	O
sold	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
at	O
a	O
Cooks	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
concerned	O
with	O
Jefforson	O
in	O
carrying	O
on	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
and	O
employ	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
meat	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
confest	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
when	O
first	O
taken	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Free	O
:	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Jefforson	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
about	O
10	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
day-time	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Person	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
feloniously	O
(	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
Instant	O
)	O
5	O
Dowlace	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
15s	O
.	O
5	O
Smocks	O
10s	O
.	O
3	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
15s	O
.	O
2	O
Cloath	O
Coats	O
20s	O
.	O
&	O
c.	O
Mr.	O
Matthews	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
7	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
lockt	O
his	O
Door	O
fast	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
his	O
return	O
about	O
10	O
a	O
Clock	O
he	O
found	O
his	O
Door	O
bolted	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Back-door	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
lying	O
packt	O
up	O
together	O
upon	O
the	O
Floor	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
further	O
search	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
sitting	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
hiding	O
her	O
self	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Goods	O
she	O
had	O
packt	O
up	O
,	O
were	O
but	O
of	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
5s	O
.	O
and	O
the	O
Lock	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
only	O
pusht	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
nothing	O
was	O
found	O
broke	O
;	O
yet	O
by	O
a	O
late	O
Act	O
of	O
Parliament	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
made	O
Felony	O
without	O
benefit	O
of	O
Clergy	O
,	O
to	O
break	O
open	O
and	O
rob	O
any	O
House	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
time	O
;	O
but	O
nothing	O
was	O
carried	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
but	O
5s	O
.	O
value	O
,	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
proved	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
broke	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Goods	O
were	O
carried	O
away	O
.	O
So	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
was	O
arraigned	O
and	O
tried	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
one	O
Seat	O
of	O
a	O
Coach	O
cover	O
'd	O
with	O
Flowred	O
Velvet	O
,	O
value	O
40s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
of	O
Hackney	O
.	O
The	O
Coachman	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
passing	O
from	O
London	O
to	O
Hackney	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
a	O
clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
empty	O
Coach	O
,	O
(	O
having	O
been	O
carrying	O
some	O
persons	O
to	O
London	O
that	O
dined	O
that	O
day	O
with	O
his	O
Master	O
)	O
the	O
seat	O
was	O
stolen	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
between	O
Bishopgate	O
and	O
Shoreditch	O
Church	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
conjectured	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
person	O
upon	O
the	O
Road	O
afterwards	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Woman	O
produced	O
as	O
a	O
Witness	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
bought	O
several	O
pieces	O
of	O
Velvet	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
made	O
into	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
.	O
The	O
Coachman	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Velvet	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
replied	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Velvet	O
of	O
one	O
Charles	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
a	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
-man	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	O
for	O
18d	O
.	O
which	O
was	O
reckoned	O
a	O
ping	O
pennyworth	O
.	O
He	O
could	O
give	O
no	O
good	O
account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
Velvet	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Kennedy	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
seven	O
pair	O
of	O
Womens	O
Wosted	O
Stockins	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Timothy	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
.	O
This	O
Fellow	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
more	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Lucas	O
in	O
Coleman-street	B-place
,	O
and	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Hose	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Stockins	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
they	O
dropt	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Stockins	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Lucas	O
's	O
Shop	O
by	O
a	O
stranger	O
that	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
only	O
stopt	O
and	O
seized	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
getting	O
away	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stole	O
the	O
Stockins	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
denying	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Henry	B-pers
Howes	I-pers
not	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
five	O
Childrens	O
Clouts	O
,	O
value	O
10d	O
.	O
two	O
Caps	O
20d	O
.	O
&	O
c.	O
from	O
Edward	B-pers
[	I-pers
Text	I-pers
unreadable	I-pers
in	I-pers
original	I-pers
.	I-pers
]	I-pers
.	O
The	O
evidence	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
apprehended	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
strived	O
to	O
shuffle	O
the	O
matter	O
off	O
of	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
upon	O
Howes	O
.	O
In	O
his	O
defence	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Howes	O
brought	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
leave	O
them	O
there	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
none	O
that	O
could	O
give	O
any	O
account	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Howes	O
was	O
called	O
for	O
(	O
by	O
the	O
Cryer	O
)	O
who	O
came	O
into	O
Court	O
,	O
(	O
being	O
Bailed	O
)	O
and	O
was	O
arraigned	O
upon	O
the	O
same	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
tried	O
for	O
the	O
Fact	O
:	O
But	O
none	O
could	O
swear	O
they	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
robbing	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
one	O
Samuel	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
Gent	O
of	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
and	O
17s	O
.	O
in	O
money	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Howard	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Fleetstreet	B-place
in	O
a	O
Crowd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
amongst	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
upon	O
suspition	O
,	O
having	O
lost	O
his	O
Sword	O
from	O
his	O
side	O
and	O
his	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
:	O
But	O
neither	O
Sword	O
nor	O
Money	O
could	O
be	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
found	O
guilty	O
,	O
therefore	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Goffe	I-pers
was	O
arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
30s	O
.	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
value	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
Christopher	B-pers
Pearse	I-pers
.	O
To	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Erick	B-pers
Cornelius	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
232	O
yards	O
of	O
Serge	O
of	O
a	O
great	O
value	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Bath	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
in	O
counterfeiting	O
and	O
making	O
several	O
Halfcrowns	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
of	O
false	O
and	O
counterfeit	O
Metal	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
being	O
searched	O
near	O
Hidepark	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Flasks	O
,	O
some	O
Shears	O
,	O
melting	O
Pots	O
,	O
Files	O
and	O
Crucibles	O
,	O
with	O
all	O
other	O
convenient	O
Utensils	O
,	O
fit	O
for	O
the	O
Trade	O
of	O
Coining	O
,	O
besides	O
several	O
pieces	O
of	O
false	O
money	O
;	O
all	O
which	O
were	O
brought	O
into	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
alone	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
one	O
else	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Fire-place	O
where	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Fire	O
lately	O
made	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Bricks	O
were	O
even	O
hot	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
there	O
was	O
several	O
pieces	O
of	O
false	O
Metal	O
found	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
stranger	O
who	O
was	O
wont	O
to	O
frequent	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
suspected	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
great	O
Clipper	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
an	O
Associate	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
is	O
fled	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
when	O
first	O
apprehended	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
let	O
the	O
Room	O
to	O
one	O
Baldwin	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
produce	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
denied	O
all	O
the	O
matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
did	O
at	O
the	O
Tryal	O
,	O
saying	O
Baldwin	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Room	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
there	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
;	O
neither	O
could	O
he	O
tell	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
nor	O
the	O
stranger	O
,	O
and	O
denied	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
him	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Witnesses	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
barr	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
stuft	O
the	O
Key-hole	O
with	O
old	O
Rags	O
,	O
denying	O
them	O
entrance	O
at	O
first	O
.	O
He	O
disown	O
'd	O
all	O
that	O
was	O
swore	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
Being	O
asked	O
what	O
Trade	O
he	O
was	O
?	O
Answered	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
Hair	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
a	O
Peruke	O
maker	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
called	O
divers	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
,	O
who	O
could	O
say	O
no	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
that	O
being	O
afraid	O
of	O
being	O
Arrested	O
,	O
made	O
him	O
so	O
timorous	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
not	O
so	O
clear	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
satisfy	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
guilty	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
;	O
which	O
caused	O
him	O
to	O
pray	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Bench	O
,	O
with	O
tears	O
in	O
his	O
eyes	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
ten	O
Yards	O
of	O
Norwich	O
Stuff	O
value	O
17s	O
.	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
8s	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
Instant	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
confess	O
that	O
she	O
Robbed	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
one	O
Lewis	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
's	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
gloried	O
in	O
doing	O
of	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
declared	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
that	O
the	O
Stuff	O
was	O
her	O
own	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
at	O
the	O
Taffy	O
Manapos	O
;	O
s	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
stuff	O
Gown	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
then	O
again	O
Williams	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
confess	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
L	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
steal	O
the	O
Gown	O
which	O
was	O
owned	O
to	O
be	O
Mrs.	O
William	O
's	O
Gown	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Fleming	I-pers
a	O
High	O
German	O
was	O
Tryed	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
one	O
Rants-Lowe	B-pers
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
8s	O
.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
second	O
for	O
Robbing	O
George	B-pers
Neale	I-pers
of	O
5s	O
.	O
Rants-Lowe	O
's	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
shop	O
,	O
to	O
Cheapen	O
some	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
and	O
offered	O
a	O
Guinea	O
to	O
be	O
changed	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
by	O
the	O
Art	O
of	O
Legerdemain	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
money	O
abovesaid	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
positively	O
sworn	O
and	O
was	O
the	O
more	O
readily	O
discover	O
'd	O
by	O
Neale	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
served	O
so	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
whom	O
he	O
was	O
Apprehended	O
,	O
as	O
is	O
set	O
forth	O
in	O
the	O
second	O
Indictment	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Neale	O
was	O
called	O
to	O
swear	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
George	B-pers
Barbara	I-pers
came	O
to	O
him	O
being	O
a	O
Trunk-maker	O
,	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Trunk	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
him	O
two	O
Guineas	O
,	O
desiring	O
him	O
to	O
exchange	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
Bag	O
to	O
do	O
;	O
and	O
Barbara	O
standing	O
by	O
whilst	O
he	O
lookt	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
offered	O
to	O
help	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
be	O
fingering	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
insomuch	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
keep	O
his	O
hands	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
heap	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
poured	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Bag	O
,	O
to	O
tell	O
out	O
enough	O
to	O
change	O
the	O
two	O
Guineas	O
,	O
so	O
afterwards	O
going	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
agree	O
for	O
the	O
Trunk	O
and	O
a	O
way	O
they	O
went	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
said	O
Neale	O
having	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
being	O
Cheated	O
,	O
he	O
Immediately	O
repairs	O
to	O
his	O
Bag	O
and	O
found	O
3l	O
.	O
wannting	O
except	O
3s	O
.	O
this	O
was	O
lookt	O
upon	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
strange	O
kind	O
of	O
a	O
Cheat	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
meer	O
Trick	O
that	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
practised	O
by	O
those	O
two	O
foreign	O
Sparks	O
,	O
not	O
only	O
upon	O
these	O
two	O
Persons	O
,	O
Neale	O
and	O
Rants-Lowe	O
,	O
bit	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
presumed	O
others	O
had	O
been	O
served	O
so	O
before	O
them	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
by	O
an	O
Interpreter	O
denied	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
any	O
ill	O
design	O
of	O
a	O
Cheat	O
;	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
hand	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
only	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
to	O
buy	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
really	O
a	O
stranger	O
to	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
would	O
not	O
work	O
upon	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
to	O
believe	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
upon	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Mersham	I-pers
a	O
French	O
man	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
Peter	B-pers
Debofree	I-pers
,	O
and	O
breaking	O
his	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
carrying	O
away	O
three	O
Watch	O
Cases	O
val	O
.	O
50s	O
.	O
three	O
Brass	O
Movements	O
10l	O
.	O
an	O
Alarm	O
3l	O
.	O
two	O
Pereuks	O
30s	O
.	O
a	O
Hat	O
50l	O
.	O
a	O
Brass	O
Sun-Dial	O
30s	O
.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
besides	O
3l	O
.	O
7s	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Debofree	O
swore	O
against	O
him	O
by	O
an	O
Interpreter	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
robbed	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
only	O
that	O
he	O
spread	O
Bills	O
amongst	O
the	O
Watchmakers	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Herbert	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
brought	O
some	O
Movements	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
Sell	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
suspected	O
the	O
Goods	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
honestly	O
come	O
by	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
stopt	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Movements	O
were	O
owned	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Debofree	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Davye	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
a	O
Robbery	O
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
near	O
St.	B-place
Pancras	I-place
Church	I-place
,	O
and	O
Tryed	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
first	O
was	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
,	O
who	O
swore	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Hampstead	O
about	O
9	O
or	O
10	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
Men	O
met	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Lane	O
near	O
St.	O
Pancras	O
Church	O
;	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
Field	O
,	O
and	O
bound	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
took	O
25s	O
.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Buckles	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shoes	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
Corroborated	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Stephens	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Frymley	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
swore	O
,	O
but	O
Wheeler	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
utterly	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
much	O
wrong	O
done	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
Mr.	O
Stephens	O
;	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Frymley	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Stephens	O
first	O
acquainted	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
attempted	O
to	O
break	O
open	O
a	O
House	O
once	O
together	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Stephens	O
said	O
further	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
Robbed	O
a	O
Coach	O
the	O
same	O
night	O
of	O
about	O
3l	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
having	O
considered	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Symbole	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
together	O
with	O
her	O
Two	O
Sisters	O
,	O
were	O
all	O
Indicted	O
,	O
First	O
,	O
For	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Jacob	B-pers
Reginer	I-pers
,	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
kill	O
and	O
murder	O
one	O
Isaac	B-pers
Symbole	I-pers
,	O
late	O
Husband	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Elizabeth	O
Symbole	O
.	O
Secondly	O
,	O
For	O
being	O
present	O
,	O
aiding	O
and	O
abetting	O
the	O
said	O
Jacob	O
Reginer	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
stabbing	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Symbole	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
no	O
Weapon	O
drawn	O
,	O
nor	O
having	O
first	O
struck	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Indictment	O
set	O
forth	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
the	O
said	O
Jacob	O
Reginer	O
,	O
not	O
having	O
the	O
Fear	O
of	O
God	O
before	O
their	O
Eyes	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
Instigated	O
by	O
the	O
Devil	O
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
past	O
,	O
In	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
said	O
Isaac	O
Symbole	O
they	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
Assault	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
said	O
Jacob	O
Reginer	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
Right	O
Hand	O
drawn	O
,	O
did	O
give	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Isaac	O
Symbole	O
One	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
near	O
to	O
the	O
Right	O
Pap	O
of	O
the	O
Breadth	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
Six	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
Instantly	O
died	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Councel	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
first	O
opened	O
the	O
Nature	O
of	O
both	O
the	O
Indictments	O
to	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
shewing	O
how	O
malicious	O
a	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
a	O
Barbarous	O
Murder	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
stood	O
charged	O
with	O
;	O
it	O
being	O
the	O
more	O
aggravated	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
Relation	O
and	O
Affinity	O
was	O
so	O
Conjugal	O
as	O
the	O
Wife	O
to	O
the	O
Husband	O
,	O
therefore	O
it	O
was	O
no	O
less	O
than	O
Petty-Treason	O
in	O
her	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
Felony	O
and	O
Murder	O
:	O
Therefore	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Crime	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
High	O
Nature	O
in	O
them	O
all	O
,	O
if	O
so	O
be	O
that	O
they	O
should	O
be	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
required	O
their	O
serious	O
and	O
mature	O
Consideration	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
were	O
called	O
and	O
sworn	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
was	O
one	O
Jane	O
Williams	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Symbole	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
day	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Reginer	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Symbole	O
's	O
two	O
Sisters	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Symbole	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Mrs.	O
Symbole	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
ordered	O
her	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Fire	O
in	O
the	O
Parlor	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
Cards	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Reginer	O
had	O
brought	O
some	O
Wine	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
drank	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
merry	O
.	O
Then	O
Mrs.	O
Symbole	O
sent	O
the	O
said	O
Williams	O
for	O
her	O
master	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Lamberts	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
home	O
till	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
of	O
the	O
clock	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
a	O
Supper	O
was	O
ordered	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
eat	O
together	O
,	O
seeming	O
to	O
be	O
good	O
Friends	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
Supper	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
Cards	O
again	O
,	O
playing	O
at	O
a	O
Game	O
called	O
Bone	O
Ace	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
Farthing	O
Bone	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Farthing	O
Ace	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
went	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
fell	O
asleep	O
;	O
afterwards	O
awakening	O
,	O
hearing	O
the	O
Watchman	O
knockt	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
found	O
Mr.	O
Reginer	O
standing	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
with	O
a	O
Naked	O
Sword	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
all	O
bloody	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
wiped	O
his	O
Coat	O
;	O
and	O
her	O
master	O
she	O
found	O
sunk	O
down	O
in	O
his	O
Chair	O
behind	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
with	O
one	O
Leg	O
upon	O
the	O
Chair	O
.	O
She	O
going	O
towards	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
out	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
speak	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
died	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
the	O
said	O
Reginer	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
the	O
two	O
Sisters	O
,	O
her	O
mistress	O
Symbole	O
being	O
only	O
left	O
,	O
who	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
Agony	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
run	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
one	O
Stoneman	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Springback	O
,	O
that	O
were	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
lifted	O
up	O
Mr.	O
Symbole	O
from	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
perceiving	O
his	O
Lips	O
to	O
move	O
,	O
they	O
got	O
Strong-waters	O
,	O
and	O
poured	O
into	O
his	O
mouth	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
no	O
effect	O
;	O
for	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
Stoneman	O
and	O
Springback	O
deposed	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
A	O
Watchman	O
being	O
sworn	O
,	O
declared	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
but	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
the	O
murder	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
knockt	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
some	O
Woman	O
answer	O
'd	O
him	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
All	O
was	O
well	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
other	O
confirming	O
Proofs	O
how	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
what	O
manner	O
Mr.	O
Symbole	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Symbole	O
was	O
much	O
troubled	O
,	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
She	O
was	O
undone	O
.	O
Being	O
asked	O
,	O
Who	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
murder	O
'd	O
her	O
Husband	O
?	O
She	O
would	O
give	O
no	O
account	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
only	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Lawyer	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Temple	O
;	O
at	O
length	O
when	O
more	O
people	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
them	O
his	O
Name	O
was	O
Reginer	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
further	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Symbole	O
nor	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
did	O
not	O
offer	O
to	O
stop	O
the	O
said	O
Reginer	O
,	O
but	O
suffer	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Surgeon	O
gave	O
in	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
upon	O
search	O
of	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
no	O
less	O
than	O
18	O
Wounds	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
five	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
mortal	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
made	O
with	O
one	O
and	O
the	O
same	O
Sword	O
as	O
he	O
believed	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Bruise	O
under	O
his	O
ear	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
perhaps	O
done	O
by	O
his	O
Fall	O
off	O
his	O
Chair	O
,	O
for	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Searchers	O
(	O
an	O
old	O
Woman	O
)	O
swore	O
that	O
she	O
thought	O
that	O
was	O
done	O
by	O
a	O
fall	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
blacker	O
,	O
except	O
he	O
had	O
died	O
at	O
the	O
Tree	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
knew	O
it	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
by	O
experience	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
an	O
old	O
Stripper	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
the	O
sum	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Then	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
to	O
make	O
their	O
Defence	O
;	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Symbole	O
first	O
began	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
wholly	O
Innocent	O
of	O
the	O
Murder	O
,	O
and	O
declared	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
how	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Reginer	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Sisters	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
whilst	O
Mr.	O
Symbole	O
was	O
abroad	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
some	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
sent	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Symbole	O
to	O
come	O
home	O
and	O
bear	O
them	O
Company	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
Cards	O
;	O
and	O
about	O
Nine	O
or	O
Ten	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
night	O
Mr.	O
Symbole	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Humour	O
,	O
very	O
kindly	O
embracing	O
Mr.	O
Reginer	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
highly	O
honoured	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
complemented	O
him	O
very	O
civilly	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
,	O
a	O
Supper	O
was	O
provided	O
(	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Symbole	O
's	O
Order	O
)	O
which	O
they	O
eat	O
very	O
amicably	O
together	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
they	O
played	O
at	O
Cards	O
again	O
,	O
at	O
Bone	O
Ace	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Symbole	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Reginer	O
,	O
happening	O
to	O
turn	O
up	O
two	O
Sevens	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Symbole	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Cards	O
should	O
be	O
dealt	O
again	O
,	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Reginer	O
denied	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
high	O
Words	O
arose	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Symbole	O
telling	O
Reginer	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
Crown-Office	O
.	O
Reginer	O
replying	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
;	O
so	O
to	O
boxing	O
they	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Reginer	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
and	O
stabbed	O
Mr.	O
Symbole	O
.	O
She	O
further	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
so	O
much	O
affrighted	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
screamed	O
out	O
as	O
loud	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
able	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Old	O
Woman	O
being	O
asleep	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
make	O
her	O
hear	O
,	O
besides	O
,	O
she	O
called	O
a	O
whole	O
Cloud	O
of	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
always	O
lived	O
very	O
lovingly	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Symbole	O
had	O
been	O
often	O
times	O
heard	O
to	O
speak	O
very	O
respectively	O
of	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
loved	O
her	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
besides	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
divers	O
very	O
credible	O
Persons	O
,	O
who	O
appeared	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
an	O
Excellent	O
Testimony	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Symbole	O
's	O
Reputation	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
always	O
bred	O
very	O
Religiously	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
modest	O
Carriage	O
and	O
Behaviour	O
,	O
not	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
manner	O
of	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
or	O
Disregard	O
in	O
the	O
Comporting	O
of	O
herself	O
towards	O
Mr.	O
Symbole	O
,	O
never	O
since	O
she	O
was	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
much	O
surprised	O
she	O
knew	O
not	O
how	O
Mr.	O
Reginer	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
supposed	O
that	O
her	O
Sisters	O
had	O
gone	O
out	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
got	O
away	O
before	O
any	O
Assistance	O
came	O
.	O
One	O
Sister	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
,	O
alledged	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
there	O
the	O
same	O
night	O
the	O
Murder	O
was	O
Committed	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Symbole	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Reginer	O
were	O
good	O
friends	O
,	O
till	O
they	O
fell	O
out	O
about	O
turning	O
up	O
two	O
Sevens	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
so	O
much	O
affrighted	O
when	O
she	O
saw	O
them	O
fight	O
,	O
she	O
ran	O
down	O
Stairs	O
and	O
went	O
home	O
crying	O
out	O
and	O
making	O
a	O
noise	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
only	O
she	O
remembered	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
Quarrel	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Symbole	O
called	O
Mr.	O
Reginer	O
Cowardly	O
Rogue	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
Crown	O
Office	O
.	O
Then	O
Mr.	O
Reginer	O
replied	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
so	O
great	O
a	O
Rogue	O
as	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
Sister	O
declared	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
effect	O
,	O
as	O
did	O
the	O
former	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
also	O
much	O
affrighted	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Sister	O
going	O
away	O
in	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
Quarrel	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
also	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
designing	O
any	O
Murder	O
,	O
she	O
knew	O
not	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
both	O
the	O
same	O
Evidence	O
as	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
,	O
as	O
had	O
Mrs.	O
Symbole	O
.	O
So	O
,	O
then	O
all	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
having	O
been	O
examined	O
fairly	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
patience	O
and	O
Indulgence	O
from	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
for	O
their	O
Trial	O
lasted	O
very	O
long	O
;	O
the	O
Court	O
gave	O
the	O
Charge	O
to	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
distinguishing	O
the	O
Law	O
in	O
the	O
Case	O
of	O
Murder	O
;	O
and	O
because	O
,	O
where	O
any	O
Person	O
shall	O
stab	O
another	O
,	O
other	O
People	O
being	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
interrupting	O
him	O
yet	O
he	O
only	O
is	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Stabbing	O
and	O
Death	O
of	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
thrust	O
;	O
so	O
this	O
Evidence	O
did	O
not	O
affect	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
upon	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
Stabbing	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Penalty	O
of	O
that	O
Statute	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
positive	O
Proof	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
Abet	O
,	O
Aid	O
,	O
or	O
Assist	O
the	O
said	O
Reginer	O
in	O
the	O
Perpetration	O
of	O
so	O
Barbarous	O
and	O
Bloody	O
a	O
Murder	O
,	O
or	O
had	O
any	O
hand	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
a	O
Verdict	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
not	O
guilty	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Becket	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
her	O
Mistress	O
,	O
one	O
Lydia	B-pers
Campion	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
;	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
carrying	O
away	O
a	O
silver	O
Cann	O
value	O
50s	O
.	O
a	O
Salt	O
10s	O
.	O
two	O
Silver	O
Porringers	O
4l	O
.	O
20	O
Ounces	O
of	O
silver	O
5l	O
.	O
with	O
other	O
Plate	O
of	O
great	O
value	O
;	O
Mistress	O
Campion	O
swore	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
her	O
Servant	O
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
same	O
night	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
by	O
some	O
Boys	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Mobb	O
that	O
gathered	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
who	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
to	O
Mistress	O
Campions	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Plate	O
also	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
before	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
defence	O
that	O
was	O
material	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Geeris	I-pers
a	O
Chirurgion	O
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Mare	O
price	O
9l	O
.	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Biggs	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
that	O
the	O
Mare	O
was	O
stolen	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Orchard	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Biggs	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
place	O
called	O
Branton	B-place
Gleeford	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
County	I-place
of	I-place
Wilts	I-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Mare	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
London	O
at	O
the	O
Woolpack	O
at	O
Smithfield-Bars	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Custody	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
seized	O
and	O
taken	O
;	O
so	O
the	O
said	O
Biggs	O
had	O
Intelligence	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
the	O
Mare	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
Mare	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
the	O
Woolpack	O
abovesaid	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Biggs	O
his	O
Son	O
in	O
Newgate	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Mare	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
it	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
for	O
one	O
damn	O
'd	O
Son	O
of	O
a	O
Whore	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
Mare	O
again	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
behaved	O
himself	O
very	O
impudently	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Mare	O
of	O
one	O
Feazy	O
a	O
Prisoner	O
now	O
in	O
Newgate	O
who	O
was	O
fetch't	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
examined	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
year	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
bought	O
any	O
such	O
Mare	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Repremanded	O
;	O
why	O
says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
could	O
have	O
given	O
an	O
account	O
but	O
he	O
will	O
not	O
,	O
he	O
can	O
if	O
he	O
will	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
further	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Horse	O
that	O
I	O
called	O
Old	O
Broom	O
which	O
I	O
led	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
need	O
to	O
steal	O
a	O
Mare	O
;	O
Then	O
being	O
asked	O
what	O
Inn	O
he	O
Lodged	O
at	O
when	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
he	O
answered	O
(	O
with	O
a	O
kind	O
of	O
Laughter	O
)	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
stranger	O
at	O
this	O
Town	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
forgot	O
the	O
Sign	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
like	O
a	O
Lyon	O
,	O
or	O
some	O
such	O
Sign	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
being	O
askt	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
more	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
answered	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
more	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
only	O
that	O
the	O
Mare	O
cost	O
him	O
6	O
Guineas	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
dear	O
Bargain	O
,	O
and	O
nothing	O
vext	O
him	O
so	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
the	O
Mare	O
so	O
much	O
Corn	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
cost	O
him	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
money	O
;	O
so	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
Verdict	O
he	O
Laught	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
no	O
Laughing	O
matter	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susannah	B-pers
Pryer	I-pers
,	O
B	B-pers
-	I-pers
E	I-pers
-	I-pers
Elinor	B-pers
Goffe	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
tryed	O
for	O
robbing	O
their	O
Lodging	O
of	O
a	O
Quilt	O
val	O
.	O
2l	O
.	O
One	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
2l	O
.	O
a	O
Table-cloth	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
one	O
Francis	B-pers
Tegg	I-pers
,	O
who	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
Pryer	O
and	O
E	O
-	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
Room	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
Lodged	O
with	O
him	O
above	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
year	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
,	O
Goffe	O
and	O
Rogers	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
visit	O
the	O
said	O
Pryer	O
and	O
E	O
-	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
stolen	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
Goffe	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
carry	O
away	O
a	O
lap	O
full	O
of	O
things	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
9th	O
.	O
instant	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
came	O
again	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
did	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
and	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
did	O
absent	O
from	O
their	O
Lodgings	O
;	O
Goffe	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
carried	O
but	O
foul	O
cloaths	O
to	O
be	O
washed	O
abroad	O
:	O
They	O
were	O
indicted	O
only	O
upon	O
suspicion	O
;	O
so	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
but	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Pollard	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Girl	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
L	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
Corronet	O
val	O
20	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
the	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Percy	I-pers
;	O
the	O
witness	O
swore	O
that	O
the	O
Girl	O
worked	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
with	O
them	O
(	O
being	O
two	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
net	O
was	O
missing	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
this	O
was	O
all	O
they	O
could	O
say	O
:	O
and	O
the	O
Girl	O
called	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
for	O
her	O
reputation	O
who	O
gave	O
a	O
fair	O
counsel	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
an	O
honest	O
girl	O
and	O
had	O
always	O
behaved	O
her	O
self	O
honestly	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
Felony	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Black	O
Petticoat	O
fringed	O
with	O
Silver	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
Twilight	O
12	O
l.	O
a	O
Gown	O
40	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
rich	O
Goods	O
of	O
great	O
value	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Robertson	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
above	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
7	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
one	O
George	B-pers
[	I-pers
Text	I-pers
unreadable	I-pers
in	I-pers
original	I-pers
.	I-pers
]	I-pers
who	O
swore	O
1	O
l.	O
Boat	O
lay	O
at	O
Wapping	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Robertson	O
being	O
a	O
Custom-House	O
Officer	O
seized	O
the	O
Boat	O
thereby	O
to	O
engage	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
which	O
he	O
would	O
fain	O
have	O
neglected	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
said	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original.	O
]	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
was	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
from	O
Joan	B-pers
Hatley	I-pers
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
they	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Belwood	I-pers
were	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
together	O
with	O
Anne	B-pers
York	I-pers
not	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gratwick	I-pers
Mercer	O
in	O
Covent	B-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
16	O
Yards	O
of	O
Lute	O
string	O
Silk	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
they	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mark	B-pers
Fenton	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Felton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
Sr.	O
John	B-pers
Brownlow	I-pers
Knight	O
,	O
Scituate	O
in	O
the	O
Pall-Mall	B-place
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
swore	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
House	O
(	O
it	O
being	O
to	O
Lett	O
)	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
Christmas	O
last	O
;	O
as	O
also	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
and	O
robbed	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
suspected	O
to	O
have	O
done	O
the	O
mischief	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
lost	O
Tables	O
,	O
Stands	O
,	O
and	O
Looking	O
Glasses	O
,	O
besides	O
several	O
Feather-Beds	O
,	O
Bolsters	O
,	O
Pillows	O
,	O
Blankets	O
,	O
Rugs	O
,	O
Coverlets	O
,	O
flower	O
'd	O
silk	O
Curtains	O
,	O
divers	O
new	O
Cane	O
Chairs	O
,	O
Sheets	O
,	O
fine	O
Bed	O
Linnen	O
of	O
all	O
sorts	O
;	O
the	O
Sockets	O
of	O
two	O
Glass	O
Sconces	O
a	O
Portmantua	O
Trunk	O
,	O
two	O
Coppers	O
,	O
a	O
Brass	O
Frying	O
pan	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Iron	O
Dripping	O
pan	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
Houshold	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
value	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
less	O
then	O
three	O
Cart	O
Loads	O
of	O
Goods	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
House	O
for	O
another	O
Person	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
therefore	O
his	O
House	O
being	O
searcht	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
found	O
a	O
Feather-Bed	O
marked	O
with	O
Sir	O
John	O
Brownlows	O
name	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
a	O
Japan	O
Looking	O
Glass	O
,	O
several	O
Kane	O
Chairs	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
silver	O
Sconces	O
&	O
c.	O
all	O
which	O
were	O
owned	O
to	O
be	O
Sir	O
John	O
Brownlows	O
Goods	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
Iron	O
Betty	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
house	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
lost	O
by	O
a	O
Butcher	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Thieves	O
call	O
an	O
Embroidering	O
Needle	O
,	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
first	O
discovered	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
by	O
a	O
Chairman	O
that	O
Lodged	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
house	O
(	O
he	O
hearing	O
the	O
printed	O
Bill	O
read	O
that	O
was	O
publisht	O
to	O
give	O
the	O
World	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
Loss	O
;	O
)	O
took	O
Notice	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
which	O
he	O
saw	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
Notice	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
:	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Maid	O
that	O
showed	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
swore	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
came	O
with	O
the	O
woman	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
alledge	O
nothing	O
that	O
was	O
material	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
but	O
told	O
a	O
long	O
Story	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Molkin	O
an	O
Upholsterer	O
,	O
with	O
whom	O
the	O
Key	O
was	O
left	O
to	O
shew	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
paid	O
25	O
l.	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
false	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
run	O
away	O
when	O
first	O
T	O
ed	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
January	O
;	O
and	O
was	O
not	O
found	O
till	O
the	O
22d	O
Instant	O
;	O
upon	O
this	O
whole	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Giles	B-pers
Matolister	I-pers
was	O
Tryed	O
for	O
Committing	O
two	O
Robberies	O
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
near	O
Hackney	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Mary	B-pers
the	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
one	I-pers
Dukes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
a	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
;	O
the	O
second	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Thomas	B-pers
Otborn	I-pers
a	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
at	O
Stoutbridge	B-place
near	I-place
Kingstone	I-place
of	O
3s	O
.	O
6d.in	O
money	O
and	O
a	O
few	O
Farthings	O
;	O
Mrs	O
Dukes	O
swore	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
Robbed	O
at	O
Stoutbridge	O
;	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original.	O
]	O
.	O
Otborn	O
says	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
from	O
London	O
driving	O
his	O
Coach	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
place	O
three	O
men	O
met	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
stopt	O
his	O
Horses	O
,	O
and	O
rifled	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
money	O
abovesaid	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
Swear	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
amongst	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
two	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
pursued	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
prisoner	O
away	O
amongst	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
Life	O
;	O
and	O
called	O
his	O
Landlady	O
where	O
he	O
Lodged	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Neighbours	O
besides	O
who	O
gave	O
a	O
Credible	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
a	O
noble	O
Captain	O
in	O
Court	O
who	O
knew	O
him	O
in	O
Flanders	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
end	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Skale	I-pers
and	I-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
his	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
were	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Looking	O
glass	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
a	O
Set	O
of	O
Curtains	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
p	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
a	O
Blanket	O
,	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Tankard	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
small	O
Houshold	O
Goods	O
from	O
George	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
.	O
They	O
came	O
to	O
lodge	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
before	O
Christmas	O
day	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
9	O
days	O
,	O
they	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
not	O
found	O
till	O
six	O
Weeks	O
after	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
time	O
they	O
confest	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
having	O
sold	O
them	O
.	O
So	O
the	O
Wife	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
that	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
was	O
in	O
C	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
to	O
her	O
Husband	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Tuttle	I-pers
not	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
Conspire	O
,	O
and	O
Charge	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Merchant	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Offence	O
of	O
Buggery	O
with	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
first	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
who	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
said	O
Bates	O
sent	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
Tavern	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
went	O
;	O
and	O
immediately	O
the	O
said	O
Lane	O
and	O
Tuttle	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
Lane	O
presently	O
charged	O
the	O
said	O
Hall	O
with	O
Buggery	O
and	O
Tuttle	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
another	O
Room	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
committed	O
the	O
Sin	O
of	O
Buggery	O
with	O
Bates	O
.	O
And	O
he	O
answered	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
innocent	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
being	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
another	O
sort	O
of	O
Conversation	O
.	O
But	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Tuttle	O
still	O
persisted	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
could	O
produce	O
one	O
that	O
would	O
swear	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
said	O
Lane	O
it	O
is	O
so	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
.	O
So	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
Consternation	O
,	O
agreed	O
with	O
Tuttle	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
Bill	O
of	O
36	O
l.	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
Lane	O
only	O
said	O
thus	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
it	O
is	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
can	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bates	O
Sister	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Tuttle	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
Brother	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
Tuttle	O
would	O
have	O
perswaded	O
him	O
to	O
lay	O
the	O
Buggery	O
upon	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
provided	O
for	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
he	O
lived	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
But	O
Bates	O
refused	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Lane	O
spake	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
all	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
been	O
bred	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
served	O
an	O
Apprenticeship	O
to	O
a	O
Wier-drawer	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
given	O
to	O
do	O
any	O
evil	O
thing	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
amiss	O
now	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
Fact	O
,	O
or	O
words	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
effect	O
in	O
favour	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
yet	O
for	O
all	O
this	O
,	O
his	O
Innocency	O
was	O
not	O
cleared	O
.	O
For	O
says	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
What	O
business	O
had	O
Mr.	O
Lane	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
,	O
along	O
with	O
Tuttle	O
;	O
Was	O
it	O
to	O
advise	O
him	O
about	O
the	O
Charge	O
and	O
Conspiracy	O
,	O
how	O
to	O
defend	O
himself	O
?	O
Surely	O
no	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
altogether	O
a	O
Stranger	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
therefore	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
conjectured	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
Tuttle	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
sheer	O
design	O
to	O
get	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
were	O
to	O
consider	O
of	O
the	O
business	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
that	O
men	O
should	O
be	O
so	O
impudent	O
to	O
impose	O
upon	O
a	O
Citizen	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
worthy	O
a	O
Merchant	O
,	O
as	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
was	O
.	O
So	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
end	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
in	O
conspiring	O
against	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
charging	O
him	O
with	O
so	O
great	O
a	O
Falshood	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Cannock	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
China	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
wound	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
upon	O
the	O
left	O
Thigh	O
,	O
near	O
to	O
his	O
Groin	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
three	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
dyed	O
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
,	O
first	O
,	O
two	O
Watchmen	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
standing	O
in	O
Arundel	O
street	O
with	O
their	O
Swords	O
drawn	O
about	O
three	O
a	O
clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
put	O
up	O
their	O
Swords	O
,	O
and	O
walking	O
together	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
,	O
Mr.	O
China	O
fell	O
down	O
dead	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
Witness	O
was	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
that	O
kept	O
the	O
Rummer	O
Tavern	O
near	O
Arundel	O
street	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
with	O
another	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
were	O
drinking	O
Wine	O
at	O
his	O
house	O
till	O
Two	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
very	O
merry	O
and	O
civil	O
;	O
another	O
Witness	O
a	O
Coffee-Woman	O
,	O
who	O
lived	O
in	O
Milford	O
lane	O
,	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
in	O
her	O
house	O
the	O
same	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
they	O
quarrelled	O
about	O
Fighting	O
in	O
Flanders	O
;	O
and	O
China	O
called	O
Cannock	O
a	O
Villain	O
and	O
Rascal	O
,	O
and	O
spit	O
in	O
his	O
face	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
That	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
come	O
out	O
and	O
fight	O
he	O
would	O
kick	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Cor	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
gave	O
account	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
wound	O
was	O
above	O
Three	O
Inches	O
deep	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
near	O
his	O
Groin	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
Mortal	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
called	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Isaacson	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Witness	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
declared	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
from	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
to	O
what	O
before	O
has	O
been	O
sworn	O
.	O
He	O
further	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
did	O
own	O
that	O
Mr.	O
China	O
did	O
dye	O
by	O
his	O
by	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
he	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
do	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
defence	O
,	O
because	O
Mr.	O
China	O
prest	O
so	O
hard	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
[	I-pers
Text	I-pers
unreadable	I-pers
in	I-pers
original	I-pers
.	I-pers
]	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
in	O
Clipping	O
of	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
Liberty	O
of	O
St.	O
Katherines	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
house	O
for	O
stolen	O
goods	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
there	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
her	O
a	O
small	O
parcel	O
of	O
Clippings	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Bed	O
were	O
found	O
some	O
shears	O
and	O
files	O
.	O
She	O
declared	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
the	O
Clippings	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
several	O
of	O
her	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
who	O
justified	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
loose	O
idle	O
Person	O
.	O
So	O
in	O
the	O
conclusion	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Banks	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
robbing	O
William	B-pers
Martyn	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Parish	I-place
(	O
on	O
the	O
First	O
instant	O
)	O
of	O
8	O
pair	O
of	O
Sleeves	O
,	O
val	O
5l	O
.	O
9	O
pair	O
of	O
Flaxen	O
Pillowbers	O
18s	O
.	O
some	O
Hoods	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
not	O
sufficient	O
to	O
find	O
her	O
Guilty	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Sudcole	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Maiden	O
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Muslin	O
Nightroyls	O
,	O
val	O
2s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Phyamete	B-pers
Cotes	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
could	O
not	O
charge	O
her	O
fully	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
good	O
Evidence	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
an	O
honest	O
maid	O
.	O
So	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Coppinger	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
for	O
entring	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Mottershed	I-pers
in	O
the	O
day-time	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
taking	O
away	O
a	O
Watch	O
value	O
7l	O
.	O
and	O
7l	O
.	O
in	O
money	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Mottershed	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
with	O
another	O
man	O
,	O
one	O
B	O
-	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Clipper	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
swear	O
it	O
,	O
giving	O
her	O
threatening	O
language	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
should	O
burn	O
as	O
Fire	O
burned	O
.	O
But	O
before	O
this	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
asked	O
her	O
to	O
lend	O
him	O
some	O
money	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Law	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
refusing	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
caused	O
her	O
to	O
open	O
her	O
Trunks	O
,	O
wherein	O
was	O
the	O
Watch	O
and	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
He	O
pretended	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
Clippings	O
and	O
clipt	O
money	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
none	O
;	O
the	O
Watch	O
and	O
the	O
money	O
lying	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
whilst	O
Mrs.	O
Mottershed	O
went	O
into	O
another	O
Room	O
to	O
dress	O
herself	O
(	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Newgate	O
as	O
she	O
thought	O
)	O
being	O
in	O
great	O
terror	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
mind	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
motions	O
,	O
upon	O
a	O
sudden	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
B	O
-	O
(	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
away	O
they	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
Watch	O
and	O
money	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
alledged	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
maliciously	O
prosecuted	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Mottershed	O
went	O
by	O
several	O
Names	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Tomson	O
,	O
Sturgess	O
,	O
and	O
Mottershed	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
all	O
her	O
Neighbours	O
knew	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Clipper	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
person	O
of	O
known	O
integrity	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
offer	O
d	O
a	O
warrant	O
for	O
his	O
doing	O
,	O
signed	O
by	O
Hugh	B-pers
Chamberlain	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
Justice	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Witness	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
the	O
Warrant	O
was	O
a	O
true	O
one	O
granted	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Chamberlain	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
proof	O
that	O
he	O
broke	O
anything	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Mottershed	O
having	O
her	O
Watch	O
sent	O
her	O
from	O
B	O
-	O
by	O
a	O
Porter	O
,	O
she	O
paying	O
four	O
Guinea	O
's	O
to	O
fetch	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
pawn	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
but	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
Matthew	O
Coppinger	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
tried	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
robbery	O
.	O
The	O
Indictment	O
set	O
forth	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Brandon	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
did	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
one	O
Humphrey	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
near	O
Lincolns-Inn	B-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
where	O
was	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
,	O
and	O
there	O
did	O
rob	O
her	O
of	O
30	O
Guinea	O
's	O
;	O
the	O
said	O
Brandon	O
having	O
a	O
Sword	O
drawn	O
in	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
,	O
did	O
put	O
Mrs.	O
Powell	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
tells	O
Mr.	O
Powell	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
kindness	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
therefore	O
came	O
to	O
acquaint	O
him	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Warrant	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
against	O
him	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
for	O
Clipping	O
,	O
which	O
would	O
be	O
sworn	O
against	O
him	O
by	O
own	O
Rogues	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
arraigned	O
for	O
a	O
misdemeanour	O
,	O
in	O
conspiring	O
against	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Powell	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
for	O
falsly	O
charging	O
them	O
with	O
the	O
Crime	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
thereby	O
to	O
bring	O
them	O
to	O
final	O
death	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
first	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
the	O
Parliament	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
Warrant	O
or	O
Order	O
for	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
the	O
Clippers	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Powell	O
declared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
men	O
at	O
a	O
Coffee-house	O
hard	O
by	O
,	O
had	O
a	O
Warrant	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
knowing	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Friend	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
worthy	O
Person	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
know	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
secure	O
himself	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
and	O
Coppinger	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
a	O
Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
entring	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
comes	O
Brandon	O
and	O
Smith	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
rude	O
manner	O
accosted	O
him	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
Warrant	O
against	O
him	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
;	O
and	O
immediately	O
seized	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
threatened	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
strange	O
manner	O
,	O
with	O
horrid	O
Oaths	O
and	O
Execrations	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
were	O
Clippers	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
burnt	O
;	O
at	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Powel	O
was	O
much	O
surprised	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
Mrs.	O
Powel	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
removed	O
from	O
the	O
Tavern	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
would	O
swear	O
it	O
downright	O
against	O
them	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
Mrs.	O
Powell	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
affrighted	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
into	O
a	O
Swoon	O
;	O
so	O
Coppinger	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
her	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
troubled	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Friend	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
nothing	O
but	O
a	O
Trick	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
were	O
Rogues	O
,	O
and	O
only	O
wanted	O
money	O
;	O
so	O
they	O
at	O
last	O
compounded	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
30	O
Guineas	O
,	O
which	O
Mrs.	O
Powell	O
had	O
fetch	O
'd	O
from	O
home	O
,	O
unknown	O
to	O
her	O
Husband	O
;	O
so	O
away	O
they	O
went	O
.	O
They	O
came	O
with	O
a	O
Warrant	O
,	O
but	O
without	O
any	O
Constable	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
appeared	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Coppinger	O
was	O
privy	O
to	O
the	O
whole	O
Design	O
,	O
and	O
joined	O
with	O
the	O
said	O
Brandon	O
and	O
Smyth	O
in	O
carrying	O
on	O
the	O
Villany	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Horse-Shoe	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
just	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
received	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Powel	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
said	O
Brandon	O
nor	O
Smith	O
,	O
nor	O
had	O
any	O
great	O
Acquaintance	O
with	O
Coppinger	O
.	O
Other	O
Evidence	O
proved	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Guineas	O
to	O
his	O
Share	O
:	O
And	O
that	O
he	O
made	O
his	O
humble	O
Application	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Powel	O
(	O
by	O
Letters	O
)	O
,	O
That	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
pardon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
so	O
merciful	O
to	O
him	O
as	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
said	O
Brandon	O
and	O
Smith	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
upon	O
Oath	O
discover	O
the	O
Design	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Brandon	O
nor	O
Smith	O
did	O
ever	O
know	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Powel	O
.	O
He	O
could	O
not	O
urge	O
any	O
thing	O
material	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
being	O
very	O
well	O
satisfied	O
of	O
the	O
Heinousness	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
Innocence	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Powel	O
and	O
Madam	O
Powel	O
,	O
being	O
Persons	O
of	O
an	O
unblemish	O
'd	O
Reputation	O
;	O
this	O
therefore	O
was	O
duly	O
considered	O
by	O
both	O
Court	O
and	O
Jury	O
;	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Robbery	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Misdemeanor	O
died	O
in	O
course	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Sentence	O
as	O
followeth	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
17	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Nichols	O
,	O
Mary	O
Goffe	O
,	O
Elinor	O
Griffeth	O
,	O
Priscilla	O
Hamar	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Hitch	O
,	O
James	O
Fleming	O
,	O
James	O
Mersham	O
,	O
Errick	O
Cornelius	O
,	O
Richard	O
Jones	O
,	O
Mark	O
Fenton	O
,	O
William	O
Cannock	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Jefforson	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Barnes	O
,	O
Sarah	O
Becket	O
,	O
Jane	O
Browne	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Belwood	O
,	O
Jane	O
Newel	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
3	O
.	O
Robert	O
Geerish	O
,	O
John	O
Davis	O
,	O
Matthew	O
Coppinger	O
.	O
James	O
Pattison	O
,	O
formerly	O
Convicted	O
for	O
Clipping	O
,	O
was	O
called	O
to	O
his	O
former	O
Judgments	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
,	O
3	O
.	O
Martha	O
Free	O
,	O
Mary	O
Foster	O
,	O
William	O
Skale	O
Thomas	O
Lane	O
was	O
fined	O
40	O
Mark	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
to	O
stand	O
Three	O
times	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
,	O
once	O
near	O
the	O
Mitre	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Fenchurchstreet-	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
at	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Third	O
Time	O
in	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
usual	O
days	O
;	O
and	O
to	O
find	O
good	O
Sureties	O
for	O
his	O
Quiet	O
Behaviour	O
for	O
a	O
Twelvemonth	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Hitch	O
,	O
James	O
Fleming	O
,	O
Errick	O
Cornelius	O
,	O
and	O
Richard	O
Jones	O
,	O
took	O
a	O
Lifting	O
Shilling	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
entertain	O
'd	O
into	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Service	O
An	O
Indictment	O
was	O
brought	O
against	O
Owen	B-pers
Sullivan	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Kane	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Kalligan	I-pers
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
together	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dunning	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Macartey	I-pers
,	O
Timothy	B-pers
Brenot	I-pers
,	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
did	O
break	O
the	O
Savoy	O
Prison	O
,	O
whereby	O
several	O
persons	O
who	O
were	O
committed	O
there	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
made	O
their	O
Escape	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Tried	O
for	O
the	O
Offence	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
The	O
Humble	O
Presentment	O
of	O
the	O
Grand	O
Jury	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
Judges	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
this	O
Honourable	O
Court	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
1694/5	O
.	O
Whereas	O
by	O
sad	O
Experience	O
,	O
the	O
currant	O
Coyn	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
is	O
diminished	O
,	O
defaced	O
,	O
imbased	O
,	O
and	O
counterfeited	O
to	O
less	O
than	O
one	O
half	O
of	O
the	O
due	O
Intrinsick	O
Value	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Ruin	O
of	O
Trade	O
,	O
and	O
great	O
Dishonour	O
of	O
the	O
Nation	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
find	O
by	O
Exchange	O
abroad	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
our	O
great	O
Detriment	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
if	O
not	O
speedily	O
prevented	O
by	O
some	O
new	O
Law	O
,	O
which	O
shall	O
punish	O
Confederate	O
Dispersers	O
of	O
Clipt	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
mercenary	O
Exchangers	O
of	O
Broad	O
money	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
the	O
Criminals	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
of	O
Clipping	O
,	O
will	O
have	O
a	O
great	O
tendency	O
to	O
the	O
inevitable	O
Ruin	O
of	O
Trade	O
,	O
and	O
Disturbance	O
in	O
the	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
than	O
can	O
be	O
retrieved	O
.	O
That	O
we	O
conceive	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
necessity	O
of	O
further	O
Power	O
to	O
be	O
given	O
to	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Magistrates	O
for	O
frequent	O
Examination	O
of	O
Loose	O
and	O
Unsettled	O
persons	O
that	O
have	O
no	O
Habitation	O
nor	O
Business	O
,	O
but	O
live	O
on	O
Pilfering	O
and	O
Begging	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
Examination	O
of	O
such	O
Persons	O
so	O
found	O
and	O
detected	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
be	O
imployed	O
in	O
the	O
Service	O
of	O
the	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
as	O
Soldiers	O
,	O
would	O
prevent	O
the	O
unreasonable	O
Imposition	O
by	O
Press-masters	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
loose	O
vicious	O
Women	O
,	O
and	O
Black-guard	O
Boys	O
be	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Plantations	O
.	O
That	O
Salisbury-Court	O
,	O
White-Friers	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
pretended	O
Priviledge	O
places	O
,	O
are	O
notorious	O
for	O
entertaining	O
Lewd	O
People	O
,	O
Clippers	O
,	O
and	O
Highway-men	O
,	O
and	O
sheltering	O
such	O
as	O
Defraud	O
their	O
Creditors	O
.	O
That	O
all	O
Lotteries	O
,	O
except	O
what	O
be	O
established	O
by	O
the	O
Government	O
,	O
be	O
supprest	O
as	O
publick	O
Nusances	O
to	O
the	O
Debauchery	O
and	O
Ruin	O
of	O
Youth	O
and	O
Servants	O
.	O
All	O
which	O
we	O
humbly	O
present	O
fit	O
to	O
be	O
recommended	O
by	O
this	O
Honourable	O
Court	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Wisdom	O
of	O
this	O
Parliament	O
,	O
that	O
such	O
Laws	O
may	O
be	O
enacted	O
to	O
redress	O
these	O
Grievances	O
.	O
Signed	O
by	O
James	B-pers
Denew	I-pers
William	B-pers
Carbonell	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Mead	I-pers
Peter	B-pers
Cartwight	I-pers
William	B-pers
George	I-pers
John	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Herle	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Cahmbree	I-pers
James	B-pers
Parr	I-pers
Josiah	B-pers
Ragdale	I-pers
Jonathan	B-pers
Kendale	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
Anthony	B-pers
Stratton	I-pers
John	B-pers
Talbot	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Speed	I-pers
.	O
Books	O
Printed	O
for	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
Thomas	O
Cockerill	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Legs	O
in	O
the	O
Poultery	O
,	O
over-against	O
the	O
Stocks-Market	O
.	O
THE	O
Instrumentality	O
of	O
Faith	O
,	O
Asserted	O
,	O
Proved	O
,	O
Explained	O
,	O
Compared	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
Preferred	O
to	O
a	O
Conditional	O
Relation	O
thereof	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
Pardon	O
and	O
Happiness	O
,	O
when	O
strictly	O
taken	O
in	O
a	O
Legal	O
or	O
Foederal	O
sence	O
.	O
By	O
W.	O
Cross	O
M.A	O
.	O
A	O
Sermon	O
on	O
the	O
Resurrection	O
,	O
occasioned	O
by	O
the	O
Funeral	O
of	O
Friend	O
.	O
By	O
Walter	O
Cross	O
,	O
M.A	O
.	O
Good	O
Deeds	O
done	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
House	O
:	O
A	O
Sermon	O
Preached	O
on	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
Dr.	O
Jeremiah	O
Butt	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Physicians	O
appointed	O
for	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Fleet	O
.	O
By	O
Ed	O
.	O
Veal	O
.	O
Infant-Baptism	O
God	O
's	O
Ordinance	O
:	O
Or	O
a	O
clear	O
proof	O
,	O
that	O
all	O
the	O
Children	O
of	O
believing	O
parents	O
are	O
in	O
the	O
Covenat	O
of	O
Grace	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
as	O
much	O
Right	O
to	O
baptism	O
,	O
the	O
now	O
Seal	O
of	O
the	O
Covenant	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Infant-Seed	O
of	O
the	O
Jews	O
had	O
to	O
circumsion	O
,	O
the	O
then	O
Seal	O
of	O
the	O
Covenant	O
.	O
By	O
Michael	O
Harrsion	O
.	O
A	O
Remedy	O
against	O
Trouble	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
discourse	O
on	O
John	O
14	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
Wherein	O
something	O
is	O
also	O
briefly	O
attempted	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
clearing	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
faith	O
;	O
of	O
Justification	O
;	O
of	O
the	O
Covenant	O
of	O
Grace	O
,	O
Assurance	O
,	O
the	O
Witness	O
,	O
Seal	O
and	O
Earnest	O
of	O
the	O
Spirit	O
;	O
and	O
Preparation	O
for	O
the	O
Conversion	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
Necessity	O
of	O
Holiness	O
.	O
By	O
Henry	O
Lukin	O
.	O
A	O
Discourse	O
of	O
Schism	O
.	O
By	O
Edward	O
Polhill	O
Esq	O
;	O
of	O
Burwash	O
in	O
Sussex	O
.	O
Instructions	O
about	O
Heart-work	O
,	O
what	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
on	O
God	O
's	O
part	O
and	O
ours	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Cure	O
and	O
keeping	O
of	O
the	O
Heart	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
by	O
that	O
Eminent	O
Gospel-minister	O
Mr.	O
Richard	O
Alleyn	O
.	O
With	O
a	O
Preface	O
by	O
Dr.	O
Annesley	O
.	O
The	O
2d	O
Edition	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
of	O
Things	O
not	O
sen	O
:	O
Or	O
divers	O
Spiritual	O
and	O
Philosophical	O
Discourses	O
,	O
concerning	O
the	O
state	O
of	O
Holy	O
Men	O
after	O
Death	O
.	O
By	O
that	O
Eminently	O
Learned	O
Divine	O
,	O
Moses	O
Amyraldus	O
.	O
Translated	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
French	O
Tongue	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
Minister	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
of	O
England	O
.	O
Mr.	O
John	O
Flavel	O
's	O
Remains	O
,	O
being	O
two	O
Sermins	O
.	O
The	O
one	O
preached	O
at	O
Dartmouth	O
in	O
Devon	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
Coronation	O
of	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
.	O
The	O
latter	O
intended	O
to	O
be	O
preached	O
at	O
a	O
Meeting	O
o	O
f	O
the	O
United	O
Ministers	O
of	O
Several	O
Counties	O
.	O
With	O
some	O
Account	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
.	O
A	O
Discourse	O
of	O
Regeneration	O
,	O
Faith	O
and	O
Repentance	O
,	O
Preached	O
at	O
the	O
Merchants	O
Lecture	O
in	O
Broad-street	O
.	O
By	O
Tho	O
.	O
Cole	O
,	O
Minister	O
of	O
the	O
Gospel	O
.	O
A	O
Discourse	O
of	O
Christian	O
Religion	O
in	O
sundry	O
Points	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Christ	O
the	O
Hope	O
of	O
Glory	O
;	O
what	O
it	O
is	O
to	O
know	O
God	O
in	O
Christ	O
;	O
Christ	O
the	O
only	O
saviour	O
,	O
the	O
only	O
Mediator	O
,	O
Foundation	O
of	O
our	O
Adoption	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Preached	O
at	O
the	O
Merchants	O
Lecture	O
.	O
Bu	O
Tho	O
.	O
Cole	O
.	O
A	O
succinct	O
and	O
seasonable	O
Discourse	O
of	O
the	O
Occasions	O
,	O
causes	O
,	O
Natures	O
,	O
Rise	O
,	O
Growth	O
and	O
Remedies	O
of	O
Mental	O
Errors	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
(	O
1	O
.	O
)	O
An	O
Answer	O
to	O
some	O
Antinomian	O
Errors	O
.	O
(	O
3	O
)	O
A	O
Sermon	O
about	O
Union	O
.	O
By	O
John	O
Flavel	O
.	O
poems	O
on	O
several	O
Occasions	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Pastoral	O
;	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
A	O
Discourse	O
of	O
Life	O
.	O
By	O
John	O
Tutchin	O
.	O
Eutropii	O
Historiae	O
Romana	O
Breviarium	O
ab	O
urbe	O
Conditum	O
usque	O
ad	O
Valendianum	O
&	O
Valentem	O
Augustos	O
.	O
Ex	O
recensione	O
cum	O
Notulis	O
&	O
tanquilli	O
Fabri	O
ut	O
&	O
Sexti	O
Aurelii	O
Vitoris	O
de	O
Vires	O
Illustribus	O
,	O
Liber	O
in	O
Usum	O
Scholarium	O
.	O
Phaedri	O
Augusti	O
gasavis	O
Liberti	O
Fabularum	O
AEsopiarum	O
.	O
Libri	O
Quinque	O
.	O
In	O
usum	O
Serenissumi	O
Delphini	O
.	O
Notis	O
Illustravit	O
Petrus	O
Danet	O
.	O
Geography	O
rectified	O
;	O
or	O
a	O
Description	O
of	O
the	O
World	O
in	O
all	O
its	O
Kingdoms	O
,	O
Provinces	O
,	O
Countryes	O
,	O
Islands	O
,	O
Cities	O
,	O
Towns	O
,	O
Seas	O
,	O
Rivers	O
,	O
Bayes	O
,	O
Capes	O
,	O
Names	O
,	O
Inhabitants	O
,	O
Scituations	O
,	O
Histories	O
,	O
Customs	O
,	O
Commodities	O
,	O
Government	O
.	O
Illustrated	O
with	O
about	O
80	O
Maps	O
.	O
Third	O
Edition	O
.	O
By	O
Robert	O
Morden	O
.	O
Books	O
Printed	O
for	O
Richard	O
Baldwin	O
.	O
A	O
Brief	O
Enquiry	O
into	O
the	O
Ancient	O
Constitution	O
and	O
Government	O
of	O
England	O
:	O
As	O
well	O
in	O
respect	O
of	O
the	O
Administration	O
,	O
as	O
Succession	O
thereof	O
.	O
Set	O
forth	O
by	O
way	O
of	O
Dalogue	O
,	O
and	O
fitted	O
for	O
men	O
of	O
Ordinary	O
Learning	O
and	O
Capacities	O
.	O
By	O
James	O
Tyrrel	O
Esq	O
;	O
The	O
Works	O
of	O
F.	O
Rabelais	O
,	O
M.D	O
.	O
in	O
five	O
Books	O
:	O
Or	O
the	O
Lives	O
Heroic	O
Deeds	O
and	O
sayings	O
of	O
the	O
good	O
Gargantua	O
and	O
Pantagruel	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Voyage	O
to	O
the	O
Oracle	O
of	O
the	O
Bottle	O
.	O
As	O
also	O
his	O
Historical	O
Letters	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
the	O
Author	O
's	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
Explanatory	O
Remarks	O
.	O
By	O
Mr.	O
Motteaux	O
.	O
Never	O
before	O
Printed	O
in	O
English	O
.	O
The	O
remarkable	O
Sayings	O
,	O
Apothegms	O
,	O
and	O
Maxims	O
of	O
the	O
Estern	O
nations	O
,	O
abstracted	O
and	O
translated	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
Books	O
,	O
written	O
in	O
the	O
Arabian	O
,	O
Persian	O
,	O
and	O
Turkish	O
Language	O
;	O
with	O
Remarks	O
.	O
By	O
Monsieur	O
Galland	O
,	O
who	O
lived	O
many	O
Years	O
in	O
those	O
Countries	O
.	O
Translated	O
out	O
of	O
French	O
.	O
A	O
new	O
and	O
easy	O
Method	O
to	O
understand	O
the	O
Roman	O
History	O
.	O
With	O
an	O
exact	O
Chronology	O
of	O
the	O
reign	O
of	O
the	O
Emperors	O
.	O
An	O
Account	O
o	O
f	O
the	O
most	O
eminent	O
Authors	O
when	O
they	O
flourish	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Abridgment	O
of	O
the	O
Roman	O
Antiquities	O
and	O
Customs	O
.	O
By	O
way	O
of	O
Dialogue	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Burgundy	O
Done	O
out	O
of	O
French	O
,	O
with	O
very	O
large	O
Additions	O
and	O
Amendaments	O
.	O
By	O
Mr	O
Tho	O
.	O
Brown	O
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
Bibliotheca	O
Politica	O
:	O
Or	O
an	O
Enquiry	O
into	O
the	O
Ancient	O
Constitution	O
of	O
the	O
English	O
Government	O
;	O
Both	O
in	O
respect	O
to	O
the	O
just	O
Extent	O
of	O
Regal	O
power	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Rights	O
and	O
Liberties	O
of	O
the	O
Subject	O
.	O
Wherein	O
all	O
the	O
Chief	O
Arguments	O
,	O
and	O
well	O
against	O
as	O
for	O
the	O
Revolution	O
,	O
are	O
impartially	O
represented	O
and	O
considered	O
in	O
Thirteen	O
Dialogues	O
.	O
Collected	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
best	O
Authors	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
Ancient	O
as	O
Modern	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
an	O
Alphabetical	O
Index	O
to	O
the	O
whole	O
Work	O
.	O
By	O
James	O
Tyrrel	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
The	O
Bounds	O
set	O
to	O
France	O
by	O
the	O
Pyrenean	O
Treaty	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Interest	O
of	O
the	O
Confederates	O
not	O
to	O
accept	O
of	O
the	O
Offers	O
of	O
Peace	O
made	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
by	O
the	O
French	O
King	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
are	O
added	O
some	O
short	O
Reflections	O
,	O
shewing	O
how	O
far	O
England	O
is	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
restitution	O
of	O
that	O
Treaty	O
.	O
Together	O
with	O
a	O
List	O
of	O
the	O
Towns	O
and	O
Counties	O
that	O
the	O
French	O
have	O
taken	O
since	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
to	O
give	O
Notice	O
to	O
all	O
Persons	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
the	O
Publick	O
,	O
That	O
W.	O
Elmy	O
,	O
Prosfessor	O
of	O
Physick	O
,	O
and	O
Operator	O
,	O
of	O
known	O
Integrity	O
,	O
and	O
above	O
25	O
Years	O
Practice	O
,	O
liveth	O
at	O
the	O
Blue	O
Ball	O
in	O
Whalebone-Court	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Lower	O
End	O
of	O
Bartholomew-Lane	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
:	O
Who	O
most	O
safely	O
and	O
expeditiously	O
cures	O
Deafness	O
,	O
and	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
Ears	O
of	O
any	O
,	O
of	O
what	O
Age	O
soever	O
,	O
(	O
if	O
Curable	O
)	O
and	O
at	O
first	O
sight	O
,	O
by	O
Inspection	O
,	O
resolves	O
the	O
Patient	O
,	O
if	O
so	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
as	O
most	O
eminent	O
Persons	O
of	O
Quality	O
in	O
this	O
City	O
can	O
testify	O
.	O
He	O
hath	O
likewise	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Gargarism	O
or	O
mouth-water	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
make	O
Black	O
or	O
Yellow	O
Teeth	O
as	O
White	O
as	O
Ivory	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
times	O
using	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
will	O
certainly	O
Cure	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
Diseases	O
incident	O
to	O
the	O
mouth	O
,	O
Teeth	O
and	O
Gums	O
.	O
The	O
Glasses	O
are	O
of	O
several	O
Prices	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
.	O
That	O
you	O
may	O
not	O
mistake	O
,	O
my	O
House	O
is	O
at	O
the	O
Blew	O
Ball	O
,	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
see	O
it	O
as	O
you	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
THE	O
person	O
that	O
lately	O
lived	O
at	O
Ludgate-hill	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
the	O
Kings-Arms	O
Tavern	O
near	O
Fleetbridge	O
,	O
is	O
now	O
removed	O
,	O
and	O
any	O
one	O
that	O
wants	O
the	O
water	O
for	O
taking	O
away	O
Freckles	O
,	O
Pimples	O
,	O
Worms	O
,	O
and	O
Morphew	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
;	O
or	O
the	O
other	O
Preparations	O
for	O
the	O
easing	O
and	O
curing	O
of	O
most	O
Distempers	O
incident	O
to	O
Humane	O
Bodies	O
,	O
prepared	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
B.L	O
.	O
may	O
be	O
furnished	O
at	O
these	O
places	O
following	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
at	O
the	O
first	O
Door	O
on	O
the	O
Left	O
Hand	O
in	O
Essex	O
Court	O
,	O
going	O
through	O
the	O
Bolt	O
and	O
Tun	O
Inn	O
in	O
Fleetstreet	O
,	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Hamptons	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
the	O
Golden	O
Ball	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
.	O
And	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Labrahams	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Crown	O
in	O
Blue	O
Anchor	O
Alley	O
over	O
against	O
the	O
Artillary	O
Ground	O
,	O
on	O
Bunhil	O
.	O
To	O
prevent	O
counterfeits	O
and	O
mistakes	O
,	O
my	O
Bottles	O
will	O
be	O
Sealed	O
with	O
my	O
Coat	O
of	O
Arms	O
viz	O
.	O
the	O
Three	O
Water-Bugets	O
and	O
Half-Moon	O
.	O
