TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
OF	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
on	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
9th	O
,	O
10th	O
and	O
11th	O
Days	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
1695	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
Seventh	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTIES	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
Held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bayly	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
9th	O
,	O
10th	O
and	O
11th	O
Days	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
1695	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
Salathiel	B-pers
Lovell	I-pers
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
follows	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
William	B-pers
Peirce	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Casbeard	I-pers
James	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
William	B-pers
Woollaston	I-pers
James	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
William	B-pers
Durham	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
John	B-pers
Eales	I-pers
Giles	B-pers
Stretton	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Dennis	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Timothy	B-pers
Thornbury	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Nicholls	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Rammidge	I-pers
William	B-pers
Blinkhorne	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Bowler	I-pers
James	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
John	B-pers
Uncles	I-pers
John	B-pers
Cave	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
John	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Trials	O
are	O
as	O
follow	O
:	O
Edward	B-pers
White	I-pers
late	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Seventh	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Cooke	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bartholomew	I-place
by	I-place
the	I-place
Exchange	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Ward	I-place
of	I-place
Broadstreet	I-place
,	O
and	O
did	O
steal	O
one	O
Alamode	O
Hood	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
one	O
long	O
Scarf	O
,	O
a	O
Tippet	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
Sleeves	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Mantua	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Silk	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Cooke	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
alledged	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
inquire	O
for	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Maid	O
going	O
up	O
Stairs	O
about	O
nine	O
or	O
ten	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
Trunk	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
struggled	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
till	O
she	O
could	O
get	O
assistance	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
very	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Chizzal	O
being	O
found	O
,	O
supposed	O
to	O
be	O
left	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Pancrass	B-place
,	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Ann	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
Ann	B-pers
Deane	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Infant	O
of	O
seven	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
Daughter	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Deane	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
one	O
Serge	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
one	O
Serge	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
2s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
Harris	O
and	O
Williams	O
going	O
over	O
Lincoln-Inn	B-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
met	O
the	O
said	O
Deane	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
intice	O
her	O
with	O
promises	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
Cakes	O
and	O
Ale	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
decoyed	O
the	O
Child	O
into	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
did	O
there	O
strip	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
call	O
'd	O
People	O
to	O
speak	O
on	O
her	O
behalf	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Cholmley	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Robertson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Sixth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
,	O
two	O
Holland	O
Smocks	O
,	O
three	O
Head-dresses	O
laced	O
with	O
Flanders	O
lace	O
,	O
two	O
Night-railes	O
,	O
a	O
Looking-Glass	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
value	O
from	O
Mark	B-pers
Fenton	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
several	O
substantial	O
People	O
,	O
to	O
justify	O
her	O
Honesty	O
.	O
So	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Norman	I-pers
of	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rouse	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
for	O
giving	O
the	O
Deceased	O
one	O
mortal	O
Blow	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
side	O
of	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
near	O
to	O
his	O
right	O
Eye	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
wooden	O
Leaver	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
5th	O
following	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
he	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
alledged	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
unloading	O
Timber	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Lighter	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
piece	O
being	O
very	O
large	O
,	O
and	O
lying	O
somewhat	O
cross	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
unload	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
Rouse	O
bid	O
him	O
be	O
gone	O
pout	O
of	O
his	O
Lighter	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
alledged	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
imployed	O
by	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Dodd	O
,	O
to	O
deliver	O
the	O
Lighter	O
;	O
but	O
words	O
arose	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
stick	O
an	O
Iron-Crow	O
into	O
his	O
Body	O
,	O
and	O
holding	O
up	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
struck	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Leaver	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
having	O
considered	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Allom	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Perrin	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
murthering	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Gee	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Infant	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Age	O
of	O
Eight	O
years	O
,	O
by	O
Choaking	O
and	O
Strangling	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1d	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
found	O
dead	O
in	O
a	O
Cellar	O
window	O
one	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
about	O
his	O
Neck	O
in	O
the	O
New	B-place
Buildings	I-place
by	I-place
the	I-place
Privy	I-place
Garden	I-place
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
alledged	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
believed	O
there	O
might	O
be	O
some	O
Bruise	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Death	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Ware-house	O
of	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Castleman	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
and	O
pretended	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Muslin	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4l	O
.	O
they	O
sliped	O
away	O
with	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Muslin	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
they	O
dropt	O
it	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
being	O
counted	O
Shoplifters	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
brought	O
them	O
in	O
both	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wine	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Brittin	I-pers
in	O
Newgate	B-place
Market	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Bag	O
,	O
value	O
1d	O
.	O
and	O
of	O
one	O
Guinea	O
in	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
25s	O
.	O
with	O
40s	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
numbred	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Brittin	O
missing	O
her	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
Persons	O
had	O
been	O
seen	O
to	O
follow	O
her	O
,	O
being	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
suspected	O
Persons	O
,	O
they	O
pursued	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Brittin	O
's	O
Bag	O
being	O
found	O
on	O
Bennet	O
between	O
her	O
Stays	O
and	O
her	O
Shift	O
.	O
She	O
alledged	O
,	O
She	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
Newgate-street	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
her	O
.	O
So	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
,	O
and	O
Wine	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Boyce	I-pers
of	O
London	O
,	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Brown	O
Horse	O
,	O
value	O
12s	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
Arthur	B-pers
Capel	I-pers
of	O
S.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
London	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Capel	O
lost	O
his	O
Horse	O
off	O
a	O
Common	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Person	O
came	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Red-Lyon-Inn	O
in	O
Brownlowe-street	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
his	O
ways	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
Boyce	O
did	O
not	O
steal	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Obed	B-pers
Benton	I-pers
,	I-pers
and	I-pers
Mary	I-pers
his	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
Hannah	B-pers
Grevill	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twenty	O
four	O
Yards	O
of	O
Wosted	O
crape	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
Yards	O
of	O
Silk	O
Crape	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Coomes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Little	B-place
St.	I-place
Bartholomew	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
Obed	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
his	O
Wife	O
not	O
guilty	O
;	O
but	O
Grevil	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Benton	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Benton	O
:	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Grevil	O
:	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charity	B-pers
Parrot	I-pers
and	O
Margery	B-pers
Garret	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Sackvill	B-pers
Erbery	I-pers
,	O
five	O
pints	O
of	O
Canary	O
Wine	O
,	O
four	O
pounds	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Pewter-plates	O
and	O
Napkins	O
,	O
and	O
seven	O
pound	O
of	O
Candles	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
The	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
having	O
considered	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Metcalfe	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Stubberfled	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
Ware-house	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Easterne	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Ward	I-place
of	I-place
Farringdon	I-place
without	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
Nine	O
and	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
one	O
Pistol	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Silk	O
Scarf	O
,	O
two	O
Shifts	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Blew-Frock	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Trial	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Tiles	O
were	O
broken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Boy	O
that	O
was	O
got	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
handed	O
the	O
goods	O
to	O
Metcalfe	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
a	O
Ladder	O
bringing	O
the	O
Goods	O
down	O
;	O
and	O
search	O
being	O
made	O
,	O
Hudson	O
and	O
Stubberfield	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
would	O
help	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Goods	O
again	O
that	O
was	O
their	O
share	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
against	O
Hudson	O
and	O
Stubberfield	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Metcalfe	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Parthenia	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Petty-Treason	O
,	O
in	O
assaulting	O
of	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
George	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Sixth	O
Year	O
of	O
King	O
William	O
and	O
Queen	O
Mary	O
,	O
by	O
biting	O
,	O
bruising	O
,	O
and	O
dislocating	O
the	O
first	O
Joynt	O
on	O
the	O
middle	O
Finger	O
of	O
his	O
Right	O
Hand	O
,	O
which	O
swelled	O
afterwards	O
to	O
his	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
languished	O
until	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
April	O
following	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
She	O
alledged	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
happened	O
some	O
Words	O
between	O
her	O
and	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
liking	O
to	O
fall	O
to	O
Blows	O
,	O
she	O
by	O
accident	O
got	O
his	O
Finger	O
into	O
her	O
Mouth	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
bite	O
him	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
Evidence	O
which	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Husband	O
spoke	O
well	O
of	O
his	O
Wife	O
when	O
he	O
languished	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
nursed	O
him	O
very	O
kindly	O
during	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
So	O
the	O
Jury	O
having	O
considered	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Goodall	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Exeter	I-pers
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Catherine	B-place
Coleman-street	I-place
,	O
one	O
Necklace	O
of	O
Pearl	O
,	O
one	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
five	O
Silver	O
Porringers	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
to	O
considerable	O
value	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
of	O
London	O
,	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
with	O
one	O
other	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Hull	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
's	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
;	O
and	O
whilst	O
Mr	O
.	O
Hull	O
was	O
busy	O
with	O
other	O
Company	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
opportunity	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Tankard	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
several	O
Persons	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
drinking	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
at	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Bailey	O
's	O
in	O
Mutton-lane	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
having	O
considered	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Gillet	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
in	O
stamping	O
and	O
making	O
several	O
false	O
pieces	O
of	O
Coyn	O
of	O
Copper	O
,	O
Brass	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
mixt	O
Metals	O
,	O
(	O
that	O
is	O
to	O
say	O
)	O
twenty	O
pieces	O
called	O
Shillings	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
April	O
in	O
the	O
Seventh	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
very	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
did	O
see	O
him	O
Stamp	O
several	O
pieces	O
in	O
his	O
Shed	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
several	O
Stamps	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Clippings	O
in	O
a	O
Water-trough	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
pieces	O
of	O
stampt	O
and	O
unstampt	O
Metal	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
but	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
on	O
his	O
behalf	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
in	O
clipping	O
and	O
diminishing	O
of	O
twenty	O
pieces	O
of	O
Silver	O
of	O
Lawful	O
Coyn	O
of	O
this	O
Realm	O
,	O
(	O
that	O
is	O
to	O
say	O
)	O
twenty	O
pieces	O
of	O
Silver	O
called	O
Shillings	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
said	O
24th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
likewise	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susan	B-pers
Reddal	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Dutton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Quilo	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Portuguese	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Leather	O
Purse	O
,	O
value	O
4d	O
.	O
eight	O
pieces	O
of	O
coyned	O
Gold	O
,	O
called	O
Guineas	O
,	O
8l	O
.	O
12s	O
.	O
five	O
pieces	O
of	O
Eight	O
,	O
23s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
a	O
Portugal	O
piece	O
of	O
Silver	O
,	O
6d	O
.	O
and	O
22s	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
numbred	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Quilo	O
going	O
along	O
Rosemary-Lane	B-place
,	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
she	O
consenting	O
thereto	O
,	O
and	O
Quilo	O
spent	O
2s	O
.	O
in	O
Meat	O
and	O
Drink	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
observing	O
where	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
advantage	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
alledged	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
That	O
Quilo	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
fain	O
have	O
been	O
naught	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
having	O
considered	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Elinor	B-pers
Twisell	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Twisell	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
in	O
clipping	O
and	O
diminishing	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coyn	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
past	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
(	O
that	O
is	O
to	O
say	O
)	O
twenty	O
pieces	O
of	O
Silver	O
Coyn	O
,	O
called	O
Half-Crowns	O
,	O
and	O
twenty	O
of	O
his	O
pieces	O
of	O
Silver	O
,	O
called	O
Shillings	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
coming	O
to	O
search	O
,	O
found	O
between	O
the	O
Mat	O
and	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
Shears	O
,	O
two	O
Files	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
rubbing	O
Cloath	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Clippings	O
,	O
with	O
one	O
Half-Crown	O
clipt	O
three	O
parts	O
about	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
alledged	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
or	O
how	O
the	O
things	O
came	O
there	O
.	O
She	O
brought	O
several	O
People	O
to	O
speak	O
on	O
her	O
behalf	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
a	O
very	O
favourable	O
Account	O
of	O
her	O
Life	O
and	O
Conversation	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
poor	O
Woman	O
,	O
that	O
did	O
take	O
great	O
pains	O
for	O
her	O
Livelihood	O
.	O
So	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Seventh	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
one	O
Muslin	O
Cornet	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Gause-head	O
,	O
laced	O
with	O
Flanders	O
Lace	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
one	O
Jane	B-pers
Josser	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Rine	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
Mary	I-place
Mington	I-place
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Stone-Horse	O
,	O
coloured	O
Black	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
7l	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Seventh	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
Kings	O
Reign	O
,	O
from	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
.	O
It	O
being	O
within	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
Act	O
of	O
Indemnity	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Granger	I-pers
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Silk	O
Purse	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
7s	O
.	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
broad	O
Gold	O
,	O
2l	O
.	O
6s	O
.	O
and	O
one	O
0s	O
.	O
piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
money	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Fuller	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
the	O
Prosecuter	O
's	O
Wife	O
said	O
,	O
She	O
having	O
an	O
occasion	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
about	O
some	O
business	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
into	O
her	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Keys	O
of	O
her	O
Chamber	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
not	O
sufficient	O
to	O
find	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
them	O
both	O
in	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Giles	B-pers
Loverane	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
and	O
robbing	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
between	O
Mile	O
end	O
and	O
Stratford	O
,	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
1694	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Mare	O
,	O
value	O
4l	O
.	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
1d	O
.	O
And	O
36l	O
.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
besides	O
thirty	O
or	O
fourty	O
Ounces	O
of	O
molten	O
Silver	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ambrose	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
of	O
Westham	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Essex	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
alledged	O
,	O
That	O
one	O
Jenkins	O
and	O
he	O
drinking	O
together	O
,	O
Jenkins	O
told	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
might	O
take	O
a	O
Clipper	O
that	O
would	O
come	O
to	O
London	O
on	O
a	O
little	O
Mare	O
from	O
Westham	O
,	O
with	O
Clippings	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
other	O
Person	O
,	O
accordingly	O
went	O
and	O
met	O
Powell	O
near	O
Stratford	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
How	O
now	O
John	O
?	O
And	O
searching	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
found	O
36l	O
.	O
of	O
Counterfeit	O
money	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
a	O
Constable	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Powell	O
made	O
his	O
Escape	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Anderson	O
and	O
Smith	O
would	O
have	O
stifled	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
discharged	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Terry	I-pers
,	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Moulton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Seventh	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
Eleven	O
and	O
Twelve	O
at	O
Night	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
rob	O
Mr.	O
Moulton	O
.	O
Moore	O
's	O
Wife	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
corrupt	O
the	O
Maid	O
,	O
and	O
promised	O
her	O
a	O
Share	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
open	O
her	O
Master	O
's	O
Doors	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
them	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
Moore	O
's	O
Wife	O
had	O
provided	O
a	O
sleepy	O
potion	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
given	O
to	O
Moulton	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
if	O
they	O
called	O
for	O
any	O
Drink	O
at	O
their	O
Supper	O
,	O
the	O
Maid	O
acquainted	O
her	O
Master	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
provided	O
several	O
Persons	O
to	O
take	O
and	O
apprehend	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
accordingly	O
did	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
they	O
not	O
having	O
time	O
to	O
do	O
mischief	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
forced	O
a	O
Hatch	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Chisel	O
found	O
upon	O
Moore	O
,	O
and	O
Strings	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
to	O
bind	O
Moulton	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
had	O
but	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
themselves	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
which	O
gave	O
but	O
a	O
slender	O
Account	O
of	O
their	O
Lives	O
and	O
Conversations	O
.	O
William	O
Moore	O
,	O
John	O
Shaw	O
,	O
and	O
John	O
Terry	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Christopher	B-pers
Billop	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Billop	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Forgery	O
,	O
by	O
forging	O
one	O
Ticket	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Letter	O
of	O
Attorney	O
,	O
dated	O
the	O
Nineteenth	O
of	O
November	O
1692	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
King	O
in	O
Darby	B-place
Court	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Channel-Row	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
one	O
John	O
Sympson	O
,	O
aged	O
about	O
Sixty	O
Years	O
;	O
who	O
served	O
in	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
Ship	O
,	O
Suffolk	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
First	O
Day	O
of	O
April	O
1691	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Thirteenth	O
of	O
June	O
1692	O
;	O
and	O
stopt	O
the	O
Moneys	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
cheat	O
and	O
defraud	O
His	O
Majesty	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Pay	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
such	O
Person	O
as	O
John	O
Sympson	O
as	O
was	O
alledged	O
by	O
one	O
Richard	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
who	O
swore	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
see	O
the	O
Captain	O
,	O
Christopher	O
Billop	O
,	O
sign	O
the	O
Letter	O
of	O
Attorney	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Sympson	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
see	O
Thomas	O
Billop	O
seal	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
witnessed	O
by	O
Christopher	O
Billop	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Benton	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
;	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Bedford	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Captain	O
's	O
Boy	O
,	O
swore	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
effect	O
.	O
Williams	O
being	O
a	O
Baliff	O
's	O
Follower	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
a	O
great	O
Reputation	O
sufficient	O
to	O
charge	O
so	O
worthy	O
a	O
Person	O
as	O
Captain	O
Billop	O
with	O
so	O
base	O
a	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Captain	O
called	O
some	O
Noble	O
Peers	O
of	O
the	O
Realm	O
to	O
Speak	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
besides	O
several	O
Merchants	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
Credit	O
and	O
Reputation	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
having	O
considered	O
of	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Fenn	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Ley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Alhallows	O
Barking	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Ward	O
of	O
the	O
Tower	O
,	O
London	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Fifth	O
Day	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Seventh	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
Ley	O
came	O
amongst	O
the	O
Trained	O
Bands	O
on	O
Tower-Hill	B-place
,	O
and	O
jesting	O
amongst	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pushed	O
him	O
down	O
the	O
Hill	O
;	O
Ley	O
falling	O
,	O
broke	O
his	O
right	O
Leg	O
in	O
two	O
several	O
places	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
Eighth	O
following	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
he	O
died	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
no	O
Malice	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Major	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Robbery	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
Ralph	B-pers
Harwood	I-pers
between	O
the	O
Hours	O
of	O
Nine	O
and	O
ten	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Twelfth	O
Day	O
of	O
September	O
in	O
the	O
Fifth	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
Late	O
Queen	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
one	O
Cane	O
value	O
Ten	O
Shillings	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Gold	O
Buttons	O
value	O
Twenty	O
five	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
Five	O
and	O
twenty	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Silver	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
one	O
Fri	O
ley	O
who	O
gave	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
other	O
Felonies	O
and	O
Burglaries	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Manning	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
Thirteenth	O
day	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Seventh	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
reign	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Blankets	O
value	O
Twenty	O
Shillings	O
,	O
one	O
Calico	O
Quilt	O
lined	O
with	O
Silk	O
value	O
,	O
Forty	O
Shillings	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
besides	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
.	O
Mrs	O
Rose	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
home	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
write	O
a	O
Letter	O
in	O
his	O
Chamber	O
;	O
came	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
pretending	O
that	O
he	O
stumbled	O
,	O
and	O
goes	O
out	O
with	O
his	O
pretended	O
Letter	O
,	O
but	O
comes	O
back	O
again	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
desires	O
his	O
Landlady	O
to	O
fetch	O
him	O
some	O
of	O
her	O
Beer	O
,	O
And	O
whilst	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
his	O
way	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Tethrington	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Amey	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.Leonard	B-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Robbery	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
committed	O
on	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Garrett	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Infant	O
of	O
the	O
Age	O
of	O
Six	O
Years	O
and	O
Daughter	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Garrett	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Twenty	O
seventh	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Seventh	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
her	O
one	O
Woosted	O
Damask	O
Child	O
's	O
Coat	O
value	O
Six	O
Shillings	O
,	O
one	O
Child	O
's	O
Holland	O
Cap	O
value	O
Two	O
Pence	O
,	O
Tetherington	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
,	O
and	O
Brown	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Dimmott	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
Harbouring	O
and	O
Abetting	O
one	O
William	B-pers
York	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Newell	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Edge	I-pers
,	O
who	O
broke	O
the	O
Spanish	O
Ambassadors	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
also	O
for	O
making	O
and	O
Procuring	O
an	O
Iron	O
Instrument	O
called	O
a	O
Betty	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
bespoke	O
by	O
one	O
Stephens	O
.	O
Stephens	O
met	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Green	O
Dragon	O
at	O
Bridewell	O
Ditch	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
drink	O
;	O
so	O
they	O
agreed	O
together	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
to	O
bring	O
it	O
into	O
Breadstreet	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Stephens	O
goes	O
and	O
acquaints	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Cooper	O
,	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
such	O
a	O
time	O
a	O
Person	O
would	O
come	O
by	O
with	O
a	O
Betty	O
;	O
the	O
Constable	O
sets	O
out	O
his	O
Watch-men	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Betty	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
artificially	O
dropped	O
in	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
as	O
accessory	O
before	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Catherine	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
and	O
Anne	B-pers
Benton	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Stephen	B-pers
Stretch	I-pers
,	O
one	O
Canvas	O
bag	O
,	O
and	O
11l	O
.	O
in	O
money	O
numbred	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
day	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Seventh	O
year	O
of	O
his	O
Majesties	O
Reign	O
;	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
Burton	O
and	O
Benton	O
came	O
both	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
to	O
pawn	O
a	O
Coat	O
for	O
2s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
and	O
seeing	O
where	O
he	O
laid	O
his	O
money	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
to	O
change	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
as	O
Mr	O
.	O
Stretch	O
alledged	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
not	O
sufficient	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
6l	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
day	O
of	O
April	O
in	O
the	O
Seventh	O
year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Reign	O
,	O
from	O
Joseph	B-pers
Horton	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
's	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confessed	O
she	O
took	O
off	O
of	O
a	O
Table	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Horton	O
's	O
Kitchen	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Martha	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
day	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Seventh	O
year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Reign	O
,	O
one	O
Laced	O
Tippet	O
,	O
value	O
30s	O
.	O
one	O
silk	O
Petty	O
coat	O
;	O
2l	O
.	O
with	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
value	O
,	O
from	O
Anthony	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
Clerk	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Hill	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
brought	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
into	O
his	O
house	O
about	O
Seven	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
hid	O
him	O
under	O
his	O
best	O
bed	O
;	O
and	O
several	O
things	O
being	O
removed	O
from	O
their	O
places	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
Chimney-Corner	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
last	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
speaking	O
Treasonable	O
words	O
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
one	O
Abraham	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Soldier	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
in	O
drink	O
;	O
so	O
in	O
the	O
end	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Ward	I-place
of	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
Without	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
a	O
sable	O
Tippet	O
from	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Ryland	I-pers
Wife	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Ryland	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
day	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Seventh	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Reign	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
between	O
Leighton	O
and	O
Stratford	O
;	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Constable	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Tippet	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
very	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Arrowsmith	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Tried	O
for	O
Felony	O
,	O
in	O
stealing	O
the	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Newell	I-pers
,	O
value	O
7l	O
.	O
10s	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
.	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
6th	O
year	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
Queen	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Field	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Bowman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Drugget	O
Curtain	O
,	O
value	O
3s	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Horne	I-pers
;	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
likewise	O
Indicted	O
upon	O
a	O
Second	O
Indictment	O
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bed	O
Tick	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
said	O
2d	O
.	O
day	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
B	B-pers
-	I-pers
W	I-pers
-	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michaels	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
7th	O
year	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
did	O
procure	O
Broad	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
unlawful	O
gain	O
and	O
lucre	O
to	O
himself	O
,	O
got	O
into	O
his	O
hands	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
1000l	O
.	O
of	O
Broad	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
means	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Mark	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
,	O
procured	O
a	O
Correspondence	O
with	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
of	O
Chester	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
allow	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Simpson	O
2l	O
.	O
per	O
Cent	O
.	O
for	O
Broad	O
money	O
,	O
(	O
excepting	O
New	O
money	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
not	O
fit	O
for	O
his	O
payments	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
Council	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
alledged	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
Correspondence	O
had	O
been	O
held	O
from	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
1694.	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
there	O
had	O
several	O
Letters	O
passed	O
from	O
Mr.	O
B	O
-	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Simpson	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Simpson	O
believed	O
upon	O
his	O
Oath	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Letters	O
came	O
from	O
Mr.	O
B	O
-	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
above	O
40l	O
.	O
for	O
Commission-money	O
.	O
Mr.	O
B	O
-	O
alledged	O
that	O
the	O
Broad	O
money	O
was	O
for	O
payment	O
of	O
some	O
Dutch	O
Soldiers	O
in	O
Flanders	O
,	O
and	O
whereby	O
he	O
could	O
make	O
an	O
Advance	O
:	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
eminent	O
Citizens	O
that	O
gave	O
a	O
fair	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
credible	O
Life	O
and	O
Conversation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
having	O
considered	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
notwithstanding	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
H	B-pers
-	I-pers
W	I-pers
-	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Yeoman	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
procuring	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
50l	O
.	O
of	O
Broad	O
money	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
make	O
unlawful	O
Gain	O
thereof	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
Jan.	O
last	O
.	O
And	O
it	O
being	O
proved	O
that	O
he	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
7l	O
.	O
10s	O
.	O
profit	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
L	B-pers
-	I-pers
W	I-pers
-	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
in	O
procuring	O
Broad	O
money	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
make	O
an	O
unlawful	O
Gain	O
thereof	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
for	O
every	O
100l	O
.	O
he	O
should	O
receive	O
15l	O
.	O
over	O
and	O
above	O
the	O
100l	O
.	O
the	O
Tryal	O
lasted	O
long	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
made	O
it	O
plainly	O
appear	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Hardy	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Pierceson	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pierceson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
procuring	O
,	O
and	O
causing	O
to	O
be	O
procured	O
,	O
a	O
Letter	O
of	O
Attorney	O
from	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Hardy	I-pers
,	O
late	O
belonging	O
to	O
Their	O
Majesties	O
Ship	O
the	O
Bredah	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
Letter	O
of	O
Administration	O
out	O
of	O
Doctors	O
Commons	O
as	O
Sister	O
and	O
nearest	O
of	O
Kin	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
Hardey	O
,	O
entitling	O
herself	O
to	O
the	O
pay	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
Hardey	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
positively	O
proved	O
against	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Muttleberry	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
demiseing	O
a	O
Celler	O
to	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Dover	I-pers
a	O
Printer	O
,	O
without	O
giving	O
notice	O
thereof	O
first	O
to	O
the	O
Master	O
and	O
Wardens	O
of	O
the	O
Company	O
of	O
Stationers	O
,	O
London	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Statute	O
in	O
that	O
Case	O
made	O
and	O
provided	O
;	O
which	O
Dover	O
did	O
set	O
up	O
a	O
Printing-Press	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Celler	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Wife	O
did	O
let	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
called	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
a	O
good	O
account	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joyce	B-pers
Pawling	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Pawling	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Christ-Church	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
in	O
Clipping	O
and	O
Diminishing	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
One	O
and	O
twentieth	O
day	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
seventh	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
with	O
Shears	O
and	O
other	O
Iron	O
Instruments	O
did	O
clip	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
twenty	O
pieces	O
of	O
Silver	O
called	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
twenty	O
other	O
pieces	O
of	O
Silver	O
called	O
Six-pences	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
declared	O
that	O
a	O
little	O
Girl	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
Clippings	O
at	O
Pawling	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
the	O
Constable	O
accordingly	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Clippings	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
Drawer	O
over	O
the	O
Bed's-tester	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
declared	O
she	O
knew	O
not	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
there	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
intending	O
unlawful	O
Gain	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
unjust	O
Lucre	O
and	O
Profit	O
in	O
procuring	O
Broad	O
money	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
intent	O
the	O
same	O
should	O
be	O
Clipt	O
and	O
diminished	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
a	O
long	O
Debate	O
between	O
the	O
Councils	O
,	O
on	O
either	O
side	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
was	O
also	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Offence	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
found	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
S	B-pers
-	I-pers
T	I-pers
-	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
procuring	O
and	O
buying	O
of	O
Broad	O
money	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
make	O
an	O
unlawful	O
Gain	O
thereof	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
for	O
every	O
hundred	O
pounds	O
of	O
Broad	O
money	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
Bills	O
for	O
one	O
hundred	O
twenty	O
two	O
pounds	O
and	O
ten	O
Shillings	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
hundred	O
pounds	O
of	O
Broad	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
hundred	O
twenty	O
five	O
pounds	O
in	O
Narrow	O
money	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
King	O
's	O
Evidence	O
was	O
very	O
positive	O
to	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
having	O
considered	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
C	B-pers
-	I-pers
E	I-pers
-	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Farendine	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
laced	O
Petticoat	O
with	O
a	O
silver	O
Fringe	O
,	O
a	O
long	O
Scarf	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
value	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
one	O
Henry	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolphs	I-place
Bishop'sgate	I-place
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
alledged	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
and	O
she	O
kept	O
the	O
Taphouse	O
at	O
the	O
Bull	O
and	O
Mouth	O
Inn	O
by	O
Aldergate-street	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Women	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
Worcestershire	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
left	O
the	O
Petticoat	O
for	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
was	O
hers	O
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Tooley	I-pers
was	O
arraigned	O
upon	O
an	O
Indictment	O
for	O
Murder	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
tried	O
the	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
pronounce	O
Sentence	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
11	O
.	O
Edward	O
White	O
Mary	O
Bennet	O
John	O
Cole	O
Elizabeth	O
Harris	O
James	O
Gillet	O
William	O
Moore	O
John	O
Shaw	O
John	O
Terry	O
Peter	O
Major	O
Elizabeth	O
Tetherington	O
William	O
Wake	O
alias	O
Dimmot	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
12	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Field	O
alias	O
Bowman	O
Richard	O
Arrowsmith	O
Thomas	O
Norman	O
Mary	O
Vaughan	O
Ann	O
Chapman	O
Obed	O
Benton	O
John	O
Metcalfe	O
Elizabeth	O
Goodall	O
alias	O
Exeter	O
Jane	O
Granger	O
Ann	O
Cox	O
George	O
Manning	O
Sarah	O
Austin	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
.	O
Hannah	O
Griffell	O
Ann	O
Hardy	O
fined	O
20l	O
.	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
upon	O
the	O
Pillory	O
at	O
the	O
Navy	O
Office	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
Security	O
for	O
her	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
.	O
John	O
Muttleberry	O
fined	O
5l	O
.	O
and	O
Security	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
.	O
B	O
-	O
W	O
-	O
fined	O
1000l	O
.	O
and	O
to	O
give	O
Security	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
for	O
a	O
Twelvemonth	O
.	O
H	O
-	O
W	O
-	O
fined	O
100	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
remain	O
in	O
Custody	O
till	O
he	O
pay	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
L	O
-	O
W	O
-	O
fined	O
200	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
find	O
Sureties	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
behaviour	O
for	O
a	O
Twelvemonth	O
.	O
S	O
-	O
T	O
-	O
fined	O
1000l	O
.	O
and	O
to	O
remain	O
in	O
Prison	O
till	O
he	O
pays	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
find	O
Sureties	O
for	O
a	O
Twelve	O
month	O
.	O
Ordered	O
into	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Service	O
Richard	O
Arrowsmith	O
Thomas	O
Norman	O
Obed	O
Benton	O
John	O
Metcalfe	O
George	O
Manning	O
Books	O
Printed	O
for	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
Thomas	O
Cockerill	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Legs	O
in	O
the	O
Poultrey	O
,	O
over-against	O
the	O
Stocks-Market	O
.	O
A	O
Free	O
Discourse	O
against	O
Customary	O
Swearing	O
,	O
And	O
a	O
Dissuasive	O
from	O
Cursing	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
late	O
Honourable	O
Robert	O
Hoyle	O
.	O
Published	O
by	O
John	O
Williams	O
,	O
D.D	O
.	O
8	O
vo	O
.	O
Sermons	O
preached	O
on	O
several	O
Occasions	O
.	O
By	O
John	O
Conant	O
,	O
D.D	O
.	O
Geography	O
Rectified	O
;	O
or	O
a	O
Description	O
of	O
the	O
World	O
in	O
all	O
its	O
Kingdoms	O
Provinces	O
,	O
Countries	O
,	O
Island	O
,	O
Cites	O
,	O
Towns	O
,	O
Seas	O
,	O
Rivers	O
,	O
Bays	O
,	O
Capes	O
,	O
Ports	O
,	O
Inhabitants	O
,	O
Scituations	O
,	O
Customs	O
,	O
Commodities	O
,	O
Government	O
.	O
Illustrated	O
with	O
about	O
80	O
maps	O
.	O
Third	O
Edition	O
.	O
By	O
Robert	O
Morden	O
.	O
4	O
to	O
.	O
A	O
demonstration	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
Principles	O
of	O
the	O
Protestant	O
Applications	O
of	O
the	O
Apocalypse	O
.	O
By	O
Drue	O
Cressener	O
,	O
D.	O
D.	O
4to	O
.	O
Conformity	O
of	O
the	O
Ecclesiastical	O
Discipline	O
of	O
the	O
Reform	O
'd	O
Churches	O
of	O
France	O
with	O
that	O
of	O
the	O
Primitive	O
Christians	O
.	O
By	O
M.	O
Laroque	O
.	O
4to	O
.	O
A	O
Practical	O
Grammar	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
The	O
earnest	O
and	O
Shortest	O
was	O
to	O
Initiate	O
Young	O
Children	O
in	O
the	O
Latine	O
Tongue	O
.	O
8	O
vo	O
.	O
Geography	O
Anatomiz	O
'd	O
;	O
Or	O
a	O
compleat	O
Geographical	O
Grammar	O
;	O
being	O
a	O
short	O
and	O
exact	O
Analysis	O
of	O
the	O
whole	O
Body	O
of	O
Modern	O
Geography	O
,	O
after	O
a	O
new	O
,	O
plain	O
and	O
easy	O
method	O
;	O
whereby	O
any	O
person	O
may	O
in	O
a	O
short	O
time	O
attain	O
to	O
the	O
knowledge	O
of	O
that	O
most	O
noble	O
and	O
useful	O
Science	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
To	O
which	O
subjoined	O
the	O
present	O
state	O
of	O
the	O
European	O
Plantations	O
in	O
the	O
East	O
and	O
West-Indies	O
;	O
with	O
a	O
reasonable	O
Proposal	O
for	O
the	O
Propagation	O
of	O
the	O
blessed	O
Gospel	O
in	O
all	O
Pagan	O
Countries	O
.	O
Illustrated	O
with	O
divers	O
Maps	O
.	O
By	O
Patrick	O
Gordon	O
,	O
M.	O
A	O
.	O
Philosophical	O
Discourses	O
of	O
the	O
Soul	O
and	O
State	O
of	O
Man	O
after	O
Death	O
.	O
By	O
Moses	O
Amyraldus	O
.	O
A	O
Discourse	O
of	O
Schism	O
.	O
By	O
Edward	O
Polhill	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Essays	O
on	O
Trade	O
and	O
Navigation	O
.	O
By	O
Sir	O
Francis	B-pers
Brewster	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
8vo	O
.	O
The	O
Future	O
State	O
:	O
A	O
Discourse	O
attempting	O
some	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
of	O
the	O
Soul	O
's	O
Happiness	O
,	O
in	O
regard	O
to	O
that	O
Eternally	O
Progressive	O
knowledge	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
which	O
is	O
among	O
the	O
Blessed	O
in	O
Heaven	O
.	O
By	O
a	O
Country	O
Gentleman	O
.	O
The	O
Reasonableness	O
of	O
Personal	O
Reformation	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Necessity	O
of	O
Conversion	O
.	O
The	O
true	O
Method	O
of	O
making	O
all	O
men	O
happy	O
in	O
this	O
World	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
which	O
is	O
to	O
come	O
.	O
By	O
H.	O
H.	O
English	O
Exercises	O
for	O
Schoolboys	O
to	O
Translate	O
into	O
Latin	O
comprizing	O
all	O
the	O
Rules	O
of	O
Grammar	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
necessary	O
Observations	O
.	O
By	O
J.	O
Garretson	O
,	O
Schoolmaster	O
.	O
The	O
Life	O
and	O
Death	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Nathaniel	O
Husband	O
,	O
minister	O
of	O
Ormskirk	O
in	O
Lancashire	O
.	O
Who	O
died	O
in	O
the	O
58th	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
Age	O
.	O
Dedicated	O
to	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Hugh	O
Lord	O
Willoughby	O
by	O
Sir	O
H.	O
Ashurst	O
.	O
The	O
Almost	O
Christian	O
discovered	O
,	O
in	O
some	O
Sermon	O
on	O
Acts	O
26	O
.	O
28	O
.	O
With	O
a	O
Blow	O
at	O
Prophaneness	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
Right	O
Reverend	O
Ezekiel	O
Hopkins	O
,	O
late	O
Lord	O
Bishop	O
of	O
Londonderry	O
.	O
A	O
work	O
of	O
Solliloquies	O
and	O
Prayers	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
the	O
Holy	O
Communion	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
By	O
Peter	O
Du	O
Moulin	O
.	O
A	O
Dialogue	O
between	O
a	O
Popish	O
Priest	O
and	O
an	O
English	O
Protestant	O
.	O
Wherein	O
the	O
Principal	O
Points	O
of	O
both	O
Religions	O
are	O
truly	O
proposed	O
and	O
examined	O
.	O
By	O
Matthew	O
Pool	O
.	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
Synopsis	O
Criticorum	O
.	O
A	O
Short	O
Introduction	O
to	O
English	O
Orthography	O
and	O
Method	O
of	O
True	O
Spelling	O
.	O
By	O
Richard	O
Mather	O
.	O
Familiar	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
Christopheri	O
H	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
seris	O
Gressensis	O
olim	O
ex	O
Erasmo	O
Roterodamo	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Whereas	O
Proposals	O
have	O
been	O
formerly	O
made	O
for	O
the	O
Reprinting	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Matthew	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
the	O
Holy	O
Bible	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
Review	O
'd	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Daniel	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
and	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
with	O
the	O
Addition	O
of	O
a	O
Concordance	O
and	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
Contents	O
before	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
Chapter	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original.	O
]	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
the	O
Press	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Subscribers	O
are	O
asked	O
to	O
send	O
their	O
Subscription	O
by	O
the	O
25th	O
.	O
of	O
June	O
next	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
Time	O
the	O
Undertakers	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
obliged	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
Allowance	O
of	O
the	O
Seventh	O
Book	O
.	O
The	O
Undertakers	O
are	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Parkhurst	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cockerill	I-pers
,	O
Brabazon	B-pers
Aylmer	I-pers
,	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
Books	O
Printed	O
for	O
Richard	O
Baldwin	O
.	O
A	O
Letter	O
to	O
a	O
Member	O
of	O
Parliament	O
,	O
occasioned	O
by	O
the	O
Votes	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Commons	O
against	O
their	O
late	O
Speaker	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
.	O
A	O
Brief	O
Enquiry	O
into	O
the	O
Antient	O
Constitution	O
and	O
Government	O
of	O
England	O
.	O
As	O
well	O
in	O
respect	O
of	O
the	O
Administration	O
,	O
as	O
Succession	O
thereof	O
.	O
Set	O
forth	O
by	O
way	O
of	O
Dialogue	O
,	O
and	O
fitted	O
for	O
men	O
of	O
ordinary	O
Learning	O
and	O
Capacity	O
.	O
By	O
a	O
true	O
Lover	O
of	O
this	O
Country	O
.	O
The	O
Remarkable	O
Sayings	O
,	O
Apothegms	O
and	O
Maxims	O
of	O
the	O
Eastern	O
Nations	O
;	O
Abstracted	O
and	O
translated	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
Books	O
,	O
written	O
in	O
the	O
Arabian	O
,	O
Persian	O
and	O
Turkish	O
Language	O
;	O
With	O
Remarks	O
.	O
By	O
Monsieur	O
Galland	O
,	O
who	O
liv	O
'd	O
many	O
years	O
in	O
those	O
Countries	O
.	O
Translated	O
out	O
of	O
French	O
.	O
A	O
New	O
and	O
Easy	O
Method	O
to	O
understand	O
the	O
Roman	O
History	O
.	O
With	O
an	O
Exact	O
Chronology	O
of	O
the	O
Reign	O
of	O
the	O
Emperors	O
;	O
An	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
Eminent	O
Authors	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
flourish	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
an	O
Abridgment	O
of	O
the	O
Roman	O
Antiquities	O
and	O
Customs	O
.	O
By	O
way	O
of	O
Dialogue	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Use	O
of	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Burgundy	O
.	O
Done	O
out	O
of	O
French	O
,	O
with	O
very	O
large	O
Additions	O
and	O
Amendments	O
,	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Tho	O
.	O
Brown	O
.	O
The	O
French	O
King	O
's	O
Declaration	O
for	O
settling	O
the	O
general	O
Poll-Tax	O
:	O
Together	O
with	O
his	O
Edict	O
,	O
ordering	O
all	O
Communities	O
,	O
both	O
Regular	O
and	O
Secular	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
particular	O
Persons	O
(	O
who	O
have	O
any	O
Water	O
from	O
Rivers	O
,	O
Brooks	O
,	O
Springs	O
,	O
and	O
Fountains	O
,	O
or	O
otherwise	O
,	O
whether	O
for	O
the	O
Ornament	O
of	O
their	O
Houses	O
,	O
or	O
Improving	O
of	O
their	O
Estates	O
)	O
to	O
pay	O
such	O
Sums	O
as	O
shall	O
be	O
impos	O
'd	O
upon	O
them	O
in	O
Council	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Waters	O
confirmed	O
to	O
them	O
for	O
the	O
future	O
.	O
Given	O
at	O
Fountainbleau	O
,	O
Octob	O
.	O
1694.	O
and	O
Recorded	O
in	O
Parliament	O
.	O
The	O
Works	O
of	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
Rabelais	O
,	O
M.	O
D.	O
in	O
five	O
Books	O
:	O
Or	O
the	O
Lives	O
,	O
H	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
Deeds	O
and	O
Sayings	O
of	O
the	O
good	O
Gargantua	O
and	O
Pantagrua	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Voyage	O
to	O
the	O
Oracle	O
of	O
the	O
Bottle	O
.	O
As	O
also	O
his	O
Historical	O
Letters	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
the	O
Author	O
's	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
Explanatory	O
Remarks	O
.	O
By	O
Mr.	O
Motteux	O
.	O
Never	O
before	O
Printed	O
in	O
English	O
These	O
are	O
to	O
give	O
Notice	O
to	O
ill	O
persons	O
for	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
the	O
Publick	O
,	O
That	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
Professor	O
of	O
Physick	O
,	O
and	O
Operator	O
,	O
of	O
known	O
Integrity	O
,	O
and	O
above	O
25	O
years	O
Practice	O
,	O
liveth	O
at	O
the	O
Blew	O
Ball	O
in	O
Whalebone	O
Court	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Lower	O
End	O
of	O
Bartholomew	O
Lane	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
:	O
Who	O
most	O
safely	O
and	O
expeditiously	O
Cures	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
of	O
what	O
Age	O
soever	O
(	O
if	O
Curable	O
)	O
and	O
at	O
first	O
sight	O
;	O
by	O
Inspection	O
Resolves	O
the	O
Patient	O
if	O
so	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
as	O
most	O
eminent	O
Persons	O
of	O
Quality	O
in	O
this	O
City	O
can	O
testify	O
.	O
He	O
hath	O
likewise	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Gargarism	O
or	O
mouth-wash	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
make	O
Black	O
or	O
Yellow	O
Teeth	O
as	O
White	O
as	O
Ivory	O
in	O
few	O
times	O
using	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
will	O
certainly	O
cure	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
Diseases	O
incident	O
to	O
the	O
mouth	O
,	O
Teeth	O
,	O
and	O
Gums	O
.	O
The	O
Glasses	O
are	O
of	O
several	O
Prices	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
.	O
That	O
you	O
may	O
not	O
mistake	O
,	O
my	O
House	O
is	O
at	O
the	O
Blew	O
Ball	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
;	O
you	O
may	O
see	O
it	O
as	O
you	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
THE	O
person	O
that	O
lately	O
lived	O
on	O
Ludgate	O
Hill	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
the	O
Kings	O
Arms	O
tavern	O
near	O
Fleetbridge	O
,	O
is	O
now	O
removed	O
into	O
Essex	O
Court	O
in	O
White	O
Fryars	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
Door	O
on	O
the	O
Left	O
hand	O
,	O
where	O
any	O
one	O
may	O
be	O
furnished	O
with	O
the	O
Water	O
for	O
taking	O
away	O
Freckles	O
,	O
Pimples	O
,	O
Warts	O
and	O
Morphew	O
in	O
Face	O
;	O
and	O
excellent	O
Water	O
and	O
Ointment	O
for	O
the	O
Eyes	O
,	O
Ointments	O
for	O
the	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
Burns	O
,	O
Scalds	O
,	O
Wounds	O
,	O
Aches	O
,	O
Sprains	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Powders	O
,	O
Dentrifices	O
,	O
Essence	O
,	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
,	O
Oyls	O
,	O
Spirits	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
for	O
the	O
easing	O
and	O
curing	O
of	O
Most	O
Discharges	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
to	O
Human	O
Bodies	O
,	O
prepared	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original.	O
]	O
.	O
The	O
Water	O
for	O
taking	O
away	O
the	O
Freckles	O
,	O
Pimples	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
is	O
also	O
sold	O
at	O
these	O
places	O
following	O
;	O
viz	O
.	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Mathers	O
in	O
Popes	O
Head	O
Alley	O
,	O
Camshop	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Hampton	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
the	O
Golden	O
Ball	O
in	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
.	O
Mrs	O
Hicks	O
Guilder	O
,	O
on	O
Ludgate-hill	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Fleetbridge	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Miners	O
Semstress	O
in	O
the	O
Inner	O
Temple	O
Lane	O
.	O
And	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
L	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
house	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Crown	O
in	O
Blew	O
Anchor	O
Alley	O
over	O
against	O
the	O
Artillery	O
Ground	O
on	O
Bunhil	O
.	O
To	O
prevent	O
mistakes	O
and	O
counterfeits	O
my	O
Bottles	O
will	O
be	O
Sealed	O
with	O
my	O
Coat	O
of	O
Arms	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
the	O
Three	O
Water	O
Bugets	O
and	O
Half-Moon	O
.	O
Doctor	O
Wheeler	O
,	O
being	O
of	O
Dean	O
's	O
Court	O
at	O
the	O
Hand	O
and	O
Urinal	O
,	O
new	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
between	O
Newgate-street	O
and	O
Aldersgate-street	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
le	O
Grand	O
,	O
hath	O
an	O
Infallible	O
Cure	O
for	O
the	O
Gout	O
and	O
Sciatica	O
,	O
and	O
Convulsion	O
Fits	O
,	O
and	O
Falling	O
Sickness	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
hath	O
never	O
undertaken	O
any	O
,	O
but	O
hath	O
perfectly	O
cured	O
them	O
,	O
as	O
can	O
be	O
testified	O
by	O
many	O
Persons	O
of	O
Quality	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
,	O
if	O
desired	O
,	O
cured	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
he	O
takes	O
this	O
way	O
of	O
Publishing	O
,	O
because	O
that	O
several	O
pretend	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
by	O
this	O
Mistakes	O
may	O
be	O
prevented	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
desired	O
to	O
take	O
good	O
notice	O
of	O
this	O
Doctor	O
's	O
Name	O
and	O
House	O
.	O
