TOKEN	NE
The	O
Proceedings	O
of	O
the	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
on	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-bayly	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
,	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
Wednesday	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
14th	O
,	O
15th	O
,	O
16th	O
and	O
18th	O
Days	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
1695	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
Seventh	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bayly	O
,	O
on	O
Monday	O
,	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
Wednesday	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
14th	O
,	O
15th	O
,	O
16th	O
and	O
18th	O
Days	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
1695.	O
before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
Salathiel	B-pers
Lovell	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
follow	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Stanley	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Villers	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Kimble	I-pers
,	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Spinlowe	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lawrance	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Joslin	I-pers
,	O
Jeremy	B-pers
Ives	I-pers
,	O
Andrew	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Banks	I-pers
,	O
Edmund	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Partridge	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Wylde	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Freebody	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dunke	I-pers
,	O
Anthony	B-pers
Nurse	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Friar	I-pers
,	O
Phillip	B-pers
Burgis	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Lacy	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Graves	I-pers
,	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Rufford	I-pers
,	O
Giles	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Steele	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Trials	O
are	O
as	O
follow	O
:	O
Katherine	B-pers
Buckingham	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Barber	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Barnet	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
17	O
yards	O
of	O
Flowered	O
Silk	O
from	O
Paul	B-pers
Clousley	I-pers
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
likewise	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
14	O
yards	O
of	O
Green	O
satin	O
Silk	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Cheshire	I-pers
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
likewise	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
likewise	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
30	O
yards	O
of	O
Silk	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Rider	I-pers
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
also	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
felony	O
in	O
stealing	O
one	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
val	O
6l	O
.	O
from	O
Mary	B-pers
Rennolds	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
day	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
:	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
some	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Tankard	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
with	O
it	O
under	O
his	O
Coat	O
;	O
and	O
search	O
was	O
made	O
after	O
him	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
produced	O
it	O
,	O
taking	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
some	O
Weeds	O
,	O
wherein	O
he	O
had	O
hid	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
Garden	O
near	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
House	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
alledged	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
use	O
to	O
frequent	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
drunk	O
there	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
drink	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
it	O
being	O
a	O
counted	O
but	O
a	O
frivolous	O
Excuse	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Frances	B-pers
Boddyman	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
murdering	O
of	O
her	O
Male	O
Bastard-child	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
throwing	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
;	O
it	O
appeared	O
upon	O
the	O
Trial	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
being	O
in	O
Bed	O
with	O
two	O
young	O
Women	O
,	O
five	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
she	O
complained	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
sat	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
for	O
a	O
considerable	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
pretended	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
got	O
down	O
she	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
out	O
,	O
which	O
caused	O
a	O
young	O
Woman	O
to	O
rise	O
and	O
go	O
down	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
just	O
got	O
down	O
,	O
she	O
heard	O
something	O
go	O
thump	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
,	O
which	O
caused	O
the	O
young	O
Woman	O
to	O
think	O
that	O
all	O
was	O
not	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
confessed	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
discover	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
make	O
away	O
with	O
her	O
self	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
alledged	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
a	O
month	O
before	O
her	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Child	O
being	O
found	O
dead	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
;	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
Prison	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
ashamed	O
of	O
her	O
wicked	O
Act	O
,	O
had	O
little	O
else	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Michael	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
and	O
Assaulting	O
one	O
Richard	B-pers
Cobb	I-pers
on	O
the	O
3d	O
day	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
Seven	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
in	O
an	O
Alley	B-place
near	I-place
Bearbinder-lane	I-place
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
Two	O
pence	O
three	O
farthings	O
in	O
moneys	O
numbred	O
;	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Cobb	O
going	O
to	O
go	O
through	O
the	O
Alley	O
,	O
there	O
stept	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
just	O
before	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Alley	O
and	O
turned	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
stopt	O
,	O
then	O
there	O
came	O
four	O
more	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
jostled	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
began	O
to	O
feel	O
about	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
struck	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Stick	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
,	O
Dam	O
ye	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
cry	O
out	O
?	O
Then	O
he	O
strugled	O
to	O
save	O
his	O
Silver	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
another	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
all	O
fell	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
beat	O
him	O
very	O
grievously	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
worthy	O
Gentleman	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
hearing	O
the	O
noise	O
,	O
the	O
Rogues	O
fled	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
Hall	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
lately	O
from	O
Sea	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
that	O
way	O
he	O
was	O
stopt	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
and	O
declared	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
willing	O
to	O
serve	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Chase	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Edmunds	I-place
the	I-place
King	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
50l	O
.	O
the	O
Monies	O
of	O
one	O
Richard	B-pers
Burman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
day	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Burman	O
sent	O
his	O
Servant	O
into	O
Lombard	O
street	O
to	O
receive	O
forescore	O
Pounds	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
told	O
out	O
50l	O
.	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
bag	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
by	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
lean	O
over	O
the	O
Stall	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
mist	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
several	O
Persons	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
frequent	O
the	O
Church	O
,	O
and	O
endeavoured	O
hard	O
to	O
maintain	O
his	O
Family	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
and	O
Cornelius	B-pers
Throft	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Wallis	I-pers
two	O
Pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Ballendine	O
Silk	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
day	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
Throft	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
his	O
Arraignment	O
,	O
but	O
Johnson	O
put	O
himself	O
upon	O
his	O
Trial	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
both	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
and	O
cheapened	O
some	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
Throft	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
reach	O
over	O
the	O
Compter	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Johnson	O
pretended	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
give	O
no	O
good	O
account	O
of	O
himself	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Cornelius	B-pers
Shaftsburgher	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Murthering	O
one	O
Stephen	B-pers
Higgens	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
with	O
a	O
Carbine	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
London	O
Bullet	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
then	O
and	O
there	O
discharge	O
the	O
same	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
near	O
to	O
the	O
right	O
Ear	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Stephen	O
Higgens	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Wound	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
six	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
Drinking	O
in	O
a	O
low	O
Room	O
in	O
New	B-place
Tuttle-street	I-place
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
little	O
Window	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Garret	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
shot	O
off	O
the	O
Carbine	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Deceased	O
fell	O
down	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
People	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
inquiring	O
who	O
shot	O
off	O
the	O
Piece	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
declared	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
he	O
that	O
did	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
hoped	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
no	O
harm	O
.	O
He	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
much	O
concerned	O
at	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Death	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Malice	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
the	O
man	O
before	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Scarlett	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonards	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Mary	B-pers
Warsdell	I-pers
Spinster	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Bodies	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
a	O
Holland	O
Apron	O
6d	O
.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
wosted	O
Stockings	O
4d	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
Yard	O
of	O
Ribon	O
2d	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appearing	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
missing	O
her	O
Goods	O
,	O
found	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Wifes	O
Legs	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
very	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
on	O
his	O
own	O
behalf	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mooney	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Bray	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
Blackfryars	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Walter	B-pers
Corbett	I-pers
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
Four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
one	O
Pewter	O
Dish	O
value	O
3s	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
heard	O
to	O
lock	O
and	O
unlock	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
wondring	O
what	O
should	O
be	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Bidgood	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
100	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Silver	O
Plate	O
,	O
and	O
50	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Silver	O
Thread	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Glynn	I-pers
Widow	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Gold	O
and	O
Silver-lacemaker	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
employed	O
about	O
that	O
work	O
,	O
did	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
take	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
positive	O
to	O
the	O
stuff	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Glynn	O
owned	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
be	O
hers	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
likewise	O
Indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
for	O
Clipping	O
forty	O
pieces	O
of	O
Silver	O
called	O
Shillings	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
as	O
the	O
Constable	O
went	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
the	O
Goods	O
that	O
were	O
stolen	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Glynn	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
Nest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
were	O
two	O
Files	O
,	O
a	O
Rubbing	O
Leather	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Scissars	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
declared	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
not	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
none	O
of	O
hers	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Burrows	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Ward	I-place
of	I-place
Farringdon	I-place
without	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
in	O
Clipping	O
2	O
100	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
100	O
Sixpences	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
October	O
in	O
the	O
fifth	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
late	O
Queen	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
had	O
seen	O
her	O
clip	O
several	O
times	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
Pounds	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
.	O
And	O
another	O
Witness	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
her	O
clip	O
with	O
one	O
Yorke	O
at	O
the	B-place
Three	I-place
Sugar	I-place
Loaves	I-place
in	I-place
Bond	I-place
stables	I-place
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
alledged	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
House	O
she	O
very	O
willingly	O
gave	O
them	O
the	O
Key	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
had	O
searched	O
they	O
could	O
find	O
nothing	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Night	O
Walker	O
,	O
yet	O
she	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
prove	O
her	O
Reputation	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Luke	B-pers
Page	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Hanwell	B-place
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
on	O
the	O
3d	O
.	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
One	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
three	O
silk	O
Hoods	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
Scarf	O
,	O
1	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
forescore	O
and	O
ten	O
Pounds	O
in	O
Moneys	O
number	O
'd	O
;	O
it	O
appeared	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Chapman	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
three	O
men	O
more	O
broke	O
into	O
his	O
House	O
at	O
an	O
upper	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
and	O
broke	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
bound	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Chapman	O
's	O
Child	O
made	O
a	O
noise	O
and	O
cried	O
out	O
they	O
would	O
hurt	O
his	O
Mother	O
,	O
they	O
forced	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
quiet	O
his	O
Child	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
great	O
fear	O
,	O
desired	O
of	O
them	O
that	O
they	O
would	O
shew	O
him	O
mercy	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
God	O
dam	O
him	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
as	O
much	O
mercy	O
as	O
they	O
had	O
when	O
they	O
should	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
Gallows	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
stood	O
Mute	O
for	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
Plead	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
ordered	O
that	O
his	O
Two	O
Thumbs	O
should	O
be	O
tyed	O
very	O
hard	O
together	O
with	O
a	O
Cord	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
sensible	O
of	O
Pain	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
not	O
think	O
it	O
an	O
easy	O
matter	O
to	O
be	O
Pressed	O
to	O
Death	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
accordingly	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
being	O
ready	O
to	O
pronounce	O
the	O
sentence	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
Pressed	O
to	O
Death	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Law	O
,	O
he	O
then	O
Pleaded	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
Guilty	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
his	O
Trial	O
he	O
declared	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
fact	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
committing	O
a	O
Robbery	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
Robbing	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Acton	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Bay	O
Gelding	O
and	O
a	O
leather	O
Saddle	O
,	O
and	O
2l	O
.	O
5s	O
.	O
in	O
moneys	O
number	O
'd	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Acton	O
was	O
going	O
over	O
Hounslow	B-place
Heath	I-place
about	O
Five	O
or	O
Six	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
Page	O
rode	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
bade	O
him	O
Stand	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
came	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Gang	O
afoot	O
;	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Horses	O
Bridle	O
,	O
then	O
Page	O
held	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
his	O
breast	O
and	O
made	O
him	O
dismount	O
,	O
and	O
bade	O
the	O
Footman	O
to	O
mount	O
and	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
Robbed	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
bade	O
the	O
other	O
Fellow	O
to	O
ride	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
positive	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
his	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
no	O
ways	O
denying	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ley	I-pers
,	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Hetton	I-pers
,	O
Henrietta	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
the	O
9th	O
of	O
October	O
1694	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4s	O
.	O
10	O
Flaxen	O
Napkins	O
,	O
5s	O
.	O
a	O
Brass	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
board	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
12	O
yards	O
of	O
Silk	O
satin	O
Ribbons	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
called	O
several	O
people	O
as	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
not	O
thinking	O
the	O
Evidence	O
sufficient	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ley	I-pers
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
harbouring	O
comforting	O
,	O
and	O
maintaining	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Hetton	I-pers
.	O
She	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Lewis	B-pers
Bentin	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
in	O
Counterfeiting	O
and	O
Forging	O
the	O
currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
day	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
one	O
false	O
piece	O
of	O
Black	O
Tin	O
like	O
to	O
a	O
Crown	O
piece	O
,	O
two	O
other	O
pieces	O
like	O
Halfcrowns	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
other	O
pieces	O
like	O
Shillings	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
made	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
teach	O
him	O
to	O
do	O
the	O
same	O
also	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
declared	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
said	O
any	O
such	O
words	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Money	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
he	O
received	O
it	O
for	O
his	O
Pay	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
he	O
did	O
acknowledge	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
be	O
nought	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Hillendon	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
Septem	O
.	O
Last	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
Hours	O
of	O
eleven	O
and	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
20	O
Cloth	O
Coifs	O
value	O
20l	O
.	O
20	O
Fustian	O
Frocks	O
55s	O
.	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
to	O
a	O
great	O
value	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
and	O
Quartered	O
at	O
Uxbridge	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Shop	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
that	O
upon	O
search	O
after	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
Blue-Anchor-alley	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Sute	O
of	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
,	O
upon	O
his	O
back	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
commit	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
directed	O
them	O
where	O
they	O
should	O
go	O
to	O
find	O
more	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
accordingly	O
did	O
at	O
the	O
Blue	O
Bell	O
in	O
Southwark	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
body	O
else	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
;	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Fuller	I-pers
together	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Costin	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ellinor	B-pers
Ives	I-pers
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Clipping	O
10	O
Halfcrowns	O
,	O
5	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
10	O
Sixpences	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
day	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
Costin	O
and	O
Ives	O
were	O
Clipping	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
coming	O
in	O
hastily	O
upon	O
them	O
did	O
see	O
them	O
clip	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
Fuller	O
was	O
sitting	O
by	O
and	O
did	O
nothing	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
clip	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Bucker	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolphs	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
8	O
yards	O
of	O
Bonelace	O
from	O
Edward	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
Yards	O
of	O
Lace	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fellows	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
some	O
Lace	O
was	O
stolen	O
from	O
the	O
Lace-Chamber	B-place
in	I-place
Aldersgate-street	I-place
,	O
and	O
search	O
was	O
made	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
search	O
'd	O
her	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
the	O
Goods	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
Wooden	O
Prints	O
for	O
Stuffs	O
from	O
James	B-pers
Wattson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
several	O
People	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
great	O
pains	O
for	O
his	O
Livelihood	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Symonds	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
seven	O
Pounds	O
and	O
five	O
Shillings	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Gibbins	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
day	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Quested	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Quested	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Hornsey	B-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
forging	O
and	O
coining	O
20	O
false	O
Guinea	O
's	O
,	O
100	O
King	O
Charles	O
the	O
First	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
10	O
King	O
James	O
's	O
the	O
Second	O
milled	O
shillings	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
likewise	O
Indicted	O
for	O
clipping	O
the	O
currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
day	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
kept	O
a	O
house	O
at	O
Winsmore	B-place
Hill	I-place
beyond	I-place
Hornsey	I-place
,	O
and	O
having	O
Information	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
search	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
File	O
and	O
Filings	O
,	O
and	O
False	O
money	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
they	O
found	O
a	O
Cutter	O
to	O
cut	O
out	O
the	O
Plate	O
fit	O
for	O
Coining	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
an	O
Outhouse	O
they	O
found	O
a	O
Press	O
to	O
coin	O
money	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Fly	O
.	O
Something	O
farther	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Dyes	O
to	O
make	O
Guinea	O
's	O
,	O
Shillings	O
and	O
Halfpence	O
,	O
in	O
an	O
old	O
Stocking	O
hid	O
under	O
the	O
earth	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Orchard	O
they	O
found	O
Instruments	O
to	O
mill	O
the	O
Edges	O
of	O
Milled	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Dyes	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
further	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
seen	O
to	O
coin	O
several	O
times	O
at	O
Hornsey	O
new	O
milled	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
King	O
Charles	O
the	O
First	O
Shillings	O
:	O
That	O
his	O
Wife	O
put	O
the	O
Pieces	O
under	O
the	O
Mill	O
whilst	O
they	O
were	O
coined	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
coin	O
several	O
false	O
Guinea	O
's	O
of	O
a	O
course	O
sort	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
each	O
of	O
those	O
Guinea	O
's	O
was	O
worth	O
20s	O
.	O
as	O
Guinea	O
's	O
go	O
now	O
.	O
Other	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
clip	O
several	O
hundred	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
clip	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
Groat	O
in	O
the	O
pound	O
.	O
That	O
his	O
Wife	O
did	O
file	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
allow	O
for	O
21s	O
.	O
of	O
broad	O
money	O
,	O
32s	O
.	O
of	O
false	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Brass	O
costs	O
him	O
l.	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
instrument	O
for	O
milling	O
the	O
money	O
cost	O
3l	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
followed	O
this	O
Trade	O
for	O
several	O
years	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
formerly	O
when	O
he	O
coined	O
money	O
he	O
struck	O
it	O
with	O
a	O
Hammer	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
never	O
clip	O
nor	O
coin	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Mills	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Instruments	O
were	O
none	O
of	O
his	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
nor	O
give	O
any	O
good	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
that	O
his	O
Wife	O
was	O
never	O
any	O
ways	O
concerned	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
declared	O
in	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
his	O
Wife	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
Indicted	O
likewise	O
with	O
one	O
J	B-pers
-	I-pers
C	I-pers
-	I-pers
,	O
for	O
counterfeiting	O
20s	O
.	O
and	O
40	O
Sixpences	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
C	O
-	O
house	O
in	O
Bell-yard	B-place
at	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
to	O
search	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
found	O
Files	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Scissars	O
,	O
a	O
false	O
milled	O
shilling	O
,	O
Hand	O
cutters	O
,	O
Crucibles	O
,	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
Plate	O
fit	O
for	O
to	O
Coin	O
.	O
They	O
both	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
C	O
-	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
use	O
the	O
File	O
for	O
to	O
make	O
Pendants	O
for	O
Watches	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
but	O
little	O
practice	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
the	O
Crucibles	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
profess	O
Physick	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
to	O
calcine	O
Antimony	O
in	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
declared	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
used	O
them	O
to	O
any	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original.	O
]	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Nicolas	B-pers
Oliver	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
committing	O
a	O
Rape	O
upon	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wale	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
;	O
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Sharpe	I-pers
of	O
the	O
same	O
Parish	O
,	O
for	O
aiding	O
and	O
abetting	O
the	O
said	O
Oliver	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Brandy	O
Shop	O
in	O
Shug-lane	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
some	O
Liquors	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
where	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
while	O
;	O
and	O
had	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
came	O
to	O
2s	O
.	O
and	O
2d	O
.	O
Sharpe	O
went	O
down	O
Stairs	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
the	O
Maid	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
thrust	O
him	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
that	O
Oliver	O
came	O
down	O
Stairs	O
and	O
catcht	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Maid	O
by	O
the	O
middle	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
her	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
Entry	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
forced	O
her	O
against	O
her	O
Will	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Maid	O
crying	O
out	O
her	O
Mistress	O
came	O
down	O
to	O
her	O
assistance	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Maid	O
declared	O
that	O
he	O
Carnally	O
knew	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
her	O
Body	O
was	O
much	O
out	O
of	O
order	O
.	O
But	O
two	O
Midwives	O
being	O
ordered	O
by	O
the	O
Justice	O
for	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
,	O
declared	O
that	O
they	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
hurt	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
a	O
suspected	O
Bawdyhouse	O
they	O
did	O
prosecute	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
thinking	O
to	O
get	O
some	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
jury	O
taking	O
it	O
into	O
consideration	O
,	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Luke	B-pers
Page	I-pers
was	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
Indicted	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Peter	B-pers
Clerk	I-pers
sick	O
in	O
Goal	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
about	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
value	O
4l	O
.	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
37s	O
.	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
West	O
,	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
Silk	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
Silverhilted	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Nightgown	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jacob	B-pers
Broad	I-pers
.	O
Page	O
owned	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Broad	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
verily	O
believe	O
that	O
the	O
Nightgown	O
was	O
his	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
Carter	O
's	O
House	O
and	O
since	O
made	O
into	O
Childrens	O
Frocks	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Carter	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Brother	O
died	O
and	O
left	O
him	O
his	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
amongst	O
which	O
was	O
this	O
Gown	O
.	O
He	O
utterly	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
several	O
good	O
people	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
poor	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
take	O
great	O
pains	O
for	O
his	O
Livelihood	O
to	O
maintain	O
his	O
Family	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
having	O
considered	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
Page	O
guilty	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Morgan	B-pers
Bourne	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Clipping	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
the	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
likewise	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Coyning	O
False	O
Guineas	O
;	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
bring	O
flatted	O
pieces	O
of	O
false	O
Gold	O
to	O
Quested	O
's	O
House	O
at	O
Hornsey	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
done	O
by	O
the	O
best	O
Workman	O
in	O
England	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
but	O
two	O
Parts	O
in	O
four	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
Coin	O
it	O
into	O
Guineas	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
followed	O
this	O
Trade	O
for	O
Three	O
years	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
farther	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
Clip	O
the	O
Friday	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
at	O
Mile-End	B-place
;	O
and	O
in	O
searching	O
of	O
his	O
House	O
they	O
found	O
a	O
paper	O
of	O
Clippings	O
,	O
Crucibles	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
File	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
pair	O
of	O
Shears	O
in	O
the	O
Stables	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
paper	O
of	O
Filings	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
an	O
old	O
Trunk	O
they	O
found	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Brass	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Stable	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
ock	O
in	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Quested	O
's	O
Press	O
stood	O
:	O
There	O
was	O
Evidence	O
that	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
Coin	O
Half	O
Crowns	O
at	O
Sutton	O
in	O
Surrey	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
utterly	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
bred	O
a	O
Merchant	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
formerly	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
Ship	O
and	O
Cargo	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
did	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
in	O
all	O
his	O
life	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Jury	O
having	O
considered	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
the	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Clipping	O
Half-Crowns	O
,	O
54	O
Shillings	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
of	O
April	O
in	O
the	O
Sixth	O
year	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
late	O
Queen	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
seen	O
her	O
Clip	O
Shillings	O
and	O
Sixpences	O
at	O
the	B-place
Three	I-place
Sugar	I-place
Loaves	I-place
in	I-place
Bond	I-place
's	I-place
Stables	I-place
in	I-place
Fosterlane	I-place
;	O
and	O
another	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
Clip	O
in	O
Salisbury	B-place
Court	I-place
and	O
the	O
Constable	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
confess	O
(	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
Clipp	O
'd	O
)	O
before	O
Justice	O
Eaton	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
three	O
days	O
before	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
Clippings	O
to	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
in	O
Fosterlane	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
alledged	O
that	O
what	O
she	O
confessed	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
poor	O
woman	O
and	O
took	O
great	O
pains	O
for	O
her	O
livelyhood	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
some	O
People	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Purser	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Forging	O
and	O
Counterfeiting	O
20	O
of	O
King	O
Charles	O
the	O
First	O
Shillings	O
and	O
Elizabeth	O
's	O
Shillings	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
.	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
year	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
late	O
Queen	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
Indicted	O
a	O
Second	O
time	O
for	O
Coining	O
of	O
False	O
Guineas	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
.	O
of	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
Quested	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
Hornsey	B-place
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
flatted	O
Silver	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Sunday	O
he	O
Cut	O
it	O
out	O
fit	O
for	O
Coining	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Monday	O
he	O
Coined	O
it	O
:	O
and	O
another	O
Evidence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
see	O
him	O
Coining	O
of	O
False	O
Guinea	O
's	O
of	O
King	O
William	O
and	O
Queen	O
Mary	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
Evidence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
see	O
him	O
in	O
Co	O
lles	O
Fields	O
Coin	O
Sixpences	O
and	O
Shillings	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
declared	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
poor	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
5s	O
.	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
in	O
all	O
his	O
life	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
prosecuted	O
out	O
of	O
spight	O
and	O
malice	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
fact	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
Evidence	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Buffin	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Whitechappel	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
his	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
upon	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
and	O
untiled	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
got	O
in	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
discovered	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Watchman	O
searching	O
found	O
him	O
upon	O
the	O
Rafters	O
and	O
Knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
declared	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
intend	O
to	O
do	O
any	O
harm	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
nothing	O
stole	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
in	O
Cheating	O
the	O
Bank	B-pers
of	I-pers
England	I-pers
of	O
720l	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
day	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
with	O
one	O
Price	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Randal	O
,	O
did	O
contrive	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
little	O
Money	O
Honourably	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
called	O
it	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
thus	O
,	O
Davis	O
forged	O
a	O
false	O
Writing	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Charles	O
Lloyd	O
called	O
a	O
Title	O
,	O
and	O
forged	O
the	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
's	O
Hand	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
pretending	O
that	O
Charles	O
Lloyd	O
had	O
an	O
Interest	O
in	O
the	O
Chamber	O
of	O
London	O
of	O
1858l	O
.	O
9s	O
.	O
2d	O
.	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
claimed	O
in	O
the	O
Right	O
of	O
his	O
Wife	O
Mary	O
,	O
Daughter	O
and	O
Orphan	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Sidney	I-pers
Mercer	O
,	O
deceased	O
;	O
which	O
Title	O
he	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Bank	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
know	O
whether	O
the	O
Bank	O
would	O
lend	O
Money	O
on	O
Orphan	O
's	O
Interest	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
told	O
that	O
the	O
Bank	O
would	O
lend	O
40l	O
.	O
per	O
Cents	O
Which	O
being	O
agreed	O
upon	O
,	O
they	O
directed	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
's	O
Office	O
and	O
make	O
an	O
Assignment	O
of	O
his	O
Interest	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
he	O
goes	O
and	O
forges	O
an	O
Assignment	O
subscribed	O
Charles	O
Lloyd	O
,	O
purporting	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
assigned	O
his	O
Interest	O
to	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Abney	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Obadiah	B-pers
Sedgwick	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Lordell	I-pers
then	O
Directors	O
of	O
the	O
Bank	O
,	O
and	O
forged	O
the	O
Common	O
Sergent	O
's	O
Clerks	O
Hands	O
as	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
the	O
Sealing	O
and	O
Delivery	O
thereof	O
;	O
which	O
Assignment	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
backside	O
endorsed	O
,	O
registered	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
's	O
Hand	O
forged	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
likewise	O
forged	O
an	O
Attestation	O
,	O
whereby	O
the	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
declared	O
that	O
Charles	O
Lloyd	O
had	O
assigned	O
his	O
interest	O
in	O
the	O
Chamber	O
of	O
London	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Directors	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
the	O
Commons	O
Serjeant	O
's	O
Hand	O
was	O
forged	O
likewise	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
said	O
Davis	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Bank	O
with	O
the	O
false	O
Assignment	O
and	O
Attestation	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Walder	O
a	O
Secretary	O
,	O
who	O
believing	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
at	O
the	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
's	O
Office	O
,	O
and	O
true	O
,	O
made	O
a	O
Bond	O
that	O
Charles	O
Lloyd	O
should	O
repay	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
Davis	O
signed	O
and	O
sealed	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Charles	O
Lloyd	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
such	O
Person	O
as	O
Charles	O
Lloyd	O
that	O
had	O
any	O
Interest	O
in	O
the	O
Chamber	O
of	O
London	O
.	O
Then	O
Mr.	O
Walder	O
gave	O
him	O
Three	O
Bank	O
Bills	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Speed	O
a	O
Casheer	O
one	O
of	O
300l	O
.	O
another	O
of	O
200l	O
.	O
and	O
the	O
last	O
of	O
220l	O
.	O
which	O
Money	O
was	O
paid	O
upon	O
the	O
said	O
Bills	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Hodgkins	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
June	O
following	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
all	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
240l	O
.	O
for	O
his	O
Share	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Misdemeanor	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
like	O
Cheat	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
July	O
did	O
personate	O
himself	O
to	O
be	O
Thomas	O
Knight	O
,	O
who	O
Married	O
the	O
Daughter	O
and	O
Orphan	O
of	O
one	O
Sherman	O
,	O
and	O
pretending	O
he	O
had	O
an	O
interest	O
of	O
998l	O
.	O
10s	O
.	O
4d	O
.	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
such	O
person	O
as	O
Thomas	O
Knight	O
that	O
had	O
any	O
interest	O
in	O
the	O
Chamber	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
same	O
Forgeries	O
did	O
get	O
1000l	O
.	O
from	O
the	O
Bank	B-pers
.	O
It	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Misdemeanor	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Randal	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
like	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
July	O
did	O
personate	O
himself	O
to	O
be	O
Thomas	O
Harvey	O
,	O
who	O
married	O
the	O
Daughter	O
and	O
Orphan	O
of	O
Richard	O
Moreley	O
,	O
Esquire	O
:	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
such	O
person	O
as	O
Thomas	O
Moreley	O
that	O
had	O
any	O
Interest	O
in	O
the	O
Chamber	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
likewise	O
get	O
1000l	O
.	O
from	O
the	O
Bank	B-pers
by	O
the	O
like	O
means	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
was	O
likewise	O
Indicted	O
for	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
Cheat	O
the	O
Bank	B-pers
of	I-pers
England	I-pers
of	O
920l	O
.	O
and	O
personating	O
himself	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
William	O
Bird	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
such	O
person	O
as	O
William	O
Bird	O
that	O
had	O
any	O
Interest	O
in	O
the	O
Chamber	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
who	O
Married	O
the	O
Daughter	O
and	O
Orphan	O
of	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Bank	O
with	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
Assignment	O
and	O
false	O
Attestation	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
who	O
happily	O
discovered	O
the	O
Cheat	O
,	O
and	O
suspecting	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
shewed	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Directors	O
,	O
who	O
ordered	O
come	O
again	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
accordingly	O
he	O
Walder	O
ordered	O
him	O
that	O
be	O
should	O
come	O
again	O
an	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
Mr.	O
Walder	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Common	O
Serjeants	O
Office	O
,	O
and	O
searching	O
the	O
Book	O
,	O
could	O
find	O
no	O
such	O
N	O
box	O
as	O
that	O
was	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
,	O
who	O
declared	O
that	O
that	O
day	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
set	O
his	O
hand	O
on	O
any	O
such	O
Assignment	O
and	O
Attestation	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
False	O
and	O
Counterfeit	O
,	O
and	O
advised	O
Mr.	O
Walder	O
to	O
Apprehend	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
accordingly	O
did	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
upon	O
his	O
Trial	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Young	O
,	O
who	O
owned	O
him	O
some	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
way	O
to	O
get	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
such	O
means	O
.	O
He	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Misdemeanor	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Stanford	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Durnall	I-pers
on	O
the	O
17th	O
.	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
two	O
Inches	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Belly	O
nigh	O
to	O
the	O
Navel	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
were	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
Ship	B-place
Tavern	I-place
in	I-place
Claremarket	I-place
,	O
and	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
drunk	O
two	O
Pints	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
they	O
played	O
at	O
All-Fours	O
for	O
another	O
Pint	O
.	O
The	O
Master	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
being	O
called	O
up	O
stairs	O
to	O
other	O
Company	O
,	O
left	O
them	O
playing	O
together	O
,	O
they	O
falling	O
out	O
drew	O
their	O
Swords	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
pass	O
at	O
each	O
other	O
.	O
The	O
Master	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
hearing	O
the	O
clashing	O
of	O
Swords	O
ran	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
Stanford	O
sitting	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
under	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
and	O
Durnall	O
standing	O
on	O
his	O
feet	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
back	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
go	O
no	O
further	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
ran	O
the	O
Deceased	O
into	O
the	O
Belly	O
,	O
and	O
Durnall	O
afterwards	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Chair	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
but	O
died	O
Immediately	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Grantham	I-pers
a	O
Blackamoor	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bartholomews	I-place
by	I-place
the	I-place
Exchange	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
taking	O
a	O
Bible	O
,	O
a	O
Hood	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Pettycoat	O
,	O
a	O
Fringe	O
,	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
and	O
Pettycoat	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
of	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Trod	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Newington	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
trunk	O
behind	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
come	O
to	O
Kingstand	O
,	O
the	O
Trunk	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
enquiry	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
told	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
a	O
Trunk	O
upon	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Trunk	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Road	O
between	O
Newington	O
and	O
Kingstand	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
proof	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
take	O
it	O
from	O
behind	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Grant	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
day	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
value	O
12d	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
Belly	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
three	O
Inches	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
Difference	O
between	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
met	O
in	O
Salisbury-court	B-place
where	O
the	O
Deceased	O
struck	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
over	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
Deceased	O
struck	O
him	O
upon	O
the	O
Legs	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
drew	O
likewise	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ran	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Belly	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
retreat	O
backwards	O
after	O
his	O
sword	O
was	O
drawn	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
done	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Minister	O
who	O
declared	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
pray	O
with	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
did	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
what	O
was	O
done	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original.	O
]	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
design	O
to	O
kill	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
done	O
he	O
did	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
defence	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
having	O
considered	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
erman	B-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Ward	I-place
of	I-place
Farringdon	I-place
without	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Clipping	O
the	O
currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
day	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
kept	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Wharton-court	B-place
in	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
and	O
having	O
information	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
drive	O
that	O
way	O
of	O
Trade	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
and	O
searcht	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
they	O
found	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
clipt	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Paper	O
of	O
Filings	O
and	O
some	O
Clippings	O
in	O
a	O
Coffee-dish	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
his	O
Goods	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
came	O
at	O
them	O
afterwards	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
that	O
could	O
say	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
see	O
him	O
clip	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Capett	I-pers
and	O
Anne	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Dicks	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
12	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Yarn	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
Wosted	O
Stocking	O
,	O
five	O
pair	O
of	O
new	O
Shoes	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Clothe	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Yard	O
of	O
Stuff	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
Capell	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Shop	O
and	O
pretended	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Childrens	O
Pumps	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
round	O
to	O
see	O
how	O
things	O
stood	O
,	O
he	O
bad	O
them	O
half	O
the	O
prices	O
they	O
askt	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
his	O
ways	O
.	O
Afterwards	O
there	O
was	O
Information	O
given	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
such	O
Goods	O
at	O
Capell	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
search	O
they	O
could	O
find	O
none	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
searcht	O
Richardson	O
's	O
Room	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
found	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Breeches	O
which	O
were	O
cut	O
to	O
pieces	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Breeches	O
were	O
her	O
Husbands	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
bought	O
the	O
Stockings	O
for	O
her	O
Daughter	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
having	O
considered	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Rawson	I-pers
Wife	O
of	O
Morris	B-pers
Rawson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
value	O
40s	O
.	O
and	O
two	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
18s	O
.	O
and	O
nine	O
Yards	O
of	O
Dimity	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Norton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Norton	O
's	O
own	O
Hands	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
brought	O
him	O
the	O
Money	O
afterwards	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
tax	O
with	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
declared	O
that	O
what	O
was	O
done	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
malice	O
and	O
Spight	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
Prosecuted	O
Mr.	O
Norton	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
for	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
6l	O
.	O
19s	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
of	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Hurst	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Clipping	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
.	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
it	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
see	O
her	O
Clip	O
about	O
10	O
Ounces	O
Ruff	O
in	O
a	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
file	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
to	O
smooth	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
melt	O
it	O
down	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
3s	O
.	O
a	O
Week	O
for	O
divers	O
Weeks	O
together	O
to	O
get	O
in	O
Broad	O
money	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
maliciously	O
Prosecuted	O
:	O
So	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Diana	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Sherry	I-pers
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Alice	B-pers
Hubbard	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
in	O
Lisle-street	B-place
in	I-place
Leicester-fields	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Crochet	O
of	O
Diamonds	O
with	O
Forty	O
two	O
large	O
Stones	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
100l	O
.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Gilt	O
Buckles	O
with	O
19	O
Stones	O
40l	O
.	O
a	O
Gold	O
Locket	O
with	O
a	O
large	O
Topaz	O
and	O
Rubies	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
value	O
;	O
it	O
appeared	O
upon	O
the	O
Trial	O
,	O
that	O
Cox	O
put	O
a	O
Girl	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
who	O
let	O
her	O
self	O
in	O
the	O
Garret	O
,	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
Door	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
Cox	O
and	O
Sherry	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
Sherry	O
was	O
dress	O
'd	O
in	O
man	O
's	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
bound	O
the	O
lady	O
in	O
her	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
gagg	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
tied	O
a	O
Napkin	O
over	O
her	O
Eyes	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
threw	O
a	O
Night-Gown	O
over	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
the	O
Girl	O
to	O
look	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
then	O
Sherry	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
bind	O
the	O
Maid	O
,	O
who	O
being	O
pretty	O
Strong	O
struggled	O
hard	O
with	O
her	O
till	O
Cox	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
bound	O
her	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
Cox	O
took	O
a	O
Fire-fork	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
open	O
a	O
Skrutore	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
said	O
Jewels	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
broke	O
open	O
a	O
Trunk	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Plate	O
and	O
Linnen	O
,	O
and	O
bundled	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
their	O
ways	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
the	O
Linnen	O
into	O
a	O
Cellar	O
;	O
Sherry	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Goldsmiths	O
to	O
sell	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
plate	O
and	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
her	O
a	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Crotchet	O
of	O
Diamonds	O
;	O
Sherry	O
declared	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
drawn	O
in	O
by	O
Cox	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
she	O
had	O
never	O
done	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
;	O
and	O
Cox	O
inveigled	O
the	O
Lady	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
and	O
help	O
her	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
the	O
Thieves	O
,	O
and	O
led	O
her	O
about	O
from	O
place	O
to	O
place	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Days	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
being	O
tax	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Crime	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
confess	O
it	O
;	O
Cox	O
afterwards	O
would	O
have	O
evaded	O
the	O
matter	O
upon	O
her	O
Trial	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Andrew	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Bragg	I-pers
on	O
the	O
27th	O
.	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
drinking	O
together	O
at	O
the	O
Rose	B-place
and	I-place
Crown	I-place
in	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
of	O
a	O
half	O
Guinea	O
,	O
Eight	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Book	O
of	O
Accounts	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
several	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
declared	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
believe	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
need	O
not	O
to	O
do	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
were	O
ordered	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
what	O
money	O
he	O
had	O
occasion	O
for	O
.	O
So	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
Mary	I-place
Savoy	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Counterfeiting	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coyn	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
100	O
false	O
pieces	O
of	O
Copper	O
like	O
to	O
Sixpences	O
;	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
lodgings	O
in	O
Somerset	B-place
Yard	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Strand	I-place
,	O
where	O
they	O
found	O
a	O
Crucible	O
full	O
of	O
Mettal	O
,	O
a	O
melting	O
over	O
a	O
Charcoal	O
Fire	O
red	O
hot	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
clapt	O
an	O
empty	O
Saucepan	O
upon	O
the	O
Fire	O
to	O
cover	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
found	O
a	O
Skrew	O
and	O
a	O
Flask	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
were	O
the	O
prints	O
of	O
the	O
Sixpences	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
Clip	O
them	O
afterwards	O
and	O
scowre	O
them	O
,	O
did	O
Feeg	O
them	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
sell	O
3l	O
.	O
of	O
false	O
Money	O
for	O
1l	O
.	O
of	O
good	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
none	O
of	O
her	O
Room	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
fact	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Bostock	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Beeston	I-pers
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Silk	O
Mantua	O
Gown	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
suspicion	O
that	O
these	O
people	O
did	O
live	O
an	O
idle	O
Life	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
and	O
searcht	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Beeston	O
and	O
Martin	O
a	O
bed	O
with	O
their	O
Cloaths	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sleeves	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
owned	O
to	O
be	O
hers	O
.	O
Bostock	O
being	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
about	O
her	O
occasions	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
and	O
Martin	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
wash	O
by	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
;	O
and	O
Beston	O
did	O
affirm	O
the	O
same	O
likewise	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
Beeston	O
and	O
Martin	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
and	O
not	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
;	O
and	O
Bostock	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
Wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
(	O
commonly	O
called	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Jenny	O
Precious	O
)	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Terret	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
with	O
a	O
Turkey	O
Stone	O
value	O
8s	O
.	O
and	O
one	O
other	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
value	O
14s	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
body	O
appeared	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Eades	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mitchell	I-pers
,	O
who	O
having	O
been	O
formerly	O
sentenced	O
and	O
pardoned	O
,	O
on	O
condition	O
that	O
they	O
should	O
transport	O
themselves	O
into	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Western	O
Islands	O
in	O
Nine	O
months	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
broke	O
the	O
Conditions	O
of	O
their	O
pardon	O
,	O
are	O
ordered	O
to	O
their	O
former	O
Judgment	O
to	O
be	O
executed	O
.	O
The	O
trials	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgement	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
10	O
.	O
Catherine	O
Buckingham	O
,	O
alias	O
Barber	O
,	O
alias	O
Barnett	O
.	O
Frances	O
Boddyman	O
Robert	O
Barnes	O
Morgan	O
Bourne	O
Diana	O
Cox	O
Luke	O
Page	O
Thomas	O
Purser	O
Samuel	O
Quested	O
Jane	O
Sherrey	O
Elizabeth	O
Wright	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Eades	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mitchell	I-pers
,	O
who	O
having	O
been	O
formerly	O
sentenced	O
and	O
pardoned	O
,	O
on	O
condition	O
that	O
they	O
should	O
transport	O
themselves	O
into	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Western	O
Islands	O
in	O
Nine	O
months	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
broke	O
the	O
Conditions	O
of	O
their	O
pardon	O
,	O
are	O
ordered	O
to	O
their	O
former	O
Judgment	O
to	O
be	O
executed	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Wright	O
,	O
Diana	O
Cox	O
,	O
Jane	O
Sherrey	O
,	O
and	O
Catherine	O
Buckingham	O
,	O
alias	O
Barber	O
,	O
alias	O
Barnett	O
,	O
pleaded	O
their	O
bellies	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
being	O
Impannelled	O
,	O
found	O
that	O
Diana	O
Cox	O
,	O
Jane	O
Sherrey	O
,	O
and	O
Catherine	O
Buckingham	O
,	O
alias	O
Barber	O
,	O
alias	O
Barnett	O
,	O
were	O
with	O
Quick-Child	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	O
Wright	O
not	O
with	O
Quick-Child	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
Burnt	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
6	O
.	O
Hannah	O
Bidgood	O
Jeremiah	O
Hart	O
John	O
Johnson	O
Cornelius	O
Shaftsburgher	O
Cornelius	O
Throft	O
Elizabeth	O
Robinson	O
.	O
Samuel	O
Grant	O
produced	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
a	O
Reprieve	O
,	O
to	O
stay	O
execution	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
burnt	O
in	O
the	O
hand	O
;	O
and	O
John	O
Stanford	O
being	O
dangerous	O
ill	O
of	O
his	O
Wounds	O
,	O
his	O
execution	O
of	O
being	O
burnt	O
in	O
the	O
hand	O
is	O
deferred	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
shall	O
be	O
in	O
condition	O
fit	O
to	O
undergo	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
3	O
.	O
Jane	O
Bucker	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Beeston	O
,	O
Jane	O
Martin	O
.	O
David	O
Davis	O
fined	O
720l	O
.	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
committed	O
till	O
he	O
pay	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
three	O
several	O
days	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
at	O
Grocers	O
Alley-End	O
in	O
the	O
Poultrey	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Chancery-Lane-End	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Carter	O
fined	O
1000l	O
.	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
committed	O
till	O
he	O
pay	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
three	O
other	O
several	O
days	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
at	O
Grocers	O
Alley-End	O
in	O
the	O
Poultrey	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
Chancery-Lane-End	O
in	O
Fleetstreet	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Randall	O
fined	O
1000l	O
.	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
committed	O
till	O
he	O
pay	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
three	O
other	O
several	O
days	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
at	O
Grocers	O
Alley-End	O
in	O
the	O
Poultrey	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
Chancery-Lane-End	O
in	O
Fleetstreet	O
.	O
John	O
Clarke	O
fined	O
500l	O
.	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
committed	O
till	O
he	O
pay	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
three	O
other	O
several	O
days	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
at	O
Grocers	O
Alley-End	O
in	O
the	O
Poultrey	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
Chancery-Lane-End	O
in	O
Fleetstreet	O
.	O
Henry	O
Long	O
,	O
and	O
Joseph	O
Pantalina	O
,	O
were	O
fined	O
twenty	O
Nobles	O
each	O
for	O
taking	O
in	O
of	O
Dyer	O
's	O
News	O
Letters	O
.	O
Benjamin	O
Baker	O
Traversed	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
Ordered	O
into	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Service	O
at	O
Sea	O
,	O
John	O
Scarlet	O
.	O
Ordered	O
to	O
serve	O
His	O
Majesty	O
as	O
Soldier	O
,	O
Michael	O
Hall	O
,	O
John	O
Johnson	O
,	O
and	O
Cornelius	O
Throft	O
.	O
The	O
last	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
Sessions	O
James	O
Lock	O
living	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bayly	O
,	O
was	O
brought	O
into	O
Court	O
by	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
of	O
a	O
Warrant	O
from	O
the	O
Lord-Mayor	O
to	O
search	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
search	O
there	O
was	O
found	O
a	O
great	O
quantity	O
of	O
Serpents	O
in	O
a	O
Chest	O
,	O
(	O
such	O
as	O
are	O
fired	O
off	O
in	O
the	O
streets	O
)	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Pound	O
of	O
Gunpowder	O
loose	O
in	O
a	O
Tray	O
,	O
which	O
might	O
have	O
endangered	O
the	O
Neighbouring	O
houses	O
by	O
Fire	O
.	O
To	O
hinder	O
him	O
all	O
such	O
persons	O
as	O
shall	O
offend	O
in	O
like	O
manner	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
an	O
Indictment	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
preferred	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
all	O
persons	O
may	O
take	O
warning	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
deterred	O
from	O
the	O
like	O
practice	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
Books	O
Printed	O
for	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
Thomas	O
Cockerill	O
,	O
Senr	O
and	O
Junr	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Legs	O
in	O
the	O
Poultrey	O
,	O
over-against	O
the	O
Stocks-Market	O
.	O
Historical	O
Collections	O
,	O
the	O
Third	O
Part	O
,	O
in	O
two	O
Volumes	O
,	O
never	O
before	O
printed	O
.	O
Containing	O
the	O
principal	O
matters	O
which	O
have	O
happen	O
'd	O
from	O
the	O
meeting	O
of	O
the	O
Parliament	O
,	O
Novemb	O
.	O
1640.	O
to	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
year	O
1644	O
.	O
By	O
John	O
Rushworth	O
Esq	O
;	O
Folio	O
.	O
Life	O
of	O
Mary	O
Queen	O
of	O
Scots	O
.	O
Folio	O
.	O
Christus	O
in	O
Corde	O
:	O
Or	O
the	O
Mystical	O
Union	O
between	O
Christ	O
and	O
Believers	O
.	O
Octavo	O
.	O
-	O
Precious	O
Faith	O
considered	O
,	O
in	O
its	O
Naure	O
,	O
Growth	O
and	O
Working	O
.	O
Octavo	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
Discourse	O
of	O
Schism	O
.	O
Octavo	O
.	O
All	O
three	O
by	O
Edward	O
Polhill	O
Esq	O
;	O
Moses	O
Amyraldus	O
's	O
Philosophical	O
Discourses	O
concerning	O
the	O
Nature	O
of	O
the	O
Soul	O
,	O
its	O
Existence	O
after	O
Death	O
,	O
and	O
Happiness	O
of	O
the	O
Just	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Octavo	O
.	O
Geography	O
Rectified	O
:	O
Or	O
a	O
Description	O
of	O
the	O
World	O
in	O
all	O
its	O
Kingdoms	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
..	O
By	O
Robert	O
Murden	O
.	O
Quarto	O
.	O
Geography	O
Anatomiz	O
'd	O
:	O
Or	O
a	O
Geographical	O
Grammar	O
,	O
being	O
an	O
Exact	O
Analysis	O
of	O
the	O
whole	O
Body	O
of	O
Modern	O
Geography	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
By	O
Patr	O
.	O
Gordon	O
M.A	O
.	O
Octavo	O
.	O
Brewster	O
's	O
Essays	O
of	O
Trade	O
and	O
Navigation	O
.	O
Octavo	O
.	O
The	O
Necessity	O
of	O
Love	O
to	O
Christ	O
.	O
Octavo	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
Mourner	O
's	O
Directory	O
.	O
Octavo	O
.	O
Both	O
by	O
Tho	O
.	O
Doolittle	O
.	O
The	O
Righteous	O
Man	O
's	O
Hope	O
at	O
Death	O
.	O
By	O
Samuel	O
Doolittle	O
.	O
The	O
Morning	O
Exercise	O
at	O
Cripplegate	O
:	O
Or	O
several	O
Cases	O
of	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
practically	O
resolved	O
,	O
by	O
sundry	O
Quarto	O
.	O
Accompaniment	O
to	O
the	O
Morning	O
Exercise	O
,	O
or	O
more	O
Cases	O
of	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
Quarto	O
.	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
Or	O
a	O
View	O
of	O
some	O
Divine	O
truth	O
.	O
By	O
Edward	O
Polhill	O
Esq	O
;	O
Quarto	O
.	O
Succinct	O
and	O
Seasonable	O
Discourse	O
or	O
Mental	O
Books	O
Sold	O
by	O
Richard	O
Baldwin	O
.	O
A	O
letter	O
to	O
the	O
Paris	O
Gazetteer	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Siege	O
and	O
Taking	O
of	O
Namur	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
Author	O
of	O
the	O
Safety	O
of	O
Europe	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Done	O
out	O
of	O
French	O
.	O
Some	O
Cautions	O
offered	O
to	O
the	O
Consideration	O
of	O
those	O
who	O
are	O
cause	O
Members	O
to	O
serve	O
in	O
the	O
Ensuing	O
Parliament	O
.	O
An	O
exact	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Siege	O
of	O
Namur	O
;	O
With	O
a	O
perfect	O
Diary	O
of	O
the	O
Campagne	O
in	O
Flanders	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
departure	O
from	O
Kensington	O
,	O
May	O
the	O
12th	O
,	O
to	O
His	O
Return	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
October	O
the	O
11th	O
.	O
1695	O
.	O
By	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
attending	O
His	O
Majesty	O
during	O
the	O
whole	O
Campaign	O
.	O
THE	O
person	O
that	O
lately	O
lived	O
on	O
Ludgate-hill	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
the	O
Kings-Arms	O
Tavern	O
near	O
Fleetbridge	O
,	O
is	O
now	O
removed	O
into	O
Essex	O
Court	O
in	O
White	O
Fryers	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
Door	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
hand	O
,	O
where	O
any	O
one	O
may	O
be	O
furnished	O
with	O
the	O
Water	O
for	O
taking	O
away	O
Freckles	O
,	O
Pimples	O
,	O
Worms	O
,	O
and	O
Morphew	O
in	O
the	O
face	O
;	O
and	O
excellent	O
water	O
and	O
Oyntment	O
for	O
the	O
Eyes	O
,	O
Ointments	O
for	O
the	O
Rickets	O
,	O
Burns	O
,	O
Scalds	O
,	O
Wounds	O
,	O
Aches	O
,	O
Sprains	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Powders	O
,	O
Dentrifices	O
,	O
Elixirs	O
,	O
Essences	O
,	O
Oyls	O
,	O
Spirits	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
for	O
the	O
easing	O
and	O
curing	O
of	O
most	O
Distempers	O
incident	O
to	O
Humane	O
Bodies	O
,	O
prepared	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
B.	O
L.	O
The	O
Water	O
for	O
taking	O
away	O
the	O
Freckels	O
,	O
Pimples	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
is	O
likewise	O
sold	O
at	O
these	O
places	O
following	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Miners	O
in	O
Popes	O
Head	O
Alley	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Suttons	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Exchange-Ally	O
over-against	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
in	O
Cornhil	O
,	O
Cane-shops	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Hamptons	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Blue-Boar's-head	O
in	O
Islington	O
.	O
Mrs	O
Miners	O
,	O
Semstress	O
in	O
the	O
Inner	O
Temple	O
Lane	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Labrahams	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Crown	O
in	O
Blew	O
Anchor	O
Alley	O
,	O
over-against	O
the	O
Artillery-Ground	O
,	O
on	O
Bunhill	O
.	O
And	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Palmers	O
House	O
on	O
Osay-hill	O
at	O
Epsom	O
.	O
To	O
prevent	O
mistakes	O
and	O
counterfeits	O
,	O
my	O
Bottles	O
will	O
be	O
Sealed	O
with	O
my	O
Coat	O
of	O
Arms	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
the	O
Three	O
Water	O
Bugets	O
and	O
Half-Moon	O
.	O
ELIXIR	O
STOMACHICUM	O
;	O
Or	O
the	O
great	O
Cordial	O
Elixir	O
for	O
the	O
Stomach	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
delicate	O
flavour	O
,	O
and	O
pleasant	O
(	O
though	O
bitterish	O
)	O
taste	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
drank	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
especially	O
in	O
a	O
Morning	O
,	O
in	O
any	O
Liquor	O
,	O
as	O
Ale	O
,	O
Tea	O
,	O
canary	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Which	O
for	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
,	O
to	O
purify	O
the	O
Blood	O
,	O
expel	O
Wind	O
,	O
for	O
all	O
Indispositions	O
of	O
the	O
Stomach	O
;	O
as	O
want	O
of	O
appetite	O
,	O
Sickness	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
for	O
Vapours	O
in	O
Women	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
other	O
most	O
certain	O
Vertues	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Bills	O
sold	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
be	O
had	O
gratis	O
at	O
the	O
places	O
where	O
't	O
is	O
sold	O
;	O
excess	O
any	O
one	O
Medicine	O
ever	O
made	O
publick	O
to	O
the	O
World	O
;	O
and	O
of	O
such	O
Excellency	O
and	O
Usefulness	O
for	O
all	O
Persons	O
,	O
as	O
never	O
to	O
be	O
without	O
it	O
about	O
them	O
'T	O
is	O
sold	O
by	O
some	O
one	O
Bookseller	O
in	O
most	O
Cities	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
great	O
Towns	O
in	O
England	O
By	O
Mr.	O
Levington	O
,	O
Fruiterer	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
Gate	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
most	O
Eminent	O
Coffee	O
houses	O
in	O
or	O
about	O
London	O
.	O
Also	O
by	O
John	O
Harris	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Harrow	O
in	O
the	O
Poultrey	O
;	O
J.	O
Dunston	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Raven	O
in	O
Jewin-street	O
;	O
S.	O
Howkins	O
,	O
in	O
George	O
yard	O
in	O
Lombard-street	O
;	O
Hugh	O
Newman	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Poultrey	O
;	O
H.	O
Rhodes	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Star	O
in	O
Fleetstreet	O
;	O
Booksellers	O
.	O
The	O
Author	O
having	O
appointed	O
the	O
Three	O
last	O
only	O
(	O
bedsides	O
himself	O
)	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
by	O
Wholesale	O
.	O
Any	O
Person	O
wanting	O
it	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
,	O
or	O
sell	O
again	O
,	O
may	O
be	O
there	O
furnish	O
'd	O
,	O
with	O
Allowance	O
for	O
selling	O
.	O
Price	O
One	O
Shilling	O
each	O
Bottle	O
,	O
Retail	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
to	O
give	O
notice	O
,	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Norridghe	O
lodgeth	O
at	O
the	O
Pewterer	O
's	O
right	O
against	O
the	O
New-Exchange	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
who	O
hath	O
an	O
infallible	O
and	O
matchless	O
Powder	O
for	O
the	O
Stone	O
and	O
Gravel	O
in	O
the	O
Kidneys	O
,	O
Stone	O
and	O
Stranguary	O
,	O
and	O
Stone-Cholicks	O
:	O
Which	O
great	O
Secret	O
,	O
with	O
many	O
more	O
,	O
her	O
Father	O
Dr	O
Duncan	O
,	O
left	O
her	O
at	O
his	O
Decease	O
,	O
who	O
practised	O
Physick	O
for	O
the	O
space	O
of	O
Sixty	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
lived	O
till	O
the	O
age	O
of	O
Eighty	O
Eight	O
.	O
One	O
Dose	O
of	O
this	O
Powder	O
generally	O
cures	O
a	O
fit	O
of	O
the	O
Stone	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
the	O
Party	O
be	O
weak	O
,	O
or	O
worse	O
,	O
then	O
usually	O
it	O
may	O
require	O
two	O
:	O
It	O
is	O
sealed	O
up	O
in	O
Ten	O
Shilling	O
Papers	O
for	O
those	O
of	O
full	O
Age	O
,	O
and	O
Five	O
Shillings	O
for	O
those	O
of	O
younger	O
years	O
.	O
And	O
also	O
in	O
Halfcrown	O
Papers	O
to	O
take	O
sometimes	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
fasting	O
to	O
prevent	O
the	O
Stone	O
from	O
contracting	O
again	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
likewise	O
very	O
expert	O
in	O
cleansing	O
the	O
Teeth	O
,	O
and	O
taketh	O
out	O
any	O
perisht	O
part	O
betwixt	O
the	O
Teeth	O
;	O
and	O
cureth	O
the	O
Tooth-ach	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
in	O
the	O
Gums	O
,	O
and	O
setteth	O
in	O
Artificial	O
Teeth	O
.	O
She	O
hath	O
also	O
a	O
most	O
Excellent	O
Water	O
for	O
Sore	O
Eyes	O
,	O
and	O
Strengthens	O
the	O
weak	O
sight	O
,	O
and	O
cures	O
the	O
Evil	O
in	O
the	O
Eyes	O
,	O
even	O
from	O
the	O
birth	O
.	O
Were	O
the	O
virtue	O
of	O
this	O
Water	O
generally	O
known	O
,	O
never	O
a	O
Family	O
in	O
England	O
would	O
be	O
without	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
for	O
washing	O
with	O
it	O
twice	O
or	O
thrice	O
in	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
preserves	O
the	O
Sight	O
,	O
and	O
prevents	O
the	O
settling	O
any	O
humor	O
in	O
the	O
Eyes	O
,	O
proceeding	O
from	O
what	O
cause	O
soever	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
sealed	O
up	O
in	O
Twelve	O
penny	O
,	O
Halfcrown	O
,	O
and	O
Crown	O
Bottles	O
.	O
She	O
hath	O
likewise	O
a	O
very	O
useful	O
Water	O
for	O
either	O
Man	O
or	O
Woman	O
,	O
that	O
keeps	O
the	O
Hair	O
from	O
falling	O
,	O
and	O
makes	O
it	O
grow	O
where	O
it	O
is	O
thin	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
Sealed	O
up	O
in	O
Twelve	O
Penny	O
,	O
and	O
Halfcrown	O
Bottles	O
.	O
And	O
she	O
will	O
undertake	O
to	O
cure	O
the	O
Jaundice	O
,	O
though	O
they	O
are	O
as	O
yellow	O
as	O
Saffron	O
Cloth	O
all	O
over	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
and	O
turning	O
to	O
the	O
Black	O
Jaundice	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
Spoken	O
with	O
every	O
Morning	O
till	O
Ten	O
,	O
and	O
Tuesday	O
and	O
Thursday	O
all	O
the	O
day	O
.	O
