TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
OF	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
on	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
9th	O
,	O
10th	O
,	O
and	O
13th	O
Days	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
1696	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
Eighth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTIES	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bayly	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
9th	O
,	O
10th	O
,	O
and	O
13th	O
Days	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
1696	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Houblon	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
Salathiel	B-pers
Lovell	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
are	O
as	O
follow	O
;	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Raper	I-pers
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Frier	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Perkins	I-pers
,	O
Michael	B-pers
Brett	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Sherwin	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Buck	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Chandler	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Acres	I-pers
,	O
Ralph	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Sayer	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Gerrard	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lathwell	I-pers
,	O
Nathanael	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wiburne	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Bind	I-pers
,	O
Patrick	B-pers
Mackaddom	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Tims	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bradford	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Peirson	I-pers
,	O
Arthur	B-pers
Allabone	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hull	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Mead	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
these	O
:	O
Mary	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Bowen	I-pers
,	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
Querne	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
28	O
yards	O
of	O
Flower	O
'd	O
Silk	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
7	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
45	O
yards	O
of	O
other	O
Silk	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Pickering	I-pers
;	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
Robinson	O
and	O
Davis	O
,	O
alias	O
Bowen	O
,	O
upon	O
their	O
Arraignment	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
,	O
but	O
Collins	O
put	O
her	O
self	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
all	O
three	O
go	O
together	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
to	O
cheapen	O
some	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
whilst	O
Mr.	O
Pickering	O
was	O
busy	O
,	O
they	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
Woman	O
by	O
the	O
Half-moon	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Cheapside	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
one	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
see	O
Collins	O
take	O
one	O
piece	O
of	O
the	O
Silk	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stafford	I-pers
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Castle	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bartholomews	I-place
by	I-place
the	I-place
Exchange	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Francis	B-pers
Coopen	I-pers
18	O
yards	O
of	O
Scarlet	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
Stafford	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
to	O
it	O
upon	O
her	O
Arraignment	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
put	O
her	O
self	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
suspected	O
to	O
be	O
Shop-lifters	O
;	O
they	O
followed	O
them	O
up	O
the	O
Stairs	O
into	O
the	B-place
Exchange	I-place
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
cheapned	O
some	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
their	O
advantage	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
searcht	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
find	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Black	O
Ribbon	O
tied	O
behind	O
her	O
head	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Castle	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
poor	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
work	O
at	O
winding	O
of	O
Silk	O
for	O
her	O
livelihood	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
her	O
,	O
neither	O
could	O
she	O
call	O
any	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
;	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
Ten	O
pence	O
.	O
[	O
Stafford	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Castle	O
:	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Bowen	I-pers
,	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
30	O
yards	O
of	O
Persian	O
Silk	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
7th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bing	I-pers
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
they	O
both	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bowen	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
for	O
stealing	O
63	O
yards	O
of	O
Dimity	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Boslip	I-pers
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
her	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
a	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
raw	O
Silk	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
June	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
Catharine	B-pers
Jordon	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Cancer	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Clipping	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
Jordon	O
declared	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
made	O
a	O
discovery	O
of	O
Clippers	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
caused	O
several	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Price	O
called	O
several	O
people	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
taking	O
it	O
into	O
consideration	O
,	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
abetting	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Beaumont	I-pers
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
with	O
one	O
Zeno	B-pers
Redcap	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
giving	O
the	O
Deceased	O
one	O
mortal	O
wound	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Body	O
nigh	O
the	O
Armhole	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
soon	O
after	O
died	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
drinking	O
at	O
a	O
Coffee-house	O
by	O
Leister-fields	B-place
and	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
arose	O
about	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
after	O
that	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Quarrel	O
being	O
further	O
aggravated	O
,	O
to	O
fighting	O
they	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
received	O
the	O
said	O
Wound	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
fighting	O
,	O
he	O
called	O
for	O
assistance	O
to	O
part	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
not	O
having	O
any	O
Offensive	O
Weapon	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Sarsfeild	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Peter	B-pers
King	I-pers
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
50	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Arnoe	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Heston	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Black	O
Gelding	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edmond	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
Gentleman	O
;	O
and	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coat	O
with	O
a	O
silver	O
Fringe	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
embroidered	O
Breeches	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Hilted	O
Sword	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Cane	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
with	O
a	O
Gold	O
fringe	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
20	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Silver	O
Fringe	O
40	O
s.	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
Baronet	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
Fact	O
that	O
he	O
ever	O
had	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
throw	O
himself	O
on	O
the	O
Mercy	O
of	O
the	O
Bench	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Mark	B-pers
Paul	I-pers
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
driving	O
the	O
off	O
Wheel	O
of	O
a	O
Cart	O
,	O
whereby	O
it	O
bruised	O
the	O
Head	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
between	O
a	O
Post	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Carter	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
a	O
descent	O
by	O
Charing-Cross	B-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
peeping	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
the	O
Post	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
drive	O
the	O
Wheel	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
not	O
knowing	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
called	O
to	O
put	O
back	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
he	O
accordingly	O
did	O
what	O
he	O
could	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Fill-horse	O
by	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
for	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
merely	O
by	O
accident	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Brewer	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Richard	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
one	O
Leonard	B-pers
Prior	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Black	O
Hat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
robbed	O
,	O
found	O
his	O
Hat	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
alledged	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
for	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
called	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Roach	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
a	O
Trunk	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
Holland	O
Petticoat	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
Morel	O
Petticoat	O
30	O
s.	O
five	O
yards	O
of	O
Scotch	O
Cloath	O
12	O
s.	O
five	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
8	O
l.	O
and	O
15	O
l.	O
in	O
Monies	O
numbred	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
day	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
some	O
Meat	O
,	O
and	O
whilst	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Market	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
gave	O
him	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
declared	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Palatine	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloath	O
Coat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Grimes	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
;	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
mistrusting	O
her	O
,	O
fetcht	O
a	O
Warrant	O
to	O
search	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
her	O
custody	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
thereupon	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
her	O
Trial	O
she	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
say	O
any	O
such	O
word	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
then	O
surprized	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Hillenden	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
about	O
Two	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
Five	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Moneys	O
numbered	O
;	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
declared	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
called	O
up	O
about	O
Four	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
his	O
Shop-windows	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
his	O
Money-box	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
being	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
that	O
Night	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
taken	O
with	O
a	O
Warrant	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
taking	O
it	O
into	O
consideration	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Gillet	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Rimer	I-pers
of	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
48	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
about	O
11	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
crossing	O
Smithfield	B-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
drink	O
,	O
with	O
that	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Shilling	O
,	O
having	O
the	O
Rings	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
she	O
observing	O
where	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
conveyed	O
the	O
Rings	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
coming	O
over	O
Smithfeild	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
would	O
have	O
her	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
him	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
refuse	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
straight	O
home	O
to	O
her	O
Lodgings	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Peter	I-place
Poor	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Serge	O
Frock	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
talking	O
with	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
hovering	O
about	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
she	O
went	O
in	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
watching	O
her	O
,	O
saw	O
her	O
come	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
searching	O
her	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Frock	O
in	O
her	O
Apron	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
given	O
her	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
Acquaintance	O
,	O
who	O
called	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
Ten	O
pence	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bowen	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
were	O
a	O
fourth	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
70	O
yards	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Bebey	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
Bowen	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
upon	O
her	O
Arraignment	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
put	O
her	O
self	O
upon	O
her	O
Trial	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Mohun	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Moone	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Murrey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Christ-Church	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Matthew	B-pers
Pottinger	I-pers
of	O
five	O
French	O
Pistols	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
as	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
about	O
11	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Newgate-street	B-place
,	O
and	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
drink	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
refuse	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
came	O
up	O
close	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
felt	O
her	O
hand	O
about	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
done	O
her	O
work	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
to	O
another	O
Woman	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
presently	O
missing	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
bad	O
the	O
Watchman	O
to	O
run	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
stop	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
searcht	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
ill	O
Liver	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Smart	I-pers
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolphs	I-place
without	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
dozen	O
of	O
Holland	O
Clouts	O
,	O
val	O
,	O
5	O
s.	O
24	O
Childrens	O
Caps	O
10	O
s.	O
6	O
Laced	O
Pinners	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Paul	O
Philo	O
;	O
a	O
Farrendine	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Camblet	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Pistols	O
tipt	O
with	O
Silver	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
Moneys	O
numbred	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Barns	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
lockt	O
in	O
a	O
Trunk	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
Smart	O
in	O
Little	O
Britain	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Camblet	O
Coat	O
was	O
sold	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
by	O
one	O
H	O
-	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Hughes	O
did	O
vouch	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
be	O
honestly	O
come	O
by	O
.	O
Smart	O
upon	O
her	O
trial	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
H	O
-	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
could	O
say	O
that	O
Hughes	O
stole	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
Smart	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Matthew	B-pers
Bagley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
Bottolph	I-place
without	I-place
Algate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
for	O
counterfeiting	O
20	O
s.	O
20	O
Halfcrowns	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
Guineas	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Seventh	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
one	O
Chawner	O
,	O
lately	O
executed	O
,	O
did	O
meet	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
Tavern	O
by	O
Algate	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
bespoke	O
a	O
Mill	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
make	O
false	O
Money	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
make	O
about	O
14	O
pieces	O
of	O
Copper-blanks	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
made	O
the	O
Mill	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
bespoke	O
by	O
Chawner	O
,	O
he	O
bringing	O
him	O
a	O
Model	O
of	O
Wood	O
to	O
shew	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
it	O
done	O
,	O
but	O
denied	O
that	O
he	O
ever	O
knew	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
for	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
one	O
for	O
Chawner	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
for	O
Smith	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
since	O
fled	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
abundance	O
of	O
People	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
a	O
long	O
Trial	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Phillip	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
Ann	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
for	O
Counterfeiting	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
May	O
1695.	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
shewed	O
him	O
all	O
his	O
Tools	O
for	O
the	O
Trade	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
false	O
Pistols	O
,	O
but	O
declared	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
never	O
see	O
him	O
at	O
work	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
abundance	O
of	O
people	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Eltham	I-pers
,	O
Susan	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
and	O
Alice	B-pers
Body	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
forging	O
a	O
false	O
Letter	O
of	O
Attorney	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
Mariner	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Ship	O
the	O
Ruby	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
that	O
means	O
did	O
receive	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Pay-masters	O
of	O
the	O
Navy	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
15	O
l.	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
did	O
divide	O
the	O
Money	O
amongst	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
a	O
long	O
Tryal	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susan	B-pers
Butterley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Frances	B-pers
Commins	I-pers
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Mug	O
,	O
two	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
one	O
Silver	O
Salt	O
,	O
two	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Nicholson	I-pers
and	O
Abraham	B-pers
Loveney	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
with	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
lately	O
convicted	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Offence	O
,	O
did	O
contrive	O
to	O
make	O
one	O
Edward	B-pers
Dyes	I-pers
a	O
Freeman	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
obtain	O
15	O
l.	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
affirm	O
the	O
same	O
Dyes	O
to	O
have	O
served	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Henry	B-pers
Fountain	I-pers
before	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Trevillian	O
,	O
Clerk	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Ange	O
at	O
Merchant-Taylors	O
Hall	O
:	O
They	O
had	O
but	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
on	O
their	O
own	O
behalf	O
,	O
nor	O
could	O
they	O
call	O
any	O
People	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Misdemeanor	O
.	O
Abraham	O
Loveney	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
contriving	O
to	O
make	O
one	O
Robert	B-pers
Wrane	I-pers
,	O
who	O
he	O
did	O
affirm	O
to	O
serve	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
as	O
an	O
Apprentice	O
the	O
term	O
of	O
Seven	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
likewise	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Childs	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
for	O
Counterfeiting	O
40	O
Guineas	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
having	O
information	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
drive	O
that	O
sort	O
of	O
Trade	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
and	O
searcht	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
under	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
board	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
a	O
Bag	O
fastned	O
to	O
a	O
Peircer	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
were	O
divers	O
Counterfeit	O
Guineas	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shears	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Tools	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
utterly	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
how	O
them	O
things	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
abundance	O
of	O
People	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Rossiter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
Gregory	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Stutter	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Laced	O
Headdress	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
40	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Rock	I-pers
.	O
Widow	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Rock	O
sent	O
her	O
Maid	O
to	O
fetch	O
the	O
Head-dress	O
from	O
the	O
Washers	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
came	O
two	O
men	O
and	O
shoved	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
came	O
behind	O
her	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
Evidence	O
that	O
did	O
hear	O
him	O
confess	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
and	O
thereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
taking	O
it	O
into	O
consideration	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
David	B-pers
Venables	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
for	O
washing	O
divers	O
false	O
pieces	O
of	O
Copper	O
with	O
alliquid	O
stuff	O
called	O
Feag	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
Bull	B-place
Head	I-place
Tavern	I-place
in	I-place
Cheapside	I-place
,	O
he	O
did	O
peep	O
through	O
a	O
little	O
hole	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
one	O
Williams	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
see	O
Williams	O
rubbing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
false	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
Table	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Gally-pot	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ran	O
immediately	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
threw	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Wine	O
into	O
the	O
Gally-pot	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
into	O
the	O
Chimney	O
;	O
then	O
Venables	O
fell	O
down	O
upon	O
his	O
Knees	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
beg	O
that	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
prosecute	O
him	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
further	O
observed	O
that	O
his	O
Fingers	O
and	O
his	O
Thumbs	O
were	O
seen	O
to	O
be	O
sore	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
by	O
rubbing	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
home	O
enough	O
to	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
make	O
but	O
little	O
defence	O
against	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Misdemeanor	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Frances	B-pers
Woolley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
30	O
s.	O
in	O
Moneys	O
numbred	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
for	O
three	O
Pints	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
took	O
her	O
opportunity	O
whilst	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
draw	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
her	O
ways	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
no	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Attey	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Ate	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Heston	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
for	O
Counterfeiting	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Seventh	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Moore	O
the	O
Tripeman	O
's	O
House	O
at	O
Smallberry-Green	B-place
,	O
and	O
was	O
seen	O
through	O
the	O
Key-hole	O
to	O
set	O
the	O
Mill	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
it	O
fastwith	O
a	O
Wedge	O
and	O
a	O
Hammer	O
;	O
and	O
since	O
there	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Letters	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
Punches	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
false	O
Copper	O
pieces	O
and	O
Brass	O
Flasks	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
all	O
produced	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
that	O
did	O
see	O
him	O
Coin	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
declared	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
those	O
things	O
came	O
there	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
taking	O
it	O
into	O
consideration	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Godfrey	B-pers
Gravet	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
upon	O
four	O
Indictments	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
for	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
persuade	O
one	O
Bazil	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
to	O
personate	O
one	O
Albany	B-pers
Ley	I-pers
,	O
Steward	O
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
to	O
personate	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Cooper	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Ship	O
called	O
the	O
Bonaventure	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
two	O
Affidavits	O
before	O
two	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
40	O
Butts	O
of	O
Beer	O
that	O
had	O
leek	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Ship	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
Provisions	O
for	O
80	O
men	O
for	O
6	O
days	O
at	O
whole	O
allowance	O
by	O
the	O
Captain	O
's	O
order	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Purser	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Ship	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
Ashen-tree	O
in	O
Ashen-tree	O
Court	O
,	O
in	O
White-Friers	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
propose	O
the	O
matter	O
to	O
Hill	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
refuse	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
returning	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
after	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
one	O
would	O
do	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
meet	O
in	O
Pescod	O
Street	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
did	O
produce	O
the	O
Affidavits	O
,	O
and	O
signed	O
them	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
detect	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
from	O
them	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
after	O
a	O
long	O
Tryal	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Fogam	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
for	O
forging	O
a	O
Letter	O
of	O
Attorney	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Wareing	I-pers
,	O
Mariner	O
,	O
in	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Ship	O
the	O
Unity	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Preistiley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
about	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Cloath	O
Gown	O
,	O
val	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
Bever	O
Hat	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Bible	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	O
Baker	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Breeches	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Gorden	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
lift	O
up	O
the	O
Sash	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
a	O
forked	O
Stick	O
did	O
reach	O
the	O
things	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Riley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Ralph	B-pers
Roe	I-pers
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
2	O
Silver	O
Salvers	O
,	O
3	O
Casters	O
,	O
2	O
Salts	O
,	O
2	O
Tankards	O
,	O
4	O
Cup	O
;	O
one	O
Porringer	O
,	O
9	O
Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
40	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Moneys	O
numbred	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
a	O
Laced	O
Muslin	O
Apron	O
,	O
a	O
Head-dress	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Muslin	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Petchel	I-pers
,	O
Sen.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Buckles	O
with	O
Bristol	O
Stones	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Petchel	I-pers
,	O
Jun	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
custody	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Moggs	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
Peters	I-place
de	I-place
Bonds	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Liberty	I-place
of	I-place
the	I-place
Tower	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
5	O
s.	O
Piece	O
from	O
the	O
Mint	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
;	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
fault	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
fresh	O
Indictment	O
is	O
ordered	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Drewry	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
in	O
counterfeiting	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
having	O
information	O
that	O
the	O
Trade	O
of	O
Coining	O
was	O
carried	O
on	O
in	O
George-Yard	B-place
in	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
they	O
went	O
and	O
searcht	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
20	O
Shillings	O
in	O
false	O
Milled	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Gold	O
File	O
dust	O
,	O
Shears	O
and	O
Files	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Implements	O
fitting	O
for	O
the	O
Trade	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
none	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
believe	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
another	O
man	O
's	O
that	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
;	O
he	O
called	O
abundance	O
of	O
people	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Carwell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
's	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
for	O
Counterfeiting	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
having	O
information	O
that	O
the	O
Trade	O
of	O
Coming	O
was	O
carried	O
on	O
in	O
Holloway-Court	B-place
in	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
and	O
upon	O
search	O
they	O
found	O
Flasks	O
ready	O
filled	O
with	O
the	O
Impressions	O
for	O
Money	O
in	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Crucible	O
,	O
and	O
False	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Forge	O
built	O
in	O
the	O
Chimney	O
,	O
with	O
Charcoal	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
quantity	O
of	O
broken	O
Crucibles	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
how	O
those	O
things	O
came	O
there	O
:	O
He	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
let	O
the	O
Room	O
to	O
two	O
Irish-men	O
that	O
were	O
Soldiers	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
abundance	O
of	O
people	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
after	O
all	O
found	O
him	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Counterfeiting	O
the	O
Currant	O
,	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Indictment	O
being	O
not	O
right	O
drawn	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
ordered	O
a	O
fresh	O
one	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
(	O
the	O
first	O
as	O
Principal	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
as	O
Accessary	O
)	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Jenkinson	I-pers
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
Two	O
and	O
Three	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
thence	O
6	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
s.	O
12	O
Smocks	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
:	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
declared	O
that	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
upon	O
search	O
found	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Smocks	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
marked	O
with	O
White	O
Thread	O
,	O
and	O
picked	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
deny	O
that	O
ever	O
she	O
did	O
steal	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
for	O
the	O
Shift	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
for	O
it	O
being	O
marked	O
formerly	O
with	O
an	O
F	O
and	O
an	O
I	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
pick	O
out	O
the	O
Mark	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
in	O
her	O
Name	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
thereof	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
declared	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
prosecuted	O
out	O
of	O
spight	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
Mason	O
guilty	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Alcock	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
.	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
9	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Fork	O
,	O
9	O
d.	O
and	O
Two	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Moneys	O
numbred	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
andone	O
Henry	B-pers
Wilder	I-pers
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
send	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
the	O
Bull-head	O
in	O
St.	O
Martins	O
Lane	O
,	O
after	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
one	O
Jones	B-place
's	I-place
Coffee-house	I-place
in	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
did	O
alledge	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
stopp	O
'd	O
her	O
mouth	O
with	O
his	O
Coat-sleeve	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
rifled	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
abundance	O
of	O
people	O
who	O
spake	O
very	O
well	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
taking	O
it	O
into	O
consideration	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Carr	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
with	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Wheatly	I-pers
,	O
did	O
cheat	O
one	O
Hugh	B-pers
Silk	I-pers
of	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Stuffs	O
pretending	O
that	O
William	O
Wheatly	O
was	O
one	O
Samuel	B-pers
Billingham	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Alderman	O
of	O
York	O
.	O
He	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Christian	B-pers
Callow	I-pers
,	O
together	O
with	O
Mary	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Shermar	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
7	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
Silver-hasted	O
Knife	O
and	O
Fork	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
.	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Seventh	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Rebekah	B-pers
Smart	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
:	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Henry	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
a	O
Crape	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Cloath-Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Lutestring	O
Scarf	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
.	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Boone	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Booth	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Street	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
Mr.	O
Street	O
's	O
Goods	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
by	O
the	O
Watchman	O
.	O
He	O
pretended	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Winter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Moone	I-pers
,	O
of	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
d	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
.	O
of	O
July	O
Instant	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
seen	O
hovering	O
about	O
the	O
Court	O
in	O
the	O
very	O
face	O
of	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
an	O
accident	O
pulling	O
out	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
discovered	O
by	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
that	O
stood	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
searching	O
him	O
they	O
found	O
4	O
in	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
in	O
his	O
Pockets	O
,	O
among	O
which	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Moone	O
's	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Person	O
that	O
did	O
drop	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susan	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Stuart	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Alhallows	B-place
by	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Grezet	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
flower	O
'd	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
an	O
Alamode	O
hood	O
,	O
and	O
70	O
l.	O
in	O
Moneys	O
numbred	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
.	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Servant	O
upon	O
liking	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
opportunity	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
Bridgets	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
for	O
Coining	O
Forty	O
false	O
Guineas	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
.	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
having	O
Information	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
follow	O
the	O
Trade	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
one	O
of	O
Moore	O
the	O
Tripeman	O
's	O
Gang	O
,	O
they	O
search	O
'd	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
in	O
the	O
Fleet	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
found	O
several	O
Tools	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Forge	O
,	O
and	O
hollow	O
Punches	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
Evidence	O
that	O
did	O
depose	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
him	O
a	O
Mill	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
harden	O
'd	O
some	O
Dyes	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
were	O
to	O
coin	O
King	O
Charles	O
's	O
Guineas	O
with	O
an	O
Elephant	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
give	O
12	O
d.	O
apiece	O
for	O
the	O
striking	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
12	O
d.	O
apiece	O
to	O
a	O
Frenchman	O
to	O
gild	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
edge	O
them	O
himself	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
Evidence	O
that	O
did	O
say	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
19	O
or	O
20	O
False	O
Guineas	O
of	O
King	O
William	O
and	O
Queen	O
Mary	O
,	O
and	O
produced	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Tools	O
were	O
his	O
,	O
they	O
being	O
useful	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Silversmith	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
work	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Chamber	O
.	O
After	O
a	O
long	O
Trial	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
High	O
Treason	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Nutting	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
taking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Mantua	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Crape	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Serge	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
.	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Seventh	O
Year	O
of	O
by	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Jackson	O
's	O
Wife	O
left	O
her	O
at	O
home	O
whilst	O
the	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
her	O
occasions	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
went	O
her	O
way	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Toney	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
whilst	O
they	O
went	O
at	O
Dinner	O
but	O
was	O
discovered	O
by	O
the	O
Apprentice	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
put	O
off	O
a	O
Counterfeit	O
Shilling	O
,	O
knowing	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
S	B-pers
-	I-pers
T	I-pers
-	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Peruke	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
.	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Willicat	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Parford	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
Forging	O
a	O
Letter	O
of	O
Attorney	O
,	O
to	O
receive	O
the	O
Wages	O
of	O
a	O
Seaman	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
Printing	O
a	O
most	O
Scandalous	O
label	O
,	O
called	O
,	O
An	O
Anti	O
Curse	O
,	O
which	O
,	O
upon	O
search	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
under	O
the	O
Press	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Stephens	O
the	O
Messenger	O
did	O
declare	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
him	O
several	O
times	O
for	O
such	O
Crimes	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
always	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
Popish	O
Work	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
Print	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Strutton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
32	O
Ounces	O
of	O
fine	O
silk	O
from	O
Edward	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Katherine	B-pers
Buckingham	I-pers
,	O
who	O
formerly	O
pleaded	O
her	O
Belly	O
,	O
was	O
called	O
down	O
to	O
her	O
former	O
Judgment	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
for	O
Execution	O
.	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
gave	O
Sentence	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
5	O
.	O
James	O
Arnoe	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Boone	O
,	O
alias	O
Booth	O
.	O
Jane	O
Gillet	O
.	O
Sarah	O
Moone	O
,	O
and	O
Thomas	O
White	O
.	O
Katherine	B-pers
Buckingham	I-pers
,	O
who	O
formerly	O
pleaded	O
her	O
Belly	O
,	O
was	O
called	O
down	O
to	O
her	O
former	O
Judgment	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
for	O
Execution	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
18	O
.	O
Susan	O
Butterly	O
.	O
Ann	O
bell	O
.	O
Mary	O
Collins	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Davis	O
,	O
alias	O
Bowen	O
.	O
Peter	O
Johnson	O
.	O
Susan	O
Jenkins	O
,	O
alias	O
Stuart	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Mason	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Palatine	O
.	O
John	O
Preistly	O
.	O
Mary	O
Robinson	O
.	O
Robert	O
Roach	O
.	O
George	O
Rossiter	O
,	O
Sarah	O
Riley	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Stafford	O
.	O
William	O
Satsfield	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Vaughan	O
.	O
Robert	O
Wheeler	O
,	O
and	O
Frances	O
Woolley	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
,	O
5	O
.	O
Jane	O
Castle	O
.	O
Margaret	O
Edwards	O
,	O
Rebekah	O
Smart	O
,	O
Ann	O
Turner	O
,	O
and	O
Robert	O
Winter	O
,	O
Richard	O
Eltham	O
and	O
Susan	O
Smith	O
Fined	O
20	O
Marks	O
each	O
,	O
and	O
Alice	O
Body	O
20	O
l.	O
and	O
Eltham	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
Women	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Pay-Office	O
,	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
and	O
Cheapside-Conduit	O
,	O
and	O
find	O
Sureties	O
and	O
stand	O
committed	O
till	O
they	O
pay	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Charles	O
Carr	O
Fined	O
40	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
at	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
Cheapside-Conduit	O
,	O
and	O
Temple-Bar	O
.	O
Abraham	O
Loveney	O
Fined	O
20	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
George	O
Nicholson	O
20	O
Nobles	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
last	O
Places	O
.	O
Abraham	O
Venable	O
Fined	O
100	O
l.	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
at	O
the	O
said	O
Three	O
Places	O
.	O
David	O
Edwards	O
Fined	O
50	O
l.	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
at	O
the	O
last	O
Three	O
Places	O
.	O
Godfrey	O
Grevett	O
Fined	O
40	O
l.	O
only	O
.	O
John	O
Parker	O
Fined	O
a	O
Noble	O
only	O
.	O
Some	O
Books	O
Printed	O
for	O
B.	O
Aylmer	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Pigeons	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
.	O
THE	O
Works	O
of	O
the	O
Most	O
Reverend	O
Dr.	O
John	O
Tillotson	O
,	O
late	O
Lord	O
Archbishop	O
of	O
Canterbury	O
,	O
containing	O
fifty	O
four	O
Sermons	O
and	O
Discourses	O
on	O
Several	O
Occasions	O
;	O
together	O
with	O
the	O
rule	O
of	O
Faith	O
.	O
Being	O
all	O
that	O
were	O
published	O
by	O
his	O
Grace	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
collected	O
into	O
one	O
Volume	O
:	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
an	O
Alphabetical	O
Table	O
of	O
the	O
Principal	O
Matters	O
.	O
Price	O
20	O
s.	O
Six	O
Sermons	O
;	O
viz	O
.	O
Of	O
Stedfastness	O
in	O
Religion	O
.	O
Of	O
Family	O
Religion	O
.	O
Of	O
Education	O
of	O
Children	O
.	O
Of	O
the	O
Advantages	O
of	O
an	O
Early	O
Piety	O
.	O
By	O
his	O
Grace	O
,	O
John	O
,	O
late	O
Archbishop	O
of	O
Canterbury	O
.	O
In	O
120.	O
price	O
18	O
d.	O
A	O
Persuasive	O
to	O
frequent	O
Communion	O
in	O
the	O
Holy	O
Sacrament	O
of	O
the	O
Lord	O
's	O
Supper	O
;	O
Also	O
by	O
his	O
Grace	O
,	O
John	O
,	O
late	O
Archbishop	O
of	O
Canterbury	O
.	O
in	O
120	O
.	O
Bound	O
6	O
d.	O
or	O
Stitch	O
'd	O
in	O
8vo	O
.	O
3	O
d.	O
or	O
something	O
Cheaper	O
to	O
those	O
that	O
are	O
so	O
Charitable	O
to	O
give	O
away	O
Numbers	O
.	O
The	O
Holy	O
Bible	O
,	O
Containing	O
the	O
Old	O
Testament	O
and	O
the	O
New	O
;	O
with	O
Annotations	O
and	O
very	O
exact	O
Parallel	O
Scriptures	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
Annex	O
'd	O
the	O
Harmony	O
of	O
the	O
Gospels	O
;	O
as	O
also	O
the	O
Reduction	O
of	O
the	O
Jewish	O
Weights	O
,	O
Coins	O
and	O
Measures	O
,	O
to	O
our	O
English	O
Standards	O
.	O
And	O
a	O
Table	O
of	O
the	O
Promises	O
in	O
Scripture	O
.	O
By	O
Samuel	O
Clark	O
,	O
Minister	O
of	O
the	O
Gospel	O
.	O
Printed	O
in	O
Folio	O
on	O
a	O
very	O
Fair	O
Letter	O
;	O
the	O
like	O
never	O
before	O
in	O
one	O
Volume	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
newly	O
added	O
a	O
very	O
Exact	O
and	O
Useful	O
Concordance	O
.	O
Price	O
30	O
Shill	O
.	O
Practical	O
Discourses	O
upon	O
the	O
Consideration	O
of	O
our	O
Latter	O
End	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Danger	O
and	O
Mischief	O
of	O
Delaying	O
Repentance	O
.	O
By	O
Dr.	O
Isaac	O
Barrow	O
,	O
in	O
8vo	O
.	O
Price	O
18	O
d.	O
The	O
Four	O
Last	O
Things	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Death	O
,	O
Judgment	O
,	O
Heaven	O
,	O
and	O
Hell	O
:	O
Practically	O
Considered	O
and	O
Applied	O
.	O
By	O
W.	O
Bates	O
,	O
D.	O
D.	O
in	O
120	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
The	O
Great	O
Duty	O
of	O
Resignation	O
to	O
the	O
Divine	O
Will	O
in	O
Afflictions	O
.	O
Also	O
by	O
Dr.	O
Bates	O
.	O
In	O
8vo	O
.	O
18	O
d.	O
Sermons	O
of	O
the	O
Forgiveness	O
of	O
Sins	O
.	O
On	O
Psalm	O
130.	O
v.	O
4	O
.	O
Also	O
by	O
Dr.	O
Bates	O
.	O
Price	O
18	O
d.	O
The	O
Cure	O
of	O
Distractions	O
in	O
Attending	O
upon	O
God	O
.	O
In	O
several	O
Sermons	O
.	O
By	O
Nathanael	O
Vincent	O
,	O
M.	O
A	O
.	O
In	O
8	O
vo	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
Also	O
several	O
Sermons	O
against	O
the	O
Love	O
of	O
the	O
World	O
.	O
By	O
N.	O
Vincent	O
.	O
In	O
120	O
.	O
Price	O
12	O
d.	O
Also	O
his	O
Sermon	O
at	O
the	O
Funeral	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Lawrence	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
Bishop	O
of	O
Gloucester	O
's	O
Thansgiving	O
Sermon	O
preached	O
before	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Lords	O
,	O
April	O
16	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Stephens	O
of	O
Sutton	O
in	O
Surrey	O
,	O
his	O
Thanksgiving	O
Sermon	O
preached	O
before	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
and	O
Aldermen	O
at	O
Bow-Church	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
.	O
Mr.	O
John	O
Showers	O
his	O
Thanks	O
giving	O
Sermon	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Strype	O
of	O
Low-Layton	O
in	O
Essex	O
,	O
his	O
Thanksgiving	O
Sermon	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gardiner	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
his	O
Thanksgiving	O
Sermon	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Butler	O
's	O
Fast-Sermon	O
preached	O
before	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
;	O
.	O
at	O
Bow-Church	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
1696	O
.	O
Dr.	O
Towerson	O
's	O
Sermon	O
concerning	O
Vocal	O
and	O
Instrumental	O
Musick	O
in	O
the	O
Church	O
.	O
A	O
Sermon	O
preached	O
at	O
the	O
Meeting	O
of	O
Protestent	O
Diffenters	O
,	O
called	O
Quakers	O
,	O
in	O
Turner	O
's	O
Hall	O
,	O
London	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
the	O
Second	O
Month	O
,	O
1696	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Publick	O
Day	O
of	O
Thanksgiving	O
for	O
the	O
Deliverance	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
Kingdom	O
.	O
By	O
George	O
Keith	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
a	O
Testimony	O
of	O
Fidelity	O
and	O
Subjection	O
to	O
King	O
William	O
the	O
IIId	O
.	O
from	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
People	O
on	O
behalf	O
of	O
themselves	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Persuasion	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
An	O
Exact	O
Narrative	O
of	O
the	O
Proceedings	O
at	O
Turners-Hall	O
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
the	O
Month	O
called	O
June	O
,	O
1696	O
.	O
Together	O
with	O
the	O
Disputes	O
and	O
Speeches	O
,	O
there	O
,	O
between	O
George	O
Keith	O
and	O
other	O
Quakers	O
,	O
differing	O
from	O
him	O
in	O
some	O
Religious	O
Principles	O
.	O
The	O
whole	O
Published	O
and	O
Revised	O
by	O
George	O
Keith	O
.	O
With	O
an	O
Appendix	O
containing	O
some	O
New	O
Passages	O
to	O
prove	O
his	O
Opponents	O
guilty	O
of	O
Gross	O
Erros	O
and	O
Self-Contradictions	O
.	O
The	O
Advice	O
of	O
a	O
Father	O
:	O
Or	O
Counsel	O
to	O
a	O
Child	O
;	O
Directing	O
him	O
how	O
to	O
demean	O
himself	O
in	O
the	O
most	O
important	O
Passages	O
of	O
this	O
Life	O
.	O
By	O
E.	O
C.	O
Gent	O
.	O
In	O
12	O
s.	O
Price	O
12	O
d.	O
A	O
Conference	O
with	O
an	O
Anabaptist	O
.	O
By	O
Dr.	O
Asheton	O
of	O
Beckenham	O
in	O
Kent	O
.	O
Price	O
12	O
d.	O
A	O
Theological	O
Discourse	O
of	O
Last	O
Wills	O
and	O
Testaments	O
.	O
Also	O
by	O
Dr.	O
Asheton	O
Price	O
12	O
d.	O
Several	O
small	O
Books	O
against	O
Debauchery	O
,	O
Prosaneness	O
,	O
Blasphemy	O
,	O
Cursing	O
and	O
Swearing	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
;	O
.	O
Also	O
by	O
Dr.	O
Ashewon	O
Price	O
2	O
d.	O
each	O
,	O
and	O
something	O
cheaper	O
to	O
them	O
that	O
give	O
away	O
Numbers	O
.	O
Contemplations	O
of	O
Death	O
and	O
Immortality	O
:	O
By	O
the	O
late	O
Earl	O
of	O
Manchester	O
.	O
The	O
15th	O
Edition	O
,	O
In	O
120	O
.	O
Price	O
12	O
d.	O
A	O
Familiar	O
Guide	O
to	O
the	O
Right	O
and	O
Profitable	O
Receiving	O
of	O
the	O
Lord	O
's	O
Supper	O
:	O
Wherein	O
also	O
the	O
Way	O
and	O
Method	O
of	O
our	O
Salvation	O
is	O
briefly	O
and	O
plainly	O
declared	O
.	O
By	O
T.	O
Dorrington	O
.	O
Price	O
12	O
d.	O
Mr.	O
Flamstead	O
of	O
Greenwich	O
,	O
his	O
exact	O
Correct	O
Tide-Table	O
;	O
shewing	O
the	O
true	O
Times	O
of	O
the	O
High-Water	O
at	O
London-Bridge	O
to	O
every	O
day	O
in	O
the	O
year	O
1696	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
d.	O
(	O
very	O
proper	O
for	O
all	O
publick	O
Houses	O
)	O
.	O
An	O
Admirable	O
Water	O
against	O
Convulsion	O
Fits	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Falling	O
Sickness	O
.	O
Being	O
a	O
Secret	O
kept	O
in	O
an	O
Eminent	O
Family	O
for	O
many	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
for	O
general	O
good	O
made	O
publick	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
sold	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Aylmer	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Pidgeons	O
against	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
.	O
The	O
smaller	O
Bottle	O
at	O
3	O
s.	O
At	O
the	O
Blew	O
Ball	O
in	O
Whale	O
Bone-Court	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Lower	O
End	O
of	O
Bartholomew	O
Lane	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
;	O
Liveth	O
W.	O
Eimy	O
.	O
Professor	O
of	O
Physick	O
,	O
of	O
known	O
Integrity	O
:	O
Who	O
most	O
safely	O
and	O
expeditiously	O
Cures	O
Deafness	O
and	O
Noises	O
in	O
the	O
Ears	O
in	O
any	O
,	O
of	O
what	O
Age	O
soever	O
(	O
if	O
Curable	O
)	O
and	O
at	O
first	O
sight	O
,	O
by	O
Inspection	O
,	O
resolves	O
the	O
Patient	O
if	O
so	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
as	O
most	O
eminent	O
Persons	O
of	O
Quality	O
can	O
testify	O
.	O
The	O
Ear	O
is	O
the	O
Organ	O
of	O
Hearing	O
,	O
the	O
most	O
Spiritual	O
Sense	O
,	O
the	O
Agent	O
of	O
Understanding	O
,	O
the	O
Gate	O
through	O
which	O
Sense	O
,	O
Truth	O
,	O
and	O
Virtue	O
,	O
hath	O
its	O
Entrance	O
into	O
the	O
Soul	O
.	O
He	O
hath	O
likewise	O
a	O
Pill	O
which	O
Cleanseth	O
the	O
Blood	O
from	O
all	O
Impurities	O
,	O
infallibly	O
curing	O
the	O
Scurvey	O
:	O
It	O
cures	O
the	O
Head-Ach	O
to	O
Admiration	O
,	O
taking	O
away	O
Vapours	O
Offensive	O
to	O
the	O
Brain	O
:	O
It	O
creates	O
a	O
good	O
Stomach	O
and	O
Digestion	O
;	O
takes	O
away	O
Sharpness	O
of	O
Urine	O
,	O
and	O
Cleanseth	O
the	O
Reins	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
a	O
certain	O
and	O
present	O
remedy	O
for	O
the	O
Gout	O
.	O
It	O
cures	O
all	O
Joynt-Pains	O
,	O
resists	O
Feavers	O
and	O
Surseits	O
;	O
and	O
preserves	O
the	O
Body	O
in	O
perfect	O
Health	O
.	O
He	O
hath	O
Boxes	O
of	O
several	O
Prices	O
,	O
according	O
as	O
Necessity	O
requires	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
,	O
from	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
to	O
3	O
s.	O
Also	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Gargarism	O
or	O
mouth-water	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
make	O
Black	O
or	O
Yellow	O
Teeth	O
as	O
White	O
as	O
Ivory	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
times	O
using	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
will	O
certainly	O
cure	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
Diseases	O
incident	O
to	O
the	O
Mouth	O
,	O
Teeth	O
,	O
and	O
Gums	O
,	O
The	O
Glasses	O
are	O
of	O
several	O
Prices	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
.	O
