TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesdy	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
1st	O
,	O
3d	O
,	O
4th	O
,	O
and	O
6th	O
Days	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
1697	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
Ninth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bayly	O
;	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
1st	O
,	O
3d	O
,	O
4th	O
,	O
and	O
6th	O
Days	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
1697	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Edward	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Crispe	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
are	O
as	O
follow	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hayward	I-pers
Nathanael	B-pers
Spinlowe	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
Isaac	B-pers
Ash	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Blagrave	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Garthorne	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Whittell	I-pers
William	B-pers
Attlebey	I-pers
Matthew	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
John	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Westcoat	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Attley	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Fitzgerald	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Rich	I-pers
John	B-pers
Tims	I-pers
William	B-pers
Pitts	I-pers
John	B-pers
Woodford	I-pers
John	B-pers
Francklyn	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
these	O
:	O
Anne	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
Lionel	I-place
Backchurch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
13	O
Yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Bone-Lace	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Valentine	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolph	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
three	O
Stuff	O
Gowns	O
,	O
six	O
Stuff	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Graves	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Deale	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
Sattin	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
4	O
Guineas	O
in	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Clarkeson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
likewise	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Tabby	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
six	O
lac	O
'd	O
Aprons	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Night-roil	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Latham	I-pers
;	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
likewise	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloath	O
Coat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Westcoat	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shooes	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Hood	O
and	O
Scarf	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Fidwell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
she	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
Entry	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
her	O
Lap	O
full	O
of	O
things	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
a	O
Glover	O
lived	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
replied	O
,	O
No	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
Do	O
n't	O
be	O
angry	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
harm	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
about	O
her	O
business	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Lodger	O
going	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
called	O
to	O
Fidwell	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Do	O
you	O
use	O
to	O
let	O
people	O
go	O
up	O
Stairs	O
and	O
no	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
see	O
whether	O
all	O
was	O
safe	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
pursued	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
dropt	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
other	O
people	O
were	O
there	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
she	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
might	O
steal	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Hellens	I-place
by	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Giles	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
Margaret	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
his	O
Daughter	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
7	O
l.	O
a	O
Whistle	O
,	O
a	O
Hood	O
and	O
Scarf	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
his	O
Daughter	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
her	O
Husband	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
Cup	O
was	O
sold	O
for	O
30	O
s.	O
to	O
one	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
,	O
by	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
Church	O
in	O
Southwark	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
what	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
was	O
by	O
the	O
command	O
of	O
her	O
Husband	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Judith	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
and	O
Joanna	B-pers
Faux	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bartholomew	I-place
the	I-place
Less	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
26	O
Yards	O
of	O
NorwichStuff	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Combes	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
Joanna	O
Faux	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
put	O
her	O
self	O
upon	O
her	O
Trial	O
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
that	O
they	O
both	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
cheapned	O
some	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
whilst	O
they	O
were	O
busy	O
they	O
took	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Stuff	O
called	O
Eslimine	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
their	O
ways	O
;	O
Wilson	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
her	O
,	O
they	O
being	O
both	O
Comrades	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Tabitha	B-pers
Peck	I-pers
and	O
Rebeccah	B-pers
Slade	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Lothbury	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
5	O
Yards	O
of	O
stain	O
'd	O
Cloath	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Timothy	B-pers
Rutter	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declar	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
to	O
cheapen	O
some	O
Druggits	O
,	O
and	O
Peck	O
desired	O
the	O
Maid	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Necessary	O
House	O
,	O
which	O
accordingly	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
looking	O
upon	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Spoon	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Dripping-Pan	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
after	O
they	O
went	O
their	O
ways	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
missing	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
had	O
nothing	O
found	O
upon	O
them	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
abundance	O
of	O
people	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Danzey	I-pers
,	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Whitechappel	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
taking	O
two	O
dozen	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buttons	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoe-Buckles	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shirt-Buckles	O
,	O
from	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Son	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Highway	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Minories	O
and	O
tempted	O
the	O
little	O
Boy	O
into	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
cut	O
the	O
Buttons	O
off	O
his	O
Cloaths	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
but	O
young	O
in	O
Years	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
notorious	O
Offender	O
in	O
such	O
kinds	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
several	O
times	O
in	O
Newgate	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
after	O
all	O
,	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Andrew	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Ann	B-pers
Holford	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
did	O
combine	O
and	O
conspire	O
to	O
take	O
Susan	B-pers
Lovering	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Heiress	O
of	O
great	O
Substance	O
in	O
Moneys	O
,	O
Lands	O
and	O
Tenements	O
,	O
against	O
her	O
Will	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Custody	O
of	O
those	O
to	O
whom	O
the	O
Charge	O
of	O
her	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
join	O
her	O
in	O
Matrimony	O
with	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
Mitchel	O
:	O
And	O
the	O
better	O
to	O
effect	O
their	O
Designs	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
they	O
caused	O
a	O
Precept	O
called	O
a	O
Bill	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
against	O
the	O
Young	O
Lady	O
and	O
her	O
Maid	O
Mary	B-pers
Brand	I-pers
,	O
for	O
100	O
l.	O
at	O
the	O
Suit	O
of	O
one	O
Wilcox	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
such	O
person	O
as	O
Wilcox	O
.	O
It	O
farther	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
with	O
Mitchel	O
to	O
the	O
Bayliff	O
's	O
Follower	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
great	O
Care	O
in	O
executing	O
the	O
Process	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
for	O
a	O
Friend	O
of	O
his	O
;	O
accordingly	O
they	O
went	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
to	O
Lincoln's-Inn	O
Gate	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
stood	O
waiting	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
the	O
Lady	O
and	O
her	O
Maid	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Walks	O
,	O
a	O
Woman	O
that	O
set	O
them	O
,	O
run	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
Bayliffs	O
,	O
who	O
accordingly	O
forced	O
the	O
Lady	O
and	O
her	O
Maid	O
into	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
carrying	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
crying	O
out	O
Murder	O
,	O
the	O
Coach	O
was	O
stopt	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Lady	O
bail	O
'd	O
by	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Young	O
,	O
who	O
caused	O
the	O
Bayliffs	O
to	O
be	O
seized	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
brought	O
out	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
could	O
not	O
make	O
it	O
appear	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
such	O
person	O
as	O
Wilcox	O
,	O
or	O
had	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
from	O
him	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Misdemeanor	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Griffyth	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
100	O
l.	O
weight	O
of	O
Iron	O
,	O
val	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Walter	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Journeyman	O
,	O
and	O
work	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
observed	O
to	O
carry	O
Iron	O
out	O
with	O
him	O
every	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
Cobler	O
;	O
his	O
Master	O
being	O
made	O
acquainted	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
marked	O
a	O
Parcel	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
afterwards	O
upon	O
search	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Cobler	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
the	O
Cobler	O
declared	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
not	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Penny	O
a	O
Pound	O
for	O
it	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
Iron	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Hester	B-pers
Metcalf	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
Bridget	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Lawson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Head-Dress	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Steel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
144	O
Yards	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Matthew	B-pers
Whitster	I-pers
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Grace	B-pers
Pierce	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
8	O
Yards	O
of	O
Flower	O
'd	O
Damask	O
Silk	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Barrow	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
they	O
both	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
38	O
Yards	O
of	O
strip	O
'd	O
Silk	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Rufford	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Cheeses	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Lucy	B-pers
Pottinger	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Lawrence	I-place
Jury	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
4	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
5	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
two	O
lac	O
'd	O
Crevats	O
,	O
a	O
Hood	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
Moneys	O
numbred	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Skolthrope	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Yards	O
of	O
Green	O
Bays	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
Yards	O
of	O
Camblet	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Metcalf	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Chepsey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Greenstreet	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
all	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
word	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
think	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Man	O
above	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
need	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Joan	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Honyhoone	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Flora	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Flower	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Chamberlain	I-pers
,	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Robbery	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
10	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bendy	I-pers
an	O
Italian	O
,	O
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
s.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
Flower	O
and	O
Chamberlain	O
,	O
with	O
others	O
unknown	O
,	O
came	O
about	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Sweet	O
Powder	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
sent	O
his	O
Maid	O
out	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
Sixpenny	O
worth	O
of	O
Farthings	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
returned	O
they	O
shut	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
upon	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
his	O
Maid	O
,	O
who	O
crying	O
out	O
Murder	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
next	O
Neighbours	O
came	O
over	O
the	O
Wall	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
hard	O
by	O
,	O
who	O
being	O
search	O
'd	O
they	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Pistols	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
Scimiter	O
,	O
a	O
Betty	O
,	O
with	O
Gaggs	O
and	O
Cords	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
fitting	O
for	O
their	O
purpose	O
.	O
Flower	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
lye	O
on	O
the	O
Mercy	O
of	O
the	O
Bench	O
;	O
but	O
Chamberlain	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
making	O
a	O
halt	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
they	O
offered	O
to	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
thinking	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
Bayliffs	O
,	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
Companions	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Robbery	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Wilsden	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Ram	O
and	O
two	O
Lambs	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Butteridge	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
were	O
taken	O
at	O
Paddington	O
about	O
7	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
rode	O
upon	O
a	O
Mare	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Handbasket	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Lamb	O
in	O
each	O
Basket	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
men	O
gave	O
him	O
leave	O
to	O
ride	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
a	O
Witness	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
poor	O
Fellow	O
,	O
who	O
workt	O
hard	O
for	O
his	O
Livelihood	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Stuff	O
Gowns	O
,	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
lose	O
her	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
back	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
an	O
End	O
of	O
Gold	O
and	O
Silver	O
Woman	O
in	O
Monmouth-street	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
nor	O
could	O
she	O
give	O
any	O
good	O
account	O
of	O
her	O
self	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shorditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Crevat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
;	O
and	O
two	O
Holland	O
Aprons	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
August	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Harrow	B-place
on	I-place
the	I-place
Hill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
an	O
Ewe	O
Sheep	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
16	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Crossby	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
Dram-Cup	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Flanders	O
lac	O
'd	O
Head-dress	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Scarf	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Roach	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
:	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
lying	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
into	O
the	O
Closet	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
what	O
business	O
she	O
had	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
Pressmasters	O
;	O
but	O
mistrusting	O
her	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
her	O
Cap	O
next	O
her	O
Head	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Dram-Cup	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
that	O
she	O
stole	O
them	O
,	O
saying	O
she	O
saw	O
them	O
lye	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Christian	B-pers
Callow	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Le	I-place
Savoy	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Walter	B-pers
Crump	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
two	O
French	O
Pistoles	O
,	O
and	O
Five	O
Pound	O
in	O
Silver	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
the	O
Strand	B-place
about	O
10	O
or	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
minute	O
's	O
time	O
his	O
Money	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
he	O
seized	O
and	O
carried	O
her	O
before	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
told	O
them	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
threw	O
his	O
Money	O
into	O
the	O
Kennel	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
they	O
went	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
found	O
about	O
10	O
s.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
she	O
gave	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
30	O
s.	O
of	O
his	O
Money	O
again	O
,	O
desiring	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
favourable	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
her	O
Trial	O
said	O
she	O
met	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
coming	O
under	O
Somerset-Gate	O
with	O
his	O
Breeches	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Money	O
to	O
lye	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Common	O
Nightwalker	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
David	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
Shrider	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Dutchman	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
,	O
for	O
ravishing	O
and	O
carnally	O
knowing	O
one	O
Esther	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
Age	O
of	O
10	O
Years	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
had	O
got	O
some	O
hurt	O
by	O
taking	O
a	O
large	O
Step	O
down	O
some	O
Stairs	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Penn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Clarkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Child	O
's	O
Stuff	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
Flannel	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Hays	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
not	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Offence	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
called	O
Witness	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
honestly	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Daintree	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Buckles	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
whilst	O
his	O
back	O
was	O
turned	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
went	O
his	O
ways	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
positive	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
making	O
a	O
very	O
frivolous	O
Excuse	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Slocroft	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Slograve	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
for	O
counterfeiting	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
see	O
him	O
Coin	O
Groats	O
,	O
and	O
King	O
Charles	O
the	O
Seconds	O
Mill	O
'd	O
Money	O
,	O
in	O
Carnaby	B-place
street	I-place
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
did	O
do	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
in	O
all	O
his	O
life	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
poor	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
drove	O
a	O
Hackney-Coach	O
for	O
his	O
living	O
;	O
he	O
called	O
divers	O
people	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
all	O
declared	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
think	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Edminton	B-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Hosier	I-pers
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
two	O
and	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Clayton	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
in	O
fear	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
3	O
Muslin	O
Suits	O
of	O
Headcloaths	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
Holland	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
two	O
Muslin	O
Neckcloath	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Hosier	O
declared	O
that	O
being	O
abroad	O
,	O
one	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
Thieves	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
home	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
searcht	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
Top	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
behind	O
the	O
Chimney	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
deny	O
his	O
being	O
there	O
;	O
saying	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Debt	O
,	O
and	O
pursued	O
by	O
Bayliffs	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
run	O
in	O
there	O
for	O
shelter	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
an	O
Offender	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
for	O
diminishing	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Eighth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
Castle	O
's	O
Gang	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
seen	O
her	O
file	O
the	O
New	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
put	O
the	O
Edges	O
on	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
calling	O
divers	O
to	O
prove	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
poor	O
Woman	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ingleton	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
South-Mims	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Black	O
Gelding	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Arthur	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
second	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Black	O
Sattin	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
Blue	O
Linnen	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Garnet	I-pers
and	O
Arthur	O
Dixon	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
Dixon	O
was	O
the	O
Kendal	O
Carrier	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
between	O
Mims	O
and	O
Coney	O
took	O
the	O
Pack-horse	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Gang	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
the	O
Pack	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
the	O
Horse	O
after	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
but	O
being	O
pursued	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Bed	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
hearing	O
them	O
come	O
,	O
ran	O
away	O
in	O
his	O
Shirt	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
pursued	O
and	O
taken	O
in	O
a	O
Hayloft	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
upon	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
and	O
burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
this	O
last	O
Assizes	O
at	O
Wickham	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
Horse	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Isabella	B-pers
Henderson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolphs	I-place
without	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
4	O
Silver	O
Tankards	O
,	O
a	O
flower	O
'd	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Silk	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
not	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Claxton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
Ludgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
40	O
Yards	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Massey	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
Savill	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
the	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Bramstone	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
a	O
Gentleman	B-pers
in	O
the	O
Temple	O
;	O
the	O
Circumstances	O
appeared	O
plain	O
,	O
but	O
having	O
no	O
Positive	O
Evidence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Alhallows	B-place
Barkin	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Masters	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Brass	O
Kettle	O
and	O
a	O
Brass	O
Pot-lid	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Mason	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
;	O
but	O
Allen	O
having	O
confessed	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
door	O
being	O
open	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
B	B-pers
-	I-pers
C	I-pers
-	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Wincomb	B-pers
Syler	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
beating	O
and	O
bruising	O
the	O
said	O
Syler	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
Breast	O
,	O
Neck	O
,	O
and	O
Sides	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
to	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
having	O
arrested	O
C	O
-	O
for	O
some	O
Money	O
that	O
was	O
owing	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
C	O
-	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
Deceased	O
to	O
the	O
George	B-place
and	I-place
Vulture	I-place
Tavern	I-place
,	O
where	O
C	O
-	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
him	O
forgive	O
him	O
the	O
Charges	O
of	O
the	O
Arrest	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
with	O
that	O
he	O
fell	O
foul	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
Beat	O
him	O
.	O
Barnard	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
meddle	O
or	O
make	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Christophers	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
5	O
Muslin	O
Nightroils	O
and	O
4	O
Aprons	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Mennel	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
over	O
his	O
Counter	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
dropt	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
soon	O
after	O
taken	O
:	O
He	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
drop	O
them	O
,	O
nor	O
was	O
ever	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
in	O
all	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolphs	I-place
without	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Yards	O
of	O
Muslin	O
Cloath	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Josias	B-pers
Hale	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
:	O
There	O
was	O
nothing	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Dorcas	B-pers
Morrell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Istleworth	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
7	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Stamp	I-pers
.	O
It	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Lindsey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Whitechappel	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Green	I-pers
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
10	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Serge	O
Breeches	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Spectacles	O
and	O
Case	O
,	O
a	O
French	O
Pistole	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Half	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
23	O
Shillings	O
and	O
Tenpence	O
halfpenny	O
in	O
Moneys	O
numbred	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
that	O
his	O
Chamber	O
Door	O
being	O
open	O
about	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Breeches	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
when	O
taken	O
by	O
the	O
Constable	O
at	O
Mile-end	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Wilsdon	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Abel	B-pers
Sadler	I-pers
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
12	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
5	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
val	O
12	O
s.	O
5	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
2	O
Pewter	O
Tankards	O
,	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
there	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
pretended	O
to	O
help	O
his	O
Wife	O
to	O
a	O
Nurse-Child	O
,	O
but	O
took	O
her	O
view	O
where	O
the	O
weakest	O
place	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
;	O
and	O
accordingly	O
the	O
next	O
night	O
she	O
came	O
and	O
broke	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
in	O
a	O
Field	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
sorting	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
an	O
old	O
Apron	O
,	O
designing	O
to	O
hide	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
Hedge	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
her	O
Employment	O
was	O
to	O
gather	O
Physical	O
Herbs	O
for	O
the	O
Apothecaries	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
was	O
out	O
early	O
that	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Field	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
looking	O
upon	O
them	O
when	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
took	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
denied	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
ever	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
in	O
all	O
her	O
life	O
.	O
But	O
she	O
being	O
an	O
Ill	O
Person	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
having	O
any	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Buckingham	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Hampstead	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Wootten	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
about	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
two	O
Featherbeds	O
,	O
a	O
Bolster	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Curtains	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
a	O
Field	O
by	O
the	O
Half-way	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
that	O
he	O
broke	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
together	O
with	O
George	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Timothy	B-pers
Beaghan	I-pers
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Breast	O
,	O
near	O
to	O
the	O
Right	O
Pap	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
4	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
It	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
committed	O
the	O
Murther	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
thereupon	O
acquitted	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Fulham	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Martin	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
driving	O
a	O
Chariot	O
with	O
two	O
Horses	O
over	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
soon	O
after	O
died	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
by	O
Accident	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Winder	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Adam	B-pers
Greenaway	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Dewin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
for	O
counterfeiting	O
the	O
currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
see	O
him	O
help	O
to	O
finish	O
some	O
Counterfeit	O
Money	O
in	O
Buckridge-street	B-place
;	O
he	O
was	O
convicted	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
for	O
procuring	O
of	O
False	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Dealer	O
in	O
this	O
sort	O
of	O
Trade	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ray	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Oldershaw	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
combining	O
and	O
conspiring	O
by	O
unlawful	O
means	O
to	O
enrich	O
themselves	O
,	O
and	O
thereby	O
to	O
lessen	O
the	O
Esteem	O
and	O
Credit	O
of	O
Exchequer-Bills	O
,	O
maliciously	O
they	O
did	O
contrive	O
to	O
Forge	O
and	O
Counterfeit	O
as	O
many	O
as	O
should	O
amount	O
to	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
40000	O
l.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
that	O
about	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
he	O
met	O
Oldershaw	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
a	O
Jacobite	O
Engraver	O
,	O
they	O
could	O
get	O
40000	O
l.	O
between	O
Four	O
of	O
them	O
Some	O
time	O
after	O
they	O
met	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
Project	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
an	O
Engraver	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Broker	O
would	O
put	O
them	O
off	O
in	O
a	O
Week	O
's	O
time	O
:	O
(	O
In	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
the	O
Lords	O
of	O
the	O
Treasury	O
were	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
who	O
ordered	O
that	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
traced	O
to	O
the	O
bottom	O
:	O
)	O
And	O
accordingly	O
he	O
met	O
Oldershaw	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
an	O
Engraver	O
,	O
and	O
appointed	O
a	O
Meeting	O
;	O
but	O
Oldershaw	O
refused	O
to	O
come	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
That	O
two	O
Evidences	O
would	O
hang	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
still	O
ordering	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
on	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
the	O
Engraver	O
wanted	O
a	O
Pattern	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
procured	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Bill	O
of	O
Five	O
Pounds	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
left	O
him	O
a	O
Watch	O
in	O
the	O
lieu	O
thereof	O
:	O
After	O
that	O
he	O
brought	O
him	O
several	O
Bills	O
that	O
were	O
Blanks	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Ray	O
was	O
to	O
fill	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
refused	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
before	O
his	O
face	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
further	O
proved	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Engraver	O
was	O
to	O
work	O
at	O
Ray	O
's	O
House	O
on	O
London-bridge	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
case	O
of	O
Discovery	O
he	O
should	O
throw	O
the	O
things	O
into	O
the	O
Thames	O
.	O
The	O
Trial	O
lasted	O
very	O
long	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
after	O
all	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Misdemeanor	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Coward	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolph	I-place
without	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
6	O
Yards	O
of	O
Muslin	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Josiah	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
she	O
and	O
one	O
Parker	O
,	O
who	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
to	O
cheapen	O
some	O
Muslin	O
,	O
and	O
whilst	O
they	O
were	O
buisy	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Muslin	O
Nightroil	O
,	O
5	O
Diaper	O
Napkins	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Hodgson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
;	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Prosser	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolphs	I-place
without	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
for	O
Counterfeiting	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
to	O
convict	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Blount	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Acton	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bay	O
Gelding	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bristow	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
said	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
from	O
London	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
suspectiong	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
?	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
swopt	O
for	O
it	O
at	O
Uxbridge	O
Fair	O
.	O
With	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
must	O
seize	O
him	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
leap	O
'd	O
off	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
made	O
his	O
Escape	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
upon	O
his	O
Trial	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Hackney-Coachman	O
,	O
and	O
leaving	O
off	O
his	O
Employment	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Uxbridge	O
to	O
sell	O
his	O
Horses	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
sold	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
a	O
little	O
By-House	O
on	O
this	O
side	O
Uxbridge	O
he	O
swopt	O
with	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
50	O
s.	O
to	O
boot	O
for	O
the	O
Gelding	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Lambert	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Anne	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
10	O
Yards	O
of	O
Edging-Lace	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joyce	B-pers
Chamberlain	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
July	O
;	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
that	O
they	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pauls	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Crape	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
Silk	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
Cup	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Tilford	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
pursued	O
he	O
dropt	O
them	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Jacob	B-pers
Broad	I-pers
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
60	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
100	O
l.	O
in	O
Moneys	O
numbred	O
,	O
a	O
Porringer	O
,	O
4	O
Forks	O
,	O
2	O
Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
denied	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
they	O
did	O
it	O
feloniously	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Shelton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
flower	O
'd	O
Silk	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Adam	B-pers
Greenaway	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lowe	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Robbery	O
,	O
for	O
robbing	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bendy	I-pers
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
s.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
with	O
Flower	O
and	O
Chamberlain	O
when	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
did	O
knock	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
they	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Peruke	O
:	O
She	O
was	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Offender	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
positive	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joan	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Silver	O
Mugs	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
7	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Bryerly	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
proved	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pick-axe	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
Sledge-Hammer	O
8	O
s.	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Evis	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Hobbs	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
for	O
counterfeiting	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
not	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Christian	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Callow	I-pers
,	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Walter	B-pers
White	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
l	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bourne	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
and	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockins	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Metcalf	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
not	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Caudle-Cup	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
35	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
to	O
convict	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
,	O
stealing	O
a	O
Muslin	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
a	O
Hood	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
Yards	O
of	O
Bone-Lace	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
;	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
having	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
for	O
counterfeiting	O
the	O
currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
that	O
they	O
saw	O
her	O
do	O
it	O
in	O
Buckridge-street	B-place
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
calling	O
divers	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
forging	O
a	O
Bill	O
of	O
Sale	O
and	O
Letter	O
of	O
Attorney	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
one	O
Amon	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
Mariner	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Ship	O
the	O
Newcastle	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
Evidence	O
that	O
proved	O
he	O
did	O
confess	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Towers	I-pers
,	O
together	O
with	O
Daniel	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
,	O
who	O
stands	O
attainted	O
of	O
divers	O
Crimes	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Littleford	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Eighth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
300	O
Pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockins	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
60	O
l.	O
and	O
three	O
Holland	O
Caps	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
sold	O
to	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Richardson	O
in	O
Long-Acre	O
for	O
6	O
l.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
calling	O
divers	O
people	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Maddox	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
a	O
Silver	O
Chain	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
from	O
Ann	B-pers
Long	I-pers
,	O
Daughter	O
of	O
William	O
Long	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
she	O
had	O
any	O
felonious	O
Intent	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Nanson	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
stuff	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Mohair	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
an	O
Offinbridge	O
Smock	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Beasely	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
let	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lie	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
went	O
her	O
ways	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Rowland	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
unlawfully	O
Procuring	O
Flasks	O
,	O
Spawd	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Instruments	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
pernicious	O
Trade	O
of	O
Coining	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
divers	O
People	O
of	O
good	O
Esteem	O
and	O
Credit	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
Honest	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
great	O
care	O
and	O
pains	O
for	O
his	O
livelihood	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Seamer	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
upon	O
Three	O
Indictments	O
for	O
a	O
Cheat	O
;	O
the	O
First	O
for	O
Cheating	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Marriot	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
,	O
and	O
Three	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Lace	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
false	O
Affirmation	O
.	O
The	O
Second	O
for	O
Cheating	O
Isaac	B-pers
Tully	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Silk	O
by	O
such	O
means	O
.	O
The	O
Third	O
for	O
Cheating	O
Windsor	B-pers
Sands	I-pers
of	O
two	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Silk	O
by	O
the	O
like	O
means	O
.	O
The	O
Facts	O
were	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Misdemeanors	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Amlln	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stanes	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
followeth	O
,	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
.	O
8	O
.	O
Isaac	O
Blount	O
,	O
Joane	O
Browne	O
,	O
John	O
Chamberlain	O
,	O
Christian	O
Callow	O
,	O
John	O
Dewin	O
,	O
William	O
Flora	O
,	O
alias	O
Flower	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Lowe	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	O
Taylor	O
.	O
The	O
Four	O
Women	O
pleaded	O
their	O
Bellies	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
found	O
with	O
Child	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
27	O
.	O
Mary	O
Bates	O
,	O
B	O
-	O
C	O
-	O
William	O
Buckingham	O
,	O
Ann	O
Crossby	O
,	O
Mary	O
Claxton	O
,	O
Sarah	O
Coward	O
,	O
Mary	O
Deal	O
,	O
John	O
Davis	O
,	O
Joanna	O
Faux	O
,	O
Ann	O
Harding	O
,	O
Sarah	O
Holmes	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Johnson	O
,	O
John	O
Jones	O
,	O
Francis	O
Johnson	O
,	O
Esther	O
Metcalf	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Morgan	O
,	O
Grace	O
Pierce	O
,	O
Mary	O
Parker	O
,	O
Dorothy	O
Steel	O
,	O
Sarah	O
Scot	O
,	O
Mary	O
Skulthrope	O
,	O
George	O
Steward	O
,	O
William	O
Smith	O
,	O
Judith	O
Wilson	O
,	O
Margaret	O
Warren	O
,	O
Mary	O
Wood	O
,	O
and	O
Sarah	O
Winder	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
,	O
5	O
.	O
Ann	O
Allen	O
,	O
John	O
Griffith	O
,	O
Jane	O
Jones	O
,	O
Margaret	O
Nanson	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Smith	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
,	O
4	O
Henry	O
Danzey	O
,	O
John	O
Ingleton	O
,	O
alias	O
Adams	O
Richard	O
Lindsey	O
,	O
and	O
Thomas	O
Turner	O
.	O
Andrew	O
Palmer	O
Fined	O
20	O
Nobles	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
committed	O
for	O
Three	O
Months	O
.	O
Christopher	O
Dickenson	O
Fined	O
5	O
Nobles	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
at	O
Tower-hill	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
Charingcross	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
have	O
respited	O
the	O
Sentence	O
against	O
Thomas	O
Ray	O
,	O
and	O
Samuel	O
Oldershaw	O
,	O
till	O
a	O
further	O
time	O
.	O
And	O
likewise	O
the	O
Sentence	O
against	O
Mary	O
Seamer	O
.	O
Some	O
Books	O
Printed	O
for	O
B.	O
Aylmer	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Three	O
Pigeons	O
in	O
Cornhil	O
.	O
THE	O
Works	O
of	O
the	O
Most	O
Reverend	O
Dr.	O
John	O
Tillotson	O
,	O
late	O
Lord	O
Archbishop	O
of	O
Canterbury	O
,	O
containing	O
Fifty	O
four	O
Sermons	O
and	O
Discourses	O
on	O
Several	O
Occasions	O
;	O
together	O
with	O
the	O
Rule	O
of	O
Faith	O
.	O
Being	O
all	O
that	O
were	O
published	O
by	O
his	O
Grace	O
himself	O
;	O
and	O
now	O
collected	O
into	O
one	O
Volume	O
:	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
an	O
Alphabetical	O
Table	O
of	O
the	O
Principal	O
Matters	O
.	O
Price	O
20	O
s.	O
Six	O
Sermons	O
;	O
viz	O
.	O
Of	O
Stedfastness	O
in	O
Religion	O
.	O
Of	O
Family	O
Religion	O
.	O
Of	O
Education	O
of	O
Children	O
.	O
Of	O
the	O
Advantages	O
of	O
an	O
Early	O
Piety	O
.	O
By	O
his	O
Grace	O
,	O
John	O
,	O
late	O
Archbishop	O
of	O
Canterbury	O
.	O
In	O
120.	O
price	O
18	O
d.	O
A	O
Persuasive	O
to	O
frequent	O
Communion	O
in	O
the	O
Holy	O
Sacrament	O
of	O
the	O
Lord	O
's	O
Supper	O
;	O
Also	O
by	O
his	O
Grace	O
,	O
John	O
,	O
late	O
Archbishop	O
of	O
Canterbury	O
.	O
in	O
120	O
.	O
Bound	O
6	O
d.	O
or	O
Stitch	O
'd	O
in	O
8vo	O
.	O
3	O
d.	O
or	O
something	O
Cheaper	O
to	O
those	O
that	O
are	O
so	O
Charitable	O
to	O
give	O
away	O
Numbers	O
.	O
Twelve	O
select	O
Sermons	O
,	O
preach	O
'd	O
upon	O
several	O
Occasions	O
;	O
By	O
the	O
Right	O
Reverend	O
Richard	O
Lord	O
Bishop	O
of	O
Bath	O
and	O
Wells	O
.	O
In	O
8vo	O
.	O
Price	O
4	O
s.	O
The	O
Holy	O
Bible	O
,	O
Containing	O
the	O
Old	O
Testament	O
and	O
the	O
New	O
;	O
with	O
Annotations	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
exact	O
Parallel	O
Scriptures	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
Annex	O
'd	O
the	O
Harmony	O
of	O
the	O
Gospels	O
;	O
as	O
also	O
the	O
Reduction	O
of	O
the	O
Jewish	O
Weights	O
,	O
Coins	O
and	O
Measure	O
,	O
to	O
our	O
English	O
Standards	O
.	O
And	O
a	O
Table	O
of	O
the	O
Promises	O
in	O
Scripture	O
.	O
By	O
Samuel	O
Clark	O
,	O
Minister	O
of	O
the	O
Gospel	O
.	O
Printed	O
in	O
Folio	O
on	O
a	O
very	O
Fair	O
Letter	O
;	O
the	O
like	O
never	O
before	O
in	O
one	O
Volume	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
newly	O
added	O
a	O
very	O
Exact	O
and	O
Useful	O
Concordance	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
same	O
Author	O
.	O
Price	O
30	O
Shill	O
.	O
The	O
Works	O
of	O
the	O
Learned	O
Isaac	O
Barrow	O
D.	O
D.	O
late	O
Master	O
of	O
Trinity	O
Colledge	O
in	O
Cambridge	O
.	O
Published	O
by	O
the	O
Reverend	O
Dr.	O
Tillotson	O
,	O
late	O
Archbishop	O
of	O
Canterbury	O
.	O
The	O
Third	O
Volume	O
.	O
Containing	O
Forty	O
five	O
Sermons	O
,	O
upon	O
several	O
Occasions	O
,	O
compleating	O
his	O
English	O
Works	O
.	O
A	O
Brief	O
Exposition	O
of	O
the	O
Apostles	O
Creed	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Learned	O
Dr.	O
Isaac	O
Barrow	O
,	O
late	O
Master	O
of	O
Trinity	O
College	O
in	O
Cambridge	O
;	O
(	O
Never	O
before	O
printed	O
,	O
being	O
very	O
different	O
from	O
his	O
Volume	O
of	O
Sermons	O
on	O
it	O
:	O
)	O
to	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
His	O
Exposition	O
of	O
the	O
Lord	O
's	O
Prayer	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Ten	O
Commandments	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
In	O
8vo	O
.	O
Price	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Practical	O
Discourses	O
upon	O
the	O
Consideration	O
of	O
our	O
Latter	O
End	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Danger	O
and	O
Mischief	O
of	O
Delaying	O
Repentance	O
.	O
By	O
Dr.	O
Isaac	O
Barrow	O
,	O
in	O
8vo	O
.	O
Price	O
18	O
d.	O
A	O
Defence	O
of	O
the	O
B.	O
Trinity	O
:	O
Never	O
before	O
printed	O
.	O
By	O
Dr.	O
Isaac	O
Barrow	O
,	O
in	O
8vo	O
.	O
Price	O
12	O
d.	O
The	O
Four	O
Last	O
Things	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Death	O
,	O
Judgment	O
,	O
Heaven	O
,	O
and	O
Hell	O
:	O
Practically	O
Considered	O
and	O
Applied	O
.	O
By	O
W.	O
Bates	O
,	O
D.	O
D.	O
in	O
120	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
Sermons	O
of	O
the	O
Forgiveness	O
of	O
Sins	O
.	O
On	O
Psalm	O
130.	O
v.	O
4	O
.	O
Also	O
by	O
Dr.	O
Bates	O
.	O
Price	O
18	O
d.	O
A	O
Conference	O
with	O
an	O
Anabaptist	O
.	O
By	O
Dr.	O
Assheton	O
of	O
Beckenham	O
in	O
Kent	O
.	O
Price	O
12	O
d.	O
A	O
Theological	O
Discourse	O
of	O
Last	O
Wills	O
and	O
Testaments	O
.	O
Also	O
by	O
Dr.	O
Assheton	O
.	O
Price	O
12	O
d.	O
Several	O
small	O
Books	O
against	O
Debauchery	O
,	O
Profaneness	O
,	O
Blasphemy	O
,	O
Cursing	O
and	O
Swearing	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Also	O
a	O
Method	O
of	O
daily	O
Devotion	O
.	O
By	O
Dr.	O
Assheton	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
d.	O
each	O
,	O
and	O
something	O
cheaper	O
to	O
them	O
that	O
give	O
away	O
Numbers	O
.	O
A	O
Discourse	O
concerning	O
a	O
Death-Bed	O
Repentance	O
.	O
By	O
William	O
Assheson	O
,	O
D.	O
D.	O
Price	O
6	O
d.	O
A	O
Seasonable	O
Vindication	O
of	O
the	O
B.	O
Trinity	O
.	O
Being	O
an	O
Answer	O
to	O
this	O
Question	O
,	O
Why	O
do	O
you	O
believe	O
the	O
Doctrine	O
of	O
the	O
Trinity	O
?	O
Collected	O
from	O
the	O
Works	O
of	O
the	O
Most	O
Reverend	O
Dr.	O
John	O
Tillotson	O
,	O
Late	O
Lord	O
Archbishop	O
of	O
Canterbury	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Right	O
Reverend	O
Dr.	O
Edward	O
Stillingstreet	O
,	O
now	O
Lord	O
Bishop	O
of	O
Worcester	O
By	O
Dr.	O
Assheton	O
.	O
Price	O
12	O
d.	O
A	O
Familiar	O
Guide	O
to	O
the	O
Right	O
and	O
Profitable	O
Receiving	O
of	O
the	O
Lord	O
's	O
Supper	O
:	O
Wherein	O
also	O
the	O
Way	O
and	O
Method	O
of	O
our	O
Salvation	O
is	O
briefly	O
and	O
plainly	O
declared	O
.	O
By	O
T.	O
Dorrington	O
.	O
Price	O
12	O
d.	O
The	O
Council	O
of	O
Trent	O
no	O
Free	O
Assembly	O
:	O
More	O
fully	O
discovered	O
by	O
a	O
Collection	O
of	O
Letters	O
and	O
Papers	O
of	O
the	O
Learned	O
Dr.	O
Vargas	O
and	O
other	O
Great	O
Ministers	O
,	O
who	O
assisted	O
at	O
the	O
said	O
Synod	O
in	O
considerable	O
Posts	O
.	O
Published	O
from	O
the	O
Original	O
Manuscripts	O
in	O
Spanish	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
procured	O
by	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
William	O
Trumbull	O
's	O
Grandfather	O
,	O
Envoy	O
at	O
Brussels	O
in	O
the	O
Reign	O
of	O
King	O
James	O
the	O
First	O
.	O
With	O
an	O
Introductory	O
Discourse	O
concerning	O
Councils	O
,	O
shewing	O
how	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
under	O
Bondage	O
to	O
the	O
Pope	O
.	O
By	O
Michael	O
Geddes	O
,	O
LLD	O
.	O
and	O
Chancellor	O
of	O
the	O
Cathedral	O
Church	O
of	O
Sarum	O
.	O
In	O
8vo	O
.	O
Price	O
4	O
s.	O
G.	O
Keith	O
's	O
second	O
Narrative	O
of	O
the	O
Proceedings	O
at	O
Turners-hall	O
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
1697	O
.	O
In	O
410	O
.	O
Price	O
6	O
d.	O
A	O
Brief	O
History	O
of	O
Moseovioe	O
;	O
and	O
of	O
other	O
less	O
,	O
known	O
Countries	O
lying	O
,	O
Eastward	O
of	O
Russia	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Cethay	O
.	O
Of	O
their	O
Manners	O
,	O
Religion	O
,	O
Government	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Being	O
very	O
Proper	O
at	O
this	O
particular	O
Time	O
to	O
be	O
read	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Arrival	O
of	O
the	O
Czar	O
and	O
his	O
Great	O
Embassy	O
into	O
Europe	O
.	O
Gathered	O
from	O
the	O
Writings	O
of	O
several	O
Eye-Witnesses	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Best	O
Authors	O
.	O
By	O
John	O
Milter	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
(	O
before	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Sight	O
.	O
)	O
In	O
Octav	O
Price	O
12	O
d.	O
ADVERTISEMENT	O
.	O
THere	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
the	O
Press	O
,	O
and	O
will	O
be	O
Published	O
in	O
Michaelmas-Term	O
.	O
Several	O
Sermons	O
on	O
the	O
Fifth	O
Chapter	O
of	O
St.	O
Matthew	O
:	O
By	O
the	O
Learned	O
and	O
Pious	O
Dr.	O
Anthony	O
Horneck	O
,	O
late	O
Minister	O
of	O
the	O
Savoy	O
.	O
Published	O
from	O
His	O
own	O
Notes	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
Widow	O
.	O
In	O
Octavo	O
Printing	O
for	O
Brabazon	O
Aylmer	O
Cornhil	O
.	O
AN	O
Admirable	O
Water	O
against	O
Convulsion	O
Fits	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Falling-Sickness	O
.	O
Being	O
a	O
Secret	O
kept	O
in	O
an	O
Eminent	O
Family	O
for	O
many	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
for	O
general	O
good	O
made	O
publick	O
.	O
Price	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
Small	O
Bottle	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
sold	O
by	O
B.	O
Aylmer	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
.	O
You	O
that	O
do	O
want	O
a	O
Cure	O
and	O
Physician	O
need	O
,	O
If	O
that	O
you	O
come	O
betimes	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
be	O
cur	O
'd	O
with	O
speed	O
.	O
He	O
liveth	O
at	O
the	O
Blew	O
Ball	O
in	O
Whale-bone-Court	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Lower-end	O
of	O
Bartholomew-Lane	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
.	O
WHO	O
infallibly	O
cures	O
the	O
French	O
Disease	O
and	O
Claps	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
its	O
numerous	O
Attendants	O
,	O
which	O
oftentimes	O
are	O
the	O
product	O
of	O
other	O
grievous	O
and	O
lasting	O
Diseases	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
utter	O
ruin	O
of	O
many	O
,	O
besides	O
frequently	O
untimely	O
Death	O
,	O
procured	O
by	O
them	O
through	O
grand	O
Abuses	O
,	O
committed	O
by	O
the	O
irregular	O
and	O
base	O
Methods	O
and	O
Medicines	O
of	O
foolish	O
and	O
unskilful	O
Pretenders	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
therefore	O
to	O
Advertise	O
those	O
Persons	O
who	O
are	O
efflicted	O
with	O
the	O
Disease	O
abovesaid	O
,	O
to	O
repair	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
performeth	O
the	O
true	O
and	O
perfect	O
Cure	O
thereof	O
,	O
without	O
hindrance	O
of	O
Business	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
all	O
desireable	O
and	O
imaginable	O
speed	O
and	O
secrefic	O
.	O
His	O
Pills	O
only	O
prepared	O
for	O
the	O
French	O
Disease	O
and	O
the	O
Running	O
of	O
the	O
Reins	O
,	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
in	O
Boxes	O
of	O
several	O
Prices	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
Venereal	O
Arcanaes	O
,	O
at	O
occasion	O
requires	O
.	O
Price	O
from	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
to	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
from	O
3	O
s.	O
to	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
.	O
These	O
Pills	O
are	O
free	O
from	O
Mercury	O
,	O
and	O
proper	O
in	O
all	O
Diseases	O
where	O
Purging	O
as	O
requisite	O
.	O
His	O
Diet-Drink	O
cleanses	O
the	O
Reins	O
,	O
provokes	O
Urine	O
,	O
an	O
abates	O
the	O
sharp	O
pains	O
or	O
stoppage	O
of	O
Urine	O
in	O
the	O
Running	O
of	O
the	O
Reins	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Bottle	O
.	O
