TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
19th	O
,	O
20th	O
,	O
21st	O
,	O
and	O
22d	O
Days	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
1697	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
Ninth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
THe	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bayly	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
19th	O
,	O
20th	O
,	O
21st	O
,	O
and	O
22d	O
Days	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
1697	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Edward	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
Salathiel	B-pers
Lovell	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
are	O
as	O
follow	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Pearce	I-pers
Rice	B-pers
Saywell	I-pers
John	B-pers
Watmore	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Hobdey	I-pers
John	B-pers
Ridout	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Garret	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Thorpe	I-pers
William	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
Benjamin	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Pettit	I-pers
William	B-pers
Woollaston	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Edmund	B-pers
Salter	I-pers
Bennet	B-pers
Giles	I-pers
William	B-pers
Avis	I-pers
Peter	B-pers
King	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
James	I-pers
William	B-pers
Graves	I-pers
Jeremiah	B-pers
Lewin	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
Daniel	B-pers
Emms	I-pers
John	B-pers
Uncles	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
How	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
these	O
:	O
Jane	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
Mildred	I-place
Breadstreet	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Gillingham	I-pers
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cooke	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
12	O
yards	O
of	O
Scarlet	O
Stuff	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
;	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
:	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Woolchurch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Simon	B-pers
Mayne	I-pers
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
and	O
secretly	O
taking	O
a	O
Laced	O
Crivat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Laced	O
Ruffles	O
5	O
s.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Post	O
house	O
with	O
some	O
Letters	O
,	O
he	O
mist	O
the	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Neckloath	O
about	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Neck	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
given	O
him	O
by	O
one	O
Susan	B-pers
Mayle	I-pers
,	O
who	O
lived	O
in	O
Half-Moon	O
Alley	O
in	O
Bishop'sgate	O
Street	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
having	O
considered	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Magnes	I-place
by	I-place
the	I-place
Bridge	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Alderidge	I-pers
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
secretly	O
taking	O
a	O
linnen	O
Bag	O
.	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
3	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
Moneys	O
numbred	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
over	O
London-Bridge	B-place
the	O
Boy	O
came	O
of	O
one	O
side	O
of	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
feeling	O
somebody	O
give	O
his	O
Pocket	O
a	O
touch	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Boy	O
,	O
who	O
immediately	O
gave	O
him	O
his	O
Money	O
again	O
:	O
He	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
saying	O
it	O
lay	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
hearing	O
the	O
Man	O
make	O
inquiry	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
but	O
young	O
in	O
Years	O
,	O
but	O
old	O
in	O
Wickedness	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Haynes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
Buttolph	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Porringer	O
,	O
Pepper-box	O
and	O
Salt	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
:	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Golding	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Jonas	I-pers
Pettit	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hearn	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Old	I-pers
Iron	I-pers
,	O
as	O
Principals	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Raby	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
as	O
Accessary	O
after	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Powis	I-pers
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
4	O
Silver	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
16	O
l.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
having	O
an	O
occasion	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
about	O
some	O
Business	O
,	O
he	O
left	O
the	O
Plate	O
in	O
its	O
usual	O
plate	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Fellow	O
Servant	O
having	O
occasion	O
to	O
use	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
fetch	O
'd	O
a	O
pair	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
returning	O
with	O
them	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
,	O
she	O
mist	O
them	O
that	O
were	O
left	O
behind	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
applied	O
themselves	O
to	O
the	O
Keeper	O
of	O
the	O
Gate-house	O
,	O
who	O
accordingly	O
took	O
them	O
in	O
Hedge-Lane	O
with	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Pick-lock	O
Keys	O
,	O
amongst	O
which	O
was	O
one	O
called	O
a	O
500	O
l.	O
Jack	O
:	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
Evidence	O
who	O
declared	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
Golding	O
and	O
Hearn	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
andthat	O
Hearn	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
Wall	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
Picklock-key	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
Door	O
where	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
George	O
in	O
the	O
Pall-Mall	O
,	O
where	O
Raby	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
with	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Weights	O
and	O
Skales	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
6	O
l.	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
told	O
her	O
they	O
were	O
stole	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
her	O
where	O
;	O
they	O
could	O
say	O
but	O
little	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
Offenders	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
.	O
John	O
Golding	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Arrigrig	I-pers
,	O
together	O
with	O
Richard-Lewley	B-pers
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
John	B-pers
Gibbons	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silver-hilted	O
Sword	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
Golding	O
had	O
broke	O
the	O
Gate-house	O
Prison	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
got	O
a	O
Woman	O
to	O
set	O
him	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Goaler	O
's	O
Assistance	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
fearing	O
that	O
they	O
would	O
fly	O
if	O
they	O
knew	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
counterfeited	O
himself	O
Drunk	O
,	O
and	O
Arrigrig	O
seeing	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
jostled	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Sword	O
whilst	O
the	O
other	O
seemed	O
to	O
please	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Song	O
;	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
they	O
went	O
their	O
ways	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
pursued	O
them	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
getting	O
Assistance	O
they	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
knocked	O
off	O
the	O
Hill	O
of	O
the	O
Sword	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
found	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
.	O
John	O
Golding	O
and	O
Richard	O
Arrigzig	O
were	O
again	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Sir	O
Theophilus	B-pers
Ogelthorpe	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
four	O
Forks	O
,	O
a	O
Salt	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
handle	O
knife	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Door	O
lockt	O
;	O
but	O
coming	O
home	O
found	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
gone	O
:	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
Evidence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
opened	O
the	O
Door	O
with	O
false	O
Keys	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Plate	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
Hardings	O
in	O
the	O
Mint	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
them	O
4	O
s.	O
an	O
Ounce	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
had	O
but	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
themselves	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Arrigrig	O
,	O
Golding	O
,	O
Hearne	O
:	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Jackson	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Nuning	B-pers
Miles	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolphs	I-place
without	I-place
Algate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
with	O
a	O
Diamond	O
Stone	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edmund	B-pers
East	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
she	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Savoy	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
13	O
Fathom	O
of	O
Cable-rope	O
,	O
value	O
17	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
16	O
Ells	O
of	O
Linnen	O
Cloath	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Peirson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
fealoniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sattin	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
Sable	O
Tippet	O
,	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Muslin	O
Headcloaths	O
,	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Wake	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Katherine	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
an	O
Indian	O
Mantua	O
Gown	O
lined	O
with	O
Sattin	O
,	O
a	O
Callico	O
Gown	O
lined	O
with	O
Silk	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Alice	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
Black-Friers	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
Hood	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
a	O
Tippet	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Womens	O
Shoes	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Knit	O
Gloves	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Alice	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
:	O
and	O
a	O
Long	O
Scarf	O
,	O
Sarsenet-hood	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Gloves	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Horsington	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
did	O
let	O
her	O
lodge	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
opportunity	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
they	O
imployed	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Beadles	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
brought	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
she	O
confest	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
did	O
work	O
for	O
her	O
Living	O
,	O
making	O
Tapistry-Hangings	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
evil	O
Fame	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Deale	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Hood	O
and	O
Scarf	O
,	O
with	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
Moneys	O
numbred	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
;	O
and	O
another	O
Spoon	O
,	O
Hood	O
,	O
Coral	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Broad	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
Nights	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
advantage	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
taken	O
,	O
was	O
put	O
in	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
confest	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
lie	O
there	O
with	O
her	O
Mother	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
any	O
thing	O
away	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
idle	O
Body	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Golding	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Arrigrig	I-pers
were	O
again	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Creed	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
Nine	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
two	O
Cups	O
,	O
one	O
with	O
a	O
Cover	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
without	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
two	O
Tumblers	O
6	O
l.	O
a	O
Sugar-box	O
4	O
l.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
carried	O
into	O
the	O
Mint	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
sold	O
to	O
one	O
Harding	O
for	O
11	O
l.	O
and	O
shared	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
alledged	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Alderson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Duncomb	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
Eleven	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
;	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
Perriwig	O
,	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Cup	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
open	O
the	O
Lock	O
with	O
Picklock-keys	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
brought	O
out	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
his	O
ways	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
he	O
pawned	O
the	O
Gown	O
for	O
18	O
s.	O
at	O
a	O
Brokers	O
in	O
Shoe-Lane	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
formerly	O
pardoned	O
for	O
such	O
Offences	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burlary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Lumley	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Laced	O
Night-rail	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Buttons	O
set	O
with	O
Stones	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
with	O
Picklock-keys	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
also	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Cane	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Caster	O
Hat	O
,	O
a	O
Childs	O
Holland	O
Cap	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Neckcloath	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hinchman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
did	O
see	O
her	O
come	O
intothe	O
Shop	O
,	O
she	O
mistrusting	O
her	O
,	O
watched	O
her	O
as	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
being	O
stopt	O
,	O
she	O
dropt	O
the	O
Hat	O
:	O
She	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
never	O
did	O
an	O
ill	O
thing	O
in	O
all	O
her	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
workt	O
hard	O
for	O
her	O
living	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Oakely	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Hanwell	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Weather-Sheep	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
18	O
d.	O
two	O
Ewe	O
Sheep	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
Black	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Lambs	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Reeve	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3	O
d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
:	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
stole	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Grounds	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
Islington	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
hired	O
by	O
a	O
Man	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
Sixpence	O
to	O
drive	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
likewise	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
great	O
care	O
and	O
pains	O
for	O
a	O
Livelihood	O
by	O
selling	O
Stockings	O
about	O
the	O
Country	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
so	O
plain	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
How	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Hope	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Infant	O
of	O
the	O
Age	O
of	O
Six	O
years	O
,	O
by	O
driving	O
a	O
Loaded	O
Cart	O
over	O
the	O
Belly	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Infant	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
it	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
playing	O
by	O
Parker	B-place
's	I-place
Lane	I-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
by	O
with	O
his	O
Cart	O
,	O
drove	O
the	O
same	O
over	O
it	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
alledged	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
see	O
the	O
Child	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
hurt	O
,	O
except	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
by	O
the	O
Wheel	O
against	O
a	O
Stall	O
that	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Beare	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lamb	I-pers
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
3	O
Saddles	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
s.	O
4	O
Bridles	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Horse-Cloath	O
12	O
d	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
Beare	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
Jones	O
,	O
who	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
Sadler	O
in	O
Castle-Street	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Mews	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
plainly	O
proved	O
against	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
acquitted	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Golding	O
was	O
tried	O
again	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Golding	I-pers
,	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Winder	I-pers
in	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Parish	I-place
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
9	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Silk	O
Quilt	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
Pendulum	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Scarlet	O
Cloak	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
thrust	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
the	O
Clock	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Leicester-fields	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
were	O
sold	O
to	O
one	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Waters	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Hance	I-pers
,	I-pers
and	I-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
his	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
5	O
pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
18	O
Napkins	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Underwood	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Man	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
put	O
her	O
self	O
upon	O
her	O
Trial	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
was	O
by	O
her	O
Husband	O
's	O
direction	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Arrigrig	I-pers
was	O
again	O
indicted	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Denny	I-pers
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Sebastian	B-pers
Le	I-pers
Feaver	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
9	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Camblet	O
Cloak	O
,	O
a	O
Coat	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
declared	O
that	O
they	O
opened	O
his	O
Door	O
in	O
Suffolk	B-place
street	I-place
,	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
Goods	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
one	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Waters	O
,	O
who	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
them	O
:	O
Arrigrig	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
Denny	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
stranger	O
to	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
having	O
considered	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Isaac	B-pers
Blunt	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brown	O
Bay	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Lowdell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
left	O
the	O
Horse	O
at	O
Gravesend	B-place
in	O
a	O
Field	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
the	O
same	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
inquiry	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Horse	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Stable	O
in	O
White	O
Horse-street	O
in	O
Stepny	O
Parish	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
over	O
to	O
Southwark	O
with	O
an	O
Old	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
met	O
a	O
Country	O
man	O
,	O
who	O
asked	O
him	O
whether	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
help	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
Chapman	O
for	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
with	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
Swop	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
him	O
some	O
Money	O
to	O
boot	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
they	O
agreed	O
;	O
he	O
called	O
People	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Bargain	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
work	O
'd	O
the	O
Horse	O
publickly	O
in	O
the	O
Streets	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Hackny-Coachman	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Higham	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Old	I-pers
Iron	I-pers
,	O
was	O
again	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Hare	I-pers
at	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Seventh	O
year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
Sheets	O
,	O
six	O
dozen	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
twenty	O
Yards	O
of	O
Flannel	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
one	O
George	B-pers
Hind	I-pers
took	O
out	O
the	O
Pin	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Reed	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Eling	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
Richard	B-pers
Norton	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Seventh	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Gold	O
Buttons	O
with	O
Stones	O
20	O
s.	O
11	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
l.	O
in	O
Silver	O
:	O
And	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
Joseph	B-pers
Deverall	I-pers
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
of	O
an	O
Ivory	O
hasted	O
Knife	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
Moneys	O
,	O
numbred	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Norton	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
from	O
London	O
to	O
Brandford	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Deverall	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
rode	O
together	O
till	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
a	O
place	O
called	O
Gunners-Berry-Lane	B-place
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
set	O
upon	O
by	O
two	O
Highway-men	O
,	O
who	O
robb	O
'd	O
and	O
bound	O
them	O
.	O
Deverall	O
was	O
not	O
positive	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
alledged	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Serjeant	O
in	O
the	O
Marines	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Board	O
the	O
Dutchess	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
when	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
3	O
Canvas	O
Sheets	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lock	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
Smock	O
,	O
4	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Murry	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
she	O
sold	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
a	O
Cellar	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
though	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
plainly	O
against	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Gadesby	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Peters	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Ward	I-place
of	I-place
Limestreet	I-place
,	O
Butcher	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
his	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
her	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
Thigh	O
near	O
to	O
the	O
Groin	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
three	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
upon	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
Stabbing	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
in	O
his	O
Rage	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Knife	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
did	O
stick	O
and	O
stab	O
his	O
said	O
Wife	O
,	O
she	O
not	O
having	O
struck	O
first	O
,	O
or	O
having	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
defendher	O
self	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Butcher	O
in	O
Leaden-Hall	B-place
Market	I-place
.	O
The	O
first	O
Evidence	O
being	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
the	O
Market	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
hear	O
the	O
Woman	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
Mother	O
,	O
Mother	O
,	O
your	O
Son	O
has	O
kill	O
'd	O
me	O
!	O
And	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
her	O
up	O
in	O
his	O
Arms	O
,	O
and	O
say	O
,	O
Lord	O
,	O
Lord	O
,	O
what	O
have	O
I	O
done	O
!	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
lift	O
his	O
left	O
Hand	O
up	O
to	O
his	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
run	O
the	O
Knife	O
at	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
whilst	O
he	O
was	O
talking	O
with	O
some	O
People	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Mother	O
stood	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
a	O
sudden	O
the	O
Woman	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
That	O
her	O
Son	O
had	O
killed	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
her	O
Mother	O
came	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
speak	O
but	O
clapt	O
her	O
hand	O
upon	O
her	O
Wound	O
;	O
and	O
his	O
Mother	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
You	O
Rogue	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
done	O
?	O
And	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
have	O
kill	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
I	O
have	O
done	O
?	O
And	O
she	O
fell	O
down	O
between	O
them	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Collar	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
killed	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
better	O
end	O
her	O
Days	O
then	O
she	O
did	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
she	O
has	O
done	O
both	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
falls	O
out	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
some	O
swore	O
they	O
saw	O
the	O
Knife	O
sticking	O
in	O
her	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Blood	O
running	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
He	O
confest	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
two	O
days	O
before	O
in	O
ill	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
the	O
Knife	O
at	O
her	O
twice	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
for	O
what	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
get	O
none	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
gave	O
him	O
ill	O
Words	O
,	O
with	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
his	O
Knife	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
Stall	O
in	O
a	O
Passion	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
to	O
hurt	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
better	O
have	O
kill	O
'd	O
himself	O
than	O
killed	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
the	O
Wound	O
came	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
;	O
for	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Knife	O
he	O
held	O
it	O
with	O
the	O
point	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
when	O
he	O
threw	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
divers	O
People	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
his	O
Wife	O
was	O
a	O
grievous	O
Scold	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
that	O
would	O
never	O
suffer	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
quiet	O
,	O
let	O
him	O
do	O
what	O
he	O
could	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Wilful	O
Murther	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
Stabbing	O
also	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Ayres	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bridgets	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
for	O
Counterfeiting	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
see	O
him	O
stamp	O
three	O
Counterfeit	O
Pieces	O
at	O
one	O
Bulley	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
did	O
do	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
in	O
all	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
divers	O
People	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Gregg	I-pers
,	I-pers
and	I-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
his	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
for	O
counterfeiting	O
the	O
Current	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
did	O
see	O
the	O
Woman	O
coin	O
Crowns	O
and	O
Half-Crowns	O
in	O
Crown-Alley	B-place
in	I-place
Moorfields	I-place
;	O
and	O
having	O
Information	O
they	O
search	O
'd	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
found	O
all	O
things	O
fitting	O
for	O
the	O
Trade	O
.	O
The	O
Man	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
never	O
did	O
do	O
,	O
or	O
see	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
in	O
all	O
his	O
Life	O
.	O
The	O
Woman	O
did	O
Justify	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
well	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
her	O
self	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bulley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bridgets	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
for	O
Counterfeiting	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
see	O
him	O
hold	O
the	O
Tools	O
when	O
Ayres	O
struck	O
off	O
the	O
Pieces	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
divers	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
56	O
l.	O
weight	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
Evidence	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
,	O
for	O
taking	O
two	O
Brass	O
Pullies	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Crane	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Friend	I-pers
took	O
them	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
Brasier	O
in	O
Houndsditch	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
stop	O
'd	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
Friend	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
for	O
a	O
Debt	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Misdemeanor	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Whiting	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Alderson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolph	I-place
's	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
Samuel	B-pers
Birmingham	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
16	O
l.	O
in	O
Moneys	O
.	O
Whiting	O
remained	O
obstinate	O
for	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
plead	O
,	O
and	O
received	O
Sentence	O
to	O
be	O
prest	O
to	O
death	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Press	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
what	O
he	O
must	O
undergo	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
Plead	O
,	O
which	O
accordingly	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
weighing	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
,	O
they	O
dogged	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
under	O
Aldgate	B-place
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Narrow	O
Passage	O
they	O
see	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
from	O
him	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
positively	O
proved	O
against	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
Second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Bedingfield	B-pers
Higham	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Silver	O
Comb-box	O
,	O
a	O
Powder-box	O
,	O
two	O
Caudle	O
Cups	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
through	O
Devonshire	B-place
Square	I-place
,	O
they	O
saw	O
the	O
Window	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
helping	O
him	O
in	O
by	O
getting	O
upon	O
his	O
Shoulders	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
they	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
25	O
l.	O
and	O
shared	O
the	O
Money	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
Third	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Amos	I-pers
42	O
yards	O
of	O
Bone-Lace	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
they	O
cut	O
the	O
Box	O
of	O
Lace	O
from	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
White-hart	B-place
Inn	I-place
in	I-place
Aldersgate-Street	I-place
:	O
It	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Peirson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
a	O
Cup	O
,	O
two	O
Spoons	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Titcomb	I-pers
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomazin	B-pers
Steel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Lawrence	I-place
Jury	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
54	O
yards	O
of	O
Black	O
Crape	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Cutby	I-pers
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Simon	B-pers
Cadiz	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
11	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
or	O
was	O
any	O
ways	O
concerned	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Apron	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
38	O
s.	O
in	O
Moneys	O
numbred	O
,	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Doble	I-pers
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
proved	O
her	O
Innocence	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Whitechappel	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Roger	B-pers
Gwyn	I-pers
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Seventh	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Cloath	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Bever	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Curtains	O
and	O
Vallens	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
confess	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
his	O
Trial	O
denied	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
his	O
Confession	O
was	O
extorted	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
arrested	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
20	O
l.	O
in	O
Moneys	O
numbred	O
;	O
the	O
Moneys	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
get	O
a	O
Smith	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
a	O
false	O
Key	O
.	O
He	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
making	O
a	O
long	O
and	O
frivolous	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
,	O
thereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Chafingdish	O
,	O
a	O
Salt	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Goslin	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
there	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Fire	O
by	O
Darby	B-place
Court	I-place
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
help	O
the	O
People	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
by	O
a	O
Constable	O
that	O
searcht	O
him	O
:	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plain	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
for	O
counterfeiting	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Sixth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
divers	O
People	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
getting	O
and	O
procuring	O
great	O
quantities	O
of	O
King	O
James	O
's	O
Declarations	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Seditious	O
Pamphlet	O
,	O
called	O
The	O
Depredations	O
of	O
the	O
Dutch	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sent	O
some	O
Barrels	O
to	O
be	O
set	O
at	O
a	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
standing	O
there	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
they	O
happened	O
to	O
remove	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Heads	O
fell	O
out	O
,	O
discovered	O
the	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Misdemeanor	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Lewis	B-pers
Skidmore	I-pers
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
for	O
Counterfeiting	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Eighth	O
year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
And	O
was	O
likewise	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
counterfeiting	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
some	O
Year	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
followed	O
the	O
Trade	O
for	O
some	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
fled	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
Staffordshire	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
for	O
Counterfeiting	O
the	O
Current	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Seventh	O
year	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Silver-Smith	O
by	O
Trade	O
;	O
he	O
called	O
divers	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hyat	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Pancrass	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Counterfeiting	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Seventh	O
year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Birchman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
White-Chappel	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Rape	O
committed	O
on	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Bouchier	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Eighth	O
year	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
alledged	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Brother	O
James	O
,	O
forced	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
Holbourn	O
into	O
Tottenham-Court	B-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
and	O
there	O
lay	O
with	O
her	O
against	O
her	O
will	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
drank	O
with	O
her	O
several	O
times	O
;	O
and	O
called	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
proved	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
came	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
Brick	O
kiln	O
with	O
her	O
own	O
Consent	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
took	O
down	O
a	O
Truss	O
of	O
Straw	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
Bolster	O
;	O
where	O
she	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
merry	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
did	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
own	O
consent	O
by	O
reason	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
cry	O
out	O
;	O
thereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Cecilia	B-pers
Labree	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
:	O
The	O
first	O
for	O
Counterfeiting	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
Filing	O
the	O
New	O
Money	O
of	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
Tools	O
fitting	O
for	O
that	O
pernicious	O
Trade	O
of	O
false	O
Coyning	O
,	O
the	O
like	O
hath	O
scarcely	O
been	O
heard	O
of	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Mill	O
,	O
Fly	O
,	O
Edgers	O
,	O
Crucibles	O
,	O
with	O
all	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
besides	O
Money	O
that	O
was	O
unfinished	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
so	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Downes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Counterfeiting	O
the	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
he	O
drove	O
this	O
wicked	O
Trade	O
within	O
a	O
fortnight	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
bespeak	O
Dies	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Skrew	O
for	O
a	O
Mill	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
Newgate	O
before	O
upon	O
such	O
Accounts	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Golding	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hearne	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Old	I-pers
Iron	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Raby	I-pers
;	O
the	O
two	O
first	O
as	O
Principals	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
as	O
Accessary	O
after	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
great	O
value	O
,	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Dowty	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
sold	O
two	O
Gold	O
Frames	O
of	O
Pictures	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Raby	O
for	O
3	O
l.	O
It	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
all	O
guilty	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Harwood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Johns	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
divers	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
did	O
lift	O
up	O
the	O
Latch	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
noise	O
awaked	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
pursuing	O
her	O
,	O
catcht	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
dropt	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
Barbara	B-pers
Boyce	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Watch	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plain	O
against	O
Walker	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
others	O
acquitted	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Counterfeiting	O
the	O
currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Alderson	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Whiteing	I-pers
,	O
were	O
again	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
lac	O
'd	O
Night-Royl	O
,	O
a	O
Blue	O
Cloath-Cloak	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Captain	O
Samuel	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
,	O
on	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
November	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Eighth	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Heston	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Counterfeiting	O
Four	O
Sixpences	O
,	O
and	O
Eighty	O
four	O
Groats	O
;	O
and	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
for	O
putting	O
away	O
False	O
Money	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
not	O
Evidence	O
enough	O
to	O
convict	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolphs	I-place
without	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Zingham	O
Stuff	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Wale	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
She	O
was	O
acquitted	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Osborne	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
unknown	O
;	O
and	O
likewise	O
for	O
Stealing	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Roger	B-pers
Gillingham	I-pers
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Hix	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Hix	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
counterfeiting	O
the	O
currant	O
Coyn	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
for	O
counterfeiting	O
the	O
currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
followeth	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
13	O
.	O
Richard	O
Arrigrig	O
,	O
John	O
Alderson	O
,	O
William	O
Denny	O
,	O
Richard	O
Downes	O
,	O
John	O
Golding	O
,	O
George	O
Gadesby	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Gregg	O
,	O
William	O
Horne	O
,	O
Cicilia	O
Labree	O
,	O
William	O
Smith	O
,	O
Lewis	O
Skidmore	O
,	O
Richard	O
Whiting	O
and	O
Mary	O
Walker	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
13	O
.	O
Robert	O
Austin	O
,	O
Martha	O
Burton	O
,	O
Mary	O
Butler	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Cook	O
,	O
Mary	O
Deale	O
,	O
Catherine	O
Gilbert	O
,	O
Mary	O
Haynes	O
,	O
Peter	O
Hanse	O
,	O
Mary	O
Harwood	O
,	O
Mary	O
Jackson	O
,	O
John	O
Marsh	O
,	O
Thomazin	O
Steel	O
,	O
and	O
Jane	O
Williams	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
.	O
5	O
.	O
Joseph	O
Beare	O
,	O
Daniel	O
Jones	O
,	O
William	O
Oakeley	O
,	O
Alice	O
Rennolds	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	O
Watson	O
Joseph	O
Smith	O
fined	O
Five	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
committed	O
till	O
he	O
pay	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Edward	O
Morgan	O
fined	O
One	O
hundred	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
committed	O
till	O
he	O
pay	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
find	O
Sureties	O
for	O
6	O
Months	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Gregg	O
,	O
Cicilia	O
Labree	O
and	O
Mary	O
Walker	O
declared	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
with	O
Quick	O
Child	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
being	O
impanelled	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
with	O
quick	O
Child	O
,	O
therefore	O
ordered	O
for	O
Execution	O
.	O
John	O
Towers	O
,	O
formerly	O
Convicted	O
for	O
Coining	O
,	O
is	O
ordered	O
to	O
prepare	O
himself	O
for	O
Death	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
Some	O
Books	O
Printed	O
for	O
B.	O
Aylmer	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Pigeons	O
in	O
Cornhil	O
.	O
THE	O
Works	O
of	O
the	O
Most	O
Reverend	O
Dr.	O
John	O
Tilletson	O
,	O
late	O
Lord	O
Archbishop	O
of	O
Canterbury	O
,	O
containing	O
Fifty	O
four	O
Sermons	O
and	O
Discourses	O
on	O
Several	O
Occasions	O
;	O
together	O
with	O
the	O
Rule	O
of	O
Faith	O
.	O
Being	O
all	O
that	O
were	O
published	O
by	O
his	O
Grace	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
collected	O
into	O
one	O
Volume	O
:	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
an	O
Alphabetical	O
Table	O
of	O
the	O
Principal	O
Matters	O
.	O
Price	O
20	O
s.	O
Six	O
Sermons	O
;	O
viz	O
.	O
Of	O
Stedfastness	O
in	O
Religion	O
.	O
Of	O
Family	O
Religion	O
.	O
Of	O
Education	O
of	O
Children	O
.	O
Of	O
the	O
Advantages	O
of	O
an	O
Early	O
Piety	O
.	O
By	O
his	O
Grace	O
,	O
John	O
,	O
late	O
Archbishop	O
of	O
Canterbury	O
.	O
In	O
120.	O
price	O
18	O
d.	O
A	O
Persuasive	O
to	O
frequent	O
Communion	O
in	O
the	O
Holy	O
Sacrament	O
of	O
the	O
Lord	O
's	O
Supper	O
;	O
Also	O
by	O
his	O
Grace	O
,	O
John	O
,	O
late	O
Archbishop	O
of	O
Canterbury	O
.	O
In	O
120	O
.	O
Bound	O
6	O
d.	O
or	O
Stitch	O
'd	O
in	O
8vo	O
.	O
3	O
d.	O
or	O
something	O
Cheaper	O
to	O
those	O
that	O
are	O
so	O
Charitable	O
to	O
give	O
away	O
Numbers	O
.	O
The	O
Holy	O
Bible	O
,	O
Containing	O
the	O
Old	O
Testament	O
and	O
the	O
New	O
;	O
with	O
Annotations	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
exact	O
Parallel	O
Scriptures	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
Annex	O
'd	O
the	O
Harmony	O
of	O
the	O
Gospels	O
;	O
as	O
also	O
the	O
Reduction	O
of	O
the	O
Jewish	O
Weights	O
,	O
Coins	O
and	O
Measures	O
,	O
to	O
our	O
English	O
Standards	O
.	O
And	O
a	O
Table	O
of	O
the	O
Promises	O
in	O
Scripture	O
.	O
By	O
Samuel	O
Clark	O
,	O
Minister	O
of	O
the	O
Gospel	O
.	O
Printed	O
in	O
Folio	O
on	O
a	O
very	O
Fair	O
Letter	O
;	O
the	O
like	O
never	O
before	O
in	O
one	O
Volume	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
newly	O
added	O
a	O
very	O
Exact	O
and	O
Useful	O
Concordance	O
.	O
Price	O
30	O
Shill	O
.	O
The	O
Works	O
of	O
the	O
Learned	O
Isaac	O
Barrow	O
D.	O
D.	O
late	O
Master	O
of	O
Trinity	O
Colledge	O
in	O
Cambridge	O
.	O
Published	O
by	O
the	O
Reverend	O
Dr.	O
Tillotson	O
,	O
late	O
Archbishop	O
of	O
Canterbury	O
.	O
The	O
Third	O
Volume	O
.	O
Containing	O
Forty	O
five	O
Sermons	O
,	O
upon	O
several	O
Occasions	O
,	O
compleating	O
his	O
English	O
Works	O
.	O
A	O
Brief	O
Exposition	O
of	O
the	O
Apostles	O
Creed	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Learned	O
Dr.	O
Isaac	O
Barrow	O
,	O
late	O
Master	O
of	O
Trinity	O
College	O
in	O
Cambridge	O
;	O
(	O
Never	O
before	O
printed	O
,	O
being	O
very	O
different	O
from	O
his	O
Volume	O
of	O
Sermons	O
on	O
it	O
:	O
)	O
to	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
His	O
Exposition	O
of	O
the	O
Lord	O
's	O
Prayer	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Ten	O
Commandments	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
In	O
8vo	O
.	O
Price	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Practical	O
Discourses	O
upon	O
the	O
Consideration	O
of	O
our	O
Latter	O
End	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Danger	O
and	O
Mischief	O
of	O
Delaying	O
Repentance	O
.	O
By	O
Dr.	O
Isaac	O
Barrow	O
,	O
in	O
8vo	O
.	O
Price	O
18	O
d.	O
A	O
Defence	O
of	O
the	O
B.	O
Trinity	O
:	O
Never	O
before	O
printed	O
.	O
By	O
Dr.	O
Isaac	O
Barrow	O
,	O
in	O
8vo	O
.	O
Price	O
12	O
d.	O
The	O
Four	O
Last	O
Things	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Death	O
,	O
Judgment	O
,	O
Heaven	O
,	O
and	O
Hell	O
:	O
Practically	O
Considered	O
and	O
Applied	O
.	O
By	O
W.	O
Bates	O
,	O
D.	O
D.	O
in	O
120	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
Sermons	O
of	O
the	O
Forgiveness	O
of	O
Sins	O
.	O
On	O
Psalm	O
130.	O
v.	O
4	O
.	O
Also	O
by	O
Dr.	O
Bates	O
.	O
Price	O
18	O
d.	O
Enchiridion	O
Medicum	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
A	O
Manual	O
of	O
Physick	O
.	O
Being	O
a	O
Compendium	O
of	O
the	O
whole	O
Art	O
.	O
In	O
3	O
Parts	O
.	O
viz	O
.	O
I	O
.	O
Of	O
Diseases	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
.	O
II	O
.	O
Of	O
Diseases	O
of	O
the	O
Breast	O
.	O
III	O
.	O
Of	O
the	O
Diseases	O
of	O
the	O
Belly	O
.	O
Wherein	O
is	O
briefly	O
shewed	O
;	O
1	O
.	O
The	O
Names	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
The	O
Derivation	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
The	O
Causes	O
.	O
4	O
.	O
The	O
Signs	O
.	O
5	O
.	O
The	O
Prognosticks	O
.	O
And	O
6	O
.	O
A	O
Rational	O
Method	O
of	O
Cute	O
.	O
Comprehending	O
the	O
substance	O
of	O
the	O
more	O
approved	O
Authors	O
both	O
Ancient	O
and	O
Modern	O
.	O
Published	O
for	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
all	O
Persons	O
,	O
being	O
fitted	O
to	O
the	O
meanest	O
Capacity	O
.	O
By	O
Robert	O
Johnson	O
,	O
Med	O
.	O
Professor	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
A	O
Brief	O
Concordance	O
to	O
the	O
Holy	O
Bible	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
usual	O
and	O
useful	O
Places	O
which	O
one	O
may	O
have	O
occasion	O
to	O
seek	O
for	O
:	O
In	O
a	O
new	O
Method	O
.	O
By	O
Samuel	O
Clark	O
,	O
M.	O
A	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
A	O
Conference	O
with	O
an	O
Anabaptist	O
.	O
By	O
Dr.	O
Assheton	O
of	O
Beckenham	O
in	O
Kent	O
.	O
Price	O
12	O
d.	O
A	O
Theological	O
Discourse	O
of	O
Last	O
Wills	O
and	O
Testaments	O
.	O
Also	O
by	O
Dr.	O
Assheton	O
.	O
Price	O
12	O
d.	O
Several	O
small	O
Books	O
against	O
Debauchery	O
,	O
Profaneness	O
,	O
Blasphemy	O
,	O
Cursing	O
and	O
Swearing	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
By	O
Dr.	O
Assheton	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
d.	O
each	O
,	O
and	O
something	O
cheaper	O
to	O
them	O
that	O
give	O
away	O
Numbers	O
.	O
A	O
Discourse	O
concerning	O
a	O
Death-Bed	O
Repentance	O
.	O
By	O
William	O
Assheton	O
,	O
D.	O
D.	O
Price	O
6	O
d.	O
A	O
Seasonable	O
Vindication	O
of	O
the	O
B.	O
Trinity	O
.	O
Being	O
an	O
Answer	O
to	O
this	O
Question	O
,	O
Why	O
do	O
you	O
believe	O
the	O
Doctrine	O
of	O
the	O
Trinity	O
?	O
Collected	O
from	O
the	O
Works	O
of	O
the	O
Most	O
Reverend	O
Dr.	O
John	O
Tillotson	O
,	O
Late	O
Lord	O
Archbishop	O
of	O
Canterbury	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Right	O
Reverend	O
Dr.	O
Edward	O
Stilling	O
steeet	O
,	O
now	O
Lord	O
Bishop	O
of	O
Worcester	O
.	O
Price	O
12	O
d.	O
A	O
Familiar	O
Guide	O
to	O
the	O
Right	O
and	O
Profitable	O
Receiving	O
of	O
the	O
Lord	O
's	O
Supper	O
:	O
Wherein	O
also	O
the	O
Way	O
and	O
Method	O
of	O
our	O
Salvation	O
is	O
briefly	O
and	O
plainly	O
declared	O
.	O
By	O
T.	O
Dorrington	O
.	O
Price	O
12	O
d.	O
Mr.	O
Flamsteed	O
's	O
Correct	O
Tide-Table	O
,	O
shewing	O
the	O
true	O
times	O
of	O
the	O
High	O
Water	O
at	O
London-Bridge	O
,	O
every	O
Day	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
,	O
1697	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
d.	O
Proper	O
for	O
all	O
Publick	O
Houses	O
.	O
A	O
general	O
History	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
both	O
Ecclesiastical	O
and	O
Civil	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
earliest	O
Account	O
of	O
Time	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Reign	O
of	O
his	O
present	O
Majesty	O
King	O
William	O
III	O
.	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
most	O
Ancient	O
Records	O
,	O
Manuscripts	O
,	O
and	O
Printed	O
Historians	O
.	O
With	O
Memorials	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
Eminent	O
Persons	O
in	O
Church	O
and	O
State	O
.	O
As	O
also	O
the	O
Foundations	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
noted	O
Monasteries	O
,	O
and	O
both	O
Universities	O
.	O
Vol	O
.	O
I	O
.	O
By	O
James	O
Tyrrel	O
,	O
Esqz	O
.	O
Ovid	O
's	O
Metamorphosis	O
:	O
Translated	O
by	O
several	O
Hands	O
.	O
Vol	O
.	O
I	O
.	O
Containing	O
the	O
first	O
Five	O
Books	O
,	O
adorn	O
'd	O
with	O
Sculptures	O
.	O
A	O
Sermon	O
preached	O
at	O
St.	O
Mary-le-Bow	O
,	O
April	O
the	O
15th	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Societies	O
for	O
Reformation	O
of	O
Manners	O
.	O
By	O
Lilly	O
Butler	O
,	O
Minister	O
of	O
St.	O
Mary	O
Aldermanbury	O
.	O
In	O
8vo	O
.	O
Price	O
4	O
d.	O
A	O
Sermon	O
preach	O
'd	O
at	O
St.	O
Mary	O
Le	O
Bow	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
Court	O
of	O
Aldermen	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
April	O
1697.	O
being	O
a	O
Day	O
appointed	O
for	O
a	O
General	O
and	O
Publick	O
Fast	O
.	O
By	O
Lilly	O
Butler	O
,	O
Minister	O
of	O
St.	O
Mary	O
Aldermanbury	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
to	O
give	O
notice	O
to	O
all	O
Persons	O
for	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
the	O
Publick	O
,	O
That	O
W.	O
Elmy	O
,	O
Professor	O
of	O
Physick	O
,	O
and	O
Operator	O
,	O
of	O
known	O
Integrity	O
,	O
liveth	O
at	O
the	O
Blue	O
Ball	O
in	O
Whalebone-Court	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Lower	O
End	O
of	O
Bartholomew-Lane	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
WHO	O
most	O
safely	O
and	O
expeditiously	O
cures	O
Deafness	O
and	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
Ears	O
in	O
any	O
,	O
of	O
what	O
Age	O
soever	O
,	O
(	O
if	O
curable	O
)	O
and	O
at	O
first	O
fight	O
,	O
by	O
Inspection	O
,	O
resolves	O
the	O
Patient	O
if	O
so	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
as	O
most	O
Eminent	O
Persons	O
of	O
Quality	O
can	O
testify	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
Remedies	O
ready	O
prepared	O
for	O
the	O
Preservation	O
of	O
the	O
Hearing	O
,	O
in	O
those	O
who	O
through	O
some	O
great	O
defects	O
in	O
the	O
Sounding	O
Membrane	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Impediments	O
in	O
the	O
Auditory	O
Passages	O
,	O
are	O
not	O
perfectly	O
curable	O
,	O
which	O
Remedies	O
preserve	O
them	O
from	O
ever	O
growing	O
worse	O
,	O
and	O
improves	O
their	O
Hearing	O
to	O
Old	O
Age	O
.	O
He	O
hath	O
likewise	O
a	O
PILL	O
which	O
cleanseth	O
the	O
Blood	O
from	O
all	O
Impurities	O
,	O
infallibly	O
cureth	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
.	O
It	O
cures	O
the	O
Headach	O
to	O
Admiration	O
,	O
taking	O
away	O
Vapours	O
offensive	O
to	O
the	O
Brain	O
.	O
It	O
creates	O
a	O
good	O
Stomach	O
and	O
Digestion	O
,	O
takes	O
away	O
sharpness	O
of	O
Urine	O
,	O
and	O
cleanseth	O
the	O
Reins	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
a	O
certain	O
and	O
present	O
Remedy	O
for	O
the	O
Gout	O
.	O
It	O
cures	O
all	O
Joint-pains	O
,	O
resists	O
Fevers	O
and	O
Surfeits	O
,	O
and	O
preserves	O
the	O
Body	O
in	O
perfect	O
health	O
.	O
He	O
bath	O
Boxes	O
of	O
several	O
Prices	O
,	O
according	O
as	O
Necessity	O
requires	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
,	O
from	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
to	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
from	O
3	O
s.	O
to	O
6	O
s.	O
He	O
hath	O
likewise	O
a	O
most	O
Excellent	O
Gargarism	O
or	O
Mouth-water	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
make	O
black	O
or	O
yellow	O
Teeth	O
as	O
white	O
as	O
Ivory	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
times	O
using	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
will	O
certainly	O
cure	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
Diseases	O
incident	O
to	O
the	O
Mouth	O
,	O
Teeth	O
and	O
Gums	O
.	O
The	O
Glasses	O
are	O
of	O
several	O
Prices	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
.	O
