TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesdy	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
7th	O
,	O
8th	O
,	O
9th	O
,	O
and	O
10th	O
Days	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
1697	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
Ninth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice	O
Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bayly	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
7th	O
,	O
8th	O
,	O
9th	O
,	O
and	O
10th	O
Days	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
1697	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Edward	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
Salathiel	B-pers
Lovell	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
are	O
as	O
follow	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rawlinson	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Seaton	I-pers
Nicholas	B-pers
Aris	I-pers
Christopher	B-pers
Blower	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Norton	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
John	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Akers	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Manning	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
John	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
William	O
Buck	O
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pitts	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
Jonas	B-pers
Morley	I-pers
Moses	B-pers
Colwell	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Bullimore	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Rathborne	I-pers
John	B-pers
Ilford	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Nurse	I-pers
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Nevill	I-pers
John	B-pers
Wiborne	I-pers
William	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
these	O
:	O
Magdalen	B-pers
Lanceson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Catherine	I-place
Creechurch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Silver	O
Tankards	O
,	O
a	O
Portinger	O
,	O
Salt	O
,	O
and	O
Cup	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Masey	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susan	B-pers
Farrow	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Lawrence	I-place
Jury	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
silver	O
Salts	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Beaker	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Fenny	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
Second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	O
Fenny	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
his	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
bed	O
about	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
Ten	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
back	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
under	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Cutting-board	O
;	O
he	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
made	O
her	O
escape	O
upon	O
the	O
Leads	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
;	O
and	O
nothing	O
being	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Hendon	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Bernard	B-pers
Sander	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Money-bag	O
and	O
Wallet	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
four	O
pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
three	O
half	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
Eightscore	O
pound	O
in	O
Silver	O
on	O
the	O
ninth	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
;	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
saying	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
first	O
Fact	O
that	O
ever	O
he	O
committed	O
in	O
all	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
drawn	O
in	O
by	O
Ill	O
Company	O
to	O
commit	O
this	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
leave	O
himself	O
to	O
the	O
Mercy	O
of	O
the	O
Bench	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Snelling	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
Spoon	O
and	O
a	O
Diaper	O
Tablecloath	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Sheffeild	I-pers
,	O
and	O
divers	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bolesworth	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elinor	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
her	O
Female	O
Infant	O
Bastard	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
throwing	O
the	O
same	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
it	O
was	O
choaked	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
at	O
Bosomes	O
Inn	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
afraid	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
some	O
of	O
her	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
saw	O
some	O
signs	O
which	O
made	O
her	O
to	O
mistrust	O
her	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
Evidence	O
that	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
lie	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
complained	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
Three	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
she	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Vault	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
;	O
after	O
some	O
time	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
mistrusted	O
,	O
they	O
searcht	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Midwife	O
,	O
who	O
examined	O
her	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
confest	O
the	O
matter	O
to	O
her	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
Stilborn	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
Eight	O
Weeks	O
to	O
go	O
of	O
her	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
no	O
design	O
to	O
murther	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
having	O
considered	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Hester	B-pers
Duberrey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
20	O
yards	O
of	O
Muslin-Cloath	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Goddard	I-pers
and	O
Stephen	B-pers
Maxey	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
pretended	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Cloath	O
,	O
and	O
whilst	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
busy	O
with	O
other	O
Customers	O
,	O
she	O
conveyed	O
the	O
Goods	O
under	O
her	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
and	O
dropt	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
window	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
having	O
it	O
taken	O
upon	O
her	O
:	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
see	O
her	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
her	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
design	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
her	O
Trial	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
never	O
there	O
in	O
all	O
her	O
life	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
Ludgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fielder	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
standing	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Narrow	O
Passage	O
by	O
Ludgate	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
with	O
the	O
Gown	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
owned	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
walking	O
by	O
the	O
Shop	O
and	O
he	O
saw	O
theGown	O
,	O
lie	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
never	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
in	O
all	O
his	O
life	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Purcell	I-pers
,	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Banister	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Brick-batt	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
nigh	O
to	O
the	O
right	O
Ear	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
soon	O
,	O
after	O
died	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
by	O
accident	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
very	O
young	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
&	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pancrass	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
,	O
for	O
robbing	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
12	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
numbred	O
;	O
the	O
second	O
for	O
robbing	O
Robert	B-pers
Webster	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
6	O
s.	O
The	O
Prosecutors	O
declared	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
Hamstead	O
on	O
Whitsunday	O
about	O
5	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
set	O
upon	O
them	O
between	O
Tottenham-Court	B-place
and	O
Hamstead	B-place
;	O
Hart	O
said	O
that	O
Wheeler	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
set	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
Money	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
Webster	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
the	O
Stile	O
,	O
one	O
met	O
him	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
behind	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
hands	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
withal	O
he	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
leave	O
the	O
Trade	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
bring	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Gallows	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
12	O
d.	O
or	O
18	O
d.	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
provided	O
they	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
;	O
but	O
withal	O
they	O
held	O
his	O
hands	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
;	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
they	O
gave	O
Hart	O
6	O
d.	O
of	O
his	O
Money	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
Webster	O
12	O
d.	O
to	O
go	O
through	O
their	O
Journey	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
happened	O
that	O
some	O
Boys	O
going	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Hedge	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
offered	O
them	O
Money	O
to	O
pursue	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
Tottenham-Court	O
,	O
they	O
parted	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
further	O
pursued	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
taken	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
had	O
Curtlasses	O
,	O
Swords	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Weapons	O
,	O
besides	O
Cords	O
,	O
Perriwigs	O
,	O
and	O
Marks	O
;	O
they	O
all	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
plain	O
against	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samuel	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
after	O
an	O
Act	O
of	O
Parliament	O
made	O
for	O
granting	O
to	O
His	O
Majesty	O
certain	O
Duties	O
upon	O
Vellum	O
,	O
Parchment	O
,	O
and	O
Paper	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
June	O
in	O
the	O
9th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
did	O
forge	O
and	O
make	O
a	O
Counterfeit	O
Sixpenny	O
Stamp	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
stamp	O
Paper	O
with	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
uttered	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
be	O
false	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
throw	O
himself	O
on	O
the	O
Mercy	O
of	O
the	O
Bench	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Sparrow	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborne	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
God	O
,	O
value	O
24	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Dodson	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Winchley	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Locket	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Crook	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
likewise	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Timothy	B-pers
Penniston	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Forging	O
and	O
Counterfeiting	O
a	O
Sixpenny	O
Stamp	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
stamp	O
several	O
quantities	O
of	O
Paper	O
,	O
and	O
uttered	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
false	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
drive	O
the	O
Trade	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
a	O
Block	O
fitting	O
for	O
such	O
purposes	O
,	O
and	O
under	O
his	O
Bed	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Dye	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
Evidence	O
that	O
did	O
see	O
him	O
stamp	O
7	O
Quires	O
at	O
one	O
time	O
;	O
he	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Block	O
was	O
none	O
of	O
his	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Bibby	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolphs	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
76	O
Yards	O
of	O
Bonelace	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Painter	I-pers
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Randall	B-pers
Kittle	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Alhallows	I-place
Barking	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
five	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Raw	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Bodington	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Porter	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Mercer	O
's	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
work	O
in	O
a	O
Leighter	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
Skone	O
of	O
Silk	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Bale	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
it	O
lay	O
loose	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Leighter	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
Breeches	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susan	B-pers
Mayall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Vedast	I-place
,	I-place
alias	I-place
Foster-Lane	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
28	O
Yards	O
of	O
Silk-Ribbon	O
,	O
value	O
45	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Trevor	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
a	O
young	O
Man	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
and	O
cheapned	O
a	O
Hatband	O
,	O
and	O
whilst	O
she	O
was	O
busy	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
stopt	O
and	O
the	O
Ribbon	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
saying	O
she	O
was	O
never	O
there	O
in	O
all	O
her	O
life	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gates	I-pers
and	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolphs	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Littler	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
Chapman	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
put	O
her	O
self	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
He	O
kept	O
a	O
Saleshop	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
in	O
under	O
pretence	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
they	O
stole	O
one	O
away	O
;	O
he	O
mistrusting	O
them	O
,	O
followed	O
them	O
into	O
Cloath-Fair	O
,	O
where	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
stept	O
up	O
to	O
a	O
strange	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
an	O
unknown	O
Person	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
the	O
other	O
stopped	O
at	O
another	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
follow	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
pretended	O
to	O
tie	O
her	O
Shooe	O
,	O
and	O
thrust	O
the	O
Petticoat	O
into	O
a	O
Cellar	O
Window	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
;	O
she	O
would	O
fain	O
have	O
evaded	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
plain	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Hammond	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Simon	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
put	O
of	O
the	O
Belly	O
,	O
near	O
to	O
the	O
Navel	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
four	O
Inches	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
to	O
the	O
5th	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
drinking	O
together	O
at	O
the	O
Bull-Head	O
Tavern	O
by	O
the	O
Tower	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
and	O
one	O
Cunningham	O
whispered	O
and	O
talked	O
together	O
as	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Company	O
missing	O
them	O
,	O
found	O
them	O
with	O
their	O
Swords	O
drawn	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
pacified	O
them	O
to	O
prevent	O
further	O
mischief	O
;	O
afterwards	O
the	O
Quarrel	O
arose	O
between	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
drew	O
and	O
fought	O
together	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Deceased	O
received	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Wound	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
alledged	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
given	O
to	O
Quarrel	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Design	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
retreat	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
upon	O
his	O
Sword	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
having	O
considered	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Ecclestone	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Judith	B-pers
Bomsellers	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Counterfeiting	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
see	O
them	O
Coyn	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
in	O
Spittle-fieds	B-place
,	O
Shillings	O
and	O
Half	O
crowns	O
of	O
mixt	O
Metal	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
other	O
Evidence	O
that	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
Ecclestone	O
did	O
pour	O
the	O
Metal	O
into	O
the	O
Flasks	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Gregory	O
filed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
Bomsellers	O
brusht	O
it	O
with	O
a	O
Brush	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
this	O
Room	O
,	O
Flasks	O
,	O
Skrews	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Edger	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
things	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Trade	O
.	O
Gregory	O
had	O
confest	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
Coyn	O
Money	O
.	O
Ecclestone	O
and	O
Gregory	O
had	O
formerly	O
received	O
Mercy	O
for	O
this	O
great	O
Crime	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
given	O
Evidence	O
against	O
divers	O
Criminals	O
who	O
have	O
been	O
executed	O
for	O
the	O
like	O
Offence	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
take	O
warning	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
very	O
plain	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
all	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Rudwell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
Drugget	O
Cloath-coat	O
,	O
18	O
Sword-belts	O
,	O
1	O
Watch	O
,	O
24	O
Sword	O
handles	O
,	O
a	O
Pistol	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
41	O
s.	O
in	O
Moneys	O
numbered	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Horns	O
.	O
It	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
Bassishaw	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
fifteen	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Moneys	O
,	O
numbred	O
.	O
It	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
his	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
her	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Case-knife	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
upon	O
the	O
Nape	O
of	O
the	O
Neck	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
four	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
a	O
very	O
worthy	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Phipps	O
,	O
a	O
Councellor	O
,	O
in	O
Bedford-Row	B-place
in	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
;	O
and	O
her	O
Husband	O
coming	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
on	O
a	O
Sunday	O
,	O
she	O
treated	O
him	O
with	O
some	O
cold	O
Roast-Beef	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
happened	O
that	O
whilst	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
called	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
within	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
knowing	O
him	O
by	O
Sight	O
and	O
Voice	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
through	O
the	O
Pails	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
forewarned	O
her	O
of	O
keeping	O
Company	O
with	O
,	O
he	O
grew	O
instantly	O
into	O
a	O
strong	O
fit	O
of	O
Jealousy	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
the	O
said	O
Knife	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
said	O
Wound	O
with	O
that	O
force	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Knife	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
called	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
within	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
above	O
Stairs	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
his	O
ways	O
:	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Parlour	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
her	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
And	O
she	O
replied	O
,	O
It	O
was	O
no	O
great	O
matter	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
her	O
Husband	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
did	O
ask	O
what	O
Fellow	O
that	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Pails	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
going	O
to	O
pursue	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
catcht	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Knife	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
said	O
Wound	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
a	O
sudden	O
she	O
heard	O
a	O
skreeching	O
out	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Child	O
in	O
her	O
Arms	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Deceased	O
lay	O
wallowing	O
in	O
her	O
Gore	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
Whore	O
enough	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
meet	O
him	O
coming	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
askt	O
him	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
:	O
and	O
he	O
replied	O
,	O
You	O
will	O
see	O
what	O
is	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
Whore	O
long	O
enough	O
.	O
And	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
this	O
bloody	O
Act	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Lady	O
Nevill	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
upon	O
his	O
Knees	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
killed	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
her	O
pardon	O
.	O
He	O
alledged	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
very	O
ill	O
Woman	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
kept	O
company	O
with	O
one	O
Clun	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
forbad	O
her	O
to	O
do	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
for	O
one	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
tarried	O
out	O
two	O
Nights	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
till	O
afterwards	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Clunne	O
had	O
Lodgings	O
hard	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
every	O
Morning	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
continued	O
with	O
him	O
some	O
hours	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
abused	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
taken	O
his	O
Trunk	O
of	O
Cloaths	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
Clunne	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
.	O
He	O
made	O
it	O
appear	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
Rage	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
thinking	O
there	O
by	O
to	O
extenuate	O
his	O
Crime	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
having	O
considered	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
wilful	O
Murther	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Cokeley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Endfield	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
six	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Hair	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
forty	O
Ounces	O
of	O
burnt	O
Silver	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
West	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Winchester	O
Waggon	O
at	O
Egham	B-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
Endfield-Wash	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
mistrust	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
and	O
quartered	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
lying	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Quarters	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
not	O
deny	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Carthensey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Porter	O
's	O
Silver	O
Badge	O
and	O
Chain	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Pot	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Cravat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Sands	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
did	O
imploy	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
do	O
her	O
business	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
she	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
pull	O
out	O
some	O
Linnen	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
about	O
Twelve	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
she	O
hung	O
a	O
wet	O
Sheet	O
before	O
her	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
plain	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Dudley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Blundell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
Three	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Riding-hood	O
,	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
Flanders	O
Laced	O
Head-dress	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
she	O
took	O
down	O
a	O
pain	O
of	O
Glass	O
,	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Window	O
was	O
open	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
her	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Humphry	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
three	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Dish	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Atford	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
under	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
stopt	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
back	O
and	O
threw	O
the	O
things	O
down	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
design	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
l.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Lewley	I-pers
and	O
Daniel	B-pers
Spires	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gascoyne	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
Hours	O
of	O
Ten	O
and	O
Eleven	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
thence	O
a	O
Crimson	O
Velvet	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Frize	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
a	O
Snuffer	O
and	O
Pan	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Urwin	I-pers
,	O
Esquire	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Sash	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Gang	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
and	O
handed	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
the	O
rest	O
;	O
the	O
matter	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Hatsel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Hendon	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
six	O
dozen	O
of	O
Brass	O
Horse-bells	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
And	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
dozen	O
of	O
Brass	O
Horse-bells	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
him	O
at	O
Kentish	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
owned	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
them	O
again	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
small	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Catherine	B-pers
Kelley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Woollnoth	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Tongs	O
,	O
a	O
Brass	O
Chafingdish	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Rayner	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
that	O
she	O
stole	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wicks	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
cheating	O
one	O
George	B-pers
Graden	I-pers
of	O
ten	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
declared	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Smith	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
recommended	O
by	O
one	O
Stetsbury	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
Mr	O
Graden	O
's	O
Customer	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Martha	B-pers
Shorter	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Leg	I-pers
,	O
of	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
11	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
and	O
ordered	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
for	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
a	O
Common	O
Night-walker	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Dudley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Locket	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Exton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Cows	O
,	O
coloured	O
black	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
.	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
:	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Beasts	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Grounds	O
in	O
Buckinghamshire	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
Islington	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
a	O
man	O
who	O
hired	O
him	O
to	O
drive	O
them	O
to	O
Black	O
Mary	O
's	O
hole	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
neither	O
could	O
he	O
call	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Mayse	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Eling	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Murrey	I-pers
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
two	O
Stuff	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
two	O
Flaxen	O
Shirts	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
Smocks	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
l	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
go	O
out	O
to	O
Work	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
lockt	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
returned	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
his	O
Door	O
was	O
open	O
;	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Lingley	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
John	I-pers
Butcher	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Resbeck	I-pers
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
no	O
Person	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
15	O
yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
a	O
Mantua	O
Gown	O
,	O
3	O
Silk	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
4	O
Spoon	O
,	O
7	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Gold	O
Buttons	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
that	O
her	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
lockt	O
it	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
:	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
Evidence	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
say	O
but	O
very	O
little	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
call	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
three	O
Foot	O
Padders	O
,	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
one	O
Edward	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silver-hilted	O
Sword	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
59	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Cloath	O
Coat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Countess	B-pers
Dowager	I-pers
of	I-pers
Thanett	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Highgate	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
near	O
Lambs-Conduit-Fields	B-place
,	O
they	O
stept	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
askt	O
him	O
what	O
Ship	O
he	O
belonged	O
to	O
?	O
he	O
replied	O
,	O
The	O
Nonsuch	O
:	O
Then	O
they	O
took	O
his	O
Coat	O
off	O
his	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Sword	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
bound	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
positive	O
to	O
Wheeler	O
and	O
Williams	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
Smith	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
said	O
very	O
little	O
for	O
themselves	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
Wheeler	O
and	O
Williams	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elinor	B-pers
Granger	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Grimes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Fustion	O
Frock	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stuff-Breeches	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Dorrel	I-pers
on	O
the	O
4th	O
.	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
lose	O
such	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
not	O
positive	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
;	O
and	O
nothing	O
being	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Kirke	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pancrass	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Budglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Mantua	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Stuff-Petticoat	O
,	O
4	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
27	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
monies	O
numbred	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
a	O
Ditch	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
open	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomasin	B-pers
Hooper	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Alice	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
,	O
Searge-Petticoats	O
,	O
2	O
Coyfs	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Wooden	O
Box	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
none	O
could	O
say	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
nothing	O
being	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mander	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Drugget	O
Curtain	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pillowber	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
she	O
stole	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
nothing	O
being	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Greenwood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonards	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Tabby	O
Curtains	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Lyddal	I-pers
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Gowen	B-pers
Hardy	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
;	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
after	O
the	O
15th	O
day	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
did	O
utter	O
24	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Counterfeit	O
Money	O
,	O
called	O
Shillings	O
,	O
for	O
less	O
in	O
value	O
than	O
they	O
were	O
coined	O
for	O
,	O
20	O
s.	O
of	O
Good	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
knowing	O
the	O
same	O
so	O
to	O
be	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
It	O
may	O
be	O
hoped	O
it	O
will	O
put	O
an	O
end	O
to	O
this	O
pernicious	O
Trade	O
of	O
False	O
Coining	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Warburton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
for	O
counterfeiting	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
;	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
followed	O
the	O
Trade	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
one	O
of	O
Cope	O
's	O
Gang	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
formerly	O
executed	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Whitechappel	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Clipping	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
April	O
in	O
the	O
7th	O
year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dewin	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
uttering	O
False	O
Money	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
so	O
to	O
be	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Wycks	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
procuring	O
False	O
Money	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
deceive	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
his	O
Subjects	O
:	O
The	O
Money	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
but	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Martell	I-pers
,	O
a	O
French	O
Woman	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
Murthering	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Pullen	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
Paul	B-pers
Pullen	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Pine	B-place
Apple	I-place
in	I-place
Suffolk	I-place
Street	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
her	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
in	O
the	O
Throat	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
six	O
Inches	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
four	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Second	O
was	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Esquire	O
Pullen	O
of	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
2	O
Silver	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
4	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Porringer	O
,	O
3	O
Spoons	O
,	O
2	O
Gold	O
Watches	O
,	O
6	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Evidence	O
was	O
the	O
Maid-servant	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
her	O
Mistress	O
being	O
at	O
Dinner	O
,	O
and	O
near	O
dined	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
knockt	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
her	O
Mistress	O
's	O
Acquaintance	O
,	O
let	O
her	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Mistress	O
askt	O
her	O
why	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
sooner	O
,	O
whereupon	O
she	O
excused	O
her	O
self	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
brought	O
the	O
Meat	O
and	O
set	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
did	O
eat	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
Two	O
pence	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Ale	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
and	O
Ale	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
Dinner	O
was	O
over	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
set	O
down	O
upon	O
a	O
Squab	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
observed	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
Slippers	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
inquired	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
replied	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
skalded	O
her	O
Foot	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
wear	O
her	O
Shooes	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
she	O
sat	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
a	O
Paper	O
lye	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Direction	O
on	O
it	O
to	O
Madam	O
Webbs	O
in	O
Red	O
Lyon	O
Square	O
on	O
Holborn	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
askt	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
Maid	O
carry	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
granted	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
Letter	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
directed	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
one	O
Madam	O
Tempests	O
in	O
Cooks-Court	O
in	O
Lincolns-Inn-Fields	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
the	O
Maid	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
she	O
compleated	O
her	O
Bloody	O
Act	O
;	O
she	O
being	O
returned	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
her	O
Mistress	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Key	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
at	O
home	O
till	O
Seven	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
walk	O
in	O
the	O
Park	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
took	O
her	O
Work	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drew	O
the	O
Window-Curtains	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
love	O
so	O
much	O
Light	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
had	O
her	O
lay	O
down	O
her	O
Work	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
shew	O
her	O
a	O
pleasant	O
Trick	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
sit	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
Chair	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
Key	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
shut	O
her	O
Eyes	O
whilst	O
she	O
could	O
tell	O
Threescore	O
,	O
she	O
should	O
perceive	O
the	O
Person	O
whom	O
she	O
loved	O
;	O
she	O
tried	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
perceive	O
nothing	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Parlour	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
her	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
sent	O
her	O
for	O
some	O
Brandy	O
,	O
pretending	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
well	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
into	O
Leicester	O
Fields	O
and	O
bespeak	O
some	O
Shooes	O
;	O
sometime	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
her	O
Master	O
came	O
home	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
into	O
that	O
Room	O
,	O
for	O
her	O
Mistress	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Key	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
about	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
askt	O
if	O
her	O
Mistress	O
was	O
come	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Halfpenny	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
and	O
bad	O
her	O
light	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
staid	O
till	O
near	O
Eleven	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
wanted	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Buckles	O
of	O
her	O
Mistress	O
's	O
to	O
trim	O
her	O
Stays	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
Maid	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
lie	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
till	O
her	O
Mistress	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
the	O
lay	O
down	O
,	O
she	O
spied	O
some	O
Drops	O
of	O
Blood	O
upon	O
her	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
askt	O
her	O
how	O
that	O
happened	O
,	O
she	O
gave	O
her	O
no	O
answer	O
,	O
but	O
smiled	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
carried	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Your	O
Mistress	O
wo'nt	O
come	O
home	O
to	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
call	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
;	O
and	O
went	O
her	O
ways	O
.	O
About	O
Twelve	O
the	O
Maid	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
her	O
Mistress	O
was	O
not	O
come	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
afraid	O
some	O
People	O
might	O
hurt	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
see	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
coming	O
home	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
askt	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
ever	O
a	O
Key	O
that	O
would	O
open	O
that	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
her	O
yes	O
,	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
Larder	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
and	O
fetcht	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
the	O
Window-Shutters	O
were	O
shut	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
in	O
darkness	O
;	O
and	O
opening	O
the	O
Shutters	O
,	O
found	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Blood	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
print	O
of	O
a	O
Slipper	O
in	O
the	O
Blood	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Closet	O
door	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Gentlewoman	O
with	O
her	O
Throat	O
cut	O
,	O
lying	O
in	O
that	O
Condition	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
away	O
:	O
The	O
Maid	O
declared	O
that	O
no	O
body	O
was	O
there	O
but	O
the	O
French	O
Woman	O
,	O
who	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
was	O
apprehended	O
in	O
Rupert	O
Street	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
her	O
Lodging	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Trunk	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Slippers	O
that	O
was	O
bloody	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Gentlewoman	O
gave	O
them	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
her	O
Trial	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
two	O
Men	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Inner	O
Parlour	O
to	O
the	O
Gentlewoman	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
held	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
her	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
bad	O
her	O
that	O
she	O
should	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
altered	O
her	O
Story	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Lady	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
pay	O
her	O
Debts	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
was	O
minded	O
to	O
leave	O
the	O
House	O
over	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
and	O
her	O
Maid	O
would	O
become	O
Boarders	O
there	O
;	O
as	O
for	O
her	O
Slippers	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
Market	O
,	O
and	O
might	O
step	O
in	O
some	O
Blood	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
for	O
her	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
bloody	O
with	O
Meat	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
Murther	O
.	O
The	O
Trial	O
lasted	O
near	O
Four	O
hours	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
party-Jury	O
of	O
half	O
English	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
Frenchmen	O
,	O
who	O
having	O
considered	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
wilful	O
Murther	O
;	O
and	O
likewise	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealinga	O
Feather-bed	O
,	O
Bolster	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Curtains	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Barnaby	B-pers
Dunster	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
It	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
breach	O
of	O
her	O
Trust	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
Felony	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Debrass	I-pers
and	O
Philip	B-pers
Barlow	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
3	O
Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Fork	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Dormer	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
It	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
that	O
they	O
stole	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Rebekah	B-pers
Lawson	I-pers
and	O
Joan	B-pers
Carroll	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
for	O
counterfeiting	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Arromsmith	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Ludbrooke	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
Witness	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
another	O
place	O
when	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
;	O
thereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Murrey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privily	O
and	O
secretly	O
taking	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
Duccatoon	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
8	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
Strand	B-place
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
a	O
sudden	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
pursuing	O
her	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Bosom	O
;	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
behalf	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Stephen	B-pers
Lingley	I-pers
,	O
Leife	B-pers
Frier	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Whittell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Gambell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
March	O
;	O
Lingley	O
and	O
Frier	O
were	O
Principals	O
,	O
and	O
Whittell	O
as	O
Accessary	O
after	O
the	O
Fact	O
:	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
they	O
broke	O
the	O
Shutters	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
some	O
Linnen	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
Whittell	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
who	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
Leise	O
Frier	O
,	O
and	O
James	O
Whittell	O
as	O
accessary	O
,	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Bamfield	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Silk	O
Petticoat	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Lingley	O
,	O
Frier	O
:	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Whittell	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Potter	I-pers
and	O
Anne	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
three	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
and	O
one	O
Dish	O
:	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
under	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
5	O
s.	O
thereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Claverin	I-pers
,	I-pers
and	I-pers
Joan	I-pers
his	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Joan	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
black	O
Cloath	O
Coat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
s.	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Tatham	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Breeches	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hickman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
Custody	O
,	O
therefore	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Woman	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Newby	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
her	O
Lodging	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Flaxen	O
Sheet	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Feather	O
Bolsters	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Green	I-pers
.	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
any	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
relieve	O
her	O
Necessities	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Alice	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
39	O
yards	O
of	O
Green	O
Ribon	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Roger	B-pers
Gill	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
Barnes	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
put	O
her	O
self	O
upon	O
her	O
Trial	O
,	O
and	O
alledging	O
her	O
Innocence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Peirce	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilborne	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
nothing	O
being	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Baxter	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
cheating	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
of	O
12	O
s.	O
by	O
pawning	O
to	O
him	O
a	O
Horse	O
that	O
was	O
none	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
:	O
The	O
fact	O
was	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Counterfeiting	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Courts	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
followeth	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
18	O
.	O
Judith	O
Bomsellers	O
,	O
Charles	O
Ecclestone	O
,	O
Leise	O
Frier	O
,	O
Joseph	O
Gregory	O
,	O
Eleanor	O
Hunt	O
,	O
Samuel	O
James	O
,	O
David	O
Jenkins	O
,	O
Richard	O
Lewley	O
,	O
Stephen	O
Lingley	O
,	O
Margaret	O
Martell	O
,	O
Mary	O
Murrey	O
,	O
Timothy	O
Pennistone	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Smith	O
,	O
Daniel	O
Spires	O
,	O
John	O
Wilkinson	O
,	O
Robert	O
Wheeler	O
,	O
John	O
Williams	O
,	O
George	O
Warburton	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
24	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Barnes	O
,	O
Dorothy	O
Chapman	O
,	O
William	O
Colely	O
,	O
Mary	O
Carthensey	O
,	O
John	O
Claverin	O
,	O
Hester	O
Duberrey	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Dudley	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Dudleg	O
,	O
Francis	O
Exton	O
,	O
Margaret	O
Bibby	O
,	O
Susan	O
Farrow	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Gates	O
,	O
Catherine	O
Greenwood	O
,	O
George	O
Homond	O
.	O
Gowen	O
Hardy	O
,	O
Randal	O
Kettle	O
,	O
Jane	O
Kirk	O
,	O
Magdalen	O
Lanceston	O
,	O
Sutan	O
Mayol	O
,	O
Jane	O
Pritchard	O
Sarah	O
Snelling	O
,	O
Anne	O
Sparrow	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Thomas	O
,	O
James	O
Whittell	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
,	O
5	O
.	O
Humphrey	O
Chapman	O
,	O
John	O
Hatsell	O
,	O
Ann	O
Jackson	O
,	O
Mary	O
Newby	O
,	O
Mary	O
Potter	O
.	O
Ordered	O
into	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Service	O
,	O
4	O
.	O
William	O
Cokely	O
,	O
John	O
Claverin	O
Francis	O
Exton	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Thomas	O
.	O
Henry	O
Baker	O
fined	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
to	O
find	O
Sureties	O
for	O
a	O
Twelvemonth	O
.	O
John	O
Wycks	O
fined	O
13	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
d.	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
.	O
John	O
Dewin	O
fined	O
100	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
Three	O
times	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
,	O
and	O
find	O
Sureties	O
for	O
a	O
Twelvemonth	O
.	O
Judith	O
Bomsellers	O
,	O
Margaret	O
Martell	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	O
Murrey	O
,	O
pleaded	O
their	O
Bellies	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
being	O
impannell	O
'd	O
,	O
found	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
with	O
quick	O
Child	O
.	O
By	O
Order	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
Margaret	O
Martell	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
executed	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
broad	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Some	O
Books	O
Printed	O
for	O
B.	O
Aylmer	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Pigeons	O
in	O
Cornhil	O
.	O
THE	O
Works	O
of	O
the	O
Most	O
Reverend	O
Dr.	O
John	O
Tillotson	O
,	O
late	O
Lord	O
Archbishop	O
of	O
Canterbury	O
,	O
containing	O
Fifty	O
four	O
Sermons	O
and	O
Discourses	O
on	O
Several	O
Occasions	O
;	O
together	O
with	O
the	O
Rule	O
of	O
Faith	O
.	O
Being	O
all	O
that	O
were	O
published	O
by	O
his	O
Grace	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
collected	O
into	O
one	O
Volume	O
:	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
an	O
Alphabetical	O
Table	O
of	O
the	O
Principal	O
Matters	O
.	O
Price	O
20	O
s.	O
Six	O
Sermons	O
;	O
viz	O
.	O
Of	O
Stedfastness	O
in	O
Religion	O
.	O
Of	O
Family	O
Religion	O
.	O
Of	O
Education	O
of	O
Children	O
.	O
Of	O
the	O
Advantages	O
of	O
an	O
Early	O
Piety	O
.	O
By	O
his	O
Grace	O
,	O
John	O
,	O
late	O
Archbishop	O
of	O
Canterbury	O
.	O
In	O
120.	O
price	O
18	O
d.	O
A	O
Persuasive	O
to	O
frequent	O
Communion	O
in	O
the	O
Holy	O
Sacrament	O
of	O
the	O
Lord	O
's	O
Supper	O
;	O
Also	O
by	O
his	O
Grace	O
,	O
John	O
,	O
late	O
Archbishop	O
of	O
Canterbury	O
,	O
in	O
120	O
.	O
Bound	O
6	O
d.	O
or	O
Seith	O
'd	O
in	O
8vo	O
.	O
3	O
d.	O
or	O
something	O
Cheaper	O
to	O
those	O
that	O
are	O
so	O
Charitable	O
to	O
give	O
away	O
Numbers	O
.	O
Twelve	O
select	O
Sermons	O
,	O
preach	O
'd	O
upon	O
several	O
Occasions	O
;	O
By	O
the	O
Right	O
Reverend	O
Richard	O
Lord	O
Bishop	O
of	O
Bath	O
and	O
Wells	O
.	O
In	O
8vo	O
.	O
Price	O
4	O
s.	O
The	O
Holy	O
Bible	O
,	O
Containing	O
the	O
Old	O
Testament	O
and	O
the	O
New	O
;	O
with	O
Annotations	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
exact	O
Parallel	O
Scriptures	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
Annex	O
'd	O
the	O
Harmony	O
of	O
the	O
Gospels	O
;	O
as	O
also	O
the	O
Reduction	O
of	O
the	O
Jewish	O
Weights	O
,	O
Coins	O
and	O
Measures	O
,	O
to	O
our	O
English	O
Standards	O
.	O
And	O
a	O
Table	O
of	O
the	O
Promises	O
in	O
Scripture	O
.	O
By	O
Samuel	O
Clark	O
,	O
Minister	O
of	O
the	O
Gospel	O
.	O
Printed	O
in	O
Foho	O
on	O
a	O
very	O
Fair	O
Letter	O
;	O
the	O
like	O
never	O
before	O
in	O
one	O
Volume	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
newly	O
added	O
a	O
very	O
Exact	O
and	O
useful	O
Concordance	O
.	O
Price	O
30	O
Shill	O
.	O
The	O
Works	O
of	O
the	O
Learned	O
Isaac	O
Barrow	O
D.	O
D.	O
late	O
Master	O
of	O
Trinity	O
Colledge	O
in	O
Cambridge	O
.	O
Published	O
by	O
the	O
Reverend	O
Dr.	O
Tillotson	O
,	O
late	O
Archbishop	O
of	O
Canterbury	O
.	O
The	O
Third	O
Volume	O
.	O
Containing	O
Forty	O
five	O
Sermons	O
,	O
upon	O
several	O
Occasions	O
,	O
compleating	O
his	O
English	O
Works	O
.	O
A	O
Brief	O
Exposition	O
of	O
the	O
Apostles	O
Creed	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Learned	O
Dr.	O
Isaac	O
Barrow	O
,	O
late	O
Master	O
of	O
Trinity	O
College	O
in	O
Cambridge	O
;	O
Never	O
before	O
printed	O
,	O
being	O
very	O
different	O
from	O
his	O
Volume	O
of	O
Sermons	O
on	O
it	O
:	O
)	O
to	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
His	O
Exposition	O
of	O
the	O
Lord	O
's	O
Prayer	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Ten	O
Commandments	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
In	O
8vo	O
.	O
Price	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Practical	O
Discourses	O
upon	O
the	O
Consideration	O
of	O
our	O
Latter	O
End	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Danger	O
and	O
Mischief	O
of	O
Delaying	O
Repentance	O
.	O
By	O
Dr.	O
Isaac	O
Barrow	O
,	O
in	O
8vo	O
.	O
Price	O
18	O
d.	O
A	O
Defence	O
of	O
the	O
B.	O
Trinity	O
:	O
Never	O
before	O
printed	O
.	O
By	O
Dr.	O
Isaac	O
Barrow	O
,	O
in	O
8vo	O
.	O
Price	O
12	O
d.	O
The	O
Four	O
Last	O
Things	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Death	O
,	O
Judgment	O
,	O
Heaven	O
,	O
and	O
Hell	O
:	O
Practically	O
Considered	O
and	O
Applied	O
.	O
By	O
W.	O
Bates	O
,	O
D.	O
D.	O
in	O
120	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
Sermons	O
of	O
the	O
Forgiveness	O
of	O
Sins	O
.	O
On	O
Psalm	O
130.	O
v.	O
4	O
.	O
Also	O
by	O
Dr.	O
Batts	O
.	O
Price	O
18	O
d.	O
A	O
Conference	O
with	O
an	O
Anabaprist	O
.	O
By	O
Dr.	O
Assheton	O
of	O
Beckenham	O
in	O
Kent	O
.	O
Price	O
12	O
d.	O
A	O
Theological	O
Discourse	O
of	O
Last	O
Wills	O
and	O
Testaments	O
.	O
Also	O
by	O
Dr.	O
Assheton	O
.	O
Price	O
12	O
d.	O
Several	O
small	O
Books	O
against	O
Debauchery	O
,	O
Prosaneness	O
,	O
Blasphemy	O
,	O
Cursing	O
and	O
Swearing	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Also	O
a	O
Method	O
of	O
daily	O
Devotion	O
.	O
By	O
Dr.	O
Assheton	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
d.	O
each	O
,	O
and	O
something	O
cheaper	O
to	O
them	O
that	O
give	O
away	O
Numbers	O
.	O
A	O
Discourse	O
concerning	O
a	O
Death-Bed	O
Repentance	O
.	O
By	O
William	O
Assheton	O
,	O
D.	O
D.	O
Price	O
6	O
d.	O
A	O
Seasonable	O
Vindication	O
of	O
the	O
B.	O
Trinity	O
.	O
Being	O
an	O
Answer	O
to	O
this	O
Question	O
,	O
Why	O
do	O
you	O
believe	O
the	O
Doctrine	O
of	O
the	O
Trinity	O
?	O
Collected	O
from	O
the	O
Works	O
of	O
the	O
Most	O
Reverend	O
Dr.	O
John	O
Tillotson	O
,	O
Late	O
Lord	O
Archbishop	O
of	O
Canterbury	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Right	O
Reverend	O
Dr.	O
Edward	O
Stillingstreet	O
,	O
now	O
Lord	O
Bishop	O
of	O
Worcester	O
.	O
By	O
Dr.	O
Assheton	O
,	O
Price	O
12	O
d.	O
A	O
Familiar	O
Guide	O
to	O
the	O
Right	O
and	O
Profitable	O
Receiving	O
of	O
the	O
Lord	O
's	O
Supper	O
:	O
Wherein	O
also	O
the	O
Way	O
and	O
Method	O
of	O
our	O
Salvation	O
is	O
briefly	O
and	O
plainly	O
declared	O
.	O
By	O
T.	O
Dorrington	O
.	O
Price	O
12	O
d.	O
The	O
Council	O
of	O
Trent	O
no	O
Free	O
Assembly	O
:	O
More	O
fully	O
discovered	O
by	O
a	O
Collection	O
of	O
Letters	O
and	O
Papers	O
of	O
the	O
Learned	O
Dr.	O
Vargas	O
and	O
other	O
Great	O
Ministers	O
,	O
who	O
assisted	O
at	O
the	O
said	O
Synod	O
in	O
considerable	O
Posts	O
.	O
Published	O
from	O
the	O
Original	O
Manscripts	O
in	O
Spanish	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
procured	O
by	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
William	O
Trumbull	O
's	O
Grandfather	O
,	O
Envoy	O
at	O
Brussels	O
in	O
the	O
Reign	O
of	O
King	O
James	O
the	O
First	O
.	O
With	O
an	O
Introductory	O
Discourse	O
concerning	O
Councils	O
,	O
she	O
wing	O
how	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
under	O
Bondage	O
to	O
the	O
Pope	O
.	O
By	O
Michael	O
Geddes	O
,	O
LLD	O
.	O
and	O
Chancellor	O
of	O
the	O
Cathedral	O
Church	O
of	O
Sarum	O
.	O
In	O
8vo	O
.	O
Price	O
4	O
s.	O
G.	O
Keith	O
's	O
second	O
Narrative	O
of	O
the	O
Proceedings	O
at	O
Turners	O
ball	O
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
1697	O
.	O
In	O
4vo	O
.	O
stitch	O
'd	O
Price	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
Natural	O
Method	O
of	O
Teaching	O
Latin	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
Accidence	O
in	O
Questions	O
and	O
Answers	O
explained	O
,	O
amended	O
,	O
abridged	O
,	O
and	O
fitted	O
to	O
the	O
Capacity	O
and	O
Use	O
of	O
the	O
Lowest	O
Form	O
Into	O
which	O
is	O
inferted	O
a	O
Vocabulary	O
of	O
English	O
and	O
Latin	O
Words	O
under	O
each	O
Part	O
of	O
Speech	O
:	O
Also	O
Sententie	O
Pueriles	O
,	O
English	O
and	O
Latin	O
,	O
consisting	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Words	O
put	O
in	O
plain	O
Sentences	O
under	O
every	O
Syntactick	O
Rule	O
.	O
By	O
Samuel	O
Hoadly	O
,	O
Teacher	O
of	O
a	O
School	O
in	O
Hackney	O
.	O
In	O
8vo	O
.	O
Price	O
16	O
d.	O
AN	O
Admirable	O
Water	O
against	O
Convtdson	O
Fits	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Falling-sickness	O
.	O
Being	O
a	O
Secret	O
kept	O
in	O
an	O
Eminent	O
Family	O
for	O
many	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
for	O
general	O
good	O
made	O
publick	O
.	O
Price	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
Small	O
Bottle	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
sold	O
B.	O
Aybner	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
.	O
AN	O
Ointment	O
which	O
certainly	O
Kills	O
and	O
Expels	O
Worms	O
in	O
Children	O
,	O
by	O
Anointing	O
their	O
Bellies	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Nights	O
together	O
.	O
A	O
Syrrup	O
for	O
Clefts	O
and	O
Chaps	O
in	O
Women	O
Nipples	O
.	O
And	O
Mr.	O
Boyle	O
's	O
Ointment	O
for	O
the	O
Piles	O
,	O
are	O
Prepared	O
and	O
Sold	O
by	O
William	O
King	O
,	O
Apothecary	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Three	O
Crowns	O
in	O
Budg-Row	O
,	O
near	O
Cannon	O
Street	O
.	O
London	O
These	O
are	O
to	O
give	O
notice	O
to	O
all	O
Persons	O
for	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
the	O
Publick	O
,	O
That	O
W.	O
Elmy	O
,	O
Professor	O
of	O
Physick	O
,	O
and	O
Operator	O
,	O
of	O
known	O
Integrity	O
,	O
liveth	O
at	O
the	O
Blue	O
Ball	O
in	O
Whalebone-Court	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Lower	O
End	O
of	O
Bartholomew-Lane	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
WHO	O
most	O
safely	O
and	O
expeditiously	O
cures	O
Deafness	O
and	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
Ears	O
in	O
any	O
,	O
of	O
what	O
Age	O
foever	O
,	O
(	O
if	O
curable	O
)	O
and	O
at	O
first	O
sight	O
,	O
by	O
Inspection	O
.	O
resolves	O
the	O
Patient	O
if	O
so	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
as	O
most	O
Eminent	O
Persons	O
of	O
Quality	O
can	O
testify	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
Remedies	O
ready	O
prepared	O
for	O
the	O
Preservation	O
of	O
the	O
Hearing	O
,	O
in	O
those	O
who	O
through	O
some	O
great	O
defects	O
in	O
the	O
Sounding	O
Membrane	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Impediments	O
in	O
the	O
Auditory	O
Passages	O
,	O
are	O
not	O
perfectly	O
curable	O
,	O
which	O
Remedies	O
preserve	O
them	O
from	O
ever	O
growing	O
worse	O
,	O
and	O
improves	O
their	O
Hearing	O
to	O
Old	O
Age	O
.	O
He	O
hath	O
likewise	O
a	O
PILL	O
which	O
cleanfeth	O
the	O
Blood	O
from	O
all	O
Impurities	O
,	O
infallibly	O
cureth	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
.	O
It	O
cures	O
the	O
Headach	O
to	O
Admiration	O
,	O
taking	O
away	O
Vapours	O
offensive	O
to	O
the	O
Brain	O
.	O
It	O
creates	O
a	O
good	O
Stomach	O
and	O
Digestion	O
,	O
takes	O
away	O
sharpness	O
of	O
Urine	O
,	O
and	O
cleanseth	O
the	O
Reins	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
a	O
certain	O
and	O
present	O
Remedy	O
for	O
the	O
Gout	O
.	O
It	O
cures	O
all	O
Joint-pains	O
,	O
resist	O
.	O
Fevers	O
and	O
Surfeits	O
,	O
and	O
preserves	O
the	O
Body	O
in	O
perfect	O
health	O
.	O
He	O
hath	O
Boxes	O
of	O
several	O
Prices	O
,	O
according	O
as	O
Necessity	O
requires	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
,	O
from	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
to	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
from	O
3	O
s.	O
to	O
6	O
s.	O
He	O
hath	O
likewise	O
a	O
most	O
Excellent	O
Gargarism	O
or	O
Mouth-water	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
make	O
black	O
or	O
yellow	O
Teeth	O
where	O
as	O
Ivory	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
times	O
using	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
will	O
certainly	O
cure	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
Diseases	O
incident	O
to	O
the	O
Mouth	O
,	O
Teeth	O
and	O
Gums	O
.	O
The	O
Glasses	O
are	O
of	O
several	O
Prices	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
.	O
