TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
,	O
On	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
,	O
Monday	O
,	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
and	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
14th	O
,	O
15th	O
,	O
17th	O
,	O
18th	O
,	O
and	O
19th	O
Days	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
1697	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
Ninth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bayly	O
,	O
on	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
,	O
Monday	O
,	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
and	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
14th	O
,	O
15th	O
,	O
17th	O
,	O
18th	O
,	O
and	O
19th	O
Days	O
of	O
Jan.	O
1697	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
HUMPHRY	B-pers
EDWIN	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
Salathiel	B-pers
Lovell	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
are	O
as	O
follow	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
Matthew	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
Roger	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Yetts	I-pers
James	B-pers
Brokton	I-pers
William	B-pers
Trigg	I-pers
Hugh	B-pers
Granger	I-pers
Ezekiel	B-pers
Pomfrett	I-pers
John	B-pers
Dyer	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Speed	I-pers
David	B-pers
King	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Moody	I-pers
Nicholas	B-pers
Spalding	I-pers
Peter	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
George	B-pers
Palfrey	I-pers
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
William	B-pers
Diston	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Mead	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Longhand	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Pattle	I-pers
John	B-pers
Pritty	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
these	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
King	I-pers
of	O
London	O
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
George	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
one	O
Silk	O
Petticoat	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
Pewter-plate	O
,	O
6	O
Diaper	O
Napkins	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
:	O
To	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Honowan	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchers	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Packman	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
8th	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
one	O
Lutestring	O
Gown	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
4	O
Holland	O
Aprons	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
3	O
l.	O
in	O
Moneys	O
numbred	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
from	O
home	O
,	O
having	O
left	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
her	O
Room	O
behind	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Jane	O
Brown	O
perceiving	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Impression	O
of	O
it	O
upon	O
Clay	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
one	O
made	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
with	O
opening	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Locks	O
where	O
the	O
Goods	O
lay	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
off	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Williams	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
lookt	O
out	O
at	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Windows	O
to	O
prevent	O
being	O
surprized	O
.	O
It	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
that	O
William	O
Brown	O
had	O
any	O
hand	O
in	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
;	O
But	O
Jane	O
Brown	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	O
Williams	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Williams	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Brown	O
:	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Green	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolphs	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Arch	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
2	O
Silk	O
Gowns	O
value	O
9	O
l.	O
one	O
Silk	O
Petticoat	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
one	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
:	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Bridget	B-pers
Hays	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Smithies	I-pers
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
December	O
one	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
David	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
of	O
London	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Ward	O
of	O
Faringdon	B-place
without	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
6	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
value	O
45	O
s.	O
3	O
other	O
Rings	O
set	O
with	O
Stones	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
18	O
Silver	O
Seals	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
2	O
Silver	O
Nutmeg-graters	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
7	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
:	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
assistance	O
of	O
a	O
Ladder	O
to	O
a	O
Window	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
out	O
a	O
Pain	O
of	O
the	O
Glass	O
,	O
opened	O
the	O
Window	O
and	O
got	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
off	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
when	O
seized	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
part	O
discovered	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
by	O
him	O
to	O
Goldsmiths	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
which	O
occasion	O
'd	O
the	O
discovery	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
of	O
London	O
,	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Potts	I-pers
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Flaxen	O
Sheetsvalue	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
:	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Mary	B-pers
Denton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
one	O
Dowlass	O
Shirt	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Flaxen	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
also	O
tried	O
on	O
another	O
Indictment	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Sir	O
George	B-pers
Downing	I-pers
Baronet	O
,	O
one	O
Flaxen	O
Table-cloth	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
June	O
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
frequently	O
to	O
Sir	O
George	O
Downing	O
's	O
Brewhouse	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Goods	O
lay	O
for	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
:	O
but	O
she	O
having	O
a	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
not	O
being	O
positively	O
proved	O
that	O
she	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
tried	O
upon	O
two	O
several	O
Indictments	O
;	O
One	O
for	O
Robbing	O
James	B-pers
North	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
28	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
numbered	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
7th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
;	O
And	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
Wounding	O
the	O
said	O
James	O
North	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Thrust	O
with	O
a	O
Bagonet-half	O
an	O
Inch	O
broad	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
deep	O
on	O
the	O
Back	O
,	O
nigh	O
unto	O
the	O
left	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
suddenly	O
died	O
:	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
to	O
convict	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Maticay	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
County	I-place
of	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
4	O
stuff	O
Curtains	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
2	O
Blankets	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
:	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Philip	B-pers
Cary	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Twitnam	B-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Colchester	I-pers
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
Decemb	O
.	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
11	O
Diaper	O
Napkins	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
stuff	O
Petticoat	O
lined	O
with	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
:	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
where	O
there	O
was	O
none	O
at	O
home	O
but	O
Mary	B-pers
Colchester	I-pers
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
some	O
Victuals	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
gave	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
return	O
'd	O
again	O
,	O
perceiving	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
alone	O
,	O
lifted	O
the	O
Latch	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
entered	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
laying	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
Cary	O
having	O
stopt	O
her	O
Mouth	O
with	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
her	O
down	O
with	O
his	O
Knee	O
upon	O
her	O
Breast	O
,	O
whilst	O
Pain	O
rifled	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
lockt	O
the	O
door	O
to	O
keep	O
her	O
in	O
,	O
carry	O
'd	O
away	O
the	O
Key	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
back-door	O
,	O
she	O
got	O
out	O
and	O
acquainting	O
some	O
Bargemen	O
,	O
they	O
pursued	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
seized	O
them	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
about	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
them	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Duarington	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Great	B-place
Stanmore	I-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Edward	B-pers
Billingsly	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Sword	O
with	O
a	O
Princes	O
Mettle	O
Handle	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Saddle	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
two	O
Knives	O
,	O
and	O
30	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
number	O
'd	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
to	O
convict	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Halden	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Murdering	O
her	O
Female	O
Infant	O
Child	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
December	O
:	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
which	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Murder	O
,	O
nor	O
no	O
Marks	O
of	O
Violence	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Child	O
;	O
against	O
the	O
bringing	O
forth	O
of	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
made	O
provision	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Child	O
apparently	O
died	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
help	O
:	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Newland	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Borkin	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
three	O
Cows	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
stole	O
the	O
Cows	O
off	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
Butcher	O
here	O
in	O
Town	O
,	O
in	O
whose	O
possession	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
said	O
in	O
their	O
defence	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Cows	O
straying	O
in	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
without	O
being	O
owned	O
by	O
any	O
person	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
all	O
they	O
had	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
themselves	O
:	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
them	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Ingrum	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Ward	I-place
of	I-place
Farringdon	I-place
without	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Mary	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
16	O
Yards	O
of	O
Damask	O
Linen	O
Cloth	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
being	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Farrin	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
two	O
others	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
Robinson	O
near	O
Water-lane	B-place
End	I-place
in	I-place
Fleet	I-place
street	I-place
,	O
and	O
shuffling	O
her	O
close	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
pretended	O
to	O
strive	O
who	O
should	O
Kiss	O
her	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
rest	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Band-box	O
which	O
she	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
went	O
away	O
:	O
The	O
Goods	O
they	O
sold	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
shared	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
very	O
positive	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
having	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
their	O
defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
them	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Sherman	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
London	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Marrying	O
two	O
Wives	O
:	O
The	O
first	O
Mary	B-pers
Bagwell	I-pers
at	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
Church	O
Southwark	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
6th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
9th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
at	O
Trinity-Church	B-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Minories	I-place
,	O
did	O
take	O
to	O
Wife	O
Mary	B-pers
Welton	I-pers
;	O
for	O
which	O
two	O
Testificates	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
:	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
other	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
Marriages	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
denying	O
the	O
first	O
Marriage	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Dicait	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
Ludgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilder	I-pers
on	O
the	O
11th	O
Day	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
a	O
stuff	O
Gown	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
off	O
the	O
Gown	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
was	O
seized	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Dey	I-pers
;	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Floyd	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Earle	I-pers
4	O
Pewter-dishes	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
9	O
Pewter-plates	O
,	O
a	O
Brass-pot	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Window	O
being	O
left	O
open	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
thereout	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
taken	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
seized	O
about	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jarvis	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bartholomew	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
P	O
-	O
C	O
-	O
and	O
W	O
-	O
T	O
-	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
feloniously	O
steal	O
from	O
Ann	B-pers
Coombs	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
150	O
Yards	O
of	O
Stuff	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
l.	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
frequently	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
on	O
pretence	O
to	O
court	O
her	O
Maid-Servant	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
her	O
next	O
Neighbours	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
occasion	O
to	O
carry	O
off	O
the	O
Goods	O
which	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Accomplices	O
pawn	O
'd	O
and	O
sold	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
confest	O
when	O
taken	O
;	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
discovered	O
at	O
Pawn-brokers	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
frequently	O
troubled	O
with	O
distracted	O
Fits	O
;	O
to	O
prove	O
which	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
:	O
But	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
County	I-place
of	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Craven	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
a	O
Silver-hilted	O
Sword	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Sword	O
was	O
stole	O
from	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
side	O
as	O
going	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Temple	B-place
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Gang	O
being	O
watching	O
for	O
Prey	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Sword	O
being	O
carry	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Sword-Cutler	O
who	O
made	O
it	O
,	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
was	O
discovered	O
,	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
Plate	O
being	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
Handle	O
:	O
He	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Ward	I-place
of	I-place
Lime	I-place
street	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Loe	I-pers
's	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
2	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Isaac	B-pers
Jolly	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
December	O
one	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Child	O
's	O
Head-dress	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
not	O
positive	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
stealing	O
of	O
Lot	O
's	O
Goods	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
was	O
plainly	O
proved	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stole	O
Jolly	O
's	O
Goods	O
,	O
they	O
being	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
;	O
He	O
was	O
quitted	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
Indictment	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
latter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
County	I-place
of	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
William	B-pers
Goring	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
December	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silver-hilted	O
Sword	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
three	O
others	O
met	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
in	O
a	O
narrow	O
paved	O
Alley	O
,	O
near	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
lying	O
flat	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
way	O
;	O
stopt	O
his	O
passage	O
while	O
the	O
rest	O
shuffled	O
him	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Wall	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Sword	O
,	O
which	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
carry	O
'd	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
of	O
them	O
escaped	O
except	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Ward	B-place
of	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Jackman	I-pers
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
December	O
56	O
pound	O
of	O
Butter	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Ferkin	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
watching	O
an	O
opportunity	O
entered	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
shop	O
when	O
no	O
person	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
carrying	O
the	O
Ferkin	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
was	O
seized	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Pickman	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Ward	B-place
of	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Scarborough	I-pers
20	O
Yards	O
of	O
Silk	O
Ribbon	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
took	O
occasion	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
to	O
steal	O
a	O
great	O
quantity	O
of	O
Goods	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Custody	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
we	O
was	O
advised	O
to	O
it	O
by	O
bad	O
Acquaintance	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Alice	B-pers
Barnet	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
County	I-place
of	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
one	O
Mantua-Gown	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
:	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Stagg	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Stagg	I-pers
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
one	O
Feather-bed	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
laced	O
Ruffles	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
:	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Coward	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Algood	I-pers
,	O
Cathren	B-pers
De	I-pers
Roch	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
and	O
Alice	B-pers
Mitchell	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
County	I-place
of	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Breerwood	I-pers
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
6	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Snuff-box	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
Looking-Glass	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
laced	O
Scarf	O
25	O
s.	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
to	O
a	O
great	O
value	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
all	O
five	O
Indicted	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Mary	B-pers
Bull	I-pers
on	O
the	O
said	O
27th	O
of	O
December	O
two	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
a	O
laced	O
Tippet	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
5	O
Guineas	O
in	O
Gold	O
,	O
5	O
l.	O
in	O
Mill'd-money	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
to	O
a	O
great	O
value	O
.	O
John	O
Nichols	O
and	O
Sarah	O
Coward	O
were	O
a	O
3d	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
James	B-pers
Gabbs	I-pers
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
one	O
Silk	O
Petticoat	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
3	O
pair	O
of	O
laced	O
Ruffles	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
piece	O
of	O
coined	O
Gold	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
Coward	O
,	O
De	O
Roch	O
,	O
Nichols	O
and	O
Mitchel	O
advised	O
together	O
to	O
commit	O
the	O
Felonies	O
;	O
That	O
Nichols	O
the	O
day	O
and	O
time	O
the	O
Felonies	O
were	O
committed	O
,	O
having	O
got	O
Information	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Breerwood	O
's	O
Maid-servants	O
Husbands	O
name	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
Seaman	O
in	O
Jamaica	O
,	O
Nichols	O
himself	O
pretending	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
see	O
him	O
speedily	O
,	O
being	O
ingaged	O
in	O
a	O
Ship	O
suddenly	O
bound	O
thither	O
,	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
ready	O
to	O
carry	O
her	O
Message	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
keeping	O
her	O
for	O
two	O
hours	O
in	O
discourse	O
below-stairs	O
(	O
Mr.	O
Breerwood	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
being	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
)	O
while	O
Mitchel	O
and	O
De	O
Roch	O
rifled	O
the	O
Rooms	O
above-stairs	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
off	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
their	O
Custody	O
.	O
That	O
of	O
Gabb	O
's	O
Goods	O
was	O
positively	O
proved	O
against	O
Nichols	O
,	O
Coward	O
and	O
Mitchell	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
of	O
Mary	O
Bulls	O
was	O
plainly	O
proved	O
against	O
De	O
Roch	O
,	O
Mitchel	O
and	O
Nichols	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Algood	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Four	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Withers	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Dodson	I-pers
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
November	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Close-stool	O
Pan	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
6	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
:	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Wallington	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
one	O
Cloth	O
Mantua	O
Gown	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
:	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Huggins	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Gregory	I-place
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Matthew	B-pers
Sanders	I-pers
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
3	O
Yards	O
of	O
Flannel	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
entered	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
himself	O
being	O
abroad	O
,	O
leaving	O
only	O
some	O
Children	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
out	O
the	O
Candles	O
,	O
the	O
Children	O
made	O
a	O
Noise	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
overheard	O
by	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
who	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
seized	O
him	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
dropt	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
plain	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Pretious	I-pers
and	O
Alice	B-pers
Pretious	I-pers
(	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Lemond	I-pers
)	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Ward	B-place
of	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
secretly	O
taking	O
from	O
a	O
Gentleman	B-pers
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
May	O
10	O
Guineas	O
,	O
value	O
22	O
s.	O
each	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
declared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
owing	O
to	O
him	O
12	O
l.	O
by	O
Note	O
,	O
Robert	O
Pretious	O
invited	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
Legrand	I-place
to	O
receive	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
found	O
only	O
Pretious	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
who	O
shuffled	O
close	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
pickt	O
his	O
Pocket	O
of	O
the	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
several	O
Bills	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
clear	O
Evidence	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
but	O
will	O
be	O
prosecuted	O
at	O
Common	O
Law	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Sickes	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
Gent	O
.	O
as	O
Principal	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Sickes	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stanley	I-pers
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Greek	I-pers
,	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Parish	O
,	O
as	O
Accessories	O
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Murdering	O
James	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
upon	O
the	O
right	O
Side	O
near	O
the	O
short	O
Ribbs	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
six	O
in	O
depth	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
to	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Month	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Clements	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
being	O
an	O
Execution	O
out	O
against	O
Mr.	O
Sickes	O
's	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
deceased	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
were	O
about	O
to	O
put	O
in	O
execution	O
:	O
For	O
which	O
end	O
the	O
deceased	O
and	O
one	O
Farell	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Yard	O
Wall	O
about	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
lurked	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
till	O
about	O
9	O
or	O
10	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
when	O
Sickes	O
's	O
Maid	O
opened	O
the	O
Back-door	O
,	O
after	O
whom	O
they	O
rushed	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
suddenly	O
after	O
they	O
heard	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Pistols	O
let	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
saw	O
Farell	O
in	O
at	O
a	O
Sash	O
window	O
leaning	O
upon	O
a	O
Table	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
wonnded	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Sickes	O
swore	O
an	O
Oath	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
approach	O
'd	O
he	O
would	O
kill	O
him	O
and	O
40	O
more	O
such	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
also	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
heard	O
the	O
deceased	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
they	O
entered	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Inhabitants	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
Bailies	O
and	O
Rogues	O
:	O
upon	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Sickes	O
coming	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
met	O
Farell	O
,	O
and	O
discharged	O
two	O
Pistols	O
at	O
him	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
coming	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
lower	O
Room	O
,	O
where	O
Mr.	O
Sickes	O
's	O
Wife	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoners	O
had	O
seized	O
Anderson	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
sitting	O
upon	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
upon	O
his	O
Body	O
and	O
Legs	O
to	O
keep	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Sickes	O
himself	O
thrust	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Body	O
;	O
And	O
that	O
thereupon	O
a	O
Constable	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
Entrance	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
obtained	O
,	O
where	O
there	O
was	O
Powder	O
,	O
Bullets	O
,	O
Pistols	O
and	O
Swords	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
naked	O
Sword	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Barker	O
's	O
hand	O
.	O
They	O
also	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Sickes	O
's	O
Wife	O
's	O
Hands	O
and	O
Cloaths	O
were	O
all	O
bloody	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Sickes	O
himself	O
had	O
escaped	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
supposed	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Window	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Sickes	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
their	O
being	O
Baileys-followers	O
,	O
nor	O
that	O
they	O
came	O
upon	O
any	O
such	O
design	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
believed	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
Robbers	O
and	O
House-breakers	O
upon	O
the	O
Out	O
cry	O
below-stairs	O
of	O
Thieves	O
and	O
Murderers	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Farell	O
having	O
a	O
great	O
oaken	O
Stick	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
threatned	O
to	O
knock	O
him	O
down	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
fired	O
a	O
Pistol	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
grazed	O
in	O
his	O
Wig	O
:	O
That	O
so	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
understood	O
what	O
the	O
matter	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
ordered	O
ready	O
Entrance	O
to	O
be	O
given	O
.	O
He	O
also	O
call	O
'd	O
abundance	O
of	O
People	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
brought	O
them	O
all	O
in	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
;	O
but	O
with	O
a	O
Check	O
from	O
the	O
Bench	O
.	O
And	O
A	O
New	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
was	O
Impannelled	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
as	O
follows	O
:	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pitts	I-pers
Christopher	B-pers
Rednap	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
Andrew	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
Moses	B-pers
Colewell	I-pers
Bryan	B-pers
Turberville	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Davison	I-pers
William	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Bowler	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
William	B-pers
Strode	I-pers
.	O
William	O
Sickes	O
as	O
Principal	O
,	O
Mary	O
Sickes	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
Tho	O
.	O
Barker	O
,	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Stanley	O
and	O
Jane	O
Greek	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
as	O
Accessories	O
,	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Farrell	I-pers
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
Breast	O
near	O
to	O
the	O
right	O
Pap	O
,	O
one	O
Inch	O
broad	O
and	O
10	O
in	O
depth	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
suddenly	O
after	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
Case	O
of	O
the	O
former	O
Trial	O
about	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
James	O
Anderson	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
were	O
somewhat	O
more	O
plain	O
and	O
positive	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Circumstances	O
;	O
AndMr	O
.	O
Sickes	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
insisted	O
upon	O
the	O
same	O
Defences	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
:	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Accessories	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
William	O
Sickes	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Langstrop	I-pers
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
one	O
Cloth	O
Petticoat	O
with	O
three	O
Gold	O
Fringes	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
one	O
Stuff	O
Petticoat	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
Muslen	O
Head-dress	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
having	O
occasion	O
to	O
go	O
abroad	O
,	O
lockt	O
her	O
Door	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
the	O
Key	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
her	O
return	O
found	O
the	O
Glass-window	O
broke	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
discovered	O
at	O
a	O
House	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sold	O
them	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
kept	O
a	O
Victualing-house	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Company	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
left	O
the	O
Goods	O
for	O
their	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
make	O
appear	O
by	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
and	O
keeping	O
the	O
Goods	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Parties	O
not	O
coming	O
to	O
relieve	O
them	O
:	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Gravner	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Gravner	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Tedington	B-place
,	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Hanna	B-pers
Pick	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
two	O
Turky-hens	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
off	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
possession	O
with	O
their	O
Heads	O
cut	O
off	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
her	O
having	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
she	O
found	O
them	O
dead	O
on	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
which	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
her	O
:	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Price	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
one	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
with	O
a	O
Tortois-shell	O
Case	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Custody	O
,	O
having	O
confest	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
it	O
when	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
another	O
Felony	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Hannoway	I-pers
and	O
W	B-pers
-	I-pers
W	I-pers
-	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Chelsea	B-place
,	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Richard	B-pers
Hannoway	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
nigh	O
unto	O
the	O
right	O
Pap	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
and	O
4	O
in	O
depth	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
and	O
died	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
as	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
the	O
said	O
Richard	O
Hannoway	O
were	O
coming	O
along	O
the	O
Lord	B-place
Chinay	I-place
's	I-place
Walks	I-place
at	I-place
Chelsea	I-place
,	O
they	O
met	O
the	O
deceased	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
in	O
his	O
Company	O
,	O
betwixt	O
whom	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
justling	O
and	O
hard	O
words	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
the	O
unhappy	O
Accident	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
their	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
and	O
one	O
Child	O
used	O
them	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Richard	O
Hannoway	O
very	O
roughly	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
them	O
with	O
a	O
Link	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
over	O
the	O
Face	O
and	O
Head	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Link	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
deceased	O
received	O
his	O
Wound	O
;	O
And	O
the	O
said	O
Richard	O
Hannoway	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
drew	O
their	O
Swords	O
,	O
but	O
on	O
the	O
contrary	O
appeared	O
rather	O
to	O
be	O
sufferers	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
Evidence	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
justify	O
them	O
:	O
they	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Liberty	I-place
of	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
David	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Monky	O
David	O
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
break	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Laurence	B-pers
Mortimer	I-pers
,	O
and	O
took	O
thence	O
one	O
Cloth	O
Wastcoat	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Feather	O
Pillow	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Brother	O
the	O
Monky	O
,	O
entered	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
to	O
a	O
Room	O
where	O
the	O
Goods	O
lay	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
bringing	O
the	O
Goods	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
a	O
Noise	O
was	O
heard	O
by	O
the	O
People	O
below	O
,	O
who	O
immediately	O
,	O
being	O
upon	O
their	O
guard	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
observing	O
it	O
,	O
dropt	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
the	O
Monky	O
leading	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
seized	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
down	O
after	O
him	O
was	O
also	O
seized	O
,	O
but	O
Green	O
escaped	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
question	O
'd	O
what	O
business	O
he	O
had	O
there	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
inquire	O
for	O
a	O
Colonel	O
.	O
He	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
make	O
no	O
other	O
defence	O
:	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Bowman	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
;	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
another	O
Person	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
break	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
betwixt	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
thence	O
one	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
with	O
plate-buttons	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
Beaver	O
Hat	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Camlet-Cloak	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Bowman	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Room	O
with	O
two	O
Women	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
some	O
Ale	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
placed	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
next	O
to	O
that	O
where	O
the	O
Goods	O
lay	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
gone	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
returned	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
off	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
afterwards	O
found	O
in	O
Bowman	O
's	O
possession	O
:	O
and	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
both	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
White	O
told	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
where	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
sold	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
helpt	O
Bowman	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Window	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
breaking	O
in	O
not	O
being	O
positively	O
asserted	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
them	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Simpkins	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Ravishing	O
and	O
carnally	O
Knowing	O
Grace	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Girl	O
of	O
10	O
years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
against	O
her	O
will	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pickt	O
up	O
the	O
Girl	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
made	O
her	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
carry	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
an	O
empty	O
House	O
in	O
the	O
New	O
Buildings	O
in	O
the	O
Lestall	B-place
;	O
and	O
sitting	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Girl	O
upon	O
his	O
Lap	O
,	O
and	O
committed	O
the	O
Villany	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Pox	O
.	O
The	O
Chirurgeon	O
,	O
who	O
has	O
the	O
Girl	O
under	O
Cure	O
,	O
gave	O
his	O
Judgment	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
spoiled	O
in	O
her	O
privy	O
Parts	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
infected	O
with	O
the	O
Venereal	O
distemper	O
but	O
by	O
carnal	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
.	O
The	O
Girl	O
owned	O
in	O
Court	O
that	O
she	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
bid	O
her	O
hush	O
.	O
The	O
whole	O
Circumstances	O
being	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Sepulchers	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
County	I-place
of	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
a	O
Gold	O
Chain	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Daughter	O
having	O
put	O
her	O
Chain	O
into	O
a	O
Pail	O
of	O
Water	O
without	O
doors	O
till	O
she	O
washt	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
forgot	O
it	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
supposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
for	O
some	O
Water	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
that	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
Chain	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
given	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
40	O
s.	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Felony	O
did	O
not	O
plainly	O
appear	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
J	B-pers
-	I-pers
B	I-pers
-	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
violently	O
assaulting	O
,	O
throwing	O
down	O
,	O
heating	O
and	O
Kicking	O
Elenor	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
and	O
bruised	O
her	O
with	O
his	O
Hands	O
,	O
Knees	O
and	O
Feet	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
suddenly	O
after	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
Deposed	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
last	O
Thanksgiving	O
day	O
,	O
they	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
kick	O
and	O
beat	O
the	O
Deceased	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
thieving	O
Woman	O
,	O
had	O
stole	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Chiurrgion	O
and	O
several	O
others	O
declaring	O
that	O
they	O
found	O
no	O
marks	O
of	O
Bruises	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
which	O
might	O
occasion	O
a	O
violent	O
Death	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
an	O
aged	O
Woman	O
and	O
troubled	O
with	O
Fits	O
,	O
concluded	O
she	O
died	O
a	O
natural	O
Death	O
:	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Keckwood	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Harlington	B-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
some	O
others	O
,	O
did	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
rob	O
Edward	B-pers
Hipsly	I-pers
Gentleman	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
one	O
Silver-hilted	O
Sword	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Gold-Ring	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
numbered	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Thomas	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
on	O
the	O
said	O
29th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
one	O
Silver-hilted	O
Sword	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
Mile	O
beyond	O
Hounslow	B-place
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
them	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Robbery	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
shared	O
the	O
Spoil	O
among	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
,	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
desired	O
that	O
their	O
Swords	O
might	O
be	O
sent	O
to	O
a	O
certain	O
place	O
which	O
they	O
appointed	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
promised	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
confirmed	O
by	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
Mr.	O
Freeman	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Hipslys	O
Ring	O
was	O
also	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Elton	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Counterfeiting	O
the	O
current	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
9th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
several	O
times	O
desired	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
join	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
that	O
wicked	O
Trade	O
,	O
which	O
,	O
through	O
great	O
Importunities	O
,	O
he	O
accepted	O
:	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
let	O
him	O
see	O
several	O
Say-pieces	O
,	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
could	O
do	O
it	O
as	O
clean	O
as	O
the	O
Pattern	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
fit	O
House	O
for	O
that	O
purpose	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Say	O
pieces	O
were	O
shown	O
to	O
Sarah	O
Smith	O
for	O
her	O
Approbation	O
:	O
That	O
they	O
imploy	O
'd	O
another	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
to	O
put	O
off	O
some	O
of	O
their	O
false	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
buy	O
Melting	O
Pots	O
and	O
Files	O
:	O
That	O
Sarah	O
Smith	O
blew	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
and	O
shewing	O
some	O
dislike	O
at	O
the	O
Mixture	O
of	O
the	O
Metal	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
rather	O
have	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
Copper	O
mixture	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
sort	O
she	O
had	O
put	O
off	O
a	O
great	O
quantity	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
where	O
her	O
Husband	O
coined	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
whitened	O
and	O
finished	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
also	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
found	O
John	O
Elton	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
all	O
the	O
Utensils	O
for	O
that	O
hellish	O
Trade	O
were	O
,	O
as	O
were	O
several	O
Species	O
of	O
Counterfeit-money	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
upon	O
his	O
being	O
seized	O
,	O
he	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
escape	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
all	O
the	O
Utensils	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
leave	O
of	O
the	O
Prisonersto	O
lodg	O
them	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
owned	O
by	O
him	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
working	O
Silversmith	O
,	O
whose	O
Testimony	O
was	O
by	O
several	O
Circumstances	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
credited	O
,	O
and	O
apparently	O
brought	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
into	O
a	O
snare	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
them	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
poor	O
,	O
harmless	O
,	O
indigent	O
People	O
,	O
and	O
wrought	O
hard	O
for	O
their	O
Living	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
Case	O
proving	O
very	O
favourable	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bailham	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Finchly	B-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kirk	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
9th	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
Majestie	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Silk	O
Fringe	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Pocket-book	O
,	O
10s	O
.	O
in	O
Moneys	O
numbred	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
one	O
Holiday	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
him	O
on	O
Finchly-common	B-place
about	O
8	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
latter	O
took	O
10	O
Guineas	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
right	O
side	O
Pocket	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
searcht	O
his	O
left	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
being	O
pretty-well	O
known	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Millington	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Millington	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Duffey	I-pers
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
one	O
Stuff	O
Coat	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
2	O
Cloth	O
Wastcoats	O
value	O
30s	O
.	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
having	O
occasion	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
entrusted	O
Sarah	O
Millington	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
her	O
Room	O
and	O
Charge	O
of	O
her	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
her	O
return	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
And	O
another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
both	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Room	O
together	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
further	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Sarah	O
Millington	O
throw	O
a	O
Blanket	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Stall	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
that	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
carry	O
off	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
found	O
in	O
their	O
Custody	O
save	O
the	O
Blanket	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
owned	O
was	O
about	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
dropt	O
in	O
the	O
Stall	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
it	O
down	O
thither	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
them	O
in	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Grace	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonards	I-place
Shorditch	I-place
,	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Collet	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
4	O
Curtain	O
Window-cases	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
Holland	O
sheet	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Watch	O
going	O
their	O
Rounds	O
,	O
heard	O
a	O
great	O
Noise	O
of	O
barking	O
of	O
Dogs	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
them	O
suspect	O
Thieves	O
;	O
and	O
making	O
search	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
under	O
her	O
Arm	O
,	O
which	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
2	O
of	O
the	O
Window-Cases	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Sheet	O
wrapt	O
about	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
other	O
2	O
Cases	O
at	O
a	O
small	O
distance	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
from	O
a	O
House	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Banqueting-house	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
sheet	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
seized	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
Woman	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Necessitous	O
Condition	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
given	O
to	O
pilfering	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
brought	O
in	O
a	O
sutable	O
Verdict	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Coston	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Coston	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Steel	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
40	O
Pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Beef	O
value	O
30	O
s	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Henry	B-pers
Burges	I-pers
on	O
the	O
said	O
1st	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
one	O
Flaxen	O
Sheet	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
entred	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	O
Mills	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
the	O
Beef	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
it	O
lay	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
heard	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Son	O
,	O
and	O
pursued	O
,	O
they	O
dropt	O
the	O
Beef	O
in	O
the	O
Passage	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
their	O
being	O
seized	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	O
Burges	O
were	O
found	O
about	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Mary	O
Coston	O
,	O
with	O
4	O
Picklock	O
Keys	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
others	O
at	O
a	O
small	O
distance	O
from	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
seized	O
.	O
The	O
Burglary	O
was	O
not	O
proved	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
any	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
seem	O
to	O
affect	O
Steel	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
;	O
but	O
Coston	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Broom	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Scotman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Sir	O
George	B-pers
Downing	I-pers
,	O
Baronet	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
one	O
black-coloured	O
Weather	O
Sheep	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
the	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Sheep	O
was	O
seen	O
on	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Ground	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
miss	O
'd	O
before	O
Night	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Husband	O
was	O
seen	O
that	O
day	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
who	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
supposed	O
,	O
carry	O
'd	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
kill	O
'd	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Sheep	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
custody	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
conceal	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Liberty	I-place
of	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
December	O
about	O
8	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Coach-glasses	O
value	O
12	O
l.	O
12	O
Yards	O
of	O
green	O
Velvet	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
his	O
Royal	O
Highness	O
Prince	B-pers
George	I-pers
of	I-pers
Denmark	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
had	O
Access	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
his	O
Royal	O
Highnesses	O
Chariot	O
Stood	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
off	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
brought	O
to	O
a	O
Victualling	O
house	O
to	O
be	O
hid	O
up	O
for	O
his	O
use	O
;	O
where	O
being	O
question	O
'd	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
brought	O
them	O
from	O
Bristol	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Burglary	O
was	O
no	O
ways	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Netter	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
in	O
Counterfeiting	O
the	O
current	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
:	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Earle	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holburn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Swallow	I-pers
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
one	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
value	O
55	O
s.	O
5	O
Muslen-Cravats	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
took	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
carry	O
off	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
owned	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
his	O
Trial	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
:	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
George	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
,	O
did	O
rob	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
from	O
Sarah	B-pers
Webster	I-pers
Wife	O
of	O
Matthew	B-pers
Webster	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
October	O
one	O
Feather-Tippet	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Henry	B-pers
Borgrave	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Hewet	I-pers
,	O
did	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
Murder	O
Christopher	B-pers
Ludbrook	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
in	O
depth	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
suddenly	O
after	O
died	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
there	O
having	O
been	O
some	O
difference	O
between	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
encreased	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
fatal	O
place	O
for	O
determining	O
the	O
difference	O
appointed	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Back-side	O
of	O
Southampton	B-place
House	I-place
,	O
whither	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
repaired	O
about	O
10	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
saw	O
Borgrave	O
and	O
Hewet	O
go	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
them	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
by	O
that	O
time	O
the	O
business	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
afterwards	O
the	O
same	O
two	O
Persons	O
came	O
back	O
that	O
same	O
way	O
with	O
a	O
wounded	O
Person	O
betwixt	O
them	O
whom	O
they	O
left	O
at	O
the	O
Green	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
off	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
kill	O
'd	O
the	O
deceased	O
;	O
But	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
great	O
provocation	O
and	O
threatning	O
given	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
appearing	O
,	O
that	O
betwixt	O
the	O
quarrelling	O
and	O
fighting	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Deceased	O
continued	O
in	O
hot-blood	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
weighing	O
all	O
the	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
brought	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Bradley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonards	I-place
Shore-ditch	I-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
marrying	O
two	O
Wives	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
Helenor	B-pers
Chelsford	I-pers
at	O
Br	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
ham	O
in	O
Wiltshire	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
October	O
in	O
the	O
24th	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
Reign	O
of	O
King	O
Charles	O
the	O
2d	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
November	O
in	O
the	O
8th	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
present	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
did	O
take	O
to	O
Wife	O
Helenor	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
;	O
The	O
Evidence	O
plainly	O
proved	O
both	O
Marriages	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lived	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
Years	O
with	O
the	O
first	O
,	O
by	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Children	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
Por	O
ion	O
with	O
the	O
2d	O
Wife	O
,	O
which	O
Marriage	O
he	O
owned	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
un	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
disposed	O
of	O
her	O
Estate	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
her	O
roughly	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
in	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Dove	I-pers
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
10	O
Ewe-Sheep	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Weather	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
missing	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
search	O
'd	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Possession	O
,	O
selling	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
Butcher	O
,	O
who	O
suspecting	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
,	O
questioned	O
him	O
;	O
who	O
answered	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Robins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Hackney	B-place
in	O
Middlesex	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Henry	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
one	O
Cow	O
Calf	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
It	O
appeared	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
Calf	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
sold	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
done	O
accordingly	O
for	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
received	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
allowing	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
Milk	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
driving	O
some	O
Cows	O
along	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
the	O
Calf	O
fell	O
in	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
found	O
in	O
several	O
Contradictions	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Finchly	B-place
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
John	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
of	O
50	O
Yards	O
of	O
Calimanca	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
one	O
piece	O
of	O
Serge	O
,	O
value	O
30s	O
.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Huggins	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
a	O
Waggoner	O
,	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
,	O
was	O
followed	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
several	O
times	O
mounted	O
the	O
Waggon	O
against	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
will	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
jealous	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
inspected	O
the	O
Waggon	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
found	O
5	O
Packs	O
ript	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Goods	O
taken	O
out	O
;	O
that	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
being	O
seized	O
he	O
confest	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
brought	O
to	O
London	O
and	O
afterwards	O
sold	O
part	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
a	O
Woman	O
the	O
rest	O
to	O
put	O
off	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
sufficient	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Fellony	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
not	O
being	O
miss	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
Waggoner	O
took	O
up	O
his	O
Lodging	O
:	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Holford	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Andrew	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
,	O
and	O
several	O
others	O
,	O
did	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
July	O
meet	O
,	O
consult	O
,	O
and	O
advise	O
how	O
to	O
seize	O
and	O
carry	O
off	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Susanna	B-pers
Loverain	I-pers
a	O
Virgin	O
,	O
within	O
the	O
Age	O
of	O
15	O
Years	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
great	O
Fortune	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Design	O
to	O
marry	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
Mitchel	O
against	O
the	O
Will	O
and	O
Consent	O
of	O
the	O
young	O
Lady	O
,	O
or	O
those	O
to	O
whom	O
she	O
was	O
intrusted	O
:	O
for	O
which	O
end	O
the	O
Lady	O
and	O
her	O
Maid	O
Mary	B-pers
Brand	I-pers
were	O
arrested	O
in	O
a	O
Fob-Action	O
,	O
by	O
virtue	O
of	O
a	O
Writ	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Suit	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Wilcox	O
.	O
'T	O
was	O
deposed	O
that	O
at	O
a	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Holborn	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
proposed	O
to	O
him	O
a	O
Match	O
worth	O
500	O
l.	O
which	O
proved	O
the	O
young	O
Lady	O
's	O
Maid	O
,	O
Mary	O
Brand	O
,	O
into	O
whose	O
Company	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
procured	O
Admittance	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Design	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
more	O
easy	O
Access	O
to	O
the	O
young	O
Lady	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
afterwards	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
proposed	O
to	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
of	O
any	O
Gentleman	O
of	O
his	O
Acquaintance	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Lady	O
in	O
view	O
of	O
a	O
great	O
Fortune	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
she	O
could	O
get	O
him	O
matched	O
,	O
giving	O
her	O
a	O
Reward	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
proposed	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
Michel	O
,	O
the	O
Time	O
and	O
Place	O
of	O
seeing	O
the	O
young	O
Lady	O
was	O
proposed	O
.	O
He	O
also	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
imployed	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
desire	O
a	O
Bond	O
of	O
500l	O
.	O
from	O
Mitchel	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
Reward	O
to	O
help	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Fortune	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
against	O
it	O
.	O
Another	O
deposed	O
that	O
about	O
12	O
Months	O
ago	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
serve	O
an	O
Instrument	O
of	O
400	O
l.	O
as	O
a	O
Reward	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Mitchel	O
for	O
procuring	O
the	O
Match	O
with	O
Madam	O
Loverain	O
;	O
whom	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
get	O
carried	O
off	O
;	O
at	O
which	O
he	O
showing	O
his	O
Detestation	O
,	O
refused	O
it	O
.	O
Another	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Mitchel	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Will	O
of	O
the	O
Lady	O
's	O
Father	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Merchant	O
in	O
Barnstaple	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
afterwards	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Meeting	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Gentlewoman	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
again	O
proposed	O
to	O
carry	O
off	O
the	O
Lady	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Reward	O
of	O
about	O
500	O
l.	O
to	O
be	O
given	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
several	O
times	O
disswaded	O
Mitchel	O
from	O
such	O
an	O
unlawful	O
Attempt	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
very	O
dangerous	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Warrant	O
against	O
him	O
for	O
being	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Attempt	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
proposed	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
Coaches	O
to	O
be	O
ready	O
at	O
the	O
Dancing-School	O
where	O
the	O
young	O
Lady	O
went	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
effect	O
the	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
that	O
way	O
.	O
Mary	O
Bland	O
deposed	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
July	O
her	O
Mistriss	O
and	O
she	O
were	O
arrested	O
in	O
Chancery-Lane	O
and	O
forced	O
into	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
but	O
relieved	O
by	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
who	O
knew	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
her	O
Mistriss	O
at	O
the	O
Dancing-School	O
.	O
She	O
further	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
brought	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
see	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
proposed	O
a	O
Match	O
betwixt	O
them	O
.	O
Another	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
arrest	O
the	O
young	O
Lady	O
and	O
her	O
Maid	O
:	O
that	O
Mitchel	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
prest	O
the	O
Arrest	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
put	O
in	O
execution	O
.	O
The	O
Coach-man	O
deposed	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Mitchel	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
carry	O
off	O
a	O
young	O
Lady	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
have	O
him	O
in	O
Marriage	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
several	O
Meetings	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
she	O
proposed	O
to	O
procure	O
Mr.	O
Mitchel	O
to	O
be	O
married	O
to	O
Madam	O
Loverain	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
400	O
l.	O
Reward	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
and	O
to	O
prove	O
her	O
being	O
elsewhere	O
that	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
Arrest	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Bradford	I-pers
was	O
committed	O
to	O
Newgate	O
by	O
the	O
Bench	O
for	O
printing	O
and	O
publishing	O
a	O
false	O
and	O
scurrilous	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Trials	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Sikes	O
for	O
killing	O
the	O
Bailiffs	O
Followers	O
,	O
that	O
of	O
the	O
Woman	O
for	O
killing	O
her	O
Bastard	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
of	O
Simpkins	O
for	O
the	O
Rape	O
,	O
the	O
whole	O
circumstances	O
being	O
therein	O
mispresented	O
,	O
which	O
seem	O
to	O
reflect	O
both	O
upon	O
the	O
Justice	O
of	O
the	O
Bench	O
and	O
Jury	O
.	O
The	O
latter	O
having	O
complained	O
of	O
this	O
abuse	O
to	O
the	O
Bench	O
,	O
who	O
declared	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
only	O
punish	O
this	O
Offence	O
,	O
but	O
suppress	O
any	O
such	O
for	O
the	O
future	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
Proceeded	O
to	O
pronounce	O
Sentence	O
,	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
12	O
.	O
Jane	O
Brown	O
,	O
David	O
Owen	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Davis	O
,	O
William	O
Ingrum	O
,	O
Philip	O
Cary	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Pain	O
,	O
William	O
Stone	O
,	O
Mary	O
Price	O
,	O
Henry	O
Simpkins	O
,	O
William	O
Richardson	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Bailham	O
,	O
Francis	O
Kerkwood	O
.	O
Jane	O
Brown	O
and	O
Mary	O
Price	O
pleaded	O
their	O
Bellies	O
and	O
were	O
found	O
quick	O
with	O
Child	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
32	O
.	O
William	O
Dicaits	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Wright	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Huggins	O
,	O
Tho	O
.	O
Harris	O
,	O
Sara	O
King	O
,	O
Bridget	O
Hays	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Green	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Williams	O
,	O
William	O
Hudson	O
alias	O
Philips	O
on	O
a	O
former	O
Conviction	O
,	O
John	O
Jackson	O
,	O
Joseph	O
Newland	O
,	O
Benjamin	O
Harding	O
,	O
John	O
Nichols	O
,	O
William	O
Sikes	O
,	O
John	O
Bowman	O
,	O
Richard	O
White	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Wats	O
,	O
John	O
Earle	O
,	O
Richard	O
Radford	O
,	O
James	O
Stagg	O
,	O
Anthony	O
Robinson	O
,	O
Christopher	O
Ladbroke	O
,	O
William	O
Bradley	O
,	O
William	O
Smith	O
,	O
Edward	O
Wood	O
,	O
Richard	O
Robins	O
,	O
John	O
Ingleton	O
upon	O
a	O
former	O
Conviction	O
,	O
Alice	O
Mitchell	O
,	O
Sara	O
Coward	O
,	O
Mary	O
Costin	O
,	O
Alice	O
Moticay	O
,	O
Jane	O
Withers	O
,	O
Alice	O
Burnet	O
,	O
Mary	O
Wallington	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipp	O
'd	O
,	O
6	O
.	O
Mary	O
Gravner	O
,	O
Grace	O
Turner	O
,	O
Charles	O
Cooper	O
,	O
Mary	O
Day	O
,	O
Jarvis	O
Shaw	O
,	O
Mary	O
Pickman	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Bradford	I-pers
was	O
committed	O
to	O
Newgate	O
by	O
the	O
Bench	O
for	O
printing	O
and	O
publishing	O
a	O
false	O
and	O
scurrilous	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Trials	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Sikes	O
for	O
killing	O
the	O
Bailiffs	O
Followers	O
,	O
that	O
of	O
the	O
Woman	O
for	O
killing	O
her	O
Bastard	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
of	O
Simpkins	O
for	O
the	O
Rape	O
,	O
the	O
whole	O
circumstances	O
being	O
therein	O
mispresented	O
,	O
which	O
seem	O
to	O
reflect	O
both	O
upon	O
the	O
Justice	O
of	O
the	O
Bench	O
and	O
Jury	O
.	O
The	O
latter	O
having	O
complained	O
of	O
this	O
abuse	O
to	O
the	O
Bench	O
,	O
who	O
declared	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
only	O
punish	O
this	O
Offence	O
,	O
but	O
suppress	O
any	O
such	O
for	O
the	O
future	O
.	O
Ann	O
Holford	O
was	O
fined	O
l00	O
l.	O
and	O
to	O
lie	O
in	O
Prison	O
till	O
it	O
be	O
paid	O
.	O
BOOKS	O
printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
Andrew	O
Bell	O
at	O
the	O
Cross-keys	O
and	O
Bible	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
,	O
near	O
Stocks-Market	O
.	O
ADvice	O
to	O
the	O
Young	O
;	O
or	O
the	O
Reasonableness	O
and	O
Advantages	O
of	O
an	O
Early	O
Conversion	O
,	O
in	O
several	O
Sermons	O
on	O
Eccles	O
.	O
12	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
Price	O
2s	O
.	O
The	O
Groans	O
of	O
a	O
Saint	O
under	O
the	O
Burden	O
of	O
a	O
mortal	O
Body	O
.	O
A	O
Sermon	O
preached	O
at	O
the	O
Funeral	O
or	O
Mr.	O
John	O
Belcher	O
,	O
late	O
Minister	O
of	O
the	O
Gospel	O
,	O
from	O
Cor	O
.	O
5	O
.	O
4	O
.	O
Price	O
6	O
d.	O
Hymns	O
in	O
Commemoration	O
of	O
the	O
Sufferings	O
of	O
our	O
Blessed	O
Saviour	O
Jesus	O
Christ	O
,	O
compos	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
Celebration	O
of	O
his	O
Holy	O
Supper	O
.	O
Price	O
6	O
d.	O
A	O
Poem	O
to	O
the	O
Memory	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Timothy	O
Cruso	O
,	O
late	O
Minister	O
of	O
the	O
Gospel	O
.	O
Price	O
4.	O
d.	O
All	O
by	O
Joseph	O
Stennet	O
.	O
