TOKEN	NE
The	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
,	O
Monday	O
,	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
and	O
Thursday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
13	O
,	O
14	O
,	O
16	O
,	O
17	O
,	O
18	O
and	O
19th	O
Days	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
1699	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
Tenth	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
,	O
on	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
,	O
Monday	O
,	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
and	O
Thursday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
13	O
,	O
14	O
,	O
16	O
,	O
17	O
,	O
18	O
,	O
and	O
19th	O
Days	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
1698	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
CHILD	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
Salathiel	B-pers
Lovell	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
are	O
as	O
follow	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Pollington	I-pers
.	O
John	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
Hugh	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Brandon	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
King	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
.	O
James	B-pers
Brockden	I-pers
.	O
Jeremy	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
.	O
Roger	B-pers
Lacy	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Dyer	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Meredith	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Rednap	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Moodey	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dick	I-pers
.	O
Simon	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Miles	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barns	I-pers
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Devenish	I-pers
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Bradbury	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Giles	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Burgoine	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
these	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rachey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Catherines	I-place
Colemans	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Ward	I-place
of	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
wooden	O
Runlet	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
and	O
twelve	O
Gallons	O
of	O
sherry	O
Wine	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Dry	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
Robbed	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
lost	O
several	O
quantities	O
of	O
Wines	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
who	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
Evidence	O
that	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Watchman	O
,	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
vault	O
Door	O
with	O
a	O
false	O
key	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
help	O
him	O
up	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
in	O
Northumberland-Alley	O
by	O
the	O
Constable	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
false	O
Key	O
;	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
desire	O
to	O
be	O
helpt	O
up	O
with	O
it	O
upon	O
his	O
Shoulder	O
.	O
He	O
could	O
not	O
call	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Bray	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Olaves	I-place
Hart-street	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gallon	O
of	O
Canary	O
Wine	O
,	O
value	O
6s	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Ninth	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Frier	I-pers
:	O
he	O
was	O
likewise	O
a	O
Watchman	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
to	O
convict	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Grace	B-pers
Peirce	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Peters	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
six	O
Ells	O
of	O
Holland	O
Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Lancelot	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
the	O
Elder	O
,	O
and	O
Lancelot	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
the	O
younger	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Lee	O
's	O
Shop	O
buying	O
some	O
Linnen	O
Cloath	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
cheapened	O
some	O
blew	O
Ditte	O
,	O
and	O
whilst	O
the	O
were	O
busy	O
together	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
off	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
her	O
Coats	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Lee	O
's	O
Man	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Woman	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
mistrusting	O
they	O
would	O
search	O
her	O
,	O
drop	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
it	O
fell	O
off	O
the	O
Counter	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
plain	O
against	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bedford	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
12s	O
.	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
13s	O
.	O
a	O
Knit	O
Purse	O
,	O
with	O
17l	O
.	O
2s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
in	O
Monies	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Samey	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
:	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
to	O
Smithfield	O
Market	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Beasts	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
bought	O
some	O
he	O
went	O
home	O
to	O
fetch	O
some	O
Money	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
unlock	O
the	O
Cup-board	O
where	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
,	O
found	O
it	O
very	O
hard	O
to	O
open	O
;	O
but	O
looking	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Money	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
also	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
in	O
Shoe-Lane	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
desired	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
make	O
a	O
noise	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
tell	O
him	O
something	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
consenting	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
who	O
pretended	O
Love	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
enticed	O
her	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
who	O
opened	O
the	O
Cup-board-door	O
with	O
a	O
Case	O
Knife	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
lent	O
him	O
;	O
she	O
likewise	O
owned	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
pawned	O
the	O
Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
little	O
else	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Francklyn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Undershaft	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
half	O
hundred	O
leaden-weight	O
,	O
value	O
7s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2nd	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
weight	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
Apron	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
hired	O
by	O
one	O
Smith	O
,	O
who	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
,	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Armstrong	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Norton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
two	O
Cloath	O
Coats	O
,	O
a	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
six	O
Diaper	O
Napkins	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cotes	I-pers
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Door	O
was	O
lock	O
'd	O
with	O
a	O
Padlock	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Goods	O
were	O
there	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
Some	O
time	O
after	O
his	O
Landlady	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Door	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Goods	O
gone	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
he	O
pursued	O
after	O
the	O
Robber	O
;	O
and	O
going	O
down	O
Shoe-Lane	O
he	O
overtook	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
who	O
being	O
taken	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
at	O
St.	O
Andrew	O
's	O
Church-wall	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
likewise	O
denied	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
ever	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
in	O
all	O
his	O
Life	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
felony	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Chalkley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Chalkley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Peters	I-place
Pauls-wharfe	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
three	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Tongs	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Blankets	O
,	O
with	O
two	O
Feather	O
Pillows	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
Lodgers	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
wrongfully	O
troubled	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
for	O
having	O
Arrested	O
him	O
;	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
them	O
both	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cavelley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
Chambers	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Riggs	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
in	O
Tanfield	B-place
Court	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Inner-Temple	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Morning	O
Gown	O
and	O
Wast-coat	O
,	O
with	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
:	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
Chamber	O
,	O
broke	O
the	O
Glass	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
cut	O
the	O
Bar	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
bundled	O
up	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
shut	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
the	O
same	O
way	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Tiles	O
falling	O
off	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
discovered	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
cried	O
out	O
Thieves	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ran	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
out	O
Thieves	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
have	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
ask	O
for	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
but	O
met	O
with	O
a	O
Man	O
upon	O
the	O
Stairs	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
call	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Sherrack	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Somerset	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Ward	I-place
of	I-place
Queenhithe	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
Sixteen	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Died	O
Silk	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
9th	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stole	O
it	O
;	O
besides	O
,	O
he	O
called	O
divers	O
People	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Account	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
wrongfully	O
accused	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Molton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
black	O
Gelding	O
from	O
James	B-pers
Staughton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
;	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
at	O
Tooting	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Surry	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
Prosecuted	O
at	O
the	O
next	O
Assizes	O
in	O
Surrey	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Frogg	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
a	O
Salt	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
second	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
S	B-pers
-	I-pers
J	I-pers
-	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Pickett	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Pettman	I-pers
,	O
all	O
three	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Lawson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
six	O
Cloath	O
Coats	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Shagreen	O
Wast-coat	O
,	O
a	O
blew	O
Wast-coat	O
,	O
twelve	O
pair	O
of	O
Cloath	O
Breeches	O
,	O
a	O
Child	O
's	O
Coat	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
that	O
his	O
Shop	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Goods	O
gone	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Shops	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
Coat	O
sold	O
by	O
Pettman	O
to	O
another	O
Person	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
Brokers	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
Bought	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
one	O
Bradley	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
since	O
fled	O
;	O
and	O
Pettman	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
upon	O
a	O
Seller	O
Door	O
,	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
They	O
called	O
People	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
a	O
good	O
Account	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Rundlet	O
,	O
value	O
10d	O
.	O
and	O
two	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Brandy	O
20s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Beech	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
his	O
Door	O
at	O
Kensington	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
Man	O
lived	O
there	O
that	O
lived	O
there	O
formerly	O
,	O
with	O
that	O
he	O
replied	O
yes	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
Pembrook	O
shire	O
,	O
from	O
his	O
Sister-in-Law	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
Token	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
a	O
Vessel	O
of	O
Ale	O
,	O
a	O
Barrel	O
of	O
Pickled	O
Oysters	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Flannen	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
he	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
walk	O
in	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
treated	O
him	O
with	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
happened	O
that	O
some	O
Granadeers	O
were	O
quarrelling	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
:	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
slipt	O
into	O
the	O
Seller	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
his	O
way	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
Hide	O
Park	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
:	O
He	O
had	O
but	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
call	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Weather-Sheep	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Willingham	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
third	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
not	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Herbert	B-pers
Herring	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Edge	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Day-time	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Canvas	O
Bag	O
,	O
and	O
22s	O
.	O
the	O
Monies	O
of	O
Thomas	O
Edge	O
,	O
and	O
22l	O
.	O
12s	O
.	O
the	O
Monies	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Willet	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Peirce	I-pers
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Edge	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
whilst	O
his	O
back	O
was	O
turned	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Fire-fork	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Monies	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Ring	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
a	O
Reward	O
was	O
offered	O
for	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
accordingly	O
the	O
Beadle	O
of	O
St.	O
Martins	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
his	O
Serjeant	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
who	O
accordingly	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Ring	O
with	O
some	O
Guinea	O
's	O
and	O
two	O
Pistols	O
,	O
hid	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Shoes	O
;	O
his	O
Serjeant	O
likewise	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
much	O
value	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
before	O
with	O
a	O
cold	O
Iron	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
how	O
to	O
come	O
off	O
well	O
enough	O
for	O
this	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
receive	O
17	O
Guinea	O
's	O
from	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
sent	O
from	O
his	O
Sister	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
an	O
Offender	O
before	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Tayler	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Pewter	O
pint	O
Pots	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Crossley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
,	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Stafford	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
Sheets	O
,	O
a	O
Hood	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Muff	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Campton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Day	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mildred	I-place
Bread-street	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
yards	O
of	O
Frize	O
Cloath	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bramston	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
off	O
the	O
Stall	O
,	O
and	O
goe	O
his	O
way	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
pursued	O
he	O
dropt	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
it	O
lye	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
steal	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
could	O
not	O
call	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
or	O
way	O
of	O
Living	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Catherines	I-place
Colemans	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Paine	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
Five	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Brass	O
Porridge	O
Pot	O
,	O
a	O
Brass	O
Ladle	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Boots	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Seller	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
removed	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
stairs	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
removed	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Seller	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
went	O
in	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Floyd	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Holloway	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolphs	I-place
Bishop-gate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
seven	O
Yards	O
of	O
Muslin	O
Cloath	O
,	O
value	O
28s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Wingfeild	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
;	O
Holloway	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
Floyd	O
put	O
her	O
self	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
,	O
which	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
both	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
strip	O
'd	O
Muslin	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Holloway	O
took	O
it	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
Floyd	O
,	O
who	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
her	O
Petticoat	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
proved	O
against	O
Floyd	O
,	O
who	O
could	O
give	O
no	O
good	O
account	O
of	O
her	O
self	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Alice	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Christ-Church	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
10	O
Yards	O
of	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Wilkins	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Thirteenth	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Vedast	I-place
,	I-place
alias	I-place
Fosters	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
Nineteen	O
Yards	O
of	O
Flowered	O
Tabby	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
:	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
seen	O
to	O
come	O
into	O
Pater-Noster-Row	B-place
,	O
and	O
being	O
suspected	O
to	O
be	O
Shop-lifters	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
dogged	O
till	O
they	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
where	O
at	O
first	O
they	O
pretended	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Silk	O
for	O
Hoods	O
and	O
Scarfs	O
;	O
but	O
disliking	O
that	O
,	O
they	O
cheapened	O
some	O
Silk	O
for	O
Breeches	O
;	O
and	O
whilst	O
Mr.	O
Cooper	O
's	O
Servant	O
was	O
busy	O
in	O
turning	O
over	O
the	O
Silks	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
one	O
of	O
their	O
Coats	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
their	O
ways	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
they	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
third	O
Person	O
,	O
who	O
escaped	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
themselves	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchers	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Morley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Cloath	O
Coat	O
,	O
three	O
Callico	O
Frocks	O
,	O
a	O
Velvet	O
Cap	O
,	O
seven	O
Callico	O
Aprons	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
that	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
in	O
Goose-Alley	B-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Seacole-Lane	I-place
,	O
but	O
pursuing	O
the	O
Robbers	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Ditch-side	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Picklock	O
Keys	O
amongst	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
given	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
one	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
formerly	O
been	O
burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Person	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
,	O
Fit	O
for	O
the	O
Devil	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Susan	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
she	O
put	O
the	O
Goods	O
into	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Lap	O
,	O
to	O
save	O
her	O
own	O
Bacon	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Gang	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
receive	O
them	O
when	O
the	O
rest	O
fled	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
therefore	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
her	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susanna	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Hester	B-pers
Harwood	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hilton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Conde	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
two	O
Silk	O
Gowns	O
,	O
a	O
Callico	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Silver	O
Fringe	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Ruffles	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
that	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
in	O
New-street	B-place
,	O
and	O
his	O
Goods	O
gone	O
,	O
but	O
knew	O
not	O
who	O
had	O
them	O
.	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
declared	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Lewis	O
and	O
Hilton	O
were	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
called	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
another	O
place	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
:	O
she	O
was	O
minded	O
to	O
have	O
favoured	O
her	O
Brother	O
and	O
Harwood	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
could	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
seen	O
by	O
a	O
Servant	O
Maid	O
that	O
was	O
going	O
for	O
Coles	O
into	O
the	O
Celler	O
,	O
leaning	O
upon	O
a	O
Post	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
staying	O
longer	O
than	O
ordinary	O
,	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
,	O
Plague	O
Dam	O
the	O
Bitch	O
,	O
what	O
makes	O
her	O
stay	O
so	O
long	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
wore	O
Mr.	O
Condes	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
and	O
ript	O
off	O
the	O
Lace	O
and	O
burnt	O
it	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
heard	O
Harwood	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
least	O
it	O
should	O
discover	O
him	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
Harwood	O
carried	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
her	O
Lodgings	O
;	O
and	O
presently	O
after	O
Jones	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
they	O
removed	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
for	O
4l	O
.	O
Jones	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
his	O
Sister	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
and	O
Harwood	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
;	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Burglary	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
not	O
strong	O
enough	O
to	O
Convict	O
them	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
and	O
Lewis	O
and	O
Hilton	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Hilton	O
,	O
and	O
Susan	O
Lewis	O
,	O
were	O
a	O
Second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Clements	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Cloath	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Wast-coat	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
called	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
another	O
place	O
when	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
Five	O
Yards	O
of	O
Frize	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
French	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
Roger	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Dockwray	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Coot	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Edward	O
,	O
Lord	O
Warwick	O
and	O
Holland	O
and	O
Charles	O
Lord	O
Mohun	O
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
Edward	O
,	O
Lord	O
Warwick	O
and	O
Holland	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
did	O
give	O
unto	O
the	O
Deceased	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Breast	O
,	O
near	O
to	O
the	O
Coller-bone	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
five	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
they	O
all	O
took	O
Chairs	O
from	O
the	O
Greyhound-Tavern	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Leicester-fields	B-place
,	O
where	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
unfortunately	O
done	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
appearing	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Man-slaughter	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
Second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquest	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
likewise	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Man-slaughter	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
B	B-pers
-	I-pers
C	I-pers
-	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Molton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hurdiss	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Bay	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
18l	O
.	O
a	O
Drabberdeberry	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
30s	O
.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Spatterdashers	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
High-gate	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
set	O
upon	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
Islington	B-place
,	O
by	O
some	O
Persons	O
who	O
Robbed	O
him	O
of	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
By-lane	O
,	O
and	O
consulted	O
what	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
held	O
Pistol	O
to	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
threatned	O
to	O
kill	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
threatned	O
to	O
bind	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
them	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Sickly-man	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
B	O
-	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
his	O
Arraignment	O
.	O
Price	O
was	O
taken	O
near	O
Pancrass-Church	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Spatterdashers	O
on	O
,	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
not	O
so	O
full	O
against	O
Molton	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Price	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
Second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Bay	O
Mare	O
,	O
value	O
40s	O
.	O
a	O
Sadle	O
Pannel	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Hempen	O
Bags	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
.	O
Ford	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
met	O
him	O
at	O
Islington	B-place
,	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
off	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
B	O
-	O
confest	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
Price	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
nothing	O
being	O
against	O
Molton	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Field	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
seven	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
two	O
Diaper	O
Table	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
Hempen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
a	O
Flaxen	O
Pillow-beer	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
of	O
Oliver	B-pers
Luke	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
his	O
Door	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
by	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
upon	O
his	O
Back	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
him	O
suspect	O
him	O
;	O
Examining	O
him	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
several	O
Stories	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
who	O
committed	O
him	O
:	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Letter	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
Hand-writing	O
proved	O
;	O
wherein	O
he	O
did	O
confess	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
Banished	O
to	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
World	O
.	O
He	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
formerly	O
been	O
Guilty	O
of	O
other	O
small	O
Felonies	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Arthur	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepny	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hair	O
Camlet	O
Gown	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
Pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Symonds	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Magnes	I-place
Martyr	I-place
by	I-place
the	I-place
Bridge	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
Twenty	O
four	O
Yards	O
of	O
Linnen	O
Cloath	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hardlam	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Webster	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Merry	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Webster	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
nineteen	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
six	O
Diaper	O
Napkins	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lodge	I-pers
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
C	B-pers
-	I-pers
J	I-pers
-	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Alhallows	B-place
Barking	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
7s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
the	O
Monies	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Workman	O
at	O
the	O
Mint	O
in	O
the	O
Tower	B-place
;	O
and	O
being	O
at	O
work	O
that	O
Morning	O
upon	O
half	O
Crowns	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
his	O
opportunity	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
into	O
a	O
Tray	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
seen	O
they	O
called	O
him	O
back	O
;	O
he	O
suspecting	O
that	O
they	O
would	O
search	O
him	O
,	O
stoopt	O
and	O
laid	O
them	O
down	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
but	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
as	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
Stealing	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Conyers	I-pers
several	O
Goods	O
;	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
(	O
Conyers	O
)	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
and	O
Oath	O
being	O
made	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
Tryal	O
,	O
and	O
Proof	O
made	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
lay	O
Pawned	O
by	O
Conyers	O
Consent	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
demanded	O
Fourscore	O
Pounds	O
of	O
Stone	O
;	O
who	O
being	O
a	O
substantial	O
Man	O
;	O
and	O
his	O
Reputation	O
and	O
Honesty	O
being	O
Spoak	O
to	O
from	O
the	O
Bench	O
;	O
Proclamation	O
was	O
then	O
made	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
for	O
Conyers	O
to	O
Appear	O
and	O
Prosecute	O
the	O
said	O
Indictment	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
Body	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
looking	O
upon	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
to	O
be	O
Malicious	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Indictment	O
to	O
be	O
brought	O
only	O
to	O
extort	O
Money	O
from	O
Stone	O
,	O
ordered	O
the	O
Jury	O
to	O
Acquit	O
Stone	O
;	O
and	O
ordered	O
that	O
Conyers	O
Recognizance	O
to	O
Prosecute	O
,	O
should	O
be	O
forthwith	O
Estreated	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Trinity	I-place
Minories	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Pettycoat	O
,	O
a	O
blew	O
Cloth	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
lost	O
her	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
her	O
own	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Buckles	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Rutter	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Wattson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Paul	B-pers
Theoband	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
Gloves	O
,	O
and	O
Fifteen	O
Pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Worsted	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Theoband	O
had	O
his	O
House	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Goods	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Theoband	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
Bargain	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
25s	O
.	O
to	O
help	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
Goods	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
Robinson	O
fetch	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
Watson	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
that	O
Robinson	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
therefore	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Day	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Goodlad	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
four	O
Pistols	O
,	O
a	O
Cloath	O
Livery	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Copper	O
Chafingdish	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	O
Goodlad	O
,	O
two	O
Pewter-Dishes	O
,	O
a	O
Westphalia-Ham	O
,	O
a	O
great	O
quantity	O
of	O
Linnen	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
of	O
Sir	O
Willoughbey	B-pers
Hickman	I-pers
,	O
Baronet	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
broke	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
seller	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
Upon	O
search	O
some	O
Dishes	O
and	O
Plates	O
were	O
found	O
under	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Bed	O
.	O
He	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Burglary	O
was	O
not	O
so	O
plainly	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Badge	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Whiteman	I-pers
,	O
the	O
first	O
three	O
as	O
Principal	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
as	O
Accessary	O
,	O
both	O
before	O
and	O
after	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
Badge	O
and	O
Fisher	O
upon	O
their	O
Arraignments	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
Indicted	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
22th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
1680	O
yards	O
of	O
Stuff	O
,	O
value	O
123l	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sebastion	B-pers
Gonorea	I-pers
,	O
and	O
143	O
Hats	O
,	O
value	O
125l	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
26	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Currin	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
not	O
sufficient	O
to	O
Convict	O
Stone	O
and	O
Whiteman	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Badge	O
:	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Fisher	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Payden	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Thomas	I-pers
Lock	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Liberty	I-place
of	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
as	O
Principal	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
as	O
accessary	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Polygamy	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
1693	O
,	O
did	O
take	O
to	O
Wife	O
one	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Osborne	I-pers
,	O
and	O
to	O
her	O
was	O
Married	O
at	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	O
James	O
Dukes-place	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
afterwards	O
at	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	I-place
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
1698	O
,	O
did	O
take	O
to	O
Wife	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Adey	I-pers
,	O
his	O
first	O
Wife	O
being	O
then	O
alive	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Evidence	O
was	O
the	O
Minister	O
of	O
St.	O
James	O
Dukes-place	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
1693	O
he	O
Married	O
two	O
Persons	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Lock	O
,	O
a	O
Widower	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	O
Osborne	O
,	O
a	O
Spinster	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
he	O
remembered	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
desired	O
by	O
an	O
Honourable	O
Lady	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
present	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
said	O
Payden	O
alias	O
Lock	O
;	O
accordingly	O
he	O
went	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
saw	O
his	O
first	O
Wife	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
sooner	O
had	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
spied	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
fell	O
upon	O
his	O
Knees	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
pardon	O
for	O
his	O
fault	O
,	O
and	O
acknowledged	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Married	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
owned	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Married	O
to	O
the	O
Lady	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Elizabeth	O
Adey	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
begged	O
her	O
Pardon	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
be	O
sorry	O
for	O
his	O
Offence	O
;	O
the	O
Clerk	O
of	O
Dukes-place	O
deposed	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Father	O
that	O
gave	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
well	O
remembered	O
them	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
they	O
invited	O
him	O
to	O
their	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Lock	O
,	O
and	O
lived	O
with	O
her	O
Sister	O
as	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
Child	O
by	O
her	O
.	O
An	O
Attorney	O
gave	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
in	O
April	O
,	O
1693	O
,	O
he	O
drew	O
Writings	O
concerning	O
the	O
Marriage	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Elizabeth	O
Osborne	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
Sign	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Thomas	O
Lock	O
,	O
which	O
Writing	O
he	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
see	O
Elizabeth	O
Osborne	O
on	O
Monday	O
last	O
was	O
seven	O
Nights	O
.	O
The	O
Curate	O
of	O
St.	O
Anns	O
Westminster	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
September	O
1698	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
License	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
Marry	O
two	O
Persons	O
,	O
John	O
Payden	O
,	O
Widower	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Elizabeth	O
Adey	O
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
which	O
accordingly	O
he	O
did	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
well	O
remember	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
Man	O
,	O
his	O
Clerk	O
likewise	O
deposed	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
by	O
the	O
means	O
and	O
subtilty	O
of	O
Ward	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
Married	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
Care	O
and	O
Prudence	O
of	O
her	O
Friends	O
detected	O
the	O
Villany	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
Courted	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Sevando	B-pers
Ponteau	I-pers
,	O
and	O
had	O
divers	O
Letters	O
from	O
him	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
She	O
declared	O
also	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
Courted	O
another	O
Lady	O
of	O
a	O
great	O
Fortune	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Stiles	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
she	O
also	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
hath	O
been	O
called	O
in	O
this	O
City	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
the	O
Never-born	O
or	O
(	O
Unborn	O
)	O
Doctor	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Seventh	O
Son	O
of	O
a	O
Seventh	O
Son	O
.	O
Ward	O
pretended	O
himself	O
to	O
be	O
Paydon	O
's	O
,	O
alias	O
Lock	O
's	O
Steward	O
,	O
(	O
or	O
Rent-gatherer	O
)	O
and	O
vouched	O
that	O
his	O
Master	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
Estate	O
near	O
Norwich	O
,	O
and	O
procured	O
a	O
false	O
Settlement	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Elizabeth	O
Adey	O
,	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
a	O
great	O
Family	O
,	O
and	O
Honourably	O
descended	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
former	O
Match	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
Paydon	O
,	O
alias	O
Lock	O
,	O
made	O
a	O
frivolous	O
Defence	O
;	O
saying	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Flanders	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
Marriage	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
called	O
a	O
Condemned	O
Person	O
to	O
justify	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
having	O
considered	O
the	O
Matter	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
assaulting	O
on	O
Mary	B-pers
Bowden	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
a	O
Virgin	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
Age	O
of	O
Ten	O
Years	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
Ravish	O
,	O
and	O
Carnally	O
know	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Child	O
's	O
Mother	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
found	O
some	O
Signs	O
upon	O
the	O
Childs	O
Body	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
to	O
ask	O
her	O
Advice	O
;	O
who	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
was	O
afraid	O
some	O
Man	O
had	O
meddled	O
with	O
her	O
:	O
Asking	O
her	O
Daughter	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
would	O
have	O
lain	O
with	O
her	O
twice	O
;	O
the	O
Child	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
threw	O
her	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
enter	O
her	O
Body	O
;	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Counter	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
half	O
Guinea	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
done	O
it	O
another	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
her	O
Father	O
knocking	O
he	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
offered	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
to	O
the	O
Child	O
in	O
all	O
his	O
Life	O
;	O
but	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
tickled	O
and	O
toyed	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jonas	B-pers
Sevatt	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Horse-lock	O
,	O
value	O
4d	O
.	O
two	O
Iron	O
Keys	O
,	O
a	O
staking	O
Rope	O
,	O
and	O
ten	O
Geese	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Hamond	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
suspicion	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
searching	O
him	O
found	O
a	O
Hen	O
in	O
his	O
Coat-pocket	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
in	O
his	O
Breeches	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Hamond	O
own	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
such	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
but	O
a	O
slight	O
Defence	O
for	O
himself	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Chelsea	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
Stealing	O
from	O
Stephen	B-pers
Twyford	I-pers
,	O
one	O
Ewe-Sheep	O
,	O
Value	O
25s	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
hung	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
heels	O
in	O
a	O
Wood	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Pelham	B-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Philip	I-pers
Corbett	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Murrey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Cradock	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Chiswick	B-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Silver	O
Hilted	O
Sword	O
,	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
a	O
Ring	O
with	O
three	O
Diamonds	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Amethyst	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
And	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
John	B-pers
West	I-pers
likewise	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
;	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Bay	O
Mare	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
;	O
to	O
the	O
first	O
the	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
from	O
London	O
to	O
Sibon-Hall	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
set	O
upon	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Corbett	O
stood	O
over	O
him	O
whilst	O
he	O
was	O
Bound	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
for	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
,	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
declared	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Mr.	O
West	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Robbed	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
the	O
men	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
Acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Pendleton	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shag	O
Breeches	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Wale	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
Convict	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Strowd	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
,	O
for	O
taking	O
a	O
Copper	O
from	O
the	O
Freehold	O
of	O
Nicolas	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Trespass	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Hendon	B-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
the	O
Fourth	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
did	O
steal	O
Forty	O
Pound	O
of	O
weight	O
of	O
Lead	O
and	O
eight	O
Pidgeons	O
,	O
from	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Rawlinson	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
and	O
Four	O
Geese	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
at	O
Hamstead	O
upon	O
Andrews	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Johnson	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
in	O
his	O
Company	O
,	O
who	O
denied	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Andrews	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Oxon	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Oxley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Frances	B-pers
Dawes	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
four	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
five	O
Flaxen	O
Napkins	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
his	O
Gang	O
broke	O
through	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
discovered	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
Girl	O
cried	O
out	O
Thieves	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
rest	O
escaped	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Kind	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bartholomew	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Spott	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Fry	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
upon	O
four	O
Indictments	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
a	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Coach-house	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
,	I-pers
Earl	I-pers
of	I-pers
Dorset	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
two	O
Velvet	O
Coach	O
Seats	O
.	O
The	O
Second	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
taking	O
four	O
Brass	O
Toppings	O
,	O
eight	O
Pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Brass	O
Bullion	O
,	O
a	O
Coach	O
value	O
8l	O
.	O
and	O
two	O
Horses	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Matthew	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
.	O
The	O
third	O
,	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
taking	O
a	O
Coach	O
and	O
Horses	O
,	O
Coach-seats	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Fourth	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Cloath	O
Coats	O
,	O
three	O
Hempen	O
Sacks	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Stable	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Moss	I-pers
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
first	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
the	O
2d	O
Indictment	O
,	O
Morgan	O
said	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
carry	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
to	O
the	O
Coblers	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
while	O
they	O
drove	O
away	O
his	O
Coach	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
afterwards	O
found	O
left	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
out	O
the	O
Lining	O
of	O
his	O
Coach	O
:	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
third	O
Bates	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
set	O
down	O
his	O
Fare	O
in	O
Covent-Garden	B-place
,	O
and	O
whilst	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
receive	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
his	O
Coach	O
and	O
Horses	O
,	O
and	O
drove	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
out	O
the	O
Linings	O
of	O
his	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
four	O
new	O
Traces	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Fourth	O
,	O
Moss	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Gang	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
declared	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
present	O
in	O
all	O
the	O
Facts	O
Committed	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Fuller	O
was	O
not	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susan	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Mawson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Inman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
worsted	O
Camlet	O
Cloak	O
,	O
a	O
Drugget	O
Coat	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
was	O
not	O
sufficient	O
to	O
Convict	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
P	B-pers
-	I-pers
E	I-pers
-	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
from	O
Edward	B-pers
Shanks	I-pers
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Covey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Stephen	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
White	B-place
Chapel	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
upon	O
four	O
Indictments	O
,	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Ravenscross	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
two	O
Iron	O
Casements	O
:	O
the	O
second	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Swaine	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
Eighty	O
one	O
Pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Iron	O
:	O
the	O
third	O
for	O
taking	O
three	O
Iron	O
Casements	O
,	O
from	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Disermew	I-pers
:	O
the	O
Fourth	O
for	O
taking	O
two	O
Iron	O
Casements	O
from	O
Samuel	B-pers
Guinock	I-pers
;	O
it	O
being	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
Trespass	O
,	O
for	O
taking	O
the	O
Casements	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
Burglary	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
of	O
those	O
three	O
Indictments	O
;	O
as	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Swaines	O
Iron	O
,	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
Burglary	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sack	O
of	O
Wheat	O
Flower	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Nineteenth	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barlow	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Weather	O
Sheep	O
,	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Willingham	I-pers
on	O
the	O
third	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
not	O
Evidence	O
to	O
Convict	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Reading	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Flood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
's	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Flaxen	O
Smock	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Perkins	I-pers
;	O
and	O
the	O
second	O
for	O
taking	O
a	O
Copper	O
Pot	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Flaxen	O
Sheet	O
,	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Buck	I-pers
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
not	O
strong	O
enough	O
to	O
convict	O
her	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
first	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
;	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
Buck	O
's	O
Goods	O
she	O
confest	O
it	O
;	O
thereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Pattison	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
kettle	O
,	O
and	O
Five	O
Pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Yarn	O
,	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dodge	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
seventh	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Tod	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Peter	B-pers
Tayler	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Hornsey	B-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Ewe	O
Sheep	O
from	O
James	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Skins	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
Tayler	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
thereupon	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Tod	O
was	O
not	O
so	O
positive	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
thereupon	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Daniel	B-pers
Staines	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Edmonton	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Buck-skin	O
from	O
Henry	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
not	O
sufficient	O
to	O
Convict	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Stanley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bone	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
John	B-pers
Parrot	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Cloath	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
2s	O
.	O
in	O
Monies	O
numbred	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Amersham	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
with	O
Pork	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
set	O
upon	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
,	O
by	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
's	O
Banquetting	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
Tyburn-Road	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
Evidence	O
who	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
Second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Muggett	I-pers
,	O
at	O
Fulham	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Silk	O
Petty-coat	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
lifted	O
the	O
Door	O
off	O
the	O
Hinges	O
with	O
a	O
Pitch-fork	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Muggett	O
's	O
eldest	O
Daughter	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
her	O
there	O
whilst	O
they	O
rifled	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Rumsey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
four	O
Pistols	O
,	O
a	O
Cloath	O
Livery	O
Coat	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sir	O
Willoughby	B-pers
Hickman	I-pers
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Goodlad	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
they	O
stole	O
them	O
:	O
They	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
ed	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Machlin	O
Laced	O
Cravat	O
,	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Brandon	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Twelfth	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
he	O
stole	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Barber	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Oxley	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Molder	I-pers
,	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Parterick	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
One	O
hundred	O
thirty	O
six	O
Yards	O
of	O
Printed	O
Stuff	O
,	O
for	O
Callico	O
Quilts	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
afterwards	O
sold	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
for	O
50s	O
.	O
and	O
8d	O
.	O
and	O
shared	O
the	O
Money	O
amongst	O
them	O
.	O
It	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
Burglary	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Barber	O
,	O
Molder	O
:	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Laws	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonards	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
three	O
Yards	O
of	O
Silver	O
Fringe	O
,	O
value	O
40s	O
.	O
a	O
Cloath	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
goods	O
,	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sold	O
the	O
Fringe	O
for	O
4s	O
.	O
and	O
he	O
could	O
give	O
no	O
account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Blackmore	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Alice	B-pers
Price	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Twenty	O
eighth	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
three	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
three	O
Smocks	O
,	O
four	O
Hoods	O
,	O
two	O
Pewter	O
Pots	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
Felony	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Homes	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
three	O
Holland	O
Aprons	O
,	O
two	O
blew	O
Holland	O
Smocks	O
,	O
four	O
Smocks	O
,	O
three	O
Shirts	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Brass	O
Watch	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
lift	O
up	O
the	O
Latch	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
in	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
opened	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
given	O
her	O
by	O
another	O
Woman	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cookson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
Kidnapping	O
one	O
Edward	B-pers
Buttler	I-pers
a	O
Boy	O
,	O
and	O
carrying	O
him	O
on	O
Board	O
the	O
Ship	O
,	O
called	O
,	O
The	O
Benjamin	O
and	O
Mary	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intention	O
to	O
convey	O
him	O
beyond	O
the	O
Seas	O
to	O
Maryland	O
:	O
The	O
Boy	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
another	O
Person	O
met	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
Cooks	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
Victuals	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
him	O
drunk	O
with	O
Brandy	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
must	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
telling	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
must	O
say	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Friends	O
;	O
accordingly	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
an	O
Office	O
on	O
Pig-hill	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
bound	O
,	O
his	O
Mother	O
hearing	O
where	O
her	O
Son	O
was	O
,	O
got	O
my	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justices	O
Warrant	O
to	O
fetch	O
her	O
Son	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
but	O
little	O
for	O
Himself	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
the	O
Boy	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Friends	O
;	O
he	O
accordingly	O
bound	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
matter	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Bunch	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
20s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Oldfield	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
from	O
Frances	B-pers
Arlott	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
.	O
Arlott	O
's	O
Petty-coat	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Back	O
,	O
who	O
having	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Langton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Feather-bed	O
,	O
Bolster	O
,	O
two	O
Blankets	O
and	O
a	O
Quilt	O
from	O
Ralph	B-pers
Ladyman	I-pers
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
for	O
28	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
he	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
an	O
Alamode	O
Hood	O
;	O
a	O
Scarf	O
,	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Edgerton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
two	O
Pearls	O
,	O
a	O
9	O
s.	O
piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Edgerton	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Hood	O
upon	O
her	O
head	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
own	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
thereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Banister	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Tottenham	B-place
High	I-place
Cross	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Spade	O
and	O
a	O
Hedge-Bill	O
,	O
from	O
Ralph	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
not	O
such	O
that	O
as	O
to	O
convict	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgments	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
B	O
--	O
C	O
--	O
,	O
Pellam	O
,	O
alias	O
Phillip	O
Corbet	O
,	O
Margaret	O
Evans	O
,	O
William	O
Fry	O
,	O
Herbert	O
Herring	O
,	O
John	O
Kind	O
,	O
Joseph	O
Oxon	O
,	O
alias	O
Oxley	O
,	O
William	O
Price	O
,	O
Rebecca	O
Petty	O
,	O
alias	O
Adams	O
,	O
alias	O
Jones	O
,	O
James	O
Stanley	O
,	O
William	O
Pheasant	O
,	O
Mary	O
Harris	O
,	O
and	O
William	O
Bartholomew	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Cavelley	O
,	O
died	O
in	O
Prison	O
,	O
before	O
Judgment	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
John	O
Armstrong	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Bedford	O
,	O
William	O
Bates	O
,	O
William	O
Blackmore	O
,	O
Richard	O
Bennet	O
,	O
John	O
Clarke	O
,	O
Arthur	O
Chambers	O
,	O
C	O
--	O
J	O
--	O
,	O
John	O
Covey	O
,	O
Stephen	O
Cox	O
,	O
William	O
Day	O
,	O
Anne	O
Frogg	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Floyd	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Field	O
,	O
Joseph	O
Fisher	O
,	O
Jane	O
Holloway	O
,	O
Alice	O
Hudson	O
,	O
Hester	O
Harwood	O
,	O
Anne	O
Harris	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Jones	O
,	O
Richard	O
Jones	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Laws	O
,	O
William	O
Langton	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Moor	O
,	O
Mary	O
Philips	O
,	O
John	O
Paydon	O
,	O
alias	O
Thomas	O
Lock	O
,	O
Mary	O
Pool	O
,	O
W	O
--	O
E	O
--	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Rachey	O
,	O
Mary	O
Stafford	O
,	O
Margaret	O
Taylor	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Willis	O
.	O
Richard	O
French	O
,	O
Geroge	O
Dockwray	O
,	O
and	O
Roger	O
James	O
,	O
Samuel	O
Barber	O
,	O
and	O
William	O
Molder	O
,	O
were	O
respited	O
till	O
Further	O
Order	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
,	O
one	O
Thomas	O
Badge	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipp	O
'd	O
,	O
Jane	O
Matthews	O
,	O
Mary	O
Bunch	O
,	O
Anne	O
Coleman	O
,	O
Joseph	O
Day	O
,	O
Mary	O
Franklin	O
,	O
Grace	O
Price	O
,	O
William	O
Paterson	O
,	O
John	O
Robinson	O
,	O
Alice	O
Reading	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Simonds	O
,	O
Jonas	O
Sevatt	O
,	O
Peter	O
Tayler	O
,	O
and	O
Thomas	O
Williams	O
.	O
James	O
Brockett	O
and	O
Henry	O
Coster	O
,	O
were	O
fined	O
13	O
s.	O
and	O
4d	O
.	O
each	O
and	O
ordered	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
,	O
at	O
Charing	O
Cross	O
,	O
Admiralty	O
Office	O
and	O
at	O
Westminster-Hall	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Kookson	O
fined	O
100	O
l.	O
and	O
find	O
Suretyes	O
,	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
behaviour	O
for	O
seven	O
Years	O
.	O
John	O
West	O
fined	O
20.	O
marks	O
and	O
find	O
Suretyes	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
behaviour	O
for	O
seven	O
Years	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Stroud	O
fined	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
d.	O
and	O
find	O
Suretyes	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
The	O
Women	O
pleaded	O
their	O
Bellies	O
,	O
had	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
was	O
Impanell	O
'd	O
,	O
who	O
found	O
that	O
Rebecca	O
Petty	O
,	O
alias	O
Adams	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	O
Harris	O
to	O
be	O
not	O
with	O
quick	O
child	O
,	O
and	O
Margaret	O
Evans	O
to	O
be	O
with	O
quick	O
child	O
.	O
By	O
reason	O
of	O
so	O
many	O
Criminals	O
this	O
Sessions	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
room	O
(	O
in	O
this	O
Paper	O
)	O
to	O
put	O
in	O
the	O
Tryals	O
of	O
William	O
Pheasant	O
for	O
a	O
Rape	O
,	O
Mary	O
Poole	O
,	O
a	O
Gypsie	O
,	O
Rebecca	O
Jones	O
,	O
a	O
Notorious	O
Offender	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
An	O
Account	O
of	O
them	O
will	O
be	O
published	O
together	O
with	O
speed	O
.	O
Printed	O
by	O
F.	O
Collins	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
You	O
that	O
do	O
want	O
a	O
Cure	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Physician	O
need	O
,	O
If	O
that	O
you	O
come	O
betimes	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
be	O
cur	O
'd	O
with	O
speed	O
.	O
He	O
liveth	O
at	O
the	O
Blew	O
Ball	O
in	O
Whale-bone	O
Court	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Lower-end	O
of	O
Bartholomew	O
Lane	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
.	O
WHO	O
infallibly	O
cures	O
the	O
French	O
Disease	O
and	O
Claps	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
its	O
numerous	O
attendants	O
,	O
which	O
oftentimes	O
are	O
the	O
products	O
of	O
other	O
grievous	O
and	O
lasting	O
Diseases	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
utter	O
ruine	O
of	O
many	O
,	O
besides	O
frequently	O
untimely	O
death	O
,	O
procured	O
by	O
them	O
through	O
grand	O
Abuses	O
,	O
committed	O
by	O
the	O
irregular	O
and	O
base	O
Methods	O
and	O
Medicines	O
of	O
foolish	O
and	O
unskilful	O
Pretenders	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
therefore	O
to	O
Advertise	O
all	O
Persons	O
who	O
are	O
afflicted	O
with	O
the	O
Disease	O
abovesaid	O
to	O
repair	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
performeth	O
the	O
true	O
and	O
perfect	O
Cure	O
thereof	O
,	O
without	O
hindrance	O
of	O
business	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
all	O
desirable	O
and	O
imagineable	O
speed	O
and	O
secresie	O
.	O
His	O
Pills	O
only	O
prepared	O
for	O
the	O
French	O
Disease	O
by	O
the	O
Burning	O
of	O
the	O
Reins	O
,	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
in	O
Boxes	O
of	O
several	O
Prizes	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
Venereal	O
Arcannes	O
,	O
as	O
occasion	O
requires	O
.	O
Price	O
,	O
from	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
to	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
from	O
3	O
s.	O
to	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Box	O
with	O
Directions	O
.	O
These	O
Pills	O
are	O
free	O
from	O
Mercury	O
,	O
and	O
proper	O
in	O
all	O
Diseases	O
,	O
where	O
Purging	O
is	O
requisite	O
.	O
His	O
Diet	O
drink	O
cleanses	O
the	O
Reins	O
,	O
provokes	O
Urine	O
,	O
and	O
abates	O
the	O
sharp	O
pains	O
or	O
stoppage	O
of	O
Urine	O
in	O
the	O
Running	O
of	O
the	O
Reins	O
,	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Bottle	O
.	O
He	O
hath	O
likewiase	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Gargarison	O
of	O
Mouth-water	O
which	O
will	O
make	O
black	O
or	O
yellow	O
Teeth	O
to	O
white	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
few	O
times	O
using	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
will	O
certainly	O
cure	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
Diseases	O
incident	O
to	O
the	O
Mouth	O
,	O
Teeth	O
and	O
Gums	O
.	O
The	O
Glasses	O
are	O
of	O
several	O
Prices	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
.	O
Elixir	O
Stomachicum	O
:	O
Or	O
The	O
great	O
Cordial-Elixir	O
for	O
the	O
Stomach	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
delicate	O
Flavour	O
,	O
and	O
pleasant	O
(	O
tho	O
Bistrish	O
)	O
taste	O
,	O
not	O
Purging	O
but	O
Cordial	O
only	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
drank	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
(	O
but	O
especially	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
)	O
in	O
any	O
Liquor	O
,	O
as	O
Wine	O
,	O
Ale	O
,	O
Tea	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Fair	O
Water	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Which	O
for	O
all	O
Ailments	O
of	O
the	O
Stomach	O
,	O
as	O
want	O
of	O
Appetite	O
,	O
Indigestion	O
,	O
Wind	O
or	O
Weakness	O
,	O
Loathing	O
,	O
the	O
&	O
c.	O
more	O
especially	O
after	O
hard	O
Drinking	O
,	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
,	O
Fits	O
of	O
the	O
Mother	O
,	O
or	O
Vapour	O
in	O
Women	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
other	O
Distempers	O
incident	O
to	O
the	O
Brain	O
and	O
Stomach	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
Directions	O
given	O
with	O
each	O
Bottle	O
will	O
describe	O
more	O
at	O
large	O
;	O
It	O
is	O
certainly	O
as	O
good	O
a	O
Medicine	O
as	O
is	O
yet	O
known	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
such	O
use	O
and	O
excellency	O
,	O
for	O
all	O
Seamen	O
and	O
Travelours	O
,	O
as	O
when	O
once	O
Experienced	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
will	O
not	O
go	O
without	O
it	O
.	O
Price	O
One	O
Shilling	O
the	O
Bottle	O
.	O
Each	O
Bottle	O
Sealed	O
,	O
and	O
Directions	O
Stampt	O
with	O
my	O
Seal	O
viz	O
.	O
A	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
Surmounted	O
by	O
a	O
Fess	O
between	O
four	O
Leopards	O
Heads	O
,	O
without	O
which	O
they	O
are	O
not	O
mine	O
.	O
If	O
any	O
Captain	O
,	O
Seamen	O
,	O
Shopkeeper	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
keeping	O
Publick	O
Houses	O
,	O
want	O
any	O
quantity	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
,	O
or	O
sell	O
again	O
,	O
they	O
be	O
Furnished	O
(	O
with	O
Allowance	O
)	O
by	O
Letter	O
or	O
otherwise	O
,	O
by	O
Henry	O
Galway	O
at	O
the	O
Fruit	O
Shop	O
,	O
the	O
South	O
Entrance	O
of	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
in	O
Cornhil	O
,	O
London	O
,	O
where	O
you	O
may	O
be	O
truly	O
satisfied	O
of	O
its	O
Faithful	O
and	O
true	O
preparation	O
,	O
And	O
you	O
may	O
have	O
all	O
things	O
of	O
this	O
kind	O
truly	O
and	O
Warrantedly	O
prepared	O
.	O
Whereas	O
of	O
late	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
Persons	O
,	O
particularly	O
the	O
last	O
Execution	O
,	O
have	O
published	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Confessions	O
of	O
the	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
criminals	O
.	O
The	O
Reverend	O
Mr.	O
Allen	O
,	O
now	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
to	O
acquaint	O
the	O
World	O
,	O
to	O
prevent	O
their	O
being	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
future	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
are	O
entirely	O
false	O
,	O
not	O
that	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
the	O
Condemned	O
Prisoners	O
Behaviour	O
,	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
can	O
be	O
given	O
till	O
next	O
the	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
let	O
,	O
next	O
Door	O
in	O
the	O
Kings-Arms	O
Tavern	O
near	O
Fleet-bridge	O
.	O
