TOKEN	NE
The	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
28th	O
,	O
29th	O
,	O
30th	O
and	O
31st	O
Days	O
of	O
August	O
1700	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
Twelfth	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
28	O
,	O
29	O
,	O
30	O
,	O
and	O
31st	O
Days	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
1700	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
right	O
Honourable	O
,	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	B-pers
LEVET	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
SALATHIEL	B-pers
LOVELL	I-pers
,	O
Recorder	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
are	O
as	O
follow	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Ash	I-pers
,	O
Augustine	B-pers
Brian	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Blagrave	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Vanherhassel	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Hewen	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Billers	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Round	I-pers
,	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Stevenson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Grosvenor	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Spinlowe	I-pers
,	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Munden	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Wyan	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Cliffton	I-pers
John	B-pers
Attfeild	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
Marmaduke	B-pers
Bramley	I-pers
.	O
Phillip	B-pers
Burgis	I-pers
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Dix	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
these	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Magnus	I-place
the	I-place
Martyr	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
50	O
Yards	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stuff	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Heath	O
's	O
Wife	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
opportunity	O
and	O
convey	O
'd	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
Stuff	O
under	O
her	O
Petticoat	O
:	O
A	O
little	O
after	O
she	O
pretended	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
stopt	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
pulled	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
Cloths	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
alledg	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
not	O
sensible	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
nor	O
never	O
did	O
an	O
ill	O
thing	O
,	O
or	O
was	O
ever	O
before	O
a	O
Judge	O
or	O
Justice	O
in	O
all	O
her	O
Life	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
having	O
considered	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bellingham	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Undershaft	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
20	O
China	O
Cups	O
,	O
and	O
9	O
small	O
China	O
Dishes	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Houghton	I-pers
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
that	O
Robinson	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Ware-House	O
and	O
cheapned	O
some	O
China	O
Ware	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
her	O
ways	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
East-India	O
House	O
to	O
a	O
Sale	O
that	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
He	O
being	O
gone	O
,	O
she	O
me	O
again	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
,	O
where	O
after	O
some	O
time	O
ey	O
were	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
bag	O
between	O
Robinsons	O
Legs	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Bellingham	O
was	O
not	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Peter	B-pers
Motteux	I-pers
6	O
Yards	O
of	O
Muslin	O
on	O
the	O
said	O
13th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
on	O
this	O
Indictment	O
,	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
Convict	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Hollingsworth	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolphs	I-place
without	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Spurs	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Skinner	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Saddles	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Phillip	B-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
likewise	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Robbery	O
,	O
for	O
Robbing	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Jeremy	B-pers
Deere	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Day	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
his	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
in	O
fear	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
2	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
8	O
Smocks	O
a	O
Silver	O
Fringe	O
,	O
and	O
Divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutors	O
Wife	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
sitting	O
below	O
Stairs	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
heard	O
a	O
great	O
noise	O
above	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Street	O
and	O
called	O
some	O
People	O
to	O
her	O
assistance	O
,	O
who	O
coming	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
her	O
Lap	O
full	O
of	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Drawers	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
:	O
But	O
it	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepny	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Robbery	O
,	O
for	O
Robbing	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Benedict	B-pers
Marriot	I-pers
,	O
no	O
Person	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Crape	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Serge	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
Silk	O
Petticoats	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
Convict	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Robbery	O
,	O
for	O
Robbing	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
George	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Holland	O
Sheet	O
,	O
2	O
Shirts	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	O
George	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Shirts	O
,	O
1	O
Flannel	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
1	O
Suit	O
of	O
Laced	O
Muslin	O
Head-cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
1	O
Silver	O
Thimble	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Lydia	B-pers
Pairman	I-pers
.	O
The	O
first	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
some	O
Goods	O
bundled	O
up	O
as	O
did	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
:	O
She	O
was	O
resolved	O
to	O
watch	O
the	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
any	O
Person	O
should	O
see	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
discovered	O
by	O
a	O
Neighbours	O
Servant	O
,	O
who	O
askt	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
come	O
to	O
ask	O
for	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
Victuals	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Mother	O
that	O
was	O
Sick	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
some	O
Victuals	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
meddle	O
with	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Bentley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Boots	O
,	O
7	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
a	O
Hammer	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Nippers	O
,	O
a	O
rubbing	O
Stick	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Shoulder	O
Stick	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Gilling	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidenceagainst	O
him	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
Convict	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Thorney	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Country	I-pers
Dick	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
2	O
and	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
8	O
Serge	O
Jackets	O
,	O
a	O
stuff	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
13	O
blew	O
Linnen	O
Shirts	O
,	O
7	O
pair	O
of	O
Calamanca	O
stuff	O
Breeches	O
,	O
11	O
pair	O
of	O
Linnen	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
Convict	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
shrider	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
wrought	O
Holland	O
Quilt	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
from	O
Jeremy	B-pers
Deere	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
stuff	O
Gown	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Eve	B-pers
Harrintine	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Garden	O
,	O
news	O
was	O
brought	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Robbed	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Servant	O
ran	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Porter	O
seeing	O
them	O
run	O
followed	O
them	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Porter	O
overtook	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Grays-Inn-fields	O
,	O
who	O
threw	O
down	O
the	O
things	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
,	O
but	O
however	O
he	O
laid	O
hold	O
and	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
Steal	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
or	O
call	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
Henry	B-pers
Mosse	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Cloath	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Muslin	O
Neckcloath	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buttons	O
.	O
Mosse	O
deposed	O
that	O
his	O
Master	O
sent	O
him	O
on	O
an	O
Errand	O
into	O
Old	O
street	O
,	O
but	O
coming	O
back	O
was	O
set	O
upon	O
in	O
Bunhil-feilds	B-place
,	O
and	O
compelled	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
behind	O
the	O
Mount	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
took	O
off	O
his	O
Coat	O
and	O
Neck-cloath	O
,	O
and	O
bound	O
him	O
Hand	O
and	O
Foot	O
,	O
and	O
believed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Men	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
he	O
robbed	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
Goods	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
one	O
Seabrook	O
in	O
Barbican	O
;	O
all	O
which	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
nor	O
ever	O
did	O
an	O
ill	O
thing	O
in	O
all	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
call	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
having	O
considered	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Tackerberry	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pancras	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
Gabriel	B-pers
Baily	I-pers
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Iron	O
Shoe	O
Buckles	O
,	O
a	O
Muslin	O
Cravat	O
,	O
a	O
strip	O
'd	O
Handerchief	O
,	O
and	O
1	O
s.	O
4	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
numbred	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Mr	O
Bayly	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
North-hall	O
to	O
see	O
his	O
Wife	O
who	O
was	O
Sick	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
set	O
upon	O
between	O
Highgate	O
and	O
London	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
off	O
his	O
Shoes	O
,	O
Neckcloath	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
as	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Perriwig	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
not	O
good	O
enough	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
gave	O
him	O
them	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
afterwards	O
with	O
the	O
Shoes	O
upon	O
his	O
Feet	O
at	O
Saffron	O
hill	O
by	O
Mutton-lane	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Evidence	O
was	O
a	O
Boy	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Bear-Garden	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
Prize	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Shoes	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Feet	O
,	O
he	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Uncles	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
he	O
had	O
cleaned	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
followed	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
a	O
Coblers	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
seeing	O
him	O
stay	O
,	O
presently	O
fetch	O
'd	O
his	O
Uncle	O
who	O
seized	O
him	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
was	O
the	O
Shoe	O
makers	O
Boy	O
who	O
made	O
them	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
they	O
were	O
Mr.	O
Bailys	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
them	O
by	O
reason	O
his	O
Master	O
had	O
wrote	O
Pipe-maker	O
in	O
the	O
inside	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
utterly	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Shoes	O
at	O
the	O
Rag	O
Market	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
call	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Kentish	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Eling	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Dowlas	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ralph	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Shirts	O
were	O
wash	O
'd	O
and	O
hang	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Hedge	O
to	O
dry	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
seen	O
by	O
a	O
Boy	O
who	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
he	O
pursued	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
his	O
Breeches	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Cart-way	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
call	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
having	O
considered	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepny	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Robbery	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Danmask	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
Monair	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
3	O
Smocks	O
,	O
A	O
laced	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
a	O
Serge	O
Manlte	O
,	O
and	O
11	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Owen	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
some	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
who	O
took	O
them	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
;	O
but	O
his	O
Wife	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
her	O
Child	O
into	O
the	O
Feilds	O
to	O
quiet	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
lockt	O
her	O
Door	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
her	O
Lap	O
;	O
but	O
looking	O
found	O
she	O
was	O
Robbed	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
they	O
made	O
pursuit	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
threw	O
down	O
the	O
things	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Lap	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
carried	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
searching	O
her	O
found	O
two	O
pick	O
Lock	O
Keys	O
hid	O
in	O
her	O
Cloths	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
Swan	O
Feilds	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
Brother	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
that	O
way	O
a	O
Woman	O
came	O
out	O
with	O
such	O
things	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
mistrusting	O
her	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
whereas	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
neither	O
could	O
she	O
call	O
any	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Barnet	I-pers
and	O
Ellinor	B-pers
Dic	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Drew	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Day	O
time	O
no	O
Person	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Hood	O
,	O
a	O
Flaxen	O
Sheet	O
,	O
a	O
lac	O
'd	O
Cap	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
Pewter	O
Spoons	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutors	O
Wife	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Alley	O
Gate	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
not	O
gone	O
above	O
half	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
back	O
found	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
bundled	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
for	O
making	O
their	O
Escape	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
they	O
took	O
any	O
thing	O
except	O
a	O
black	O
Hood	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
having	O
considered	O
the	O
Matter	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hurd	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Stephen	I-place
Coleman-street	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Watch	O
with	O
a	O
Shagreen	O
Case	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Spikeman	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
Convict	O
her	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
6	O
Yards	O
of	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
17	O
Yards	O
of	O
Gold	O
Lace	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cage	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
likewise	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
Convict	O
her	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Devereux	B-pers
Feasaut	I-pers
and	O
Walter	B-pers
Terrey	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
Vintry	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Walcup	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
9	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
6	O
Dozen	O
pair	O
of	O
Mens	O
Gloves	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Walcup	O
deposed	O
that	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
gone	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
who	O
took	O
them	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
was	O
one	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
one	O
Seabrook	O
in	O
Barbican	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
divided	O
the	O
Money	O
together	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
Evidence	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
Waiter	O
Terrey	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Crosse	I-pers
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
a	O
Damask	O
Table	O
Cloth	O
2	O
yards	O
of	O
Muslin	O
,	O
108	O
yards	O
of	O
Silk	O
fooling	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Robbed	O
of	O
Oris	O
Lace	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
knew	O
not	O
who	O
took	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
one	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Shop	O
near	O
the	O
half	O
Moon	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Aldersgate-street	B-place
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
sold	O
them	O
and	O
shared	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
so	O
plainly	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Aldermanbury	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Willinton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Savoy	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henerita	B-pers
Pen	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Hood	O
and	O
Scarff	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
suit	O
of	O
Muslin	O
Head	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
theGoods	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
Watten	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Goodman	O
that	O
did	O
lodge	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
took	O
his	O
opportunity	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
afterwards	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Breeches	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
they	O
were	O
given	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
call	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Burt	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Burt	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
White	B-place
Chappel	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
dark	O
brown	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
that	O
his	O
Horse	O
was	O
stole	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Grounds	O
in	O
Buckinghamshire	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
afterwards	O
found	O
at	O
the	O
Red	O
Cow	O
at	O
White	O
Chappel	O
,	O
brought	O
by	O
John	O
Burd	O
,	O
who	O
owned	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
Acquitted	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Bird	O
,	O
alias	O
Burt	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
black	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
Gelding	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stop	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Gelding	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Custody	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
stole	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Grounds	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloath	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Wast-coat	O
,	O
a	O
Holland	O
Neck	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sleeves	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Muslin	O
Cravat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Square	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
Convict	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Maud	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepny	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mead	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
day	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
blew	O
Aprons	O
,	O
2	O
Plates	O
,	O
a	O
Copper	O
Sauce	O
Pan	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutors	O
Wife	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
broke	O
a	O
Shutter	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
a	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
She	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
early	O
to	O
Stocks	O
Market	O
,	O
she	O
met	O
a	O
Man	O
who	O
askt	O
her	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
Bell-Wharf	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
agreed	O
to	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
She	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Constantine	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Stroud	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
2	O
Pistols	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Porteguess	O
pieces	O
of	O
Silver	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
Convict	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Mathew	B-pers
Attkinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Deans	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
after	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
March	O
1700.	O
to	O
witt	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
then	O
and	O
before	O
,	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Office	O
and	O
Function	O
of	O
a	O
Popish	O
Priest	O
,	O
unlawfully	O
and	O
wickedly	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
the	O
manner	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
of	O
Rome	O
,	O
one	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Rich	I-pers
of	O
her	O
Sins	O
did	O
Absolve	O
,	O
and	O
pronounced	O
her	O
Absolved	O
.	O
She	O
first	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
seven	O
Years	O
ago	O
she	O
was	O
preverted	O
from	O
the	O
Protestant	O
to	O
the	O
Roman	O
Catholick	O
Religion	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
her	O
Grandmother	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
Confirmed	O
by	O
the	O
Bishop	O
in	O
great	O
Queens-street	O
,	O
who	O
Confirmed	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
farther	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
his	O
Chamber	O
at	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Northovers	O
,	O
a	O
great	O
Box-maker	O
in	O
great	O
Wild-street	O
,	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
,	O
about	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
come	O
to	O
Confession	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
askt	O
her	O
whether	O
she	O
was	O
ready	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
reply	O
'd	O
yes	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
her	O
into	O
a	O
Closlet	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
kneeled	O
down	O
upon	O
a	O
Cushion	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
her	O
Confession	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
Absolution	O
,	O
and	O
enjoyned	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
Pennance	O
five	O
Ave	O
Mary	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
Pater	O
Nosters	O
to	O
be	O
said	O
in	O
the	O
Jesus	O
Psalter	O
.	O
She	O
farther	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
Mass	O
about	O
two	O
Years	O
also	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
in	O
Latin	O
with	O
a	O
low	O
Voice	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
bound	O
to	O
believe	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
she	O
knew	O
no	O
better	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Evidence	O
was	O
her	O
Mother	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
her	O
Daughter	O
was	O
Christned	O
in	O
the	O
Protestant	O
Religion	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
did	O
continue	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
till	O
she	O
was	O
eleven	O
or	O
twelve	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
before	O
she	O
turned	O
Roman	O
Catholick	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
ignorant	O
of	O
what	O
was	O
laid	O
to	O
his	O
Charge	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
knew	O
her	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
but	O
a	O
Roman	O
Catholick	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
divers	O
People	O
to	O
take	O
off	O
the	O
Reputation	O
of	O
the	O
Kings	O
Witness	O
who	O
were	O
most	O
of	O
them	O
Roman	O
Catholicks	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
sufficient	O
to	O
invalidate	O
her	O
Evidence	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
therefore	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Rively	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Savoy	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
stuff	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Petticoat	O
and	O
a	O
lac	O
'd	O
Tucker	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wetherspoole	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
her	O
,	O
besides	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
call	O
any	O
body	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Deans	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cane	O
with	O
a	O
Horn	O
head	O
with	O
Silver	O
Studs	O
,	O
a	O
Cravat	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
laced	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
Yard	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Closet	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
akt	O
him	O
what	O
business	O
he	O
had	O
there	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Smithson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bradley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Christian	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Germain	I-pers
,	O
Baronet	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
3	O
pair	O
of	O
stuff	O
Curtains	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
about	O
two	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
went	O
his	O
way	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
pursued	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
Garden	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
dropt	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
it	O
was	O
dark	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
kick	O
the	O
things	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
length	O
took	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
call	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Wilsdon	B-place
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Forster	I-pers
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Day	O
time	O
,	O
no	O
Person	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Cloath	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	O
Forster	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Coats	O
,	O
a	O
Frock	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Payne	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Damask	O
stuff	O
Gown	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gage	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
he	O
broke	O
the	O
Wall	O
and	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
into	O
a	O
Wood	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
bundled	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
a	O
distance	O
from	O
them	O
with	O
his	O
Cloaths	O
all	O
Loomy	O
with	O
the	O
Wall	O
.	O
He	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
that	O
way	O
to	O
Harrow	O
on	O
the	O
Hill	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
but	O
a	O
weak	O
excuse	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Day	O
time	O
at	O
Chelsea	B-place
,	O
no	O
Person	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
Cloath	O
Coat	O
,	O
5	O
Dowlas	O
Shirts	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
Leather	O
Breeches	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
broke	O
the	O
Bolt	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
running	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
pursued	O
he	O
dropt	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
a	O
Garden	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Argent	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
time	O
,	O
no	O
Person	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Brass	O
Kettle	O
a	O
Copper	O
Pot	O
,	O
9	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shag	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
his	O
Maid	O
coming	O
home	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
out	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Kettle	O
upon	O
his	O
Head	O
;	O
upon	O
whichshe	O
followed	O
him	O
and	O
cried	O
out	O
stop	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
dropt	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
Convict	O
him	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Haden	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pauls	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Silk	O
Hoods	O
,	O
a	O
Scarf	O
,	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
,	O
1	O
Apron	O
,	O
2	O
yards	O
of	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
a	O
Fan	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
they	O
saw	O
her	O
come	O
down	O
Stairs	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
saw	O
her	O
Brothers	O
Shirt	O
in	O
her	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
bundle	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
Hood	O
and	O
Scarf	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
put	O
the	O
things	O
behind	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
her	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Huntington	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
10	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Wooden	O
Box	O
11	O
Holland	O
Sheets	O
,	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Callico	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
value	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
not	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
to	O
Convict	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
that	O
and	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Grigson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Stoakes	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
opened	O
his	O
Closet	O
Window	O
about	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
getting	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Casement	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
which	O
forced	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
fly	O
,	O
and	O
flying	O
left	O
the	O
Hat	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
afterwards	O
found	O
.	O
He	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
plainly	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Harrold	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Allmon	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Brass	O
Kettle	O
,	O
4	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
8	O
Pewter	O
Pots	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
who	O
took	O
them	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
into	O
blew	B-place
Anchor	I-place
Alley	I-place
by	I-place
Bunhill-feilds	I-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
handed	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
second	O
Evidence	O
in	O
all	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Norman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
12	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
28	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
also	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
and	O
lost	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
who	O
took	O
them	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
other	O
Evidence	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
carried	O
away	O
28	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
in	O
Old-street	O
to	O
one	O
Tong	O
;	O
he	O
farther	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
angry	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
not	O
bringing	O
a	O
Sack	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Coffee	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Clary	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Pool	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Meeling	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
4	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
6	O
Plates	O
,	O
a	O
Copper	O
Pot	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
their	O
Laps	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
was	O
not	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
of	O
that	O
and	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Ricketts	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Suits	O
of	O
Muslin	O
Head	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Holland	O
Apron	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Pounsen	I-pers
,	O
and	O
2	O
yards	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Friday	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Bilton	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hood	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
a	O
stuff	O
Gown	O
,	O
2	O
Stuff	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Sunderland	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
them	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bow	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
large	O
Bible	O
and	O
a	O
Common	O
Prayer	O
Book	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
he	O
stole	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ethelburg	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Norman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
7	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
broke	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
broke	O
down	O
the	O
Boards	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
drying	O
House	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
afterwards	O
sold	O
;	O
It	O
was	O
very	O
full	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Carey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Night-royle	O
and	O
a	O
laced	O
Cravat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Grinthur	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
Convict	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Pierce	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Christ	B-place
Church	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Cecill	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
and	O
Perriwig	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Newgate-street	B-place
at	O
Night	O
he	O
was	O
knocked	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Perriwig	O
fell	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stoopt	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
down	O
Warwick-lane	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
He	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hatfield	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bennet	I-place
Gracechurch	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
60	O
yards	O
of	O
Muslin	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Acclestone	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
felony	O
for	O
taking	O
to	O
Husband	O
one	O
Alexander	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	O
George	O
Southwark	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
2d	O
year	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
afterwards	O
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
at	O
St.	B-place
Dionis	I-place
Back	I-place
Church	I-place
,	O
did	O
take	O
to	O
Husband	O
John	B-pers
Stockton	I-pers
,	O
her	O
former	O
Husband	O
being	O
then	O
alive	O
,	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Emblem	B-pers
Gold	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Stratford	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Battersby	I-pers
a	O
Silver	O
Tankerd	O
,	O
a	O
Cup	O
,	O
2	O
Porengers	O
,	O
9	O
Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
Fork	O
,	O
a	O
Corral	O
,	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
to	O
a	O
great	O
value	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Catherine	B-pers
Battersby	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
Gold	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Battersby	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
Stratford	O
,	O
who	O
pawned	O
them	O
in	O
Shoe-lane	O
.	O
Gold	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
Felony	O
in	O
Stratford	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Hillendon	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Medal	O
and	O
a	O
Spanish	O
Royal	O
of	O
Plate	O
,	O
and	O
25	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
from	O
Chamber	B-pers
Slaughter	I-pers
,	O
and	O
8	O
s.	O
from	O
James	B-pers
Angelley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
Convict	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Lowther	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
for	O
designing	O
to	O
hinder	O
a	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Mahew	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Rutlidge	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Hair	O
Trunk	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sattin	O
Stayes	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Bodice	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Rutlidge	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
was	O
not	O
sufficient	O
to	O
Convict	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Wade	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
;	O
was	O
Indicted	O
upon	O
2	O
Indictments	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Punch-Cup	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Radham	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
2d	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Pickering	I-pers
of	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
upon	O
both	O
Indictments	O
,	O
was	O
not	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lang	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
Ann	B-pers
Mackallister	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Laced	O
Head-Cloaths	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
;	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
near	O
Charing-Cross	B-place
,	O
about	O
Ten	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
and	O
pulled	O
her	O
Head	O
Cloaths	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
very	O
desperate	O
Wound	O
,	O
almost	O
cutting	O
off	O
her	O
Nose	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
down	O
her	O
Check	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
lamentable	O
manner	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
seized	O
and	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Round	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
search	O
him	O
,	O
found	O
under	O
the	O
Bench	O
that	O
he	O
sat	O
upon	O
,	O
the	O
Womans	O
Head-Cloaths	O
:	O
It	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Robbery	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lowder	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
upon	O
2	O
Indictments	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
as	O
for	O
the	O
first	O
she	O
had	O
formerly	O
been	O
Tryed	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Fact	O
and	O
Acquitted	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
not	O
Evidence	O
to	O
convict	O
her	O
of	O
the	O
second	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Goffe	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Bedley	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Bedlo	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Damask	O
silk	O
Gown	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
10	O
Guineas	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver-tabby-Stayes	O
,	O
a	O
Velvet	O
Hood	O
and	O
Scarf	O
,	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
laced	O
Head-cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
:	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
Box	O
lockt	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Closet	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
and	O
helpt	O
one	O
another	O
into	O
the	O
Balcony	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
went	O
and	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Closet	O
door	O
.	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
shared	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
all	O
which	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
having	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
themselves	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Tonge	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Buying	O
stollen	O
Goods	O
,	O
she	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
;	O
there	O
being	O
not	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
to	O
Convict	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Hester	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Liberty	I-place
of	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
laced	O
Muslin	O
Headdress	O
,	O
a	O
Stuff-Gown	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Harold	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
they	O
stole	O
them	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Merrifield	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Hambleton	I-pers
and	O
W	B-pers
-	I-pers
J	I-pers
-	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Sumpton	I-pers
,	O
4	O
Suits	O
of	O
Muslin	O
Head-dresses	O
,	O
a	O
laced	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
4	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
with	O
other	O
Goods	O
:	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
Merrifield	O
and	O
Hambleton	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
to	O
effect	O
the	O
other	O
2	O
they	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Merrifield	O
and	O
Hambleton	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Kinch	I-pers
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
Pewter-dishes	O
:	O
The	O
Pewter	O
being	O
taken	O
upon	O
him	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
upon	O
5	O
small	O
Indictments	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bedley	I-pers
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
,	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Newsom	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Copper	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
Burglary	O
,	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Goffe	I-pers
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Beech	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
31	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
2	O
Cloath-coats	O
,	O
a	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
Burglary	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
Timothy	B-pers
Moor	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
30	O
Yards	O
of	O
Callicoe	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
White	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Martha	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
upon	O
2	O
Indictments	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Robbery	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
Robbing	O
her	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
Bedding	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
from	O
Joanna	B-pers
Lake	I-pers
Widdow	O
,	O
and	O
Bedding	O
from	O
James	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Facts	O
were	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Lydia	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Huggins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
,	O
Stephen	B-pers
Swift	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Allenson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Looking	O
glass	O
,	O
4	O
brass	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
small	O
things	O
taken	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Knight	O
and	O
Swift	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
to	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
7	O
l.	O
in	O
Monies	O
,	O
from	O
Andrew	B-pers
Laurenson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	I-pers
and	I-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
his	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
stollen	O
Goods	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
Stole	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Man	O
being	O
Indicted	O
again	O
for	O
the	O
like	O
Offence	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jacob	B-pers
Rewbrey	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
King	I-pers
of	I-pers
the	I-pers
Gypsies	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Sellers	I-pers
,	O
near	O
the	O
High	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
3	O
Gold-rings	O
,	O
and	O
9	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
11th	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Reign	O
:	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
he	O
juggled	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Tryed	O
upon	O
a	O
Writ	O
of	O
Restitution	O
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
Goods	O
that	O
were	O
Stollen	O
from	O
Mary	B-pers
Peak	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
appeared	O
none	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Hands	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
suspected	O
to	O
entertain	O
ill	O
Persons	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
give	O
good	O
Security	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
for	O
12	O
Months	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
followeth	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
17	O
.	O
John	O
Bird	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Bird	O
,	O
John	O
Bedley	O
,	O
Martha	O
Bayley	O
Devereux	O
Feasant	O
,	O
Edward	O
Fowler	O
,	O
James	O
Grigson	O
,	O
William	O
Goffe	O
,	O
John	O
Harrold	O
,	O
Mary	O
Jones	O
,	O
William	O
King	O
,	O
John	O
Lang	O
,	O
Rebecca	O
Maud	O
,	O
John	O
Pierce	O
,	O
John	O
Tackerierry	O
,	O
Walter	O
Terrey	O
,	O
John	O
Wheeler	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Cheek	O
,	O
11	O
.	O
Barthelomew	O
Allen	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Barnet	O
,	O
Ann	O
Offee	O
,	O
Elinor	O
Dick	O
,	O
Emlen	O
Gold	O
,	O
John	O
Hollinsworth	O
,	O
Jone	O
Haden	O
,	O
Timothy	O
Moor	O
,	O
Mary	O
Pool	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Thompson	O
,	O
Jane	O
Wilson	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
,	O
6	O
.	O
Christian	O
Barnet	O
,	O
Robert	O
Collins	O
,	O
William	O
Fox	O
,	O
Robert	O
Johnson	O
,	O
David	O
Martin	O
Shrider	O
,	O
Jacob	O
Resbrey	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
,	O
10	O
.	O
Mary	O
Collins	O
,	O
Margaret	O
Hambleton	O
,	O
Robert	O
Kentish	O
,	O
Lydia	O
Knight	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Lucas	O
,	O
Mary	O
Merrifield	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Robinson	O
,	O
Mary	O
Rively	O
,	O
Charles	O
Smibson	O
,	O
Stephen	O
Sanf	O
.	O
Mary	O
Jones	O
,	O
and	O
Rebecca	O
Maud	O
pleaded	O
their	O
Bellies	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
being	O
Impaneled	O
,	O
found	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
not	O
with	O
quick	O
Child	O
.	O
Mathew	O
Askinson	O
was	O
Sentences	O
Imprisonment	O
during	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
late	O
Act	O
.	O
Richard	O
Reynolds	O
Fined	O
30	O
l.	O
and	O
to	O
remain	O
in	O
Prison	O
till	O
he	O
pay	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
last	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
Sessions	O
,	O
85	O
Criminals	O
,	O
on	O
whom	O
his	O
Majesty	O
was	O
pleased	O
to	O
vouchsafe	O
his	O
Royal	O
Pardon	O
pleaded	O
the	O
same	O
on	O
their	O
Kraves	O
,	O
acknowledging	O
his	O
Majestiesmost	O
gracious	O
Clemency	O
and	O
Mercy	O
,	O
most	O
of	O
them	O
are	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
beyond	O
the	O
Seas	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
to	O
return	O
to	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
within	O
the	O
space	O
of	O
7	O
Years	O
,	O
or	O
forfeiture	O
of	O
their	O
Lives	O
.	O
WE	O
present	O
a	O
Printed	O
Paper	O
Intitaled	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Charnocks	O
Letter	O
,	O
wrote	O
to	O
a	O
Friend	O
after	O
Condemnation	O
,	O
lately	O
dispersed	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Traiterous	O
and	O
Viralent	O
Libel	O
,	O
of	O
most	O
pernicious	O
Consequence	O
,	O
tending	O
to	O
Alienate	O
the	O
Hearts	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Subjects	O
from	O
their	O
due	O
Allegiance	O
to	O
their	O
most	O
Rightful	O
and	O
Lawful	O
Soveraign	O
King	O
WILLIAM	O
,	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
Princes	O
.	O
We	O
also	O
present	O
a	O
Poem	O
called	O
The	O
Foreigners	O
WHeras	O
there	O
comes	O
out	O
generally	O
the	O
same	O
Evening	O
a	O
false	O
and	O
scandalous	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Dying	O
Criminals	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
to	O
acquaint	O
the	O
World	O
that	O
no	O
true	O
Account	O
can	O
be	O
given	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
is	O
attested	O
by	O
the	O
Ordinaries	O
own	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
constantly	O
Published	O
by	O
E.	O
Mallet	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
.	O
Whereas	O
a	O
Watch	O
was	O
lost	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
1700	O
having	O
a	O
double	O
Silver	O
Case	O
,	O
the	O
inward	O
Case	O
lined	O
with	O
Crimson-Sattin	O
,	O
the	O
Makers	O
Name	O
Jasper	O
Harmer	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Silver-Brocaide	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
upon	O
a	O
purple	O
Ground	O
;	O
if	O
sold	O
or	O
pawned	O
to	O
any	O
Person	O
,	O
their	O
Money	O
shall	O
be	O
returned	O
,	O
or	O
if	O
stopped	O
,	O
a	O
Guinea	O
for	O
their	O
Care	O
,	O
upon	O
delivery	O
to	O
Edward	O
Paige	O
,	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
White-Hart	O
in	O
Ludgate	O
street	O
,	O
over	O
against	O
Ludgate-Church	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
W.	O
Elmy	O
,	O
Professor	O
of	O
Physick	O
and	O
Operator	O
,	O
Famous	O
for	O
Relieving	O
and	O
Curing	O
Deafness	O
and	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
Ears	O
in	O
any	O
,	O
hath	O
Practised	O
almost	O
40	O
Years	O
,	O
still	O
Liveth	O
at	O
the	O
Bleu-Ball	O
in	O
Whalebone	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
lower-end	O
of	O
Bartholomew	O
lane	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Royal-Exchange	O
,	O
London	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
ready	O
upon	O
any	O
occasion	O
of	O
that	O
Nature	O
to	O
serve	O
such	O
as	O
apply	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
doth	O
challenge	O
the	O
whole	O
World	O
to	O
perform	O
the	O
like	O
Cures	O
which	O
he	O
has	O
done	O
in	O
Deafness	O
.	O
Beware	O
of	O
some	O
who	O
pretend	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
Remedies	O
ready	O
prepared	O
for	O
the	O
Preservation	O
of	O
the	O
Hearing	O
,	O
in	O
those	O
who	O
through	O
some	O
great	O
defects	O
in	O
the	O
Sounding	O
Membraine	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Impediments	O
in	O
the	O
Auditory	O
Passages	O
,	O
are	O
not	O
perfectly	O
Curable	O
;	O
which	O
Remedies	O
preserve	O
them	O
from	O
ever	O
growing	O
worse	O
,	O
and	O
improves	O
their	O
Hearing	O
to	O
Old	O
Age	O
.	O
He	O
bath	O
likewise	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Gargarisin	O
or	O
Mouth	O
Water	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
make	O
black	O
or	O
yallow	O
Teeth	O
as	O
white	O
as	O
Ivory	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
times	O
using	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
will	O
certainly	O
Cure	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
Diseases	O
incident	O
to	O
the	O
Mouth	O
,	O
Teeth	O
and	O
Gums	O
.	O
The	O
Glasses	O
are	O
of	O
several	O
Prices	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
.	O
THE	O
most	O
excellent	O
Anti-Hectic	O
LOZENGES	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
pleasant	O
Taste	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
made	O
publick	O
till	O
now	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
Prescription	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
Eminent	O
and	O
Ancient	O
Physician	O
lately	O
Deceased	O
;	O
which	O
are	O
a	O
great	O
Specifick	O
for	O
preventing	O
Consumption	O
,	O
wonderfully	O
Sweetning	O
the	O
whole	O
Mass	O
of	O
Blood	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
their	O
Noble	O
Bilsamick	O
Vertue	O
restoring	O
the	O
decay	O
of	O
Nature	O
,	O
correcting	O
the	O
Acid	O
Humour	O
in	O
the	O
Stomach	O
,	O
commonly	O
called	O
the	O
Heart-burn	O
,	O
proceeding	O
from	O
hard	O
Indigestion	O
,	O
which	O
arises	O
from	O
many	O
Causes	O
,	O
but	O
chiefly	O
hard	O
Drinking	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
a	O
great	O
Diuretick	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
prevalent	O
against	O
the	O
Stone	O
;	O
they	O
remove	O
the	O
Heat	O
and	O
Sharpness	O
of	O
Urine	O
:	O
And	O
in	O
fine	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
best	O
Medicines	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
to	O
prevent	O
Miscarriage	O
.	O
Are	O
sold	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Bilingsly	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Printing-Press	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
Piazza	O
's	O
of	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
Mr.	O
Banbury	O
Bookseller	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
lower	O
Walk	O
of	O
the	O
New	O
Exchange	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
Hannam	O
's	O
Toy	O
Shop	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Golden-Cup	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
North-side	O
of	O
St.	O
Pauls	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Lander	O
's	O
Tin-Shop	O
in	O
Fetterlane	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
Mr	O
.	O
Dancer	O
,	O
Bookseller	O
,	O
next	O
St.	O
Dunstan	O
's	O
Church	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
.	O
Price	O
one	O
Shilling	O
each	O
Box	O
.	O
B.	O
Lilburn	O
,	O
that	O
lately	O
Lived	O
on	O
Ludgate-hill	O
,	O
next	O
to	O
the	O
Kings	O
Arms	O
Tavern	O
near	O
Fleet-Bridge	O
,	O
now	O
Lives	O
at	O
the	O
Golden-Board	O
,	O
and	O
Ball	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Globe-Tavern	O
,	O
in	O
little	O
Moor-fields	O
,	O
near	O
great	O
Moor	O
gate	O
,	O
up	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
.	O
Who	O
maketh	O
and	O
selleth	O
,	O
(	O
and	O
has	O
done	O
above	O
16	O
Years	O
;	O
the	O
Water	O
for	O
taking	O
away	O
the	O
Freckels	O
Pimple	O
,	O
Worms	O
,	O
and	O
Morphew	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
:	O
With	O
Elixir	O
Salutis	O
,	O
Balsimurn	O
Vite	O
,	O
Tinctura	O
Vitae	O
.	O
Waters	O
and	O
Ointments	O
for	O
the	O
Eyes	O
,	O
and	O
Ointments	O
for	O
fore	O
Nipples	O
;	O
Ointments	O
for	O
the	O
Rickets	O
,	O
Burns	O
,	O
Scalds	O
,	O
Wounds	O
,	O
Aches	O
,	O
Strains	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Powders	O
,	O
Dentrifices	O
,	O
Elixirs	O
,	O
Essences	O
,	O
Oils	O
,	O
Spirits	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
both	O
for	O
Ornament	O
,	O
and	O
Curing	O
most	O
Distempers	O
incident	O
to	O
Humane	O
Bodies	O
;	O
where	O
you	O
may	O
have	O
Advice	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
Medicines	O
likewise	O
Judgment	O
upon	O
Urine	O
.	O
The	O
Water	O
for	O
the	O
Freckles	O
,	O
Pimples	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Author	O
has	O
for	O
some	O
Years	O
past	O
,	O
left	O
with	O
several	O
for	O
Sale	O
;	O
and	O
now	O
doth	O
understand	O
,	O
they	O
have	O
been	O
abused	O
by	O
Counterfeits	O
;	O
which	O
to	O
prevent	O
for	O
the	O
future	O
,	O
doth	O
desire	O
those	O
who	O
have	O
bought	O
from	O
them	O
-	O
and	O
not	O
found	O
the	O
Effects	O
answer	O
the	O
Ends	O
for	O
which	O
it	O
is	O
proposed	O
,	O
to	O
acquaint	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
they	O
bought	O
it	O
-	O
and	O
likewise	O
to	O
take	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
Seal	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
The	O
3	O
Water-budgets	O
,	O
and	O
B.	O
L.	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
Seal	O
.	O
The	O
Price	O
of	O
the	O
half	O
Pint-bottle	O
3	O
s.	O
A	O
Most	O
certain	O
,	O
safe	O
and	O
speedy	O
Method	O
of	O
Curing	O
the	O
French-Disease	O
without	O
Fluxing	O
,	O
Danger	O
or	O
confinement	O
,	O
tho	O
in	O
the	O
worst	O
State	O
and	O
of	O
some	O
Year	O
continuance	O
is	O
still	O
Profest	O
and	O
Practiced	O
by	O
a	O
Physician	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Golden-hall	O
,	O
next	O
door	O
but	O
one	O
to	O
Tom	O
's	O
Coffee	O
house	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Court	O
adjoining	O
to	O
Ludgate	O
.	O
His	O
Medicines	O
may	O
be	O
conveyed	O
to	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
Sea	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
taken	O
with	O
Safety	O
and	O
Success	O
.	O
They	O
Cure	O
a	O
Gonorrhaea	O
,	O
Running	O
of	O
the	O
Rein	O
or	O
Clap	O
,	O
Pain	O
,	O
Heat	O
,	O
Scalding	O
in	O
making	O
Water	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
:	O
And	O
very	O
speedily	O
take	O
away	O
all	O
Aches	O
or	O
Pains	O
in	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
Back	O
,	O
Shoulders	O
,	O
Arms	O
,	O
Legs	O
,	O
or	O
Night-Pains	O
;	O
Sores	O
or	O
Ulcers	O
in	O
the	O
Mouth	O
or	O
Throat	O
;	O
All	O
Sorn	O
and	O
stubborn	O
Scabs	O
,	O
or	O
breaking	O
out	O
in	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Body	O
;	O
preserve	O
the	O
Palate	O
and	O
Bridge	O
of	O
the	O
Nose	O
;	O
purifie	O
the	O
Blood	O
;	O
perfectly	O
free	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
the	O
Remains	O
of	O
any	O
Pox	O
or	O
Clap	O
formerly	O
ill	O
Cured	O
;	O
and	O
certainly	O
prevent	O
these	O
Diseases	O
it	O
but	O
in	O
Danger	O
.	O
They	O
Cure	O
with	O
such	O
Privacy	O
,	O
that	O
those	O
you	O
are	O
constant	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
,	O
shall	O
not	O
suspect	O
it	O
.	O
His	O
Pills	O
,	O
so	O
much	O
Fam	O
'd	O
for	O
Curing	O
this	O
Disease	O
,	O
are	O
3	O
s.	O
or	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
Box	O
with	O
Directions	O
.	O
THe	O
Famous	O
Issue-Plaister	O
,	O
prepared	O
by	O
a	O
Chirurgeon	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
Fragrant	O
and	O
Pleasant	O
Scent	O
,	O
sticking	O
without	O
Rolling	O
or	O
Binding	O
,	O
spread	O
upon	O
Issue-Paper	O
,	O
and	O
such	O
a	O
Quantity	O
sold	O
for	O
1	O
s.	O
as	O
will	O
make	O
eleven	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Plaisters	O
;	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
with	O
Printed	O
Directions	O
how	O
to	O
dress	O
your	O
Issue	O
,	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Billingsly	O
's	O
at	O
the	O
Printing-Press	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
Piazza	O
of	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
Mr.	O
Hannam	O
's	O
at	O
the	O
Golden-Cup	O
,	O
a	O
Toyshop	O
on	O
the	O
North-side	O
of	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
,	O
Mr	O
.	O
Dancer	O
's	O
Bookseller	O
next	O
St.	O
Dunstan	O
's	O
Church	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Smeaton	O
's	O
at	O
the	O
Hand	O
and	O
Pen	O
against	O
the	O
May-Pole	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Michels	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
Toy	O
Shop	O
in	O
Westminster-Hall	O
.	O
Beware	O
of	O
one	O
Garway	O
a	O
Fruiterer	O
,	O
who	O
Connterfeits	O
.	O
