TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
Queen	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
and	O
Thursday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
14th	O
,	O
and	O
15th	O
,	O
Days	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
1702	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
First	O
Year	O
of	O
her	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
and	O
Thursday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
14th	O
,	O
and	O
15th	O
,	O
Days	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
1702	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Gore	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
Salathiel	B-pers
Lovel	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
others	O
of	O
her	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
are	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Christopher	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wharton	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Church	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Brand	I-pers
Nicholas	B-pers
Eale	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Bowton	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Bywater	I-pers
,	O
Abell	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Cleere	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harwell	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Kidgeel	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Noble	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
East	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Tims	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bootes	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wiburd	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Taper	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Yeomans	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Beatnife	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
follows	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Stanton	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
Queen-hith	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sculler-boat	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
from	O
George	B-pers
Bignall	I-pers
,	O
and	O
two	O
Sculls	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
from	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
that	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
take	O
the	O
Boat	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
Sculls	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
alledging	O
their	O
Innocence	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
five	O
Bells	O
in	O
Wood-street	O
with	O
a	O
Friend	O
,	O
and	O
staying	O
late	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
Queen-hith	B-place
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Sculler	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
came	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
they	O
went	O
over	O
some	O
Lighters	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
step	O
'd	O
into	O
the	O
Boat	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Morrison	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborne	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
40	O
Yards	O
of	O
Taffety	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Rachel	B-pers
Bonner	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
Gloves	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
cross	O
her	O
Arms	O
,	O
and	O
leant	O
on	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
turned	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
him	O
in	O
discourse	O
,	O
whilst	O
she	O
got	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
three	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
every	O
time	O
took	O
something	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
went	O
her	O
ways	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
took	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
Drink	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Worsted	O
Camblet	O
Coats	O
from	O
James	B-pers
Heming	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
and	O
whilst	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
Pail	O
of	O
Water	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
but	O
pursuing	O
her	O
,	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
laid	O
them	O
down	O
where	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
were	O
.	O
She	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
call	O
any	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Hampton	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
Sattin	O
Petticoat	O
with	O
3	O
Gold	O
Laces	O
,	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Hood	O
and	O
Scarf	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Hester	B-pers
Armstrong	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
opportunity	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
afterwards	O
takenand	O
brought	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
she	O
confest	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lang	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Day	O
time	O
,	O
no	O
Person	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Serge	O
Counterpain	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Lang	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
an	O
occasion	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
Gentlemans	O
Chamber	O
in	O
the	O
Temple	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
mistake	O
the	O
Stair-Case	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
up	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
hole	O
broke	O
at	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
saw	O
a	O
Woman	O
peep	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
mistrusting	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Thief	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
spoke	O
to	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
the	O
lower	O
Room	O
,	O
desiring	O
him	O
to	O
stop	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
should	O
come	O
down	O
whilst	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
call	O
the	O
Porter	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
down	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
in	O
the	O
hole	O
found	O
some	O
Chissels	O
;	O
but	O
opening	O
the	O
Door	O
found	O
several	O
Trunks	O
and	O
Boxes	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
pack	O
'd	O
up	O
ready	O
to	O
be	O
carried	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
she	O
come	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
her	O
Counsellor	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
told	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
that	O
Stair-Case	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
:	O
All	O
which	O
Matters	O
the	O
Jury	O
having	O
considered	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
her	O
of	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Stacy	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolphs	I-place
without	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Kettle	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Belch	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
looking	O
after	O
the	O
Shop	O
two	O
Women	O
came	O
and	O
cheapen	O
'd	O
a	O
Box	O
Iron	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
agreeing	O
on	O
the	O
price	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Kettle	O
being	O
missing	O
,	O
he	O
pursued	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
upon	O
her	O
in	O
her	O
Apron	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Trunk	O
,	O
6	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
4	O
pair	O
of	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
4	O
Neckcloaths	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Phillip	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
could	O
prove	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Spackman	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Messenger	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
6	O
Diaper	O
Napkins	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Spackman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
they	O
see	O
them	O
take	O
them	O
;	O
nor	O
nothing	O
being	O
found	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
alledging	O
their	O
Innocenc	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Saxton	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Day	O
time	O
,	O
about	O
7	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
no	O
Person	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Wastcoat	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
of	O
Rich	B-pers
.	I-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
and	O
Blankets	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Saxton	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
his	O
Room	O
was	O
robbed	O
and	O
in	O
pursuit	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Passage	O
.	O
She	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
nothing	O
being	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Cicilla	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
from	O
Joseph	B-pers
Mathias	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
a	O
Mess	O
with	O
something	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Siver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
she	O
tasted	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
called	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
two	O
Spoons	O
and	O
went	O
her	O
ways	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
afterwards	O
he	O
took	O
her	O
by	O
Broomly-street	O
in	O
Mans	O
Cloaths	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
nothing	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
calling	O
divers	O
Persons	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Simon	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Fleet	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	O
.	O
Brides	O
,	O
London	O
,	O
did	O
take	O
to	O
Wife	O
one	O
Susanna	B-pers
Cornwell	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
,	O
at	O
Knightsbridge	B-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Parish	I-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
did	O
take	O
to	O
Wife	O
one	O
S	B-pers
-	I-pers
S	I-pers
-	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
September	O
following	O
,	O
his	O
former	O
Wife	O
being	O
alive	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Evidence	O
was	O
the	O
Chaplain	O
of	O
the	O
Fleet	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
marry	O
one	O
Simon	O
Johnson	O
and	O
Susanna	O
Cornwell	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
believe	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Clerk	O
deposed	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
second	O
Marriage	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
would	O
live	O
and	O
die	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
denied	O
the	O
first	O
Wife	O
,	O
altho	O
'	O
he	O
had	O
owned	O
before	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
having	O
some	O
mistrust	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
be	O
married	O
to	O
a	O
second	O
Wife	O
followed	O
him	O
to	O
Knights-bridge	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
married	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
before	O
she	O
came	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
looking	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Window	O
and	O
seeing	O
his	O
first	O
Wife	O
,	O
ran	O
away	O
into	O
Hyde	O
Park	O
,	O
leaving	O
his	O
Hat	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
never	O
coming	O
near	O
his	O
last	O
Wife	O
after	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
was	O
the	O
Minister	O
of	O
Knightsbridge	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
last	O
Wife	O
came	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Licence	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
married	O
them	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
was	O
the	O
Clerk	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
married	O
he	O
earnestly	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
keep	O
the	O
matter	O
secret	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Custody	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
two	O
Wives	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
first	O
Wife	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
Child	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
married	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Newgate	O
he	O
did	O
confess	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
two	O
Wives	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
himself	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
married	O
to	O
his	O
first	O
Wife	O
.	O
But	O
both	O
Marriages	O
being	O
so	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Dodds	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Enfield	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2208	O
Beech	O
Billets	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Wood	O
,	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barnet	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
ordered	O
him	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Rachel	B-pers
Sampson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
White-chappel	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Susan	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
two	O
Cheeses	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Gloves	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
7	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
in	O
and	O
hid	O
her	O
self	O
till	O
they	O
were	O
a	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
confest	O
when	O
taken	O
.	O
She	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
her	O
Trial	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
her	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Housden	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Newstead	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
for	O
counterfeiting	O
the	O
current	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
Information	O
given	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
followed	O
the	O
Trade	O
of	O
Coining	O
,	O
a	O
Warrant	O
was	O
granted	O
to	O
apprehend	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
by	O
Turnstile	O
,	O
they	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
false	O
Money	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
dropt	O
upon	O
her	O
Knees	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
thrust	O
the	O
Money	O
into	O
some	O
Grates	O
of	O
a	O
Window	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
prevented	O
;	O
an	O
other	O
Evidence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
bought	O
several	O
quantities	O
of	O
false	O
Money	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
confest	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
made	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
an	O
Old	O
Offender	O
in	O
this	O
kind	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
only	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Parry	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Brass	O
Porridge-pots	O
and	O
a	O
Brass	O
Kettle	O
from	O
Rich	B-pers
Southey	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
11th	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
King	O
William	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
alledged	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
7	O
Years	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
farther	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Prosecuted	O
out	O
of	O
Malice	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
he	O
had	O
lived	O
so	O
long	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
was	O
never	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
till	O
now	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Day	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
3	O
pair	O
of	O
Crimson	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Huslam	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
September	O
Last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
fitting	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
with	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
a	O
sudden	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
from	O
behind	O
the	O
Counter	O
with	O
something	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
he	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
touch	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Bourne	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
for	O
uttering	O
false	O
Money	O
,	O
she	O
knowing	O
it	O
so	O
to	O
be	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
French	O
Brandy	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
a	O
good	O
Guinea	O
to	O
change	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
weighed	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
pretending	O
that	O
she	O
must	O
not	O
give	O
so	O
much	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
Money	O
again	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
she	O
agreed	O
to	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
down	O
a	O
gilt	O
Shilling	O
instead	O
of	O
the	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
gave	O
her	O
her	O
change	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
her	O
way	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
bought	O
a	O
Shift	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
gilt	O
Six-pence	O
instead	O
of	O
a	O
half	O
Guinea	O
;	O
another	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
buy	O
3	O
l.	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
gilt	O
Six-pence	O
instead	O
of	O
a	O
half	O
Guinea	O
.	O
She	O
having	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
herself	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Walnut-tree	O
Dressing-box	O
,	O
and	O
29	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
from	O
David	B-pers
Hutchinson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Twist	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Buck	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Chelsea	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Stubbington	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
time	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
a	O
Copper	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stuff	O
Curtains	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
whilst	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
early	O
to	O
Market	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
gone	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
other	O
Evidence	O
who	O
saw	O
the	O
Women	O
near	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
carry	O
the	O
Copper	O
upon	O
her	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
the	O
Bundles	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Man	O
was	O
not	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
,	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
two	O
Women	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Lancelot	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
granted	O
to	O
him	O
by	O
Contract	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
and	O
taking	O
20	O
l.	O
weight	O
of	O
Feathers	O
,	O
a	O
blanket	O
,	O
Sheet	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mark	B-pers
Hooks	I-pers
deceased	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Manshty	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepny	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
pocket	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Linnen-purse	O
work	O
'd	O
with	O
Cruel	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
s	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
numbred	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
drinking	O
at	O
a	O
House	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
his	O
way	O
over	O
Goodmans-fields	B-place
,	O
she	O
overtook	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
him	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
drink	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
refused	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
a	O
suddain	O
got	O
her	O
Hand	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
fealing	O
,	O
she	O
snatched	O
it	O
out	O
again	O
with	O
the	O
Purse	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
other	O
Evidences	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
confest	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
the	O
Purse	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
found	O
it	O
by	O
her	O
Directions	O
.	O
She	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
call	O
any	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Martha	B-pers
Lewin	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
an	O
Indian	O
Sattin	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
silk	O
Hood	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Mercer	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
confest	O
when	O
taken	O
and	O
brought	O
before	O
the	O
Justice.She	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
for	O
breakings	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Walters	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
time	O
,	O
with	O
intention	O
to	O
steal	O
his	O
Goods	O
while	O
a	O
little	O
Girl	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Girl	O
returning	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
for	O
getting	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Girl	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
People	O
coming	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
pick-lock	O
key	O
in	O
her	O
Bosom	O
,	O
which	O
lock	O
'd	O
and	O
unlock	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepny	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
stuff	O
Gown	O
and	O
2	O
stuff	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Isabella	B-pers
Holms	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
with	O
a	O
lap	O
full	O
of	O
Things	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
pursuing	O
her	O
she	O
drop	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Tobias	B-pers
Maccarty	I-pers
,	I-pers
alis	I-pers
Dathy	I-pers
Maccarty	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Jeremy	I-pers
Maccarty	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
marrying	O
a	O
second	O
Wife	B-pers
,	O
the	O
first	B-pers
being	O
alive	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Niccolls	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Alderson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Forgery	O
for	O
Forging	O
several	O
Deeds	O
of	O
Assignments	O
;	O
which	O
Matter	O
the	O
Court	O
not	O
thinking	O
fit	O
to	O
try	O
before	O
the	O
Title	O
could	O
be	O
prov	O
'd	O
at	O
Common	O
Law	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
were	O
ordered	O
to	O
inquire	O
of	O
it	O
no	O
further	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
2	O
.	O
Jane	O
Housden	O
to	O
be	O
burnt	O
,	O
and	O
Sarah	O
Stephens	O
to	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
Simon	O
Johnson	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Left-Cheek	O
10	O
.	O
Mary	O
Buck	O
,	O
Jane	O
Collier	O
,	O
Mary	O
Cook	O
,	O
Joseph	O
Day	O
,	O
Mary	O
Johnson	O
,	O
Martha	O
Lewin	O
,	O
Sarrah	O
Morrison	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Price	O
,	O
Rachel	O
Sampson	O
and	O
Jane	O
Williams	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
whipt	O
Jane	O
Stacy	O
.	O
Jane	O
Housden	O
and	O
Sarah	O
Stephens	O
pleaded	O
their	O
Bellies	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
being	O
Impanelled	O
,	O
who	O
found	O
them	O
with	O
quick	O
Child	O
.	O
Jane	O
Bourne	O
fin	O
'd	O
20	O
Nobles	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
3	O
times	O
on	O
the	O
Pillory	O
,	O
without	O
Temple-bar	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
May-pole	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
and	O
Charing	O
cross	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Smith	O
fin	O
'd	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
to	O
be	O
whipt	O
at	O
the	O
usual	O
place	O
and	O
times	O
.	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
The	O
History	O
of	O
Living	O
Men	O
,	O
or	O
Characters	O
of	O
the	O
Royal	O
Family	O
,	O
the	O
Ministers	O
of	O
State	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
principal	O
Natives	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
Kingdoms	O
;	O
being	O
an	O
Essay	O
on	O
a	O
Thousand	O
Persons	O
that	O
are	O
now	O
living	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Poem	O
upon	O
each	O
Life	O
:	O
Dedicated	O
to	O
his	O
Royal	O
Highness	O
Prince	O
George	O
of	O
Denmark	O
,	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
Petticoat-Government	O
;	O
In	O
a	O
Letter	O
to	O
the	O
Court-Ladies	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Author	O
of	O
the	O
Post-Angel	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
The	O
New	O
Quevedo	O
,	O
Or	O
,	O
a	O
Vision	O
of	O
Charon	O
's	O
Passengers	O
:	O
From	O
the	O
Creation	O
of	O
the	O
World	O
,	O
down	O
to	O
this	O
present	O
Year	O
1702	O
.	O
With	O
their	O
Names	O
,	O
Qualities	O
,	O
and	O
particular	O
Crimes	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
The	O
second	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
New	O
Quevedo	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
further	O
Vision	O
of	O
Charon	O
's	O
Passengers	O
;	O
with	O
their	O
Names	O
,	O
Qualities	O
,	O
and	O
particular	O
Crimes	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
Eight	O
Fables	O
on	O
the	O
present	O
Posture	O
of	O
Affairs	O
in	O
Europe	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
The	O
Devil	O
and	O
the	O
Priest	O
,	O
or	O
Porto	O
Carero	O
's	O
Will	O
:	O
The	O
Courtier	O
:	O
The	O
Pilgrims	O
:	O
The	O
Usurers	O
and	O
Merchants	O
:	O
The	O
Ingrates	O
:	O
The	O
Partizan	O
:	O
The	O
Confederacy	O
:	O
The	O
Interview	O
:	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
prefix	O
'd	O
,	O
Aesop	O
's	O
Advice	O
,	O
both	O
to	O
the	O
Princes	O
and	O
People	O
of	O
Europe	O
.	O
Price	O
6	O
d.	O
||+||	O
.	O
A	O
Vindication	O
of	O
Magna	O
Charta	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Summary	O
of	O
English	O
Rights	O
and	O
Liberties	O
;	O
in	O
which	O
its	O
Antiquity	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Confirmations	O
procured	O
to	O
it	O
in	O
several	O
Reigns	O
,	O
are	O
fully	O
set	O
forth	O
.	O
The	O
glorious	O
Actions	O
of	O
the	O
Peers	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
maintain	O
the	O
Privileges	O
of	O
the	O
People	O
,	O
are	O
related	O
and	O
defended	O
:	O
And	O
the	O
excellency	O
of	O
the	O
old	O
English	O
Constitution	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
noblest	O
Constitution	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
.	O
Price	O
12	O
d.	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
An	O
Argument	O
proving	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Imposition	O
of	O
the	O
Sacrament	O
of	O
the	O
Lord	O
's	O
Supper	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
Qualification	O
for	O
a	O
secular	O
Office	O
,	O
is	O
(	O
1	O
.	O
)	O
Contrary	O
to	O
the	O
express	O
Laws	O
of	O
God	O
.	O
(	O
2	O
.	O
)	O
Contrary	O
to	O
the	O
Doctrines	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
of	O
England	O
.	O
(	O
3	O
.	O
)	O
Contrary	O
to	O
the	O
Doctrines	O
of	O
the	O
Dissenters	O
.	O
And	O
(	O
4	O
.	O
)	O
Contrary-to	O
the	O
National	O
and	O
Natural	O
Rights	O
of	O
all	O
Mankind	O
.	O
In	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
Reasonableness	O
and	O
Necessity	O
of	O
taking	O
away	O
the	O
Sacramental	O
Test	O
at	O
this	O
Juncture	O
,	O
is	O
particularly	O
consider	O
'd	O
.	O
Price	O
6	O
d.	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
The	O
present	O
Condition	O
of	O
the	O
English	O
Navy	O
,	O
set	O
forth	O
in	O
a	O
Dialogue	O
betwixt	O
young	O
Fudge	O
of	O
the	O
Admiralty	O
,	O
and	O
Captain	O
Steerwel	O
an	O
Oliverian	O
Commander	O
.	O
Price	O
6	O
d.	O
Plantation	O
Justice	O
,	O
shewing	O
the	O
Constitution	O
of	O
their	O
Courts	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
sort	O
of	O
Judges	O
they	O
have	O
in	O
them	O
:	O
By	O
which	O
Merchants	O
may	O
see	O
the	O
occasions	O
of	O
their	O
great	O
Losses	O
and	O
Sufferings	O
in	O
the	O
Plantation	O
Trade	O
:	O
Lawyers	O
may	O
see	O
such	O
a	O
Model	O
of	O
Justice	O
as	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
thought	O
of	O
;	O
and	O
Others	O
may	O
see	O
how	O
those	O
Parts	O
of	O
the	O
World	O
are	O
governed	O
.	O
The	O
second	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
3	O
d.	O
All	O
Sold	O
by	O
Elizabeth	O
Miller	O
,	O
Robert	O
Whitledge	O
,	O
Book-binder	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
in	O
Creedane	O
,	O
within	O
Ludgate	O
,	O
sells	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
Bibles	O
and	O
Common-Prayers	O
,	O
Tate	O
and	O
Brady	O
's	O
Singing-Psalms	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Books	O
,	O
neatly	O
Bound	O
,	O
at	O
reasonable	O
rates	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
B.	O
Lilburn	O
,	O
that	O
formerly	O
Lived	O
on	O
Ludgate-hill	O
,	O
next	O
to	O
the	O
Kings	O
Arms	O
Tavern	O
near	O
Fleet-Bridge	O
,	O
now	O
Lives	O
at	O
the	O
Golden-Board	O
,	O
and	O
Ball	O
in	O
the	O
Great	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
near	O
Ludgate	O
hill	O
.	O
Who	O
maketh	O
and	O
felleth	O
,	O
(	O
and	O
has	O
done	O
this	O
20	O
Years	O
)	O
the	O
Water	O
for	O
taking	O
away	O
the	O
Freckels	O
,	O
Pimple	O
,	O
Worms	O
,	O
Morphew	O
,	O
and	O
red	O
Marks	O
of	O
the	O
Small-pox	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
:	O
With	O
Elixir	O
Salutis	O
,	O
Balsamum	O
Vitoe	O
,	O
Tinctura	O
Vitoe	O
.	O
Waters	O
and	O
Ointments	O
for	O
the	O
Eyes	O
,	O
Powders	O
,	O
Dentrifices	O
,	O
Elixirs	O
,	O
Essences	O
,	O
Oils	O
,	O
Spirits	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
both	O
for	O
Ornament	O
,	O
and	O
Curing	O
all	O
Diseases	O
incident	O
to	O
Humane	O
Bodies	O
;	O
but	O
more	O
especially	O
relating	O
to	O
the	O
Female	O
Sex	O
,	O
likewise	O
Judgment	O
upon	O
Urine	O
.	O
The	O
Anti-scorbutick	O
Pills	O
,	O
price	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d	O
the	O
Box	O
.	O
The	O
Elixir	O
for	O
the	O
Collick	O
,	O
and	O
Gripes	O
.	O
I	O
s.	O
the	O
Bottle	O
.	O
The	O
Ointment	O
for	O
sore	O
Nipples	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Piles	O
,	O
I	O
s.	O
the	O
Pot	O
.	O
An	O
Ointment	O
for	O
Redness	O
,	O
Pustules	O
,	O
Heat	O
,	O
Scabs	O
,	O
Ring-worms	O
,	O
Titters	O
,	O
Itch	O
or	O
breaking	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
where	O
,	O
price	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Pot	O
.	O
The	O
Ointment	O
for	O
Aches	O
,	O
and	O
Strains	O
,	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Pot	O
.	O
The	O
Water	O
for	O
the	O
Freckles	O
,	O
Pimples	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Author	O
has	O
for	O
some	O
Years	O
past	O
,	O
left	O
with	O
several	O
for	O
Sale	O
;	O
who	O
now	O
doth	O
understand	O
,	O
they	O
have	O
been	O
abused	O
by	O
Counterfeits	O
;	O
which	O
to	O
prevent	O
for	O
the	O
future	O
,	O
doth	O
desire	O
those	O
that	O
have	O
bought	O
from	O
them	O
-	O
and	O
not	O
found	O
the	O
Effect-answer	O
the	O
Ends	O
for	O
which	O
it	O
is	O
proposed	O
,	O
to	O
acquaint	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
they	O
bought	O
it	O
-	O
and	O
likewise	O
to	O
take	O
nor	O
tice	O
of	O
the	O
Seal	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
The	O
3	O
Water-budgets	O
,	O
and	O
B.	O
L.	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
Seal	O
.	O
The	O
Price	O
of	O
the	O
half	O
Pint-bottle	O
3	O
s	O
.	O
