TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
Queen	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
and	O
Thursday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
13th	O
and	O
14th	O
Days	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
1703	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
Second	O
Year	O
of	O
Her	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
and	O
Thursday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
13th	O
and	O
14th	O
Days	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
1703	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Samuel	B-pers
Dashwood	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
Salathiel	B-pers
Lovel	I-pers
Knt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
others	O
of	O
her	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
are	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Christopher	I-pers
,	O
Jeremy	B-pers
Gerrard	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Brand	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Tromantel	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Marshal	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
,	O
Jacob	B-pers
Spooner	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nelthorp	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pitts	I-pers
,	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Garret	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bevin	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Kidgell	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
Jeremy	B-pers
Lewin	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Devenish	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hull	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bootes	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Yeomans	I-pers
,	O
Brune	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Taper	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Beatniffe	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
follow	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Waggoner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
160	O
Canes	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Pinkeman	I-pers
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Thorne	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Stanton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Peter-Cheape	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
8	O
Yards	O
of	O
Muslin	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Carbrand	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
Sept.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Muslin	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
under	O
her	O
Apron	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
seen	O
by	O
the	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
they	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
took	O
her	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
and	O
the	O
Muslin	O
dropt	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
nor	O
never	O
saw	O
it	O
before	O
they	O
took	O
it	O
off	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
Basishaw	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
2	O
leather	O
Bags	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
2	O
Shirts	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
cloth	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Prudom	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
riding	O
down	O
Basinghall-street	B-place
,	O
to	O
the	O
Bear-Inn	O
,	O
on	O
a	O
sudden	O
he	O
felt	O
his	O
Bags	O
pulled	O
from	O
off	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
turned	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
pursued	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
an	O
Alley	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
given	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
his	O
Comrades	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
them	O
:	O
He	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
Ludgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
an	O
Ounce	O
of	O
Silver	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
weigh	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
camein	O
,	O
and	O
cheapned	O
a	O
hollow	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
whilst	O
he	O
was	O
busy	O
,	O
she	O
conveyed	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
Slieve	O
.	O
She	O
denied	O
that	O
she	O
stole	O
any	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
She	O
did	O
come	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
lie	O
in	O
the	O
Scale	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
put	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
up	O
to	O
look	O
upon	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
down	O
again	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wharton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
linnen	O
Bag	O
,	O
and	O
55	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
being	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
over	O
the	O
Water	O
to	O
Westminster	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
with	O
a	O
Friend	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
who	O
sent	O
a	O
Watch-man	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
home	O
;	O
but	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
they	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
,	O
who	O
would	O
have	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
drink	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
consented	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Watchman	O
left	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
Queen's-Head	O
in	O
Charles-street	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
staid	O
some	O
time	O
;	O
afterwards	O
he	O
having	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
,	O
the	O
Watchman	O
came	O
again	O
to	O
light	O
him	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
between	O
the	O
two	O
Gates	O
at	O
Whitehall	B-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
into	O
the	O
Tilt-Yard	O
,	O
but	O
making	O
a	O
noise	O
,	O
the	O
Soldiers	O
brought	O
her	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
her	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Bag	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
,	O
a	O
little	O
Girl	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pauls	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
6	O
Yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Ribbon	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Tenderness	O
of	O
her	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
sensible	O
of	O
her	O
Fault	O
,	O
they	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Bathia	B-pers
Philps	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepny	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
Hood	O
and	O
Scarf	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Yeomans	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
took	O
her	O
in	O
to	O
work	O
by	O
the	O
Week	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
very	O
first	O
Day	O
she	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
came	O
any	O
more	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
lie	O
at	O
the	O
Mercy	O
of	O
the	O
Bench	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Seabrooke	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
Petticoat	O
and	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Winchester	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
assaulting	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
and	O
wounding	O
him	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
cut	O
his	O
Throat	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Chisnal	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepny	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
an	O
Iron	O
Bar	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
more	O
Persons	O
who	O
owned	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
not	O
being	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
3	O
gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
2	O
Hoods	O
,	O
a	O
Scarf	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
whom	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
.	O
Other	O
Evidences	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
Basket	O
full	O
of	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
Rings	O
on	O
her	O
Finger	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
one	O
proved	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
.	O
She	O
denying	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
nothing	O
being	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepny	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
75	O
Yards	O
of	O
Shaloon	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
;	O
and	O
150	O
Yards	O
of	O
Shaloon	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
another	O
100	O
Yards	O
of	O
Shaloon	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Rochester	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
left	O
in	O
a	O
Dye-House	O
to	O
be	O
dyed	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
search	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Fathers	O
Stable	O
,	O
under	O
a	O
Manger	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
calling	O
People	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
58	O
Diamonds	O
set	O
in	O
Silver	O
gilt	O
,	O
value	O
250	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Catherine	B-pers
Lady	I-pers
Herbert	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Jewels	O
were	O
put	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Closet	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
lockt	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
Coachman	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
took	O
his	O
opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
Lady	O
,	O
when	O
missing	O
them	O
,	O
offered	O
a	O
Reward	O
of	O
Fourscore	O
Pounds	O
to	O
any	O
that	O
could	O
give	O
any	O
notice	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
upon	O
enquiry	O
,	O
the	O
Lady	O
heard	O
that	O
a	O
Diamond	O
was	O
sold	O
on	O
London-Bridge	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
described	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
who	O
sold	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
pursuing	O
him	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
East-Ham	O
,	O
with	O
all	O
his	O
Goods	O
bundled	O
up	O
ready	O
to	O
be	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
his	O
Trunk	O
found	O
all	O
the	O
Diamonds	O
but	O
one	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Role	O
of	O
his	O
Stocking	O
,	O
when	O
searcht	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
He	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
He	O
found	O
them	O
upon	O
a	O
great	O
Heap	O
of	O
Rubbish	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
being	O
but	O
a	O
weak	O
Excuse	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Norris	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stanwel	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Swaine	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
10	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Calamanca-wastcoat	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Plush-Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
tarried	O
there	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Goods	O
gone	O
;	O
but	O
calling	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
they	O
pursued	O
after	O
the	O
Thieves	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Man	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
a	O
Sack	O
,	O
who	O
upon	O
sight	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
down	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
fighting	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
surrendring	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
got	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
workt	O
at	O
Harvest-work	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
poor	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
lie	O
in	O
a	O
Haycock	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
that	O
way	O
,	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
his	O
Goods	O
again	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Sabbin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
White-Chappel	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
12	O
China-Cups	O
,	O
12	O
Sawcers	O
,	O
a	O
China-Bason	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
she	O
stole	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
own	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
31th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
driving	O
a	O
Coach	O
and	O
Horses	O
over	O
his	O
Breast	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
to	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
declared	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
endeavoured	O
all	O
he	O
could	O
to	O
stop	O
his	O
Horses	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
done	O
by	O
misfortune	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stroude	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Emmerson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
1	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
8	O
Iron-Bars	O
,	O
4	O
Wedges	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
brass	O
Dial-Plates	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
called	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Shed	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
put	O
in	O
a	O
Bag	O
under	O
the	O
Pails	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
over	O
the	O
Pails	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
pursued	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
He	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
Friend	O
at	O
Fulham	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
home	O
,	O
lost	O
his	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Shed	O
being	O
no	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
a	O
Gentleman	B-pers
's	O
Pocket	O
of	O
a	O
leather	O
Purse	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
numbred	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
up	O
two	O
Nights	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
meeting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
sleepy	O
,	O
laid	O
his	O
Head	O
down	O
and	O
fell	O
asleep	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
she	O
took	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
which	O
she	O
denied	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
,	O
saying	O
she	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
before	O
in	O
all	O
her	O
Life	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Blackman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchers	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
a	O
pocket	O
Handkerchief	O
from	O
Daniel	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
through	O
Newgate	B-place
,	O
he	O
catcht	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Hand	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
pulled	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
almost	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
quite	O
,	O
so	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
possession	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Groves	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Cheat	O
,	O
for	O
cheating	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
by	O
leaving	O
several	O
Parcels	O
with	O
her	O
in	O
pawn	O
,	O
telling	O
her	O
they	O
were	O
filled	O
with	O
Silk	O
,	O
whereas	O
they	O
were	O
filled	O
with	O
Brick-bats	O
and	O
Stones	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
she	O
came	O
8	O
several	O
times	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
lent	O
her	O
,	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
27	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
desiring	O
her	O
not	O
to	O
look	O
into	O
it	O
,	O
saying	O
it	O
would	O
spoil	O
the	O
Silk	O
if	O
it	O
should	O
take	O
Air	O
:	O
Which	O
Fact	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Wallis	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Serjeant	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
Queen	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
Constable	O
to	O
May-Fair	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
suppress	O
Vice	O
and	O
Immorality	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
7	O
a	O
clock	O
they	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
lewd	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
before	O
the	O
High-Constable	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Hawkins	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
rescued	O
her	O
with	O
drawn	O
Swords	O
,	O
and	O
Hawkins	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
making	O
his	O
escape	O
with	O
a	O
drawn	O
Sword	O
;	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Cooper	O
was	O
killed	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
afterwards	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
Person	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
grey	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
who	O
he	O
believed	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
carrying	O
him	O
away	O
Pick-a-pack	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
heard	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
say	O
,	O
Damn	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
have	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
whole	O
Mob	O
came	O
running	O
with	O
their	O
Swords	O
drawn	O
,	O
and	O
rescued	O
him	O
,	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
One	O
and	O
all	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
leap	O
down	O
a	O
great	O
Ditch	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
escape	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
run	O
over	O
the	O
Field	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
drawn	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
believe	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
was	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
before	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Levet	I-pers
,	O
who	O
being	O
then	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
wait	O
a	O
while	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
Coffee-house	O
,	O
he	O
questioned	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
then	O
confess	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Riot	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
Prisoner	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
afterwards	O
rescued	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
Sword	O
drawn	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Other	O
Evidences	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
came	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
in	O
the	O
Riot	O
,	O
which	O
still	O
continued	O
till	O
the	O
Constable	O
was	O
killed	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
8	O
a	O
clock	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
grey	O
Coat	O
with	O
black	O
Buttons	O
.	O
He	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
He	O
was	O
at	O
his	O
Quarters	O
when	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
2	O
Soldiers	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Fair	O
about	O
5	O
a	O
clock	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
them	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Disturbance	O
in	O
the	O
Fair	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
go	O
back	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
Quarters	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
then	O
in	O
a	O
red	O
Coat	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
drank	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
Pints	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
till	O
past	O
8	O
a	O
clock	O
,	O
when	O
word	O
was	O
brought	O
that	O
the	O
Constable	O
was	O
killed	O
:	O
But	O
being	O
askt	O
what	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
Month	O
,	O
or	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
Week	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
one	O
saying	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Friday	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
utterly	O
false	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
agreeing	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
began	O
the	O
Riot	O
,	O
which	O
continued	O
till	O
the	O
death	O
of	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Thare	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Serge-Curtains	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Wil	B-pers
.	I-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
Oct.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
when	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
said	O
,	O
He	O
saw	O
her	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
with	O
something	O
in	O
her	O
Lap	O
,	O
and	O
pursuing	O
her	O
,	O
took	O
her	O
in	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
She	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
She	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
Woman	O
;	O
which	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Constance	B-pers
Arms	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
5	O
Holland-Aprons	O
,	O
a	O
Hood	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Sampson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
June	O
last.It	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Gallop	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepny	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
2	O
Rings	O
,	O
a	O
gold	O
Bob	O
,	O
4	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cutting	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
Oct.	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
done	O
by	O
the	O
Husband	O
,	O
who	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
Marshalseas	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonards	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Wash-house	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
4	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
6	O
Shirts	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
Smocks	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
He	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
more	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
TRIALS	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
follows	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
2	O
.	O
Ann	O
Finch	O
,	O
and	O
William	O
Wallis	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
left	O
Cheek	O
5	O
.	O
Samuel	O
Davis	O
,	O
Bathia	O
Philps	O
,	O
Mary	O
Seabrooke	O
,	O
Sarah	O
Thorne	O
,	O
and	O
Anthony	O
Waggonner	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
,	O
4	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Johnson	O
,	O
Henry	O
Norris	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Stroude	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	O
Thare	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Williams	O
,	O
respited	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
Sessions	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
to	O
be	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Burglary	O
.	O
Called	O
to	O
their	O
former	O
Judgments	O
,	O
5.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Deakins	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Manship	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Tims	I-pers
,	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Wetherley	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Bunce	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
.	O
Ann	O
Finch	O
pleaded	O
her	O
Belly	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
being	O
Impannelled	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
not	O
with	O
quick	O
Child	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Groves	O
,	O
fined	O
20	O
Nobles	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
remain	O
in	O
Prison	O
till	O
she	O
pay	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Fisher	O
,	O
fined	O
20	O
l.	O
and	O
to	O
remain	O
in	O
Prison	O
till	O
he	O
pay	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
find	O
Sureties	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
for	O
12	O
Months	O
.	O
WHeras	O
some	O
Persons	O
have	O
lately	O
assumed	O
the	O
liberty	O
of	O
putting	O
out	O
several	O
Sham-papers	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
give	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Dying	O
Criminals	O
;	O
wherein	O
they	O
are	O
so	O
far	O
defective	O
and	O
unjust	O
,	O
as	O
sometimes	O
to	O
mistake	O
even	O
the	O
Names	O
and	O
Crimes	O
of	O
those	O
Persons	O
.	O
Therefore	O
to	O
prevent	O
the	O
World	O
's	O
being	O
any	O
longer	O
impos	O
'd	O
upon	O
in	O
this	O
manner	O
:	O
These	O
are	O
to	O
give	O
notice	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
only	O
true	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Dying	O
Malefactors	O
,	O
is	O
that	O
which	O
comes	O
out	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
after	O
their	O
Execution	O
,	O
about	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
attested	O
by	O
the	O
Ordinary	O
,	O
and	O
printed	O
for	O
Elizabeth	O
Mallet	O
,	O
next	O
to	O
the	O
King's-Arms	O
Tavern	O
near	O
Fleetbridge	O
.	O
The	O
Title	O
of	O
which	O
Account	O
,	O
(	O
that	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
distinguish	O
'd	O
from	O
false	O
ones	O
)	O
constantly	O
begins	O
thus	O
,	O
The	O
ORDINARY	O
of	O
NEWGATE	O
his	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Behaviour	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Walking	O
with	O
God	O
,	O
shewn	O
in	O
a	O
Sermon	O
preach	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Funeral	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	O
Cook	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
Church	O
of	O
St.	O
James	O
Clerkenwel	O
,	O
Aug.	O
13th	O
,	O
1703	O
.	O
By	O
Paul	O
Lorrain	O
,	O
Preshyter	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
and	O
Ordinary	O
of	O
Newgate	O
.	O
Price	O
3	O
d.	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
King	O
William	O
's	O
Affection	O
to	O
the	O
Church	O
of	O
England	O
examin	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
5th	O
Edit	O
.	O
Price	O
6	O
d.	O
Both	O
Sold	O
by	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Mallet	O
,	O
near	O
Fleet-bridge	O
.	O
Robert	O
Whitledge	O
,	O
Book-binder	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
in	O
Creed-lane	O
,	O
within	O
Ludgate	O
,	O
sells	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
Bibles	O
and	O
CommonPrayers	O
,	O
both	O
large	O
and	O
small	O
:	O
Also	O
the	O
new	O
Book	O
of	O
Rates	O
compleat	O
;	O
printed	O
at	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Printing-House	O
,	O
Tate	O
and	O
Brady	O
's	O
Singing-Psalms	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Books	O
,	O
which	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
ready	O
Bound	O
,	O
at	O
reasonable	O
rates	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
W.	O
Elmy	O
,	O
Professor	O
of	O
Physick	O
and	O
Operator	O
,	O
of	O
known	O
Integrity	O
,	O
liveth	O
at	O
the	O
Blue-ball	O
,	O
in	O
Whalebone	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
lower	O
end	O
of	O
Bartholomew-lane	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Royal-Exchange	O
.	O
WHO	O
most	O
safely	O
and	O
expeditiously	O
cures	O
Deafness	O
,	O
and	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
Ears	O
in	O
any	O
,	O
of	O
what	O
Age	O
soever	O
,	O
if	O
curable	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
first	O
sight	O
,	O
by	O
Inspection	O
,	O
resolves	O
the	O
Patient	O
if	O
so	O
or	O
not	O
;	O
as	O
most	O
eminent	O
Persons	O
of	O
Quality	O
can	O
testifie	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
Remedies	O
ready	O
prepared	O
for	O
the	O
Preservation	O
of	O
the	O
Hearing	O
,	O
in	O
those	O
who	O
through	O
some	O
great	O
Defects	O
in	O
the	O
sounding	O
Membrane	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Impediments	O
in	O
the	O
auditory	O
Passages	O
,	O
are	O
not	O
perfectly	O
curable	O
;	O
which	O
Remedies	O
preserve	O
them	O
from	O
ever	O
growing	O
worse	O
,	O
and	O
improves	O
their	O
Hearing	O
to	O
old	O
Age	O
.	O
He	O
hath	O
likewise	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Gargarism	O
,	O
or	O
Mouth-Water	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
make	O
black	O
or	O
yellow	O
Teeth	O
as	O
white	O
as	O
Ivory	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
times	O
using	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
will	O
certainly	O
cure	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
Diseases	O
incident	O
to	O
the	O
Mouth	O
,	O
Teeth	O
,	O
and	O
Gums	O
.	O
The	O
Glasses	O
are	O
of	O
several	O
Prices	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
.	O
His	O
Pills	O
only	O
prepared	O
for	O
the	O
French	O
Disease	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
running	O
of	O
the	O
Reins	O
,	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
in	O
Boxes	O
of	O
several	O
Prices	O
with	O
other	O
Venereal	O
Arcanaes	O
,	O
as	O
occasion	O
requires	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
.	O
His	O
Diet-Drink	O
cleanses	O
the	O
Reins	O
,	O
provokes	O
Urine	O
,	O
and	O
abates	O
the	O
sharp	O
Pains	O
or	O
Stoppage	O
of	O
Urine	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
running	O
of	O
the	O
Reins	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Bottle	O
.	O
B.	O
Lilburn	O
,	O
that	O
formerly	O
Lived	O
on	O
Ludgate-hill	O
,	O
next	O
to	O
the	O
Kings-Arms	O
Tavern	O
near	O
Fleet-Bridge	O
,	O
now	O
lives	O
at	O
the	O
Golden-Board	O
,	O
and	O
Ball	O
,	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
Ship	O
Court	O
,	O
up	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Great	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
near	O
Ludgate-hill	O
.	O
Who	O
maketh	O
and	O
selleth	O
,	O
(	O
and	O
has	O
done	O
above	O
20	O
Years	O
)	O
the	O
Water	O
for	O
taking	O
away	O
the	O
Freckels	O
,	O
Pimple	O
,	O
Worms	O
,	O
Morphew	O
,	O
and	O
red	O
Marks	O
of	O
the	O
Small-pox	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
:	O
With	O
Elixir	O
Salutis	O
,	O
Balsamum	O
Vita	O
,	O
Tinctura	O
Vita	O
.	O
Waters	O
and	O
Ointments	O
for	O
the	O
Eyes	O
,	O
Powders	O
,	O
Dentrifices	O
,	O
Elixirs	O
,	O
Essences	O
,	O
Oils	O
,	O
Spirits	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
both	O
for	O
Ornament	O
,	O
and	O
Curing	O
all	O
Diseases	O
incident	O
to	O
Humane	O
Bodies	O
;	O
but	O
more	O
especially	O
relating	O
to	O
the	O
Female	O
Sex	O
,	O
likewise	O
Judgment	O
upon	O
Urine	O
.	O
The	O
Anti-scorbutick	O
Pills	O
,	O
price	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Box	O
.	O
The	O
Elixir	O
for	O
the	O
Collick	O
,	O
and	O
Gripes	O
,	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Bottle	O
.	O
The	O
Ointment	O
for	O
sore	O
Nipples	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Piles	O
,	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Pot	O
.	O
An	O
Ointment	O
for	O
Redness	O
,	O
Pustules	O
,	O
Heat	O
,	O
Scabs	O
,	O
Ring-worms	O
,	O
Titters	O
,	O
Itch	O
or	O
breaking	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
where	O
,	O
price	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Pot	O
.	O
The	O
Ointment	O
for	O
Aches	O
,	O
and	O
Strains	O
,	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Pot	O
.	O
The	O
Water	O
for	O
the	O
Freckles	O
,	O
Pimples	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Author	O
has	O
for	O
some	O
Years	O
past	O
,	O
left	O
with	O
several	O
for	O
Sale	O
;	O
who	O
now	O
doth	O
understand	O
,	O
they	O
have	O
been	O
abused	O
by	O
Counterfeits	O
;	O
which	O
to	O
prevent	O
for	O
the	O
future	O
,	O
doth	O
desire	O
those	O
that	O
have	O
bought	O
from	O
them	O
-	O
and	O
not	O
found	O
the	O
Effect-answer	O
the	O
Ends	O
for	O
which	O
it	O
is	O
proposed	O
,	O
to	O
acquaint	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
they	O
bought	O
it	O
-	O
and	O
likewise	O
to	O
take	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
Seal	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
The	O
3	O
Water-budgets	O
,	O
and	O
B.	O
L.	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
Seal	O
.	O
The	O
Price	O
of	O
the	O
half	O
Pint-bottle	O
3	O
s.	O
That	O
you	O
be	O
not	O
imposed	O
on	O
,	O
be	O
sure	O
remember	O
her	O
Name	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
formerly	O
lived	O
on	O
Ludgate-hill	O
.	O
