TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
Queen	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
First	O
and	O
Second	O
Days	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
1704	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
Third	O
Year	O
of	O
Her	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
and	O
Goal-delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
the	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
on	O
Thursday	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
First	O
and	O
Second	O
Days	O
of	O
June	O
1704.	O
before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
Lathiel	B-pers
Lovel	I-pers
Knight	O
,	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
of	O
Her	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
are	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Proctor	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Seawell	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hoskins	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Lamb	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Symonds	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Swan	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Littlebury	I-pers
,	O
Humphry	B-pers
Thayr	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Stables	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Norris	I-pers
,	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Niccolls	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Wingfield	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Awsiter	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Halsey	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Lord	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Rowe	I-pers
,	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
Brune	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
,	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Sheet	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pillowber	O
,	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Stanton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Laced	O
Muslin	O
Head-Cloaths	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
opened	O
the	O
Hatch	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
them	O
into	O
her	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
her	O
way	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
askt	O
her	O
who	O
she	O
would	O
speak	O
withal	O
?	O
And	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
spake	O
with	O
a	O
Woman	O
that	O
work	O
'd	O
for	O
my	O
Lady	O
Goreing	O
;	O
but	O
mistrusting	O
her	O
,	O
took	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
Parlour	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
denyed	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
ever	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
appeared	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
having	O
their	O
Goods	O
again	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susan	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Christophers	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
3	O
Gold-Rings	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Prittyman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
miss	O
'd	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
,	O
confest	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
make	O
satisfaction	O
for	O
them	O
:	O
Upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
she	O
denyed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
them	O
sweeping	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
steal	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
call	O
any	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Hutchins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Christ-Church	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
four	O
Buck-skins	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bodington	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
they	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Shammey-Skins	O
for	O
the	O
Lining	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
whilst	O
he	O
was	O
busie	O
showing	O
them	O
some	O
,	O
one	O
them	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
together	O
;	O
but	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
a	O
stranger	O
saw	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
under	O
Miller	O
's	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
who	O
mistrusting	O
them	O
,	O
gave	O
notice	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
told	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
he	O
pursued	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Skins	O
upon	O
Miller	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
of	O
them	O
Confederates	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
call	O
any	O
to	O
their	O
Reputations	O
:	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Creed-Church	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Bodice	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Kade	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Bodice	O
,	O
and	O
whilst	O
his	O
Back	O
was	O
tnrnep	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
at	O
the	O
George	O
in	O
Camomile-street	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
denyed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
she	O
met	O
with	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
,	O
who	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
call	O
any	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
and	I-place
Agnes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
11	O
Yards	O
of	O
Bone-Lace	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
And	O
the	O
second	O
for	O
privately	O
26	O
Yards	O
of	O
Bone-Lace	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Lace-Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
cheapned	O
Lace	O
of	O
divers	O
People	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
mistrusted	O
,	O
they	O
followed	O
her	O
down	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
searching	O
her	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
denyed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
given	O
her	O
to	O
carry	O
by	O
one	O
Sarah	B-pers
Collet	I-pers
;	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
call	O
any	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
having	O
their	O
Goods	O
again	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Sir	I-pers
Robert	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pauls	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
upon	O
four	O
Indictments	O
,	O
for	O
Burglary	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Ham	O
of	O
Bacon	O
,	O
5	O
Bottles	O
of	O
Cyder	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Papers	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
;	O
the	O
second	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Gibbs	I-pers
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
8	O
Indian	O
Curtains	O
,	O
4	O
Vallens	O
,	O
a	O
Squab	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
;	O
the	O
third	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Farmer	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
5	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
Huckaback	O
Table-Cloath	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Sword	O
;	O
the	O
fourth	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Christian	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Cheshire	O
Cheese	O
,	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
pound	O
of	O
Sugar-Cakes	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
first	O
Indictment	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
and	O
his	O
Goods	O
gone	O
;	O
but	O
hearing	O
that	O
some	O
Men	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
went	O
,	O
where	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
it	O
was	O
marked	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidencewas	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
going	O
off	O
the	O
Watch	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
some	O
others	O
coming	O
along	O
,	O
much	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
and	O
seized	O
him	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
when	O
he	O
broke	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
broke	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Cellar-Door	O
with	O
a	O
Betty	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Ham	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
He	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
Married	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
it	O
for	O
his	O
Wedding	O
Dinner	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
second	O
Indictment	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Sash-Window	O
who	O
left	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Gang	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
handed	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
they	O
carried	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
third	O
Indictment	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
broke	O
a	O
Hole	O
over	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Good	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Kitchen	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
Th	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
with	O
a	O
Betty	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
ried	O
them	O
to	O
Armseed	O
Clear	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
Her	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
Cheese	O
,	O
Brandy	O
,	O
and	O
Sugar	O
Cakes	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
being	O
in	O
Drink	O
they	O
made	O
every	O
one	O
drink	O
Brandy	O
and	O
Cyder	O
as	O
they	O
met	O
,	O
till	O
they	O
were	O
stopt	O
by	O
the	O
Constable	O
.	O
He	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
these	O
matters	O
,	O
neither	O
did	O
he	O
know	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
:	O
which	O
being	O
utterly	O
false	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
call	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
Indictments	O
for	O
Burglary	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
to	O
the	O
second	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Augustin	B-pers
alias	I-pers
Sebastian	I-pers
Rice	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
for	O
Burglary	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Luke	B-pers
Sapsford	I-pers
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
second	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Abbot	I-pers
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
25	O
dozen	O
of	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
a	O
Hood	O
and	O
Scarf	O
,	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
;	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
first	O
Indictment	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
;	O
and	O
other	O
Evidences	O
were	O
the	O
Constable	O
and	O
a	O
Watch-man	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
seeing	O
a	O
Light	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Cellar	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
the	O
House	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
People	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
cryed	O
out	O
Thieves	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
a	O
sudden	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
cockt	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Constable	O
's	O
Breast	O
,	O
who	O
struggling	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
fired	O
it	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
mist	O
the	O
Constable	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
firing	O
again	O
,	O
shot	O
the	O
Constable	O
through	O
the	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Watch	O
man	O
into	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
that	O
means	O
they	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
their	O
Hats	O
behind	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Persons	O
,	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
with	O
a	O
Betty	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
other	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
gone	O
for	O
an	O
Hour	O
they	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
fired	O
at	O
the	O
Watch-man	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
killed	O
him	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
he	O
had	O
disappointed	O
them	O
of	O
their	O
Robbery	O
:	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
second	O
Indictment	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
that	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Goods	O
gone	O
.	O
But	O
one	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
gave	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Person	O
,	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
with	O
a	O
Betty	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
other	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Gate-house	O
through	O
a	O
Wall	O
four	O
Foot	O
thick	O
.	O
He	O
denyed	O
both	O
the	O
Facts	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
He	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
:	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
call	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold-Ring	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Buckles	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
sometime	O
she	O
desired	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
small	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
showing	O
her	O
some	O
,	O
she	O
conveyed	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
missing	O
it	O
,	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
but	O
presently	O
fetcht	O
her	O
back	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
denyed	O
it	O
stoutly	O
at	O
the	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
be	O
searcht	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
remembring	O
she	O
had	O
laid	O
her	O
Riding-hood	O
upon	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
searcht	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
between	O
the	O
Lining	O
found	O
the	O
Ring	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
having	O
his	O
Goods	O
again	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Good	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
Anthony	B-pers
Bighton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
drawing	O
a	O
Near-Wheel	O
of	O
a	O
Coach	O
hover	O
the	O
Breast	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
Died	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
by	O
Accident	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
divers	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
to	O
prevent	O
it	O
by	O
pulling	O
back	O
the	O
Horses	O
Reigns	O
;	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Jeremy	B-pers
Barret	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Hanwell	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Pound	O
Weight	O
of	O
Loaf-Sugar	O
,	O
4	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Nutmegs	O
,	O
and	O
18	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wats	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Shop	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
at	O
Brentfort-Market	B-place
,	O
and	O
his	O
Good	O
gone	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
afterwards	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
who	O
confest	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Warters	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Pines	I-pers
and	O
Martha	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
White-Chappel	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
15	O
Yards	O
of	O
Muslin	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Hinton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
2d	O
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
2	O
Silk	O
and	O
Cotton	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Ell	O
of	O
Muslin	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Burgon	I-pers
;	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
first	O
Indictment	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Muslin	O
,	O
and	O
whilst	O
he	O
was	O
buisy	O
they	O
conveyed	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
put	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
any	O
thing	O
:	O
But	O
sometime	O
after	O
hearing	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
being	O
brought	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
on	O
Warters	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Watson	O
guilty	O
to	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
second	O
Indictment	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
Watson	O
and	O
another	O
Person	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Muslin	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
Warters	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
hovering	O
about	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
afterwards	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
when	O
taken	O
they	O
both	O
denyed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
call	O
any	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
;	O
and	O
Warters	O
being	O
an	O
Old	O
Offender	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
,	O
and	O
Watson	O
only	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Warters	O
:	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Watson	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Carr	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolphs	I-place
without	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
bright	O
Bay	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
from	O
Mile-End	B-place
,	O
which	O
was	O
afterwards	O
found	O
sold	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
in	O
Yorkshire	O
for	O
50	O
s.	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
disown	O
he	O
sold	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
his	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
could	O
prove	O
the	O
truth	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
so	O
far	O
off	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
them	O
on	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	I-pers
alis	I-pers
Cavenanah	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Head-Cloaths	O
,	O
a	O
brass	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
and	O
tinder	O
Box	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Suttleburgh	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
she	O
confest	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
her	O
first	O
fault	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
W	B-pers
-	I-pers
T	I-pers
-	I-pers
and	O
H	B-pers
-	I-pers
I	I-pers
-	I-pers
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Wisdemeaner	O
for	O
Cheating	O
the	O
late	O
King	B-pers
William	I-pers
of	O
divers	O
Summs	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
his	O
Duty	O
of	O
Excise	O
;	O
for	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
T.	O
being	O
a	O
Sworn	O
Officer	O
,	O
and	O
Ganger	O
,	O
did	O
contrary	O
to	O
his	O
Oath	O
and	O
Trust	O
reposed	O
in	O
him	O
combine	O
with	O
the	O
said	O
I	O
-	O
who	O
was	O
Clerke	O
of	O
a	O
Brewhouse	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
one	O
Prisca	B-pers
Coberns	I-pers
Widdow	O
at	O
Bromley	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
they	O
did	O
conceal	O
divers	O
quantities	O
of	O
Strong	O
and	O
Small	O
Beer	O
,	O
particularly	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
August	O
1700	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
Brewed	O
30	O
Barrels	O
of	O
strong	O
Beer	O
and	O
8	O
of	O
small	O
,	O
which	O
account	O
was	O
never	O
returned	O
into	O
the	O
Excise	O
Office	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
November	O
following	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
Brewed	O
30	O
Barrels	O
more	O
of	O
strong	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
7	O
of	O
small	O
,	O
which	O
Monies	O
they	O
shared	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
account	O
thereof	O
given	O
to	O
the	O
Excise	O
Office	O
;	O
All	O
which	O
Fact	O
was	O
proved	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Misdemeaner	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
Stealing	O
an	O
Alamode	O
Hood	O
,	O
and	O
Scarfe	O
,	O
4	O
Sheets	O
,	O
3	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
8	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Nurse	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
both	O
Sick	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
her	O
opportunity	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
give	O
any	O
account	O
why	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
without	O
leave	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
was	O
,	O
indicted	O
for	O
secretly	O
taking	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Golding	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
late	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
Temple-Bar	B-place
a	O
Watchman	O
run	O
him	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
his	O
Watch	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
but	O
giving	O
notice	O
to	O
the	O
Brokers	O
if	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
should	O
come	O
to	O
their	O
hands	O
they	O
should	O
send	O
for	O
him	O
and	O
accordingly	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
Pawned	O
in	O
Drury	O
Lane	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
one	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
who	O
was	O
his	O
Brother	O
Soldiers	O
Wife	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeaner	O
for	O
Dropping	O
a	O
Child	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pancras	I-place
Soper-Lane	I-place
,	O
whereby	O
it	O
became	O
Chargeable	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Parish	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
against	O
her	O
was	O
not	O
full	O
enough	O
to	O
Convict	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Walters	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
Queen	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
House	O
by	O
Charing-Cross	B-place
,	O
and	O
she	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
pickt	O
his	O
Pockt	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
give	O
him	O
his	O
Money	O
again	O
;	O
which	O
she	O
denyed	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
If	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
taken	O
her	O
up	O
all	O
this	O
while	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Kilby	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepny	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
2000	O
l.	O
weight	O
of	O
Hemp	O
,	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Kilby	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Rachel	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Whitechappel	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
15	O
Yards	O
of	O
Muslin	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Hinton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
second	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
two	O
Silk	O
and	O
Cotten	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Burgon	I-pers
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
on	O
both	O
the	O
Indictments	O
to	O
prove	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
on	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
,	O
was	O
a	O
fifth	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Arins	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
One	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
60	O
Yards	O
of	O
Crape	O
,	O
92	O
Yards	O
of	O
Serge	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
was	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Voyden	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
House	O
broke	O
open	O
upon	O
a	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
it	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
He	O
did	O
never	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
nor	O
was	O
never	O
there	O
,	O
which	O
appeared	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Burglary	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Tryal	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Furlong	I-pers
,	O
for	O
being	O
a	O
Romish	O
Priest	O
,	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Freeholders	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
were	O
Impanelled	O
,	O
whose	O
Names	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Child	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Leades	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Sherbrooke	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Dry	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Greenaway	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Emes	I-pers
,	O
Ezekiel	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
Roger	B-pers
Mott	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
Caleb	B-pers
Hooke	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Rider	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Micklethwaite	I-pers
.	O
Peter	O
Furlong	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
;	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
born	O
within	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Dominions	O
,	O
did	O
become	O
a	O
Seminary	O
Priest	O
,	O
and	O
voluntarily	O
did	O
reconcile	O
himself	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
See	O
of	O
Rome	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
but	O
one	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
knew	O
him	O
at	O
Cadiz	O
in	O
Spain	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
reputed	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Priest	O
,	O
but	O
declared	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
officiate	O
such	O
an	O
Office	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
always	O
accounted	O
for	O
such	O
a	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
born	O
:	O
So	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
insufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
H	B-pers
-	I-pers
C	I-pers
-	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
Jeremy	B-pers
Maccarty	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Breast	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
dyed	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
appeared	O
only	O
to	O
be	O
Manslaughter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
thereto	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Betty	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Cullender	O
,	O
2	O
Basons	O
,	O
21	O
Dishes	O
,	O
5	O
Sconces	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Katharine	B-pers
Bushell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
he	O
stole	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
alledged	O
that	O
coming	O
to	O
fetch	O
his	O
Linnen	O
from	O
Washing	O
,	O
they	O
seized	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Donglas	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Rape	O
committed	O
on	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
one	O
Martha	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
Spinster	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
:	O
But	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Rape	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolphs	I-place
without	I-place
Algate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
11	O
Neats	O
Tongues	O
,	O
10	O
l.	O
of	O
Pork	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
our	O
Soveraign	O
Lady	O
the	O
Queen	B-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
Her	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
calling	O
divers	O
People	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Slayman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Bonner	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
second	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
Queen	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
could	O
prove	O
they	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hewit	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Greencourt	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepny	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
Ann	B-pers
Abbot	I-pers
an	O
Infant	O
under	O
the	O
Age	O
of	O
6	O
Years	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Gold	O
Chain	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Kilby	I-pers
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
that	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
alledging	O
that	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
had	O
a	O
Grudge	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Ivry	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Mark	B-pers
Silvesterr	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Gabriel	B-pers
Loach	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
9	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Callico	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
;	O
and	O
crying	O
out	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
he	O
flung	O
into	O
a	O
Window	O
to	O
further	O
his	O
escape	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
none	O
could	O
say	O
he	O
broke	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
Twilight	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Deale	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
9	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
4	O
yards	O
of	O
Broad-Cloath	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Stuff-Gown	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Derow	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
,	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
given	O
her	O
by	O
another	O
Person	O
;	O
which	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
:	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
to	O
the	O
Burglary	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Betts	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Luke	B-pers
Mathews	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
second	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
Queen	O
,	O
about	O
8	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Portmantua-Trunk	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Phlip	B-pers
Prince	I-pers
of	I-pers
Hesse	I-pers
Cassell	I-pers
,	O
and	O
24	O
Shirts	O
,	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
a	O
Cane	O
with	O
a	O
Gold-Head	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jordan	B-pers
Bedaw	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
concerned	O
with	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
coming	O
by	O
chance	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
forced	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
some	O
Money	O
to	O
conceal	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Lowe	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Dr.	O
Cornelius	B-pers
a	I-pers
Tilburgh	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Holland-Sheet	O
,	O
4	O
Callico	O
Curtains	O
,	O
a	O
pairs	O
of	O
Vallence	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Watch-men	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
there	O
was	O
three	O
Persons	O
,	O
who	O
they	O
mistrusted	O
to	O
be	O
Thieves	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
followed	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Thieves	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
fired	O
off	O
a	O
Pistol	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
just	O
grazed	O
his	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
an	O
Alley	O
(	O
while	O
the	O
other	O
Watchman	O
was	O
pursuing	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
who	O
dropt	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
andmade	O
their	O
escape	O
)	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
drawn	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
prevented	O
by	O
some	O
other	O
Watch-men	O
of	O
another	O
Parish	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Assistance	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
to	O
fix	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
to	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
and	O
nothing	O
being	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
when	O
taken	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Judith	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Farrel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Fosset	I-pers
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Day	O
time	O
,	O
no	O
Person	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
3	O
Holland-Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
Farrell	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
nothing	O
upon	O
Brown	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
to	O
the	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
Farrel	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
3	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Hunter	O
,	O
Augustin	O
alias	O
Silvester	O
Rice	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	O
Warters	O
,	O
alias	O
Pines	O
.	O
Christopher	O
Hibbert	O
,	O
was	O
respited	O
,	O
being	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
till	O
further	O
Order	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
left	O
Cheek	O
8	O
.	O
Susanah	O
Davis	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Fox	O
,	O
Ann	O
Hutchings	O
,	O
Samuel	O
Kilby	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Miller	O
,	O
Mark	O
Silvester	O
,	O
Mary	O
White	O
,	O
and	O
Martha	O
Watson	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
8	O
.	O
Jeremy	O
Barret	O
,	O
Mary	O
Burnet	O
,	O
Mary	O
Brown	O
,	O
Mary	O
Dean	O
,	O
Jane	O
Eglestone	O
,	O
Mary	O
Farrel	O
,	O
Ann	O
Jones	O
,	O
and	O
John	O
Smith	O
.	O
W	O
-	O
T	O
-	O
Fined	O
200	O
l.	O
and	O
to	O
lie	O
in	O
Prison	O
for	O
three	O
Months	O
without	O
Bail	O
or	O
Mainprize	O
.	O
H	O
-	O
J	O
-	O
Fined	O
100	O
l.	O
and	O
to	O
lie	O
in	O
Prison	O
for	O
three	O
Months	O
without	O
Bail	O
or	O
Mainprize	O
.	O
Mary	O
Warters	O
pleaded	O
her	O
Belly	O
,	O
saying	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
Child	O
and	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
being	O
Impanelled	O
found	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
with	O
quick	O
Child	O
.	O
After	O
which	O
32	O
Condemned	O
Criminals	O
pleaded	O
her	O
Majesties	O
most	O
Gracious	O
Pardon	O
on	O
their	O
Knees	O
,	O
some	O
on	O
Condition	O
never	O
to	O
return	O
into	O
her	O
Majesties	O
Realms	O
during	O
their	O
Lives	O
.	O
Others	O
on	O
Condition	O
to	O
transport	O
themselves	O
into	O
America	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
to	O
come	O
into	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
during	O
the	O
term	O
of	O
Seven	O
years	O
,	O
on	O
forfeiture	O
of	O
their	O
Lives	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
to	O
go	O
as	O
Soldiers	O
into	O
Her	O
Majesties	O
Service	O
beyond	O
the	O
Seas	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
to	O
remain	O
for	O
the	O
term	O
of	O
7	O
years	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
ALL	O
Persons	O
Distemper	O
'd	O
in	O
Mind	O
by	O
Melantholy	O
,	O
or	O
Despair	O
,	O
from	O
what	O
Cause	O
soever	O
,	O
are	O
with	O
God	O
's	O
blessing	O
,	O
speedily	O
Cured	O
,	O
if	O
curable	O
(	O
with	O
the	O
most	O
kind	O
and	O
tender	O
Usage	O
,	O
allowing	O
them	O
sufficient	O
Diet	O
,	O
careful	O
Attendance	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
Other	O
comfortable	O
Accommodation	O
)	O
by	O
a	O
Physician	O
of	O
long	O
Practice	O
and	O
great	O
Experience	O
in	O
those	O
Deplorable	O
Cases	O
.	O
Living	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
Shadwell-Coffee-House	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
Church	O
and	O
Market	O
,	O
in	O
Upper-Shadwell	O
,	O
near	O
London	O
.	O
Who	O
also	O
Cures	O
any	O
kind	O
of	O
Fits	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
strange	O
impressions	O
of	O
Dread	O
and	O
Terror	O
of	O
Mind	O
;	O
also	O
Pains	O
and	O
Lameness	O
of	O
the	O
Limbs	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
useless	O
and	O
Bedrid	O
.	O
W.	O
Elmy	O
,	O
Professor	O
of	O
Physick	O
and	O
Operator	O
,	O
of	O
known	O
Integrity	O
,	O
Liveth	O
at	O
the	O
Blue-ball	O
,	O
in	O
Whale-bone	O
Court	O
;	O
the	O
lower	O
end	O
of	O
Bartholomew-lane	O
by	O
the	O
Royal-Exchange	O
.	O
WHO	O
most	O
safely	O
and	O
expeditiously	O
cures	O
Deafness	O
and	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
Ears	O
in	O
any	O
,	O
of	O
what	O
Age	O
soever	O
,	O
if	O
curable	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
first	O
fight	O
,	O
by	O
Inspection	O
,	O
resolves	O
the	O
Patient	O
if	O
so	O
or	O
not	O
;	O
as	O
most	O
eminent	O
Persons	O
of	O
Quality	O
can	O
testifie	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
Remedies	O
ready	O
prepared	O
for	O
the	O
Preservation	O
of	O
the	O
Hearing	O
,	O
in	O
those	O
who	O
thought	O
some	O
great	O
Defects	O
in	O
the	O
founding	O
Membrane	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Impediments	O
in	O
the	O
anditory	O
Passages	O
,	O
are	O
not	O
perfectly	O
curable	O
;	O
which	O
Remedies	O
preserve	O
them	O
for	O
ever	O
growing	O
worse	O
,	O
and	O
improves	O
their	O
Hearing	O
to	O
old	O
Age	O
.	O
He	O
hath	O
likewise	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Garganism	O
,	O
or	O
Mouth-Water	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
make	O
black	O
or	O
yellow	O
Teeth	O
as	O
white	O
as	O
Ivory	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
times	O
using	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
will	O
certainly	O
cure	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
Diseases	O
incident	O
to	O
the	O
Mouth	O
,	O
Teeth	O
,	O
and	O
Gums	O
.	O
The	O
Glasses	O
are	O
of	O
several	O
Prices	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
.	O
His	O
Pills	O
only	O
prepared	O
for	O
the	O
French	O
Disease	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
running	O
of	O
the	O
Reins	O
,	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
in	O
boxes	O
of	O
several	O
Prices	O
with	O
other	O
Venereal	O
Arcanaes	O
,	O
as	O
occasion	O
requires	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
.	O
His	O
Diet-Drink	O
cleanses	O
the	O
Reins	O
,	O
provokes	O
Urine	O
,	O
and	O
abates	O
the	O
sharp	O
Pains	O
or	O
Stoppage	O
of	O
Urine	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
running	O
of	O
the	O
Reins	O
,	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Bottle	O
.	O
B.	O
Lilburn	O
,	O
that	O
formerly	O
Lived	O
on	O
Ludgate-hill	O
,	O
next	O
to	O
the	O
Kings-Arms	O
Tavern	O
near	O
Fleet-bridge	O
,	O
-	O
Now	O
lives	O
at	O
the	O
Golden-Board	O
and	O
Ball	O
,	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
Ship-Court	O
,	O
up	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Great	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
near	O
Ludgate	O
hill	O
,	O
Who	O
maketh	O
and	O
selleth	O
,	O
(	O
and	O
has	O
done	O
above	O
20	O
Years	O
)	O
-	O
The	O
Water	O
for	O
taking	O
away	O
the	O
Freckles	O
,	O
Pimples	O
,	O
Worms	O
,	O
Morphew	O
,	O
and	O
red	O
Marks	O
of	O
the	O
Small-pox	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
:	O
With	O
Elixir	O
Salutis	O
,	O
Bilsamuan	O
Vite	O
,	O
Tinctura	O
Vita	O
.	O
Waters	O
and	O
Ointments	O
for	O
the	O
Eyes	O
,	O
Powders	O
,	O
Dentrifices	O
,	O
Elixirs	O
,	O
Essences	O
,	O
Oils	O
,	O
Spirits	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
both	O
for	O
Ornament	O
,	O
and	O
Curing	O
all	O
Diseases	O
incident	O
to	O
Humane	O
Bodies	O
;	O
but	O
more	O
especially	O
relating	O
to	O
the	O
Female	O
Sex	O
.	O
-	O
Likewise	O
Judgment	O
upon	O
Urine	O
.	O
The	O
Anti-scorbutick	O
Pills	O
,	O
price	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Box	O
.	O
The	O
Elixir	O
for	O
the	O
Collick	O
,	O
and	O
Gripes	O
,	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Bottle	O
.	O
The	O
Ointment	O
for	O
fore	O
Niples	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Piles	O
,	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Pot	O
.	O
An	O
Ointment	O
for	O
Redness	O
,	O
Pustules	O
,	O
Heat	O
,	O
Scabs	O
,	O
Ringworms	O
,	O
Titters	O
,	O
Itch	O
or	O
breaking	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
or	O
elsewhere	O
;	O
price	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Pot	O
.	O
The	O
Ointment	O
for	O
Aches	O
,	O
and	O
Strains	O
,	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Pot	O
.	O
The	O
Water	O
for	O
the	O
Freckles	O
,	O
Pimples	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Author	O
has	O
for	O
some	O
Years	O
past	O
,	O
left	O
with	O
several	O
for	O
Sale	O
;	O
who	O
now	O
doth	O
under	O
stand	O
,	O
they	O
have	O
been	O
abused	O
by	O
Counterfeits	O
;	O
which	O
to	O
prevent	O
for	O
the	O
future	O
,	O
doth	O
desire	O
those	O
that	O
have	O
bought	O
from	O
them	O
-	O
and	O
not	O
found	O
the	O
Effect	O
-	O
answer	O
the	O
Ends	O
for	O
which	O
it	O
is	O
proposed	O
,	O
to	O
acquaint	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
they	O
bought	O
it	O
-	O
and	O
likewise	O
to	O
take	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
Seal	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
The	O
3	O
Water-budgets	O
,	O
and	O
B.	O
L.	O
on	O
the	O
Top	O
of	O
the	O
Seal	O
.	O
The	O
Price	O
of	O
the	O
half	O
Pint-bottle	O
3	O
s.	O
That	O
you	O
be	O
not	O
imposed	O
on	O
,	O
be	O
sure	O
to	O
remember	O
her	O
Name	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
formerly	O
lived	O
on	O
Ludgate-hill	O
.	O
AN	O
Excellent	O
and	O
experienced	O
Remedy	O
,	O
for	O
Sore	O
and	O
Weak	O
Eyes	O
,	O
that	O
ever	O
yet	O
was	O
made	O
known	O
to	O
the	O
World	O
,	O
being	O
of	O
that	O
wonderful	O
Efficacy	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
insallibly	O
dispels	O
any	O
Humour	O
or	O
Salt	O
Rheum	O
distilling	O
from	O
the	O
Head	O
;	O
takes	O
away	O
all	O
Soreness	O
,	O
Redness	O
,	O
or	O
Swelling	O
:	O
It	O
also	O
mightily	O
Strengthens	O
weak	O
Eyes	O
,	O
(	O
sometimes	O
occasion	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
King's-Evil	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
Small-Pox	O
)	O
and	O
will	O
dis-Film	O
,	O
or	O
Cateract	O
growing	O
over	O
the	O
Eye	O
,	O
whereby	O
the	O
Sight	O
often-times	O
becomes	O
dim	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
times	O
using	O
this	O
excellent	O
Remedy	O
,	O
to	O
those	O
that	O
will	O
be	O
perswaded	O
to	O
use	O
it	O
often	O
,	O
it	O
will	O
(	O
by	O
Gods	O
Blessing	O
)	O
preserve	O
the	O
Sight	O
to	O
an	O
incredible	O
Age	O
,	O
and	O
read	O
even	O
the	O
smalled	O
Print	O
at	O
old	O
Age	O
.	O
This	O
being	O
an	O
incomparable	O
Secret	O
acquired	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
long	O
Study	O
,	O
whereby	O
he	O
has	O
wrought	O
wonderful	O
Cures	O
among	O
his	O
Relations	O
and	O
Acquaintance	O
;	O
and	O
now	O
made	O
publick	O
for	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
all	O
People	O
that	O
will	O
make	O
tryal	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
For	O
those	O
that	O
are	O
really	O
Poor	O
,	O
they	O
shall	O
have	O
it	O
Gratis	O
:	O
For	O
Others	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Bottle	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
had	O
only	O
by	O
the	O
Publisher	O
of	O
this	O
Paper	O
.	O
Whereas	O
the	O
Printer	O
being	O
at	O
a	O
great	O
Loss	O
by	O
Publishing	O
this	O
Sessions	O
Paper	O
at	O
2	O
d.	O
through	O
their	O
means	O
that	O
Sold	O
them	O
,	O
in	O
letting	O
Persons	O
read	O
them	O
for	O
a	O
Penny	O
,	O
therefore	O
all	O
Gentlemen	O
and	O
others	O
are	O
to	O
Note	O
,	O
that	O
from	O
hence	O
forwards	O
they	O
may	O
be	O
bad	O
for	O
the	O
Price	O
of	O
One	O
Penny	O
,	O
to	O
binder	O
so	O
great	O
Returns	O
unsold	O
as	O
have	O
heretofore	O
been	O
put	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
