TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
Queen	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
9th	O
,	O
10th	O
and	O
11th	O
Days	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
1703	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
Third	O
Year	O
of	O
Her	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
the	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
9th	O
,	O
10th	O
and	O
11th	O
Days	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
1703.	O
before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
Salathiel	B-pers
Lovel	I-pers
Knight	O
,	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
of	O
Her	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
are	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cannon	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Strange	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Burgis	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Clifton	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
,	O
Cornelius	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Boswell	I-pers
,	O
Andrew	B-pers
Dawling	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Yalding	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Bealing	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
Simon	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Meard	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Adshead	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Croker	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Giles	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Avis	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wisewall	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Nott	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Ashman	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
Bartholomews	I-place
by	I-place
the	I-place
Exchange	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silver-Porringer	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Spoons	O
,	O
from	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mander	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Robecca	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Pulham	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
13	O
Yards	O
of	O
printed	O
Callico	O
,	O
and	O
11	O
Yards	O
of	O
Muslin	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
Harvey	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
cheapened	O
some	O
Callico	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
their	O
opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
Pulham	O
,	O
who	O
waited	O
for	O
them	O
at	O
a	O
distance	O
off	O
;	O
but	O
pursuing	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
Pulham	O
,	O
who	O
denyed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
met	O
with	O
one	O
Jenny	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
,	O
who	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
six	O
pence	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Chequer-Inn	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
being	O
Confederates	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Alhallows	B-place
Staining	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
hundred	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Iron	O
from	O
Edward	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Merreday	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Merredeth	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margarets	I-place
Lothbury	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
19	O
Yards	O
of	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
and	O
28	O
Yards	O
of	O
Small	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
of	O
Nowell	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
afterwards	O
confest	O
.	O
It	O
being	O
the	O
first	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
it	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Mary	B-pers
Gill	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolphs	I-place
without	I-place
Algate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
28	O
l.	O
of	O
Malaga	O
Raisins	O
,	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stanley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
Mr.	O
Stanley	O
's	O
Goods	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
Ludgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Giblett	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Howfard	I-pers
.	O
The	O
first	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
going	O
under	O
Ludgate	B-place
with	O
the	O
Perriwig	O
in	O
a	O
Band-Box	O
he	O
was	O
thrust	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Wall	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
some	O
Persons	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
Wig	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
a	O
Constable	O
who	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
some	O
idle	O
Persons	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
at	O
first	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
from	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
into	O
St.	O
Clements	O
Church-yard	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
person	O
coming	O
by	O
,	O
struck	O
up	O
his	O
Heels	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
searching	O
him	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Perriwig	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
owned	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Howford	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
:	O
He	O
denyed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
He	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
;	O
whichwas	O
proved	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
something	O
in	O
drink	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
hold	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
taking	O
it	O
:	O
But	O
he	O
being	O
an	O
Idle	O
Fellow	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Boy	O
being	O
positive	O
;	O
besides	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
call	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
Peters	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Sword	O
with	O
a	O
Steel-Hilt	O
,	O
from	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Light	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
pursuing-him	O
,	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
that	O
means	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Sword	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
other	O
Evidences	O
who	O
heard	O
him	O
confess	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
Drink	O
who	O
quarrelled	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Sword	O
with	O
a	O
design	O
to	O
defend	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
to	O
steal	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
divers	O
People	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
his	O
first	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Ellinor	B-pers
Langston	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Banks	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Bothaw	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
2	O
Suits	O
of	O
Head-Cloths	O
,	O
a	O
Stuff-Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Cocks	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
afterwards	O
confest	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
sold	O
:	O
But	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
She	O
did	O
find	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
afterwards	O
sold	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
steal	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
call	O
any	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Steal-	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Candlesticks	O
and	O
Sconces	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
pieces	O
of	O
Plate	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
William	B-pers
Duke	I-pers
of	I-pers
Devonshire	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
Queen	O
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Duke	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
,	O
that	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
gone	O
home	O
with	O
his	O
Lady	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
Duke	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
left	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Duke	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Servants	O
being	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
the	O
Candles	O
behind	O
a	O
Door	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Defence	O
,	O
neither	O
could	O
he	O
call	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
Buttolphs	I-place
without	I-place
Algate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
the	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
William	I-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stayes	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
before	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
likely	O
to	O
be	O
overturned	O
,	O
looked	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
presently	O
mist	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ran	O
into	O
Burr-street	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
dropt	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
by	O
the	O
Coachman	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
his	O
Defence	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepny	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
one	O
Hugh	B-pers
Hartshorne	I-pers
,	O
senior	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Cloth-Coat	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Son	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Stepny	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
about	O
7	O
a	O
Clock	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Stanley	O
who	O
was	O
executed	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
past	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
them	O
Good	O
night	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
returned	O
back	O
and	O
seized	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
drew	O
their	O
Swords	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
prickt	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Breast	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
they	O
wanted	O
his	O
Watch	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
carried	O
him	O
cross	O
the	O
Fields	O
and	O
bound	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
Ditch	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
positive	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
called	O
to	O
Stanley	O
for	O
the	O
Tye-Strings	O
:	O
The	O
Boy	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
for	O
whilst	O
they	O
were	O
busie	O
in	O
binding	O
his	O
Father	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
from	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
very	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
no	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
call	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Robbery	O
.	O
Judith	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
,	O
no	O
Person	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Serge	O
Counterpaine	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutors	O
Wife	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
lockt	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Key	O
in	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
back	O
her	O
Door	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Goods	O
gone	O
.	O
But	O
other	O
Evidences	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
saw	O
her	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
with	O
something	O
in	O
her	O
Lap	O
,	O
and	O
mistrusting	O
her	O
,	O
saw	O
her	O
Drop	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
She	O
denyed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
She	O
was	O
never	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
in	O
all	O
her	O
Life	O
;	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
call	O
any	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
Magnus	I-place
New-Fishstreet	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth-Coat	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Greenfield	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
Coat	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
enquiry	O
,	O
heard	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
throw	O
an	O
Alley	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
pursued	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
dropt	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
denyed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
She	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appeared	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Edward	B-pers
Dutton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Christ-Church	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Cheshire-Cheese	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
Gloucestershire	O
Cheeses	O
,	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Child	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Porter	O
that	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
a	O
Basket	O
with	O
some	O
Straw	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
in	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
covered	O
them	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
his	O
first	O
Fault	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Querbo	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Twelves	I-pers
.	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Magnus	I-place
the	I-place
Martyr	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Bags	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Constable	I-pers
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
He	O
was	O
coming	O
over	O
London	B-place
Bridge	I-place
,	O
the	O
Bags	O
were	O
taken	O
off	O
his	O
Horse	O
from	O
behind	O
him	O
.	O
And	O
another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
denyed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
he	O
Stseet	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
false	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
call	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
Magdalen	I-place
Old	I-place
Fishstreet	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
4	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
from	O
Katherine	B-pers
Stanton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Taster	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
all	O
Night	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
confess	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
sold	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
.	O
Upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
he	O
owned	O
the	O
same	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
Sepulchers	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
,	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Sattin	O
Scarff	O
,	O
a	O
Hood	O
,	O
a	O
strip	O
'd	O
Sattin	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Davenport	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Penelope	B-pers
Davenport	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Stonystratford	O
,	O
where	O
being	O
taken	O
upon	O
suspicion	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
to	O
London	O
she	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
Upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
She	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidencewas	O
positive	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Squire	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
Sepulchers	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
4	O
Cloth-Coats	O
,	O
2	O
Wastcoats	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brookhurst	I-pers
,	O
and	O
5	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cloth	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Later	I-pers
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lord	I-pers
Ashburnham	I-pers
.	O
The	O
first	O
Evidence	O
was	O
a	O
Carrier	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
place	O
called	O
Riverhead	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Kent	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
put	O
into	O
a	O
Stable	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Rose-Inn	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
desired	O
by	O
a	O
Person	O
to	O
bring	O
them	O
to	O
London	O
to	O
sell	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
call	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Christ-Church	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
4	O
Yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Strip	O
'd	O
Kenting	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Stowel	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Strip	O
'd	O
Kenting	O
,	O
and	O
Robinson	O
took	O
her	O
opportunity	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
brought	O
back	O
,	O
pulled	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
them	O
upon	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
She	O
called	O
divers	O
People	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
her	O
first	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
having	O
his	O
Goods	O
again	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
And	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
proof	O
against	O
Bates	O
,	O
to	O
prove	O
she	O
was	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Worsted-Stockings	O
,	O
5	O
China	O
Cups	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
Dishes	O
,	O
a	O
Silver-Spoon	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Cap	O
of	O
a	O
Silver-Castor	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
behalf	O
,	O
but	O
called	O
some	O
People	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
her	O
Master	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
first	O
Fact	O
:	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Toothless	I-pers
Tom	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margarets-Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
,	I-pers
Bishop	I-pers
of	I-pers
Peterborow	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
8	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
the	O
Bishop	O
's	O
Episcopal	O
Robes	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Hair-Trnnk	O
,	O
4	O
Holland-Shirts	O
,	O
13	O
Guineas	O
and	O
40	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
given	O
orders	O
to	O
a	O
Taylor	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
a	O
Wastcoat	O
and	O
Breeches	O
of	O
a	O
Sheemar	O
that	O
was	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
other	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Wife	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
who	O
being	O
brought	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
her	O
Husband	O
then	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
clear	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
confest	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
he	O
expected	O
to	O
be	O
Hang	O
'd	O
between	O
Heaven	O
and	O
Earth	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
he	O
denyed	O
it	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
Wife	O
found	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
call	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
And	O
being	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Russe	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Woolridge	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Purse	O
,	O
two	O
Neckcloaths	O
,	O
a	O
Gold-Ring	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Hemings	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
not	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
to	O
convict	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Barrow	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolphs	I-place
without	I-place
Algate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Trevis	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Watch-man	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Left	O
Pap	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
dyed	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
his	O
Rounds	O
down	O
Rosemary-Lane	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Alley	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
who	O
he	O
suspected	O
to	O
be	O
loose	O
Persons	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
for	O
carrying	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
his	O
Sword	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
Woman	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
so	O
fast	O
as	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
a	O
sudden	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
snatch	O
this	O
Sword	O
from	O
under	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Arm	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
said	O
Wound	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
the	O
Sword	O
up	O
with	O
his	O
Hand	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
a	O
sudden	O
the	O
Deceased	O
cryed	O
out	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
Stuck	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
,	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
kill	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
pass	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
missed	O
his	O
Body	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
against	O
some	O
Pales	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Sword	O
was	O
bloody	O
by	O
reason	O
it	O
left	O
some	O
Blood	O
upon	O
his	O
Coat-Sleeve	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pulled	O
the	O
Sword	O
from	O
under	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
stuck	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
made	O
a	O
pass	O
at	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
knockt	O
him	O
down	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
was	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
probed	O
his	O
Wound	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Soldier	O
at	O
the	O
Tower-Guard	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Serjeant	O
gave	O
him	O
leave	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
see	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
but	O
going	O
up	O
Rosemary-Lane	O
had	O
occasion	O
to	O
untruss	O
a	O
Point	O
,	O
went	O
into	O
an	O
Alley	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Constable	O
found	O
him	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
his	O
Sword	O
when	O
he	O
demanded	O
it	O
:	O
He	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Watch-men	O
were	O
rude	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
several	O
Blows	O
and	O
Punches	O
with	O
their	O
Staves	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
dropt	O
the	O
Sword	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
snatch	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
Deceased	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
his	O
Sword	O
was	O
broke	O
before	O
he	O
met	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
produced	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
a	O
Sword	O
to	O
match	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
agree	O
together	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Constable	O
said	O
further	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
that	O
the	O
Sword	O
was	O
broke	O
after	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
Killed	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
made	O
his	O
pass	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Pales	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
say	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
sorry	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
killed	O
another	O
Watch-man	O
instead	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
.	O
All	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Murther	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bright	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
for	O
taking	O
a	O
Copper	O
from	O
the	O
Freehold	O
of	O
Pedingfield	B-pers
Higham	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
thatthe	O
Prisoner	O
offered	O
to	O
sell	O
t	O
,	O
but	O
mistrusting	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
Stole	O
,	O
he	O
seized	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
afterwards	O
confest	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Misdemeanor	O
.	O
Prudence	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
36	O
Yards	O
of	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Isabella	B-pers
Short	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Knot	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
positive	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Body	O
else	O
there	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
when	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
Though	O
she	O
denyed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
She	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
yet	O
was	O
was	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
George	B-pers
Mauson	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Munson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Kensington	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
about	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Cloth-Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Cloth-Wastcoat	O
,	O
a	O
Neckcloath	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Goods	O
removed	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
broke	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Forster	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
3	O
Serge	O
Curtains	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
strip	O
'd	O
Coat	O
,	O
from	O
Katherine	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
stole	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
a	O
Broker	O
.	O
Who	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Jones	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Pierce	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
12	O
Pewter-Plates	O
,	O
a	O
Pewter-Dish	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Pierce	O
,	O
And	O
the	O
second	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
3	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
Stuff-Petticoats	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
first	O
Indictment	O
,	O
was	O
not	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
a	O
single	O
Felony	O
;	O
only	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
upon	O
the	O
second	O
Indictment	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
committed	O
the	O
Fact	O
:	O
They	O
both	O
denyed	O
it	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
they	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
no	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
their	O
Reputations	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Stowell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
127	O
Yards	O
of	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
and	O
36	O
Yards	O
of	O
Edging	O
,	O
from	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Murford	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
afterwards	O
confest	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
denyed	O
it	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
:	O
But	O
it	O
appeared	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Tudor	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
her	O
Female	O
Infant	O
Bastard	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
throwing	O
the	O
same	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
,	O
whereby	O
it	O
was	O
choaked	O
and	O
strangled	O
.	O
She	O
called	O
a	O
Witness	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
Married	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
no	O
Bastard	O
.	O
She	O
further	O
called	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
she	O
communicated	O
the	O
matter	O
of	O
her	O
being	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
provided	O
things	O
fitting	O
for	O
her	O
Lying-in	O
:	O
They	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Dale	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Jasper	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Day-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
6	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
and	O
8	O
Napkins	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Goods	O
:	O
And	O
another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
committed	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
but	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Window	O
was	O
not	O
fast	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
take	O
out	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
together	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
her	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Light	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
a	O
Spoon	O
,	O
a	O
Salt	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Barbar	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Goods	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Maid	O
further	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
after	O
her	O
Master	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
he	O
telling	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Ring	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
of	O
her	O
:	O
Upon	O
which	O
she	O
consented	O
,	O
but	O
thinking	O
it	O
not	O
convenient	O
to	O
be	O
with	O
him	O
alone	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
call	O
another	O
of	O
the	O
Maids	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
away	O
.	O
He	O
denyed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
He	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
call	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
secretly	O
taking	O
a	O
Steel-Hilted	O
Sword	O
,	O
inlaid	O
with	O
Gold	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Cruis	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
third	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
St.	O
Clements	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
cross	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
mistrusting	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Ill	O
Man	O
,	O
heard	O
him	O
to	O
call	O
to	O
his	O
Accomplices	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
a	O
sudden	O
he	O
came	O
behind	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
but	O
pursuing	O
him	O
,	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
dropt	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
denyed	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
but	O
a	O
weak	O
excuse	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
secretly	O
taking	O
it	O
.	O
Arthur	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
Buttolphs	I-place
without	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
65	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Iron	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hickman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
kept	O
the	O
Cock-Inn	B-place
in	I-place
Aldersgate-street	I-place
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
a	O
Bar	O
of	O
Iron	O
,	O
but	O
pursuing	O
him	O
,	O
found	O
it	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
hired	O
by	O
a	O
Man	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Jane	B-pers
Lyne	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
Basishaw	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
her	O
Male	O
Infant	O
Bastard	O
,	O
by	O
throwing	O
it	O
into	O
an	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
,	O
whereby	O
it	O
was	O
strangled	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
perceiving	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
with-Child	O
,	O
askt	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Wife	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
Widow	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
she	O
looked	O
so	O
big	O
?	O
and	O
whether	O
she	O
was	O
with-Child	O
?	O
And	O
she	O
replyed	O
,	O
No	O
;	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
troubled	O
with	O
a	O
Timpany	O
and	O
Dropsie	O
.	O
Some	O
time	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
an	O
inquiry	O
whether	O
the	O
Vault	O
run	O
into	O
the	O
Common-Shore	O
?	O
saying	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
never	O
emptied	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
occasion	O
to	O
wash	O
some	O
Things	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
perceived	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
Lank	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
who	O
mistrusting	O
her	O
about	O
her	O
Words	O
about	O
the	O
Vault	O
,	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Child	O
wrapt	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Cloath	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
into	O
a	O
Lining	O
of	O
his	O
Sleeve	O
:	O
After	O
that	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
who	O
carried	O
her	O
that	O
Night	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
being	O
brought	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
owned	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
in	O
an	O
Error	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
kill	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
Still-born	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
other	O
Evidences	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
did	O
discover	O
something	O
of	O
such	O
Matters	O
when	O
she	O
washt	O
her	O
Linnen	O
;	O
and	O
also	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
she	O
lay	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
other	O
symptoms	O
discovered	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
delivered	O
there	O
:	O
And	O
other	O
Evidences	O
,	O
who	O
also	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
Milk	O
in	O
great	O
abundance	O
in	O
her	O
Breast	O
:	O
And	O
a	O
Midwife	O
declared	O
[	O
Pages	O
missing	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
