TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
Queen	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
,	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice	O
Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD	O
BAILEY	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
26th	O
,	O
27th	O
and	O
28th	O
Days	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
1704	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
Third	O
Year	O
of	O
Her	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
The	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Baily	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
26th	O
,	O
27th	O
,	O
and	O
28th	O
Days	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
1704	O
before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
PARSONS	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
Salathiel	B-pers
Lovell	I-pers
Knight	O
,	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
of	O
Her	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
are	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Hamond	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Chandler	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Chamberlin	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Grimstead	I-pers
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Puller	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Territ	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Creech	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dowell	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Hampton	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Munden	I-pers
,	O
Humphry	B-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Banister	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Wingfield	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Panner	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
How	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Twyford	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Nelson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Francklin	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
Katherine	I-place
Creedchurch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
Stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
from	O
Samuel	B-pers
Storey	I-pers
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Storey	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
said	O
25th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
six	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
six	O
Rings	O
set	O
with	O
Diamonds	O
,	O
a	O
Stone	O
Ring	O
,	O
a	O
5l	O
.	O
piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
fault	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Trenchfield	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
Peter	I-place
Le	I-place
Poor	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
12	O
pair	O
of	O
Blankets	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Rings	O
,	O
from	O
James	B-pers
Fordham	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
Mary	I-place
Bothaw	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
6	O
Broad	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
from	O
Samuel	B-pers
Tuckey	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
from	O
Jeremy	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Priscilla	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
Peter	I-place
Le	I-place
Poor	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
from	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Brightwell	I-pers
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
at	O
Westminster	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
alledging	O
her	O
Innocence	O
,	O
by	O
saying	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
gave	O
notice	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Daughter	O
that	O
her	O
Work	O
was	O
to	O
hard	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
therefore	O
go	O
away	O
;	O
The	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
Magdalen	I-place
Old	I-place
Fishstreet	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Wooden	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
5l	O
.	O
13s	O
.	O
and	O
6d	O
.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Villers	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Abel	I-pers
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
standing	O
at	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
waited	O
for	O
Mrs.	O
White	O
.	O
The	O
Porter	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
seeing	O
her	O
stand	O
,	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
would	O
fetch	O
her	O
a	O
Chair	O
;	O
which	O
she	O
refused	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
would	O
sit	O
upon	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Board	O
;	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
near	O
the	O
Money	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
a	O
sudden	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Box	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Porter	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
they	O
pursued	O
her	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Box	O
and	O
Money	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
Defence	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
Husband	O
,	O
who	O
made	O
her	O
sell	O
all	O
her	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
her	O
with	O
two	O
small	O
Children	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Digger	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Peter	I-place
Le	I-place
Poor	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
12	O
pair	O
of	O
Blankets	O
and	O
3	O
Rugs	O
from	O
James	B-pers
Fordham	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Sister	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
between	O
them	O
both	O
Conveyed	O
away	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
at	O
several	O
Places	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
got	O
most	O
of	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
her	O
defence	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Sister	O
gave	O
them	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
stolen	O
,	O
her	O
Sister	O
telling	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
her	O
Master	O
,	O
at	O
reasonable	O
rates	O
;	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Wiseman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
Buttolphs	I-place
without	I-place
Algate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Silver-Spoon	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
sell	O
him	O
a	O
Spoon	O
that	O
was	O
broke	O
;	O
but	O
mistrusting	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stoln	O
,	O
stopt	O
him	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
saying	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
Ditch	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
he	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
C-	B-pers
E-	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
5	O
Yards	O
and	O
a	O
Half	O
,	O
of	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
value	O
7s	O
.	O
and	O
8d	O
.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bussey	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
divers	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
her	O
Reputation	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
Giles	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Pewter-dish	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Flaxen	O
Napkin	O
,	O
from	O
Samuel	B-pers
Collerick	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
which	O
she	O
afterwards	O
confest	O
,	O
when	O
brought	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
,	O
she	O
also	O
own	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
first	O
Fact	O
;	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Field	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
36	O
Yards	O
of	O
Stuff	O
,	O
Value	O
30s	O
.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
[	I-pers
Text	I-pers
unreadable	I-pers
in	I-pers
original	I-pers
.	I-pers
]	I-pers
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Stuff	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
lay	O
upon	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
busie	O
,	O
she	O
conveyed	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
into	O
a	O
Joyners	O
Shop	O
,	O
telling	O
the	O
Joyner	O
's	O
Boy	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
was	O
following	O
her	O
to	O
beat	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
hide	O
her	O
self	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
persuing	O
her	O
,	O
there	O
she	O
dropt	O
the	O
Goods	O
behind	O
some	O
Deal-boards	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
,	O
she	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
saying	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
never	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
call	O
any	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4s	O
.	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Deverey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
Clement-Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Bag	O
and	O
ten	O
Pounds	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Rhodes	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
only	O
suspect	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
unlucky	O
Boy	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
being	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
alledging	O
his	O
Innocence	O
:	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
Catherine	I-place
Creedchurch	I-place
,	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
Royal	O
African	O
Company	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
7	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
6	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
6	O
Rings	O
,	O
set	O
with	O
Diamonds	O
,	O
a	O
Stone	O
Ring	O
,	O
a	O
5l	O
.	O
Piece	O
,	O
and	O
4l	O
.	O
5s	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Storey	I-pers
:	O
The	O
first	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
him	O
formerly	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
call	O
as	O
she	O
went	O
by	O
that	O
way	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
Mistress	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
that	O
Evening	O
there	O
,	O
being	O
no	O
body	O
at	O
home	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
convey	O
'd	O
away	O
the	O
Booty	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Evidence	O
was	O
the	O
Boy	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
standing	O
in	O
Leaden-hall	O
street	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
beckon	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
cold	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
upstairs	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
call	O
Tom	O
;	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
)	O
and	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Drink	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
consented	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
come	O
up	O
,	O
she	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
fetch	O
the	O
Drink	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
agreed	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Trunk	O
out	O
of	O
an	O
Inner	O
Room	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
double	O
lockt	O
,	O
and	O
lockt	O
the	O
same	O
again	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
coming	O
back	O
,	O
she	O
pretended	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
call	O
Tom	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
carried	O
off	O
the	O
Trunk	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
some	O
while	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
to	O
prevent	O
Discovery	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
other	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sent	O
the	O
5l	O
.	O
piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
to	O
be	O
pawn	O
'd	O
,	O
At	O
one	O
Congrell	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
Salt-Peter	O
Bank	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
only	O
saying	O
that	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
open	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Boy	O
upon	O
Tryal	O
,	O
declar	O
'd	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
Day-light	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
her	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Cray	B-pers
Mook	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
Magnus	I-place
the	I-place
Martyr	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
2	O
Pewter-Plates	O
,	O
a	O
Holland-shift	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Weston	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
relieve	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
taking	O
her	O
Opportunity	O
at	O
times	O
,	O
conveyed	O
away	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
offering	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
Spoon	O
to	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
,	O
near	O
Exeter-Exchange	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
stopt	O
,	O
and	O
confes	O
'd	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Lodgings	O
when	O
search	O
'd	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
Defence	O
,	O
nor	O
could	O
call	O
any	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
carrying	O
away	O
192	O
Yards	O
of	O
Shalloon	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Roger	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
H-	B-pers
J-	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
taking	O
away	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Womens	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
of	O
Mens	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hanwell	I-pers
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Peter	B-pers
Bulkley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
4	O
Yards	O
of	O
Callico	O
,	O
from	O
Joseph	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Walters	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
7	O
Fustian	O
Froks	O
,	O
3	O
Cloath-Coats	O
,	O
a	O
Drugget-Coat	O
,	O
2	O
Pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
those	O
Highway-men	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
taken	O
at	O
the	O
Bear-Inn	O
in	O
Basinghall-street	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Gold-Ring	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Cornelian	O
Ring	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Browning	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
11th	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
King	O
William	O
,	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
which	O
way	O
she	O
lost	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Simrow	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Atkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeaner	O
,	O
for	O
embezzelling	O
a	O
Silver-Tankerd	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Wolstenholm	I-pers
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Indictment	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Carrow	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement-Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Stuft-Pettycoat	O
,	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Rowe	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
sent	O
divers	O
Goods	O
to	O
a	O
Dyer	O
to	O
be	O
died	O
,	O
among	O
which	O
was	O
this	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
then	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
found	O
at	O
a	O
Brokers	O
pawned	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
denied	O
that	O
he	O
Stole	O
it	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
given	O
him	O
by	O
another	O
Person	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
a	O
Witness	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Dimekin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Grannt	I-pers
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
near	O
the	O
Right	O
Arm-Pit	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
dyed	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
some	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
fell	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
waking	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Passion	O
,	O
and	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
drew	O
also	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
scuffle	O
the	O
Deceased	O
received	O
his	O
wound	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
That	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
upon	O
the	O
Guard	O
,	O
and	O
waking	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
he	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
and	O
wounded	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Thigh	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
drew	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
followed	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
they	O
could	O
go	O
no	O
further	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Martha	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Holland-Sheets	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lyden	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
:	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
her	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
at	O
Greenwich	O
in	O
Kent	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Waterman	O
,	O
and	O
plyed	O
at	O
St.	O
Saviours	O
Mill	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
carried	O
her	O
to	O
King	O
Edward-Stairs	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
the	O
Water	O
he	O
mistrusted	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
Stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
ashore	O
he	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
who	O
carried	O
her	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
owned	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
She	O
denyed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
That	O
her	O
Husband	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
about	O
four	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
commanded	O
her	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Rose	O
in	O
Ratcliff	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
Stole	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
an	O
Offender	O
,	O
and	O
giving	O
no	O
good	O
account	O
of	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Davey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Gregorys	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
half	O
hundred	O
leaden	O
Weight	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Cassold	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
weight	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
a	O
nother	O
Person	O
.	O
He	O
denyed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
never	O
near	O
the	O
Shop	O
in	O
all	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
medle	O
with	O
any	O
thing	O
which	O
was	O
proved	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
call	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
2	O
Brass	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
6	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
a	O
Bason	O
,	O
4	O
Shirts	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Oliver	B-pers
Sawyer	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
Lodging	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
were	O
gone	O
to	O
Bed	O
she	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Back	O
Door	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
upon	O
inquiry	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
at	O
the	O
Cross	O
Keys	O
at	O
Whitechappel	O
,	O
playing	O
at	O
Cards	O
.	O
She	O
denyed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
She	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Offender	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
call	O
any	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Dickman	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Linvill	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
;	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Brampton	I-pers
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
4	O
Shirts	O
,	O
2	O
Smocks	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
value	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
in	O
Swan	B-place
Ally	I-place
about	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
and	O
the	O
Iron-Bar	O
of	O
a	O
Window	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Goods	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Watchman	O
coming	O
his	O
Rounds	O
about	O
3	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
making	O
inquiry	O
;	O
heard	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
Persons	O
carried	O
some	O
Linnen	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Chick-Lane	O
,	O
where	O
being	O
come	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
offering	O
them	O
to	O
Sale	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
for	O
making	O
their	O
escape	O
,	O
but	O
were	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Linvill	O
's	O
Bosom	O
they	O
found	O
a	O
Laced	O
Hankerchief	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
owned	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
.	O
They	O
both	O
denyed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
That	O
Night	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
late	O
a	O
Drinking	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Woods-Close	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
a	O
Dunghill	O
.	O
They	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
call	O
any	O
to	O
their	O
Reputations	O
.	O
They	O
being	O
both	O
Offenders	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
two	O
Yards	O
of	O
Muslin	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Haynes	I-pers
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
Yard	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
pursued	O
after	O
her	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
denyed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
steal	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
them	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
;	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
:	O
The	O
jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Silvester	B-pers
Harlackenden	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
Roger	B-pers
Wincoll	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
left	O
Pap	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
dyed	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
Stabbing	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
two	O
Ladies	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Roe-Buck	O
in	O
Suffolk-street	O
,	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
till	O
it	O
was	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
took	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
who	O
drove	O
them	O
to	O
Holly	O
Street	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
ladies	O
were	O
set	O
down	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
of	O
a	O
Coach	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Clare-Market	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Window	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
them	O
talking	O
high	O
Words	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
say	O
,	O
God	O
damn	O
him	O
;	O
Are	O
not	O
you	O
a	O
Rogue	O
to	O
impose	O
upon	O
any	O
Gentleman	O
so	O
?	O
And	O
then	O
walked	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
after	O
the	O
Deceased	O
fell	O
down	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Deceased	O
fallen	O
down	O
under	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
Watchman	O
got	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
wounded	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
home	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
in	O
Brownlow-street	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Deceased	O
declared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
him	O
but	O
a	O
Shilling	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
deserved	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
no	O
more	O
;	O
and	O
importuning	O
him	O
till	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
said	O
Wound	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
struck	O
him	O
several	O
Blows	O
with	O
the	O
stock	O
of	O
his	O
Whip	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
off	O
his	O
Hat	O
into	O
the	O
Kennel	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
Scurrilous	O
Language	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
wounding	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
alledged	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
absconded	O
but	O
went	O
publickly	O
about	O
his	O
Business	O
;	O
He	O
called	O
divers	O
People	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
quiet	O
Temper	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
given	O
to	O
any	O
manner	O
of	O
Quarrelling	O
,	O
all	O
which	O
matters	O
the	O
Jury	O
having	O
considered	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
all	O
three	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Musgrove	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
a	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Maston	I-pers
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
with	O
intention	O
to	O
steal	O
his	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
second	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Coat	O
and	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Maston	O
:	O
As	O
for	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
frighted	O
,	O
before	O
they	O
committed	O
any	O
Fact	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
acquitted	O
of	O
this	O
.	O
As	O
for	O
the	O
second	O
Indictment	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
his	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
who	O
took	O
them	O
knew	O
not	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
Evidence	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
concerned	O
with	O
Musgrove	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
rob	O
the	O
House	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
;	O
and	O
also	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
confest	O
to	O
him	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
last	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
looking	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
snack	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
Defence	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Ellis	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Sturgis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
3	O
Deal-Boards	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Moreland	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
Day	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Boards	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
upon	O
him	O
at	O
Bloomsbury	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Yard	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Consent	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
pay	O
her	O
6s	O
.	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
Outwich	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
700	O
Weight	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Corbin	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Cellar	O
was	O
robbed	O
where	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
laid	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
Examination	O
,	O
found	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
being	O
taken	O
and	O
brought	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
confest	O
the	O
same	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
.	O
He	O
denyed	O
it	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
He	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
for	O
his	O
Confession	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
promised	O
to	O
be	O
kind	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
confess	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
denyed	O
by	O
the	O
other	O
Evidence	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Nicholson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
and	I-place
Agnes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Women	O
's	O
Leather	O
Shoes	O
from	O
Abraham	B-pers
Giles	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
lost	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
off	O
his	O
Stall	O
,	O
and	O
pursuing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
his	O
Bosome	O
;	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
take	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
Steal	O
them	O
:	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
his	O
first	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Regale	B-pers
Stewart	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Wardrobe	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
,	O
the	O
First	O
was	O
for	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
the	O
th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
did	O
Ravish	O
and	O
Carnally	O
know	O
one	O
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Merrick	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Virgin	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Age	O
of	O
10	O
Years	O
and	O
10	O
Months	O
,	O
against	O
her	O
will	O
and	O
consent	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
second	O
was	O
Ravishing	O
one	O
Ellinor	B-pers
Merrick	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Infant	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
age	O
of	O
4	O
Years	O
and	O
2	O
Months	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Ann	O
Merrick	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
sent	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
come	O
back	O
he	O
catched	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
her	O
into	O
his	O
Bed	O
Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
knowledge	O
of	O
her	O
three	O
times	O
.	O
The	O
Mother	O
of	O
the	O
Children	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
were	O
abused	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
divers	O
Midwives	O
and	O
Doctors	O
who	O
had	O
viewed	O
their	O
Bodies	O
,	O
who	O
believed	O
that	O
there	O
might	O
be	O
some	O
force	O
,	O
but	O
how	O
knew	O
not	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
called	O
divers	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Violence	O
offered	O
to	O
the	O
Children	O
;	O
And	O
the	O
Midwives	O
and	O
Surgeons	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
being	O
sent	O
out	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Tryal	O
,	O
to	O
view	O
their	O
Bodies	O
,	O
found	O
that	O
the	O
Eldest	O
had	O
not	O
lost	O
her	O
Virginity	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
divers	O
other	O
matters	O
alledged	O
,	O
which	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
Impossibilities	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
to	O
be	O
only	O
Malice	O
:	O
And	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
divers	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
a	O
good	O
Report	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
the	O
Father	O
of	O
22	O
Children	O
by	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
such	O
an	O
Offence	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
concerning	O
the	O
Youngest	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
P-	B-pers
M-	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
5	O
Yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
value	O
9s	O
.	O
8d	O
.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Russey	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
,	O
that	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
ever	O
in	O
her	O
Custody	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
alledging	O
her	O
Innocence	O
,	O
called	O
divers	O
People	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Windall	I-pers
,	O
and	O
George	B-pers
Way	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
20	O
Yards	O
of	O
Muslin	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Vickery	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
they	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Kenting	O
Neck	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
whilst	O
they	O
were	O
busie	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
in	O
another	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
brought	O
back	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Woman	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
other	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
they	O
saw	O
the	O
Goods	O
into	O
the	O
Man	O
's	O
Custody	O
.	O
They	O
both	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
positive	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
to	O
4s	O
.	O
and	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Mathews	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Savoy	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
,	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Strickland	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
8	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
3	O
Yards	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Roberta	B-pers
Gibbs	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
brought	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
whilst	O
they	O
were	O
examining	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
were	O
brought	O
by	O
another	O
Person	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
that	O
way	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Sparks	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bottolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Scarlet	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutors	O
Wife	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
weekly	O
Servant	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
,	O
confest	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
Broker	O
for	O
25s	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
thereupon	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Haynes	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeaner	O
,	O
for	O
getting	O
in	O
at	O
a	O
Window	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Edward	B-pers
Dutton	I-pers
Cole	I-pers
with	O
an	O
intention	O
to	O
steal	O
his	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
they	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
Thieves	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
up	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
and	O
coming	O
down	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
other	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
saw	O
him	O
get	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
that	O
they	O
found	O
his	O
Hat	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
that	O
way	O
,	O
a	O
Man	O
took	O
off	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
get	O
upon	O
some	O
Railes	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
into	O
the	O
Window	O
to	O
fetch	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
there	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
no	O
Design	O
to	O
steal	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
or	O
call	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Randal	B-pers
Royal	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
precinct	B-place
of	I-place
Saint	I-place
Catherines	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
2	O
Fans	O
,	O
4	O
Silk	O
Hoods	O
,	O
2	O
Scarfs	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bonner	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Cloath-Coat	O
and	O
Breeches	O
,	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Diet	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Naylor	I-pers
,	O
Jun	O
.	O
Of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
Stephen	I-place
Colemanstreet	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
George	B-pers
Naylor	I-pers
,	O
his	O
Brother	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
QUEEN	O
;	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Penknife	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
left	O
Pap	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languish	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
7th	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Father	O
deposed	O
that	O
his	O
Son	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
home	O
late	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
the	O
Bed	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
refus	O
'd	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
struck	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Mother	O
said	O
,	O
Will	O
you	O
kill	O
him	O
?	O
And	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
hearing	O
the	O
Noise	O
,	O
rose	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
down	O
in	O
his	O
Shirt	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
him	O
scuffle	O
with	O
his	O
Father	O
,	O
took	O
his	O
part	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
being	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
the	O
Penknife	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
scuffling	O
together	O
again	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
received	O
the	O
said	O
Wound	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
afterwards	O
own	O
'd	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
seeking	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
matter	O
specially	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Vasse	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeaner	O
for	O
forging	O
a	O
Counterfeit	O
Writing	O
,	O
called	O
a	O
Bill	O
of	O
Sale	O
,	O
In	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
one	O
Richard	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
Her	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Ship	O
the	O
St.	O
Albans	O
Prize	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
that	O
means	O
did	O
receive	O
the	O
Summ	O
of	O
19l	O
.	O
17s	O
.	O
the	O
Wages	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Ellis	O
for	O
his	O
Service	O
in	O
the	O
War	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
with	O
one	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Melton	I-pers
,	O
for	O
the	O
like	O
Offence	O
,	O
and	O
receiving	O
the	O
Summ	O
of	O
44l	O
.	O
the	O
Wages	O
of	O
one	O
Henry	B-pers
Enman	I-pers
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
St.	O
Albans	O
Prize	O
,	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
full	O
enough	O
to	O
convict	O
them	O
on	O
this	O
Indictment	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Hartington	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Eling	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Horrible	O
and	O
abominable	O
Sin	O
of	O
Sodomy	O
,	O
committed	O
with	O
a	O
Dog	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
was	O
a	O
Girl	O
,	O
who	O
lived	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
;	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
liv	O
'd	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Hole	O
in	O
the	O
Floor	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
through	O
the	O
Ceiling	O
,	O
whereby	O
she	O
could	O
see	O
into	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
that	O
Night	O
about	O
8	O
or	O
9	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
being	O
above	O
Stairs	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
Light	O
in	O
her	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
saw	O
her	O
sitting	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Fire-side	O
,	O
looking	O
backward	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Dog	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
acted	O
with	O
her	O
as	O
to	O
a	O
Bitch	O
.	O
The	O
Mother	O
also	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
brought	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Paper	O
of	O
the	O
bigness	O
of	O
the	O
Hole	O
.	O
She	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
out	O
of	O
Malice	O
and	O
Spight	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
none	O
of	O
her	O
Dog	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
and	O
her	O
Mother	O
had	O
several	O
times	O
done	O
her	O
Injuries	O
in	O
her	O
Goods	O
and	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
by	O
throwing	O
Soap	O
Sudds	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
which	O
came	O
through	O
the	O
Seiling	O
,	O
and	O
spoilt	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
call	O
'd	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
out	O
of	O
Malice	O
and	O
Spight	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
her	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
asking	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Tryal	O
,	O
what	O
Colour	O
the	O
Dog	O
was	O
of	O
:	O
She	O
reply	O
'd	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
Dog	O
or	O
no	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
divers	O
other	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
declar	O
'd	O
that	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
several	O
Quarrels	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Constable	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
quarrelsome	O
People	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
several	O
Warrants	O
against	O
the	O
Evidence	O
and	O
her	O
Mother	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
impossible	O
for	O
any	O
Body	O
to	O
see	O
through	O
the	O
Hole	O
to	O
the	O
Fire-side	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
what	O
any	O
Person	O
was	O
doing	O
of	O
,	O
all	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
E-	B-pers
W-	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Saint	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
a	O
Guinea	O
from	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Nicholson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
to	O
distrain	O
for	O
a	O
fine	O
for	O
keeping	O
a	O
Disorderly	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
with	O
any	O
Intent	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
being	O
a	O
malicious	O
one	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
honourably	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Zachariah	B-pers
Fitch	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Chiswick	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
7	O
Perry-wiggs	O
,	O
value	O
20l	O
.	O
from	O
Corbet	B-pers
Gun	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
QUEEN	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
kept	O
a	O
Shop	O
at	O
Brentford	B-place
,	O
and	O
leaving	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
there	O
at	O
work	O
,	O
whilst	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Goods	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
but	O
pursuing	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
at	O
Cambridge	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
brought	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
:	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
a	O
Suite	O
of	O
Cloaths	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
paid	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
who	O
threatened	O
to	O
arrest	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
Notice	O
thereof	O
,	O
was	O
forc	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
,	O
without	O
leave	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
any	O
thing	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
his	O
Possession	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Humphry	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pancras	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
,	O
by	O
Counterfeiting	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coyn	O
of	O
the	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
8th	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
King	O
WILLIAM	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
so	O
long	O
since	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
he	O
coyn	O
'd	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stedman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pauls	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
one	O
Christian	B-pers
,	I-pers
the	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Dennis	I-pers
Macdonnel	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
second	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
QUEEN	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
her	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
Part	O
of	O
her	O
Body	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Loins	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
soon	O
after	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Husband	O
deposed	O
that	O
one	O
Lewis	O
and	O
one	O
Hilton	O
,	O
Soldiers	O
,	O
were	O
fighting	O
with	O
their	O
Swords	O
in	O
Covent-Garden	B-place
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
Serjeant	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
by	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
see	O
them	O
murder	O
one	O
another	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
called	O
her	O
Bitch	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
struck	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
with	O
her	O
Patten	O
,	O
which	O
cut	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Eye-brow	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
struck	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Brest	O
with	O
the	O
Point	O
of	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
getting	O
away	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Railes	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Wound	O
in	O
the	O
Back	O
,	O
which	O
Fact	O
the	O
Jury	O
having	O
consider	O
'd	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Guy	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Daytime	O
,	O
no	O
Person	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Stuff-Pettycoat	O
,	O
a	O
Fustian	O
Wast-Coat	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dagford	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Bentley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
secretly	O
taking	O
40s	O
.	O
from	O
Dorothy	B-pers
the	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
William	I-pers
Brookhurst	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bunch	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeaner	O
,	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
one	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Appleyard	I-pers
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
Rob	O
him	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Cecilie	B-pers
Labree	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
formerly	O
convicted	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
for	O
Counterfeiting	O
the	O
Current	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
and	O
pardoned	O
on	O
condition	O
to	O
Transport	O
her	O
self	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Dominions	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
to	O
return	O
no	O
more	O
;	O
having	O
broke	O
the	O
Conditions	O
of	O
her	O
Pardon	O
,	O
is	O
Ordered	O
to	O
prepare	O
her	O
self	O
for	O
Death	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
5	O
.	O
Richard	O
Dickman	O
,	O
Margaret	O
Ellis	O
,	O
William	O
Fox	O
,	O
Silvester	O
Harlackendon	O
,	O
and	O
John	O
Linvill	O
Cecilie	B-pers
Labree	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
formerly	O
convicted	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
for	O
Counterfeiting	O
the	O
Current	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
and	O
pardoned	O
on	O
condition	O
to	O
Transport	O
her	O
self	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Dominions	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
to	O
return	O
no	O
more	O
;	O
having	O
broke	O
the	O
Conditions	O
of	O
her	O
Pardon	O
,	O
is	O
Ordered	O
to	O
prepare	O
her	O
self	O
for	O
Death	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
2	O
.	O
James	O
Dimekin	O
and	O
Thomas	O
Stealman	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Cheek	O
,	O
14	O
Peter	O
Bulkley	O
,	O
Cray	O
Mook	O
,	O
Richard	O
Cook	O
,	O
Mary	O
Deane	O
,	O
Robert	O
Finch	O
,	O
Mary	O
Ford	O
,	O
Ann	O
Hawkins	O
,	O
Martha	O
Hill	O
,	O
Mary	O
Musgrove	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Sparks	O
,	O
Mary	O
Trenchfield	O
,	O
Dorothy	O
Warwick	O
,	O
Sarah	O
Windall	O
and	O
George	O
Way	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
,	O
5	O
.	O
Ann	O
Digger	O
,	O
John	O
Davey	O
,	O
Robert	O
Nicholson	O
,	O
Mary	O
Robinson	O
and	O
Ann	O
Stowe	O
.	O
H	O
-	O
J	O
-	O
Fined	O
six	O
and	O
twenty	O
Shillings	O
and	O
eight	O
Pence	O
.	O
Robert	O
Baker	O
Fined	O
20	O
Marks	O
.	O
William	O
Haynes	O
Fined	O
20	O
Nobles	O
.	O
Mary	O
Vasse	O
Fined	O
20	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
3	O
times	O
on	O
the	O
Pillory	O
at	O
the	O
Pay-Office	O
,	O
Navy-Office	O
,	O
and	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
.	O
Margaret	O
Ellis	O
pleaded	O
her	O
Belly	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
Being	O
Impanelled	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
with	O
quick	O
Child	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENT	O
.	O
All	O
Persons	O
Distemper	O
'd	O
in	O
Mind	O
by	O
Melancholy	O
or	O
Despair	O
,	O
from	O
what	O
cause	O
so	O
ever	O
,	O
are	O
with	O
God	O
's	O
Blessing	O
,	O
speedily	O
Cured	O
,	O
if	O
curable	O
(	O
with	O
the	O
most	O
kind	O
and	O
tender	O
usage	O
allowing	O
them	O
plentiful	O
Dyer	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
Comfortable	O
Accomodation	O
)	O
by	O
a	O
Physician	O
of	O
long	O
Practice	O
,	O
and	O
great	O
Experience	O
in	O
those	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
Cases	O
.	O
Living	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
Shadwell	O
Coffee-House	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
Church	O
and	O
Market	O
in	O
Upper-Shadwell	O
,	O
near	O
London	O
.	O
Who	O
also	O
Cures	O
any	O
kind	O
of	O
Fits	O
and	O
all	O
Pains	O
and	O
Lameness	O
of	O
the	O
Limbs	O
,	O
though	O
Useless	O
and	O
Bedrid	O
.	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
