TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
Queen	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
Held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
23d	O
,	O
24th	O
,	O
25th	O
,	O
and	O
26th	O
Days	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
1707	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Sixth	O
Year	O
of	O
Her	O
MAJESTIES	O
Reign	O
,	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Bedingfeld	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
my	O
Ld	O
.	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
Holt	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Dormer	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Bury	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
with	O
divers	O
of	O
Her	O
Majesties	O
Justices	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Norman	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Fawdery	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
William	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
William	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Powle	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Kimber	I-pers
Michael	B-pers
Higginson	I-pers
Edmund	B-pers
Harvy	I-pers
William	B-pers
Terrett	I-pers
Ichabod	B-pers
Dawkes	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Phipps	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Bampton	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
Willilliam	B-pers
Munden	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Winckfield	I-pers
William	B-pers
Pannet	I-pers
John	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
William	B-pers
Patridge	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
How	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
John	B-pers
Millet	I-pers
William	B-pers
Avis	I-pers
Guy	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
The	O
Procedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dickson	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Jury	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
between	O
the	O
Hours	O
of	O
1	O
and	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
Day	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
1	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
3	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
3	O
Brass	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
66	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
6	O
China	O
Cups	O
,	O
20	O
ll	O
.	O
Weight	O
of	O
Cheshire	O
Cheese	O
,	O
a	O
Breast	O
of	O
Mutton	O
,	O
a	O
Laced	O
Night	O
Cap	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
a	O
Holland	O
Neckcloath	O
,	O
a	O
Flower	O
Bagg	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	O
Jury	O
.	O
A	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Coffee-Pot	O
,	O
3	O
Coats	O
,	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
2	O
Perukes	O
,	O
2	O
Hats	O
,	O
2	O
Holland	O
Frocks	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Hodges	I-pers
.	O
4	O
Holland	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
a	O
Holland	O
Smock	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Judith	B-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
.	O
A	O
Suit	O
of	O
Muslin	O
Headcloaths	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Howel	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
Deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
was	O
fast	O
at	O
one	O
a	O
Clock	O
that	O
Morning	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
commited	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
Family	O
arose	O
about	O
6	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
a	O
Pantry	O
Window	O
that	O
leads	O
to	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Iron	O
Bar	O
bent	O
so	O
that	O
a	O
Man	O
might	O
get	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
further	O
Deposed	O
,	O
that	O
upon	O
Enquiry	O
,	O
divers	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
particularly	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
Serge	O
Frock	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Neckcloath	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Hodges	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Headcloaths	O
of	O
Mary	O
Howel	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
say	O
little	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Isaac	B-pers
Coulthouse	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pan	O
of	O
Brass	O
Scales	O
,	O
a	O
Steal	O
Tobacco-Box	O
,	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
2	O
Brass	O
Weights	O
,	O
4	O
ll	O
.	O
Weight	O
of	O
Sweetmeats	O
,	O
200	O
Apples	O
,	O
50	O
Oranges	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
Day	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
Deposed	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Stall	O
about	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
found	O
it	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
that	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
rattling	O
of	O
Scales	O
about	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
upon	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
found	O
divers	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
give	O
no	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Plug	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
's	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Hurrick	I-pers
,	O
about	O
7	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
200	O
Yards	O
of	O
Durant	O
Stuff	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cope	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
Deposed	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
about	O
7	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
middle	O
Wooden	O
Bar	O
of	O
his	O
Parlour	O
Window	O
was	O
broken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
which	O
lay	O
upon	O
a	O
Table	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
was	O
one	O
Low	O
a	O
Person	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
Deposed	O
,	O
that	O
himself	O
with	O
Matthews	O
(	O
that	O
was	O
Executed	O
last	O
Sessions	O
)	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
commited	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
He	O
further	O
Deposed	O
,	O
that	O
himself	O
stood	O
Centry	O
with	O
a	O
Pistol	O
some	O
distance	O
from	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
denyed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
call	O
none	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolphs	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
10	O
Yards	O
ofBone	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Norris	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
Day	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Evidence	O
Deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
pursu	O
'd	O
,	O
a	O
second	O
Evidence	O
saw	O
her	O
drop	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Lightfoot	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Feather	O
Bed	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
2	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Feather	O
Bolster	O
10	O
s.	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Bethia	B-pers
Rich	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
140	O
Yards	O
of	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
40	O
pieces	O
of	O
narrow	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
2	O
Stuff-Gowns	O
2	O
Stuff	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
2	O
Guineas	O
,	O
2	O
broad	O
Pieces	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Vere	B-pers
Melchham	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
positive	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
of	O
both	O
the	O
Indictments	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wittingham	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Carpenter	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
9	O
pair	O
of	O
Men	O
's	O
Shoes	O
value	O
27	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
5	O
pair	O
of	O
Women	O
's	O
Shoes	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
s.	O
On	O
the	O
second	O
Day	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
11	O
of	O
the	O
Night	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
Deposed	O
,	O
that	O
himself	O
and	O
Family	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
about	O
8	O
a	O
Clock	O
when	O
this	O
Accident	O
happen	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
11	O
he	O
was	O
called	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
his	O
House	O
broken	O
open	O
and	O
his	O
Goods	O
gone	O
,	O
but	O
making	O
Enquiry	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
found	O
them	O
all	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
say	O
little	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
Day	O
Light	O
not	O
being	O
shut	O
in	O
when	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
his	O
Family	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Mould	I-pers
,	O
by	O
driving	O
the	O
near	O
hinder	O
Wheel	O
of	O
an	O
empty	O
Coach	O
drawn	O
with	O
two	O
Horses	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
right	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Robert	O
Mould	O
,	O
which	O
gave	O
him	O
divers	O
mortal	O
Wounds	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
third	O
Day	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Wounds	O
he	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
eighth	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
Indicted	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
the	O
Manslaughter	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Robert	O
Mould	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
Deposed	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
in	O
Kings-Street	B-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
another	O
Coachman	O
came	O
with	O
their	O
Coaches	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Gentlewoman	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
sent	O
away	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
further	O
Deposed	O
,	O
that	O
while	O
the	O
other	O
Coachman	O
was	O
shutting	O
his	O
Coach	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
whiped	O
his	O
Horses	O
,	O
which	O
set	O
them	O
a	O
running	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
going	O
to	O
stop	O
them	O
,	O
was	O
beaten	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
Spring-tree	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
over	O
by	O
the	O
near	O
hinder	O
Wheel	O
,	O
which	O
gave	O
him	O
divers	O
Wounds	O
and	O
Bruises	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
Chirurgeons	O
Deposed	O
he	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
produc	O
'd	O
divers	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
Deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
strike	O
the	O
Horses	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
of	O
the	O
Murder	O
,	O
but	O
left	O
the	O
Manslaughter	O
to	O
a	O
special	O
Verdict	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Bowers	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Anne	B-pers
Langley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Henry	O
and	O
Paul	B-pers
Desbrosses	I-pers
,	O
20	O
Yards	O
of	O
Muslin	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Paul	O
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Desbrosses	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
Deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
to	O
cheapen	O
some	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Back	O
was	O
turn	O
'd	O
,	O
Bowers	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
that	O
opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
pursu	O
'd	O
and	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sophia	B-pers
Ballard	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
buying	O
of	O
200	O
Yards	O
of	O
Durant	O
Stuffs	O
of	O
Luke	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cope	I-pers
,	O
she	O
knowing	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Theophilus	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Cloath	O
Hatts	O
,	O
value	O
24	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Black	I-place
fryars	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
Day	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
John	B-pers
and	I-pers
Joan	I-pers
Revel	I-pers
were	O
likewise	O
Indicted	O
for	O
buying	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
of	O
Theophilus	O
Brown	O
,	O
they	O
knowing	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
proving	O
the	O
Facts	O
upon	O
Theophilus	O
Brown	O
and	O
Joan	O
Revel	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
John	O
Revel	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Lynnly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dionis	I-place
Back-Church	I-place
,	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Stokings	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Henry	O
Lynnly	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
Deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
and	O
cheapen	O
'd	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Black	O
Silk	O
Stokings	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
busy	O
with	O
another	O
Customer	O
,	O
She	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
that	O
Opportunity	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
say	O
little	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Crossfield	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
21	O
Yards	O
of	O
Shalloon	O
,	O
value	O
32	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Guillam	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bartholomew	I-place
the	I-place
less	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
day	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
private	O
stealing	O
8	O
Yards	O
of	O
Dutch	O
Check	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
day	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
to	O
the	O
1st	O
proved	O
clearly	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
stolen	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Shop	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
clear	O
proof	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
1st	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
but	O
accquited	O
her	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Hannah	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Callico	O
Counterpain	O
value	O
18	O
s	O
,	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Deborah	B-pers
Corner	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Coleman	I-place
Street	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
day	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
Deposed	O
that	O
she	O
miss	O
'd	O
her	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
Suspecting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
upon	O
search	O
found	O
them	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
Positive	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Floyd	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
19	O
Yards	O
of	O
Muslen	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Norman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
Deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
put	O
them	O
up	O
her	O
Petticoat	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
pursued	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
offering	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
2	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Tankard	O
,	O
a	O
Brass	O
Cover	O
of	O
a	O
Pot	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Gideon	B-pers
Bennoist	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
day	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
Deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
House	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
hebeing	O
pursu	O
'd	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
calling	O
none	O
to	O
her	O
reputation	O
,	O
nor	O
giving	O
any	O
account	O
of	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Maunders	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Galloway	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Head	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
10	O
Muslen	O
Neckcloaths	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
Sleeves	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Carr	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
prov	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
fully	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Lydal	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Mantua	O
,	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Gould	I-pers
and	O
8	O
Yards	O
of	O
Ribbon	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Phoebe	B-pers
Hodder	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
Deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
Stolen	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
taken	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Kingston	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
in	O
the	O
Left	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Iron	O
Cleaver	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
day	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Wound	O
he	O
Languished	O
till	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Dyed	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Man-slaughter	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquest	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
Deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
struck	O
the	O
Deceased	O
with	O
a	O
Basket	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Sleeve	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
reason	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
Cleaver	O
from	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Stall	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Left	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
Head	O
.	O
Several	O
Surgeons	O
(	O
that	O
dress	O
'd	O
the	O
Wound	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
and	O
opened	O
it	O
after	O
his	O
Death	O
)	O
Deposed	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
Produc	O
'd	O
Divers	O
Witnesses	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
half	O
Witted	O
Man	O
,	O
that	O
for	O
his	O
Simplicity	O
the	O
Butchers	O
in	O
Newgate	O
Market	O
,	O
used	O
frequently	O
to	O
vex	O
and	O
teaze	O
him	O
by	O
Pulling	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Hair	O
,	O
Breaking	O
his	O
Head	O
and	O
Dragging	O
him	O
about	O
the	O
Market	O
&	O
c.	O
which	O
kind	O
of	O
sport	O
would	O
make	O
him	O
commit	O
all	O
manner	O
of	O
extravagances	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
farther	O
Deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
thus	O
Baited	O
before	O
he	O
struck	O
the	O
Deceased	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Man	O
slaughter	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Muslen	O
Headcloaths	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cambrick	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Simon	B-pers
Degg	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
Positive	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Waldram	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
16	O
Guineas	O
and	O
12	O
l.	O
16	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Mony	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Hubbard	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
day	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Amy	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Diamond	O
Necklace	O
value	O
40	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jasper	B-pers
Provero	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
Proved	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
,	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Sam	B-pers
.	I-pers
Bumby	I-pers
,	O
by	O
driving	O
his	O
Coach	O
over	O
him	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
second	O
Day	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appearing	O
by	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Evidence	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
more	O
Accident	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
Henry	B-pers
Fern	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Haddington	B-place
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
9	O
Chickens	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Powsey	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joyce	B-pers
Dalt	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Iron	O
Spike	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
d.	O
2	O
Iron	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
13	O
l.	O
of	O
Iron	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Black	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Damask	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Damask	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
12	O
Diaper	O
Napkins	O
,	O
3	O
Diaper	O
Table-cloaths	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Mollinex	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
could	O
fix	O
nothing	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
aiding	O
and	O
assisting	O
John	B-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Thomas	I-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
committing	O
of	O
a	O
Rape	O
on	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Catherine	B-pers
Masters	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Age	O
of	O
10	O
Years	O
and	O
upward	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Evidence	O
was	O
the	O
Girl	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
who	O
Deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
her	O
self	O
lodged	O
together	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Night	O
when	O
this	O
thing	O
happen	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
at	O
eight	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
11	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
with	O
a	O
Man	O
to	O
her	O
Lodging	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
sleepy	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
perceive	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
Bed	O
;	O
but	O
awaking	O
about	O
2	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
Morning	O
,	O
found	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
Bed	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pull	O
'd	O
her	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
her	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
stopt	O
her	O
Mouth	O
,	O
(	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
cry	O
out	O
)	O
while	O
the	O
Man	O
gain	O
'd	O
the	O
perfect	O
knowledge	O
of	O
her	O
Body	O
.	O
Others	O
Deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Girl	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
acquainted	O
them	O
how	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
abused	O
,	O
and	O
Inspecting	O
her	O
Body	O
,	O
found	O
that	O
a	O
Man	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
the	O
Pox	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
very	O
plain	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
saying	O
little	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Underhill	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
value	O
15	O
l.	O
2	O
Cloath	O
Coats	O
,	O
2	O
Cloth	O
Wastcoats	O
,	O
with	O
Divers	O
other	O
things	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Dole	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Positive	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Flaxen	O
Sheet	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
The	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
King	I-pers
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Alice	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
in	O
Cheating	O
Joseph	B-pers
Swallow	I-pers
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
of	O
8	O
l.	O
pretending	O
to	O
leave	O
as	O
a	O
Pledge	O
of	O
Bone	O
Lace	O
,	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
Muslen	O
and	O
Holland	O
Cloth	O
,	O
when	O
in	O
reallity	O
it	O
was	O
nothing	O
but	O
old	O
rags	O
,	O
Bed	O
Matting	O
and	O
Sand	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
reaching	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Lincoln	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Wotton	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Hood	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquited	O
her	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
Labourer	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
3	O
several	O
Buggeries	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
commit	O
a	O
fourth	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evi-	O
not	O
Satisfying	O
the	O
Jury	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bromley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Smock	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
17	O
l.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Mony	O
of	O
Josias	B-pers
Milward	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
ring	O
,	O
2	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Fork	O
,	O
with	O
Divers	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
Money	O
to	O
a	O
Considerable	O
value	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
Day	O
of	O
November	O
1795	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Elenor	B-pers
Rodway	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Aiding	O
and	O
Assisting	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
in	O
the	O
Committing	O
of	O
a	O
Rape	O
on	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Mule	I-pers
a	O
Virgin	O
of	O
10	O
years	O
and	O
Upward	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
Day	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
coming	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
Ordered	O
a	O
New	O
Indictment	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
committed	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Elenor	O
Rodway	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
the	O
Girl	O
and	O
Assisting	O
one	O
in	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
Ravish	O
her	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
Proving	O
the	O
assault	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
accquitted	O
her	O
of	O
both	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Goostree	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
11	O
l.	O
weight	O
of	O
Lead	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Antony	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
clear	O
proof	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Mantua	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
positive	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Gibbons	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
a	O
Huccaback	O
Tablecloath	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Scarf	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Martha	B-pers
Brocknell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Flaxen	O
Sheet	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
.	O
But	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
accquitted	O
her	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
40	O
Lamb	O
Skins	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Phelps	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
Day	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
G	B-pers
-	I-pers
C	I-pers
-	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
on	O
three	O
Indictments	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
several	O
wounds	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Dyed	O
.	O
The	O
2d	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
Stabbing	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
3d	O
on	O
Coroners	O
Inquest	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
Scandalous	O
Women	O
,	O
and	O
contradicting	O
each	O
other	O
in	O
their	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
likewise	O
appearing	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
several	O
Surgeons	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
poxt	O
,	O
and	O
most	O
of	O
his	O
Bowels	O
wasted	O
and	O
rotten	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
having	O
consider	O
'd	O
the	O
matter	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
of	O
all	O
3	O
Indictments	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
died	O
Visitatione	O
Dei	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
,	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
3	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Dickinson	O
,	O
John	O
Goodwin	O
,	O
Alice	O
Gray	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
and	O
put	O
to	O
hard	O
Labour	O
,	O
Pursuant	O
to	O
the	O
late	O
Act	O
of	O
Parliment	O
,	O
9	O
.	O
John	O
Gibbons	O
,	O
Anne	O
Langley	O
,	O
Jane	O
Bowers	O
,	O
Theophilus	O
Brown	O
,	O
John	O
Kingston	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Maunders	O
,	O
Joan	O
Reves	O
,	O
James	O
Roberts	O
,	O
John	O
Wittingham	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
,	O
12	O
Mary	O
Newman	O
,	O
Hannah	O
Steward	O
,	O
Mary	O
Floyd	O
,	O
Jane	O
Kemp	O
,	O
Mary	O
Crossfield	O
,	O
John	O
Goostree	O
,	O
Jane	O
Booth	O
,	O
Isaac	O
Coulthouse	O
,	O
Mary	O
Lydal	O
,	O
Sarah	O
Bromley	O
,	O
Henry	O
Fern	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Webb	O
.	O
Advertisement	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Three	O
Black-birds	O
in	O
the	O
Great-Minories	O
,	O
near	O
Aldgate	O
,	O
IS	O
sold	O
,	O
a	O
never	O
failing	O
Ointment	O
,	O
that	O
Cures	O
the	O
Gout	O
,	O
although	O
the	O
Parties	O
be	O
reduced	O
to	O
their	O
Crutches	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Days	O
time	O
,	O
having	O
often	O
been	O
found	O
true	O
by	O
Experience	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
great	O
Ease	O
and	O
Comfort	O
of	O
many	O
.	O
It	O
also	O
cures	O
Rheumatick	O
pains	O
.	O
Likewise	O
a	O
certain	O
and	O
infallible	O
Cure	O
for	O
the	O
Tooth-Ach	O
without	O
Drawing	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
so	O
effectually	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Pain	O
will	O
never	O
return	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
not	O
only	O
so	O
,	O
but	O
makes	O
.	O
Teeth	O
as	O
white	O
as	O
Ivory	O
,	O
and	O
fastens	O
those	O
that	O
are	O
loose	O
to	O
Admiration	O
.	O
