TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
Queen	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
Held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAYLY	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
9th	O
,	O
10th	O
and	O
11th	O
Days	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
1708	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Seventh	O
Year	O
of	O
Her	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEfore	O
the	O
Rt	O
.	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
CHARLES	B-pers
DUNCOMBE	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Powel	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Powys	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Blencoe	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
Peter	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
;	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
Her	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Kemble	I-pers
William	B-pers
Christopher	I-pers
Jonathan	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Beard	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Inwood	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Briscow	I-pers
John	B-pers
Burgess	I-pers
John	B-pers
Woodrough	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Hammond	I-pers
James	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
Matthew	B-pers
Snasting	I-pers
James	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Giles	B-pers
Riddle	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Lake	I-pers
,	O
Hugh	B-pers
Marchant	I-pers
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Anstey	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Callow	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Yeomans	I-pers
John	B-pers
Marriot	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Boswell	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Chase	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
John	B-pers
Mist	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Spence	I-pers
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Feather	O
Bed	O
,	O
a	O
Bolster	O
,	O
2	O
Pillows	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
furnish	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
November	O
she	O
being	O
from	O
her	O
Lodging	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
sent	O
to	O
her	O
for	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
her	O
Room	O
,	O
having	O
had	O
occasion	O
for	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
That	O
with	O
the	O
Key	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sent	O
him	O
a	O
Letter	O
,	O
to	O
tell	O
him	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
rob	O
'd	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
divers	O
Pawn-Brokers	O
.	O
Which	O
Confession	O
proving	O
true	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Salter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Savoy	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
11	O
half	O
Yards	O
of	O
Scotch	O
strip	O
'd	O
Linnen	O
Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Shop	O
to	O
cheapen	O
Dyed	O
Linnen	O
,	O
but	O
watching	O
her	O
Opportunity	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
and	O
convey	O
'd	O
them	O
up	O
her	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
pursu	O
'd	O
she	O
drop	O
'd	O
them	O
from	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ralph	B-pers
Malborn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
P.	I-place
Cornhil	I-place
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
100	O
Ells	O
of	O
Garlick	O
Holland	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
48	O
Yards	O
of	O
strip	O
'd	O
and	O
plain	O
Lawns	O
,	O
6	O
l.	O
and	O
120	O
Yards	O
of	O
Muslin	O
,	O
30	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
and	O
Jasper	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Porter	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
his	O
Servants	O
were	O
gone	O
to	O
Dinner	O
,	O
he	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
about	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
who	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Ingram	I-pers
&	O
Sarah	B-pers
Faircloth	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
12	O
Yards	O
and	O
1/2	O
of	O
Gold	O
Lace	O
value	O
44	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Simson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
to	O
cheapen	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
with	O
others	O
,	O
Ingram	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
a	O
Counter	O
and	O
convey	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
Faircloth	O
,	O
on	O
whom	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
off	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
saying	O
little	O
in	O
their	O
defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Ingram	O
:	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Faircloth	O
:	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Bayley	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Brodrey	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
18	O
Furbelow	O
Scarfs	O
value	O
64	O
l.	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Pool	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
reaching	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Hood	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
7	O
Carolina	O
Hats	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
1706	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
54	O
Yards	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stuff	O
,	O
value	O
24	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
P	I-pers
ckington	I-pers
on	O
the	O
7th	O
Instant	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
the	O
Servants	O
were	O
treating	O
with	O
Robinson	O
,	O
Savage	O
was	O
observed	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
slip	O
them	O
up	O
her	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
suffer	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
then	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
clear	O
proof	O
that	O
Robinson	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
20	O
Yards	O
of	O
worsted	O
Stuff	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
another	O
Woman	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Shop	O
to	O
cheapen	O
Blankets	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
busy	O
with	O
a	O
3d	O
Person	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
desired	O
to	O
sit	O
down	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
cheapened	O
Blankets	O
,	O
but	O
bought	O
none	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
off	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
were	O
missing	O
from	O
a	O
Shelf	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
pursu	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
nothing	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jud	B-pers
.	I-pers
Hazard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
13	O
Yards	O
of	O
Broad	O
Ribbon	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Benson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Shop	O
to	O
cheapen	O
Ribbons	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Servants	O
were	O
busy	O
with	O
others	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
off	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Friend	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
a	O
gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
Diamonds	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
a	O
broad	O
Piece	O
called	O
a	O
Jacobus	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
loosing	O
their	O
Goods	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
searching	O
her	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jacobus	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
little	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Croston	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Kerrison	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Hat	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jasper	B-pers
Anthony	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stanton	I-pers
and	O
Hester	B-pers
Condon	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
Hood	O
and	O
Scarf	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
Tabby	O
Petticoat	O
trim	O
'd	O
with	O
silver	O
Lace	O
,	O
5	O
broad	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
18	O
s.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Mony	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Chandler	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
Stanton	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Servant	O
,	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
not	O
sufficient	O
proof	O
against	O
,	O
Condon	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Williams	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Rich	I-pers
.	I-pers
More	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Ann	B-pers
Craddock	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Queens	O
Highway	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Christ-Church	B-place
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Linen	O
Napkin	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
2	O
silk	O
Scarves	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Ashley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
as	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
riding	O
thro	O
Newgate	B-place
in	O
a	O
Hackney	O
Coach	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
thrust	O
his	O
Hand	O
into	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Lap	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
immediately	O
pursu	O
'd	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Patrige	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Case	O
of	O
Bottles	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
75	O
Guineas	O
and	O
15	O
l.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Mony	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Merlier	I-pers
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
12	O
Months	O
ago	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
;	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
November	O
she	O
came	O
and	O
Din	O
'd	O
with	O
a	O
Lodger	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
about	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
missing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Room	O
,	O
It	O
was	O
observ	O
'd	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
Room	O
and	O
amus	O
'd	O
the	O
Servant	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
known	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
That	O
her	O
Lodgings	O
were	O
afterwards	O
searcht	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Mony	O
were	O
found	O
under	O
her	O
Bed	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
very	O
clear	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Callice	I-pers
alias	I-pers
John	I-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Wooden	O
Box	O
,	O
a	O
Whip	O
,	O
2	O
Suits	O
of	O
Headcloths	O
,	O
9	O
Muslen	O
Neck-cloths	O
,	O
10	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
7	O
Hoods	O
,	O
18	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
value	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Patrige	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
stolen	O
from	O
an	O
Inn	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
them	O
and	O
charg	O
'd	O
them	O
with	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
who	O
frankly	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Note	O
under	O
their	O
Hands	O
with	O
a	O
Direction	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
his	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
saying	O
little	O
for	O
themselves	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
A	B-pers
-	I-pers
C	I-pers
-	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Linnen	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Betty	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
malitious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
her	O
Request	O
,	O
granted	O
her	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Eliner	B-pers
Gregg	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
in	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
Reconcile	O
Grace	B-pers
Duncomb	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Queens	O
Subjects	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Romish	O
Religion	O
.	O
But	O
none	O
appearing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
21	O
Yards	O
of	O
blue	O
Linsey	O
Stuff	O
,	O
value	O
23	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Curtis	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
the	O
Shop	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
under	O
her	O
Riding-hood	O
,	O
but	O
going	O
off	O
was	O
discover	O
'd	O
and	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
taking	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Easton	I-pers
,	O
a	O
silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
Novem	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
walking	O
along	O
Holborn	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
intic	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Watch	O
.	O
That	O
suspecting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
caus	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
search	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
little	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
D-	B-pers
S-	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2000	O
Weight	O
of	O
Rozin	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Denew	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
1703	O
.	O
It	O
appearing	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
malitious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Turk	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Turvile	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
a	O
Serge	O
Frock	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
George	O
Turvile	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Landson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Staines	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
of	O
divers	O
Persons	O
,	O
to	O
wit	O
,	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Angel	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Langly	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Susannah	B-pers
Bevis	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
a	O
Passage	O
in	O
a	O
Waggon	O
to	O
Oakingham	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
Stanes	B-place
,	O
she	O
paid	O
for	O
her	O
Supper	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
;	O
That	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
Goods	O
were	O
missing	O
from	O
the	O
Waggon	O
,	O
and	O
pursuing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
them	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
little	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Webb	B-pers
Rawlins	I-pers
,	O
Gabriel	B-pers
Huff	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Rawlins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
were	O
all	O
3	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Jacob	B-pers
Hamson	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
bruise	O
with	O
a	O
wooden	O
Staff	O
on	O
the	O
hinder	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
Head	O
near	O
the	O
Crown	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
1707.	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
Try	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquest	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Jacob	O
Hamson	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
Queen	O
,	O
was	O
one	O
Katharine	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
1707.	O
she	O
agreed	O
with	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Callow	I-pers
to	O
meet	O
that	O
Evening	O
at	O
the	O
Farthing	O
Pye	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
about	O
5	O
a	O
Clock	O
she	O
went	O
and	O
enquir	O
'd	O
for	O
him	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
told	O
by	O
Elizabeth	O
Rawlins	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
Son	O
at	O
the	O
3	O
Fighting	O
Cocks	O
in	O
Bunning-Fields	O
;	O
That	O
she	O
waited	O
some	O
time	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
she	O
sat	O
,	O
a	O
Boy	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
light	O
a	O
Link	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Daughter	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
no	O
Body	O
was	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
but	O
her	O
self	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Rawlins	O
;	O
that	O
at	O
7	O
a	O
Clock	O
she	O
heard	O
a	O
Whistling	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
Web	O
Rawlins	O
and	O
Johnson	O
brought	O
in	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
with	O
a	O
Hankerchief	O
about	O
his	O
Mouth	O
,	O
and	O
Callow	O
and	O
Huff	O
were	O
with	O
them	O
:	O
They	O
carried	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
Room	O
adjoining	O
that	O
wherein	O
she	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
all	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
shut	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
heard	O
a	O
scuffling	O
Noise	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
Mrs.	O
Rawlins	O
the	O
Reason	O
?	O
Who	O
answered	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
nothing	O
but	O
a	O
drunken	O
Man	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Noise	O
encreasing	O
,	O
she	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Rawlins	O
step	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
all	O
Bloody	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Blood	O
gush	O
'd	O
from	O
his	O
Nose	O
and	O
Mouth	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
dead	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
saw	O
his	O
Peruke	O
,	O
a	O
Spying-Glass	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Scales	O
upon	O
the	O
Table	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
Webb	O
Rawlins	O
rifled	O
him	O
of	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
Pockets	O
,	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
silver	O
oval	O
Tobacco	O
Box	O
,	O
a	O
Tooth	O
Pick-case	O
,	O
a	O
Tobacco	O
Stopper	O
,	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
50	O
s.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
Callow	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
bloody	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
which	O
Callow	O
brought	O
her	O
afterwards	O
to	O
wash	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
Elizabeth	O
Rawlins	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
(	O
when	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
Murdered	O
)	O
to	O
her	O
Son	O
,	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
done	O
?	O
My	O
Son	O
will	O
ruin	O
me	O
,	O
At	O
which	O
her	O
Son	O
and	O
Huff	O
presented	O
two	O
Pistols	O
at	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
her	O
hold	O
her	O
Tongue	O
:	O
That	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
way	O
clear	O
,	O
Johnson	O
took	O
him	O
upon	O
his	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
him	O
cross	O
the	O
Field	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
Ditch	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
bought	O
a	O
2	O
d	O
Cheese	O
Cake	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
a	O
piece	O
to	O
her	O
Bedfellow	O
.	O
This	O
Evidence	O
was	O
supported	O
by	O
abundance	O
of	O
concurrent	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
as	O
first	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
went	O
from	O
Aldersgate-street	O
between	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
,	O
was	O
met	O
about	O
7	O
within	O
30	O
Yards	O
of	O
Rawlins	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
that	O
about	O
that	O
time	O
4	O
Men	O
were	O
seen	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
1	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
a	O
Person	O
going	O
by	O
,	O
look	O
'd	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
It	O
is	O
not	O
him	O
;	O
That	O
the	O
Woman	O
at	O
the	O
next	O
House	O
,	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
of	O
Scuffling	O
,	O
and	O
(	O
as	O
she	O
express	O
'd	O
it	O
)	O
one	O
Sqwal	O
;	O
that	O
about	O
8	O
a	O
Man	O
saw	O
a	O
Person	O
looking	O
pale	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
Rawlins	O
's	O
House	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
Consternation	O
stamp	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
this	O
way	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
way	O
?	O
That	O
Miller	O
upon	O
her	O
Examination	O
describ	O
'd	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
suppos	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
Murder	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
Blood	O
upon	O
the	O
Boards	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
viewing	O
the	O
Room	O
as	O
she	O
describ	O
'd	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
place	O
in	O
the	O
Boards	O
had	O
been	O
scrap	O
'd	O
as	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
brown	O
spots	O
remaining	O
,	O
suppos	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
Blood	O
:	O
It	O
was	O
proved	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
carry	O
those	O
things	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
Miller	O
mention	O
'd	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
particularly	O
Millers	O
Bedfellow	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Miller	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
a	O
Cheescake	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
bloody	O
Handkerchief	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Webb	O
Rawlins	O
came	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
being	O
Sunday	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
a	O
silver	O
Tobacco	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
beat	O
it	O
to	O
pieces	O
with	O
a	O
Poker	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
a	O
Spying-glass	O
;	O
which	O
this	O
Witnesslooking	O
upon	O
,	O
he	O
swore	O
she	O
must	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Hampson	O
had	O
such	O
things	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
when	O
Murder	O
'd	O
;	O
with	O
many	O
other	O
Circumstances	O
too	O
large	O
to	O
incert	O
in	O
this	O
Paper	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
their	O
defence	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
and	O
Huff	O
produc	O
'd	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
Home	O
from	O
the	O
Morning	O
till	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
that	O
Night	O
at	O
Supper	O
with	O
some	O
Friends	O
at	O
his	O
own	O
House	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
at	O
Old-street	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
St.	O
Crispin	O
's	O
Day	O
,	O
a	O
remarkable	O
time	O
:	O
Webb	O
and	O
Elizabeth	O
Rawlins	O
produc	O
'd	O
Witnesses	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
from	O
Home	O
that	O
Day	O
,	O
neither	O
had	O
there	O
been	O
any	O
Company	O
at	O
their	O
House	O
from	O
the	O
Morning	O
till	O
their	O
time	O
of	O
going	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
except	O
one	O
Man	O
for	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Brandy	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
for	O
a	O
2	O
d	O
Cheescake	O
:	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
Indicted	O
with	O
one	O
James	O
Callow	O
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Jacob	O
Hamson	O
.	O
But	O
that	O
Tryal	O
depending	O
upon	O
the	O
Success	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
did	O
not	O
proceed	O
to	O
the	O
Examination	O
of	O
Witnesses	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Muslen	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
suit	O
of	O
Headcloaths	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Meckinsy	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Mantua	O
Hood	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Crape	O
Gown	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Morrison	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dennis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Trunk	O
till	O
'd	O
with	O
Linen	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
8	O
l.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Mony	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
and	O
Wounding	O
James	B-pers
Alexander	I-pers
the	O
Lord	O
Chancelor	O
's	O
Porter	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chancellors	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
Porter	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
his	O
Lordship	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
his	O
Business	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
Pass	O
for	O
Holland	O
;	O
the	O
Porter	O
directed	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Secretaries	O
Office	O
for	O
a	O
Pass	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
not	O
content	O
with	O
that	O
Answer	O
,	O
abus	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
the	O
Porter	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Arm	O
to	O
turn	O
him	O
out	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
broke	O
his	O
Head	O
with	O
a	O
Cane	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
a	O
Pistol	O
charg	O
'd	O
and	O
shot	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
flash	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Pan	O
.	O
He	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
Reverend	O
Divine	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
declar	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
read	O
Prayers	O
for	O
him	O
in	O
Petticoat-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
behav	O
'd	O
himself	O
with	O
abundance	O
of	O
Modesty	O
and	O
Sobriery	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
reason	O
to	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
disturb	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
Head	O
;	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Christian	B-pers
Valear	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
silver	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
not	O
appearing	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
stolen	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Mot	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Sincleare	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Gattenby	I-pers
50	O
l.	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Mony	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Frankling	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Facts	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mercy	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lovet	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolphs	I-place
without	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Feather	O
Bolster	O
,	O
2	O
Pillows	O
,	O
a	O
Blanket	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Callico	O
Counterpain	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
of	O
Foster	B-pers
Sidwell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
:	O
But	O
none	O
appearing	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
White	B-place
Chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
edg	O
'd	O
Hat	O
,	O
a	O
velvet	O
Cap	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ralph	B-pers
Preswick	I-pers
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
50	O
Yards	O
of	O
Bone	O
Lace	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Lace-Chamber	O
in	O
Aldersgate-street	B-place
,	O
and	O
cheapen	O
'd	O
Lace	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	B-pers
;	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hatfield	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Weatherly	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Filewood	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Show	O
Glass	O
with	O
Goods	O
in	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
130	O
l.	O
belonging	O
to	O
Samuel	B-pers
Pattison	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
about	O
7	O
,	O
the	O
Night	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
were	O
observ	O
'd	O
to	O
walk	O
to	O
and	O
fro	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
observing	O
no	O
Body	O
there	O
,	O
rush	O
'd	O
in	O
,	O
blew	O
out	O
the	O
Candles	O
and	O
convey	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
away	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
immediately	O
pursu	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Wife	O
and	O
Sister	O
,	O
who	O
sat	O
in	O
a	O
back	O
Shop	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
pursuit	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Lamp-light	O
,	O
they	O
saw	O
Weatherly	O
with	O
the	O
Glass	O
of	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
Filewood	O
with	O
a	O
wooden	O
thing	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
;	O
that	O
being	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
pursue	O
them	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Girton	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Robery	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
describ	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
the	O
3	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
further	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
Weatherly	O
was	O
seen	O
about	O
8	O
that	O
Night	O
with	O
the	O
Case	O
of	O
Goods	O
at	O
Hatfield	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
being	O
old	O
Offenders	O
,	O
and	O
saying	O
little	O
for	O
themselves	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
all	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Philip	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Thistleworth	B-place
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
-	B-pers
Hibbard	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
side	O
of	O
his	O
Back	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Leaden	O
Bullet	O
discharg	O
'd	O
from	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languish	O
'd	O
'till	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
were	O
riding	O
together	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
for	O
Thistleworth	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
alighted	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
Gunsmiths	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
charg	O
'd	O
a	O
Brace	O
of	O
Pistols	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Bell	O
Inn	O
at	O
Thistleworth	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
talk	O
'd	O
very	O
extravagantly	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
all	O
the	O
Symptoms	O
of	O
Lunacy	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
staid	O
there	O
a	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
returning	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
with	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
pulling	O
a	O
Pistol	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
presented	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Footman	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
List	O
for	O
a	O
Souldier	O
he	O
would	O
shoot	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
as	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
and	O
Prisoner	O
were	O
walking	O
together	O
he	O
shot	O
him	O
threw	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
died	O
.	O
It	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
premeditated	O
Malice	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
was	O
purely	O
the	O
Effect	O
of	O
Distraction	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Loin	O
of	O
Veal	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Gathorn	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Lavender	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
black	O
Mare	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edmund	B-pers
Peachey	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
1707.	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Murrel	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
18	O
Furbelow	O
Scarves	O
,	O
value	O
64	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Pool	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Causabon	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
left-side	O
of	O
his	O
Belly	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languish	O
'd	O
'till	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
Queen	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
with	O
one	O
Wilford	O
and	O
Noble	O
,	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Kings	O
Arm	O
's	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
between	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
meeting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Rudge	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
(	O
her	O
Husband	O
being	O
before	O
)	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
chuck	O
'd	O
her	O
under	O
the	O
Chin	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
went	O
on	O
,	O
no	O
ill	O
Language	O
passing	O
between	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
going	O
towards	O
Fleet	O
Ditch	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Rudge	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
Satisfaction	O
for	O
the	O
Affront	O
,	O
and	O
justled	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
and	O
his	O
Company	O
into	O
the	O
Dragon	O
Tavern	O
:	O
That	O
Scuffling	O
together	O
along	O
the	O
Entry	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
a	O
Box	O
on	O
the	O
Ear	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
return	O
'd	O
with	O
a	O
small	O
Push	O
;	O
Then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
threw	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Foot	O
of	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Sword	O
was	O
then	O
observ	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
drawn	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Company	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
mortally	O
wounded	O
in	O
the	O
Belly	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
discern	O
'd	O
how	O
it	O
was	O
given	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
brought	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
,	O
that	O
handing	O
Mrs.	O
Rudge	O
along	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
her	O
Husband	O
being	O
then	O
before	O
,	O
were	O
met	O
by	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
and	O
2	O
Men	O
more	O
;	O
That	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
Waist	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
taken	O
her	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
That	O
being	O
affrighted	O
they	O
were	O
forc	O
'd	O
to	O
carry	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
Green	O
Dragon	O
Tavern	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
fell	O
into	O
Fits	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
follow	O
'd	O
them	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
first	O
gave	O
the	O
Assault	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
violent	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
by	O
the	O
Collar	O
and	O
struck	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
flat	O
upon	O
his	O
Back	O
;	O
they	O
then	O
Scuffled	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
both	O
fell	O
down	O
among	O
some	O
Hampers	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Sword	O
was	O
then	O
drawn	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
any	O
Wound	O
?	O
replied	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
not	O
.	O
Not	O
withstanding	O
which	O
,	O
upon	O
search	O
,	O
a	O
Wound	O
was	O
discover	O
'd	O
upon	O
his	O
Belly	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
given	O
by	O
the	O
Sword	O
in	O
the	O
scuffle	O
;	O
but	O
how	O
was	O
not	O
known	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
,	O
brought	O
it	O
in	O
Se	O
Defendendo	O
.	O
B-	O
J-	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
and	O
Contempt	O
,	O
against	O
a	O
late	O
Act	O
of	O
Parliament	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
points	O
of	O
Law	O
being	O
offer	O
'd	O
by	O
his	O
Council	O
,	O
the	O
Record	O
will	O
be	O
removed	O
the	O
next	O
term	O
by	O
Certiorari	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
Queens	O
Bench	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
argued	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgement	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
10	O
.	O
Joseph	O
Hatfield	O
,	O
John	O
Filewood	O
,	O
John	O
Weatherly	O
,	O
Mary	O
Johnson	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Williams	O
,	O
Sarah	O
Faircloth	O
,	O
Ralph	O
Malborn	O
,	O
Mary	O
Salter	O
,	O
Mary	O
Ingram	O
.	O
And	O
Deborah	O
Churchill	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
her	O
former	O
Sentence	O
.	O
Sarah	O
Faircloth	O
pleaded	O
her	O
Belly	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
quick	O
with	O
Child	O
.	O
Burnt	O
In	O
the	O
Hand	O
9	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Gray	O
,	O
James	O
Butler	O
,	O
Ann	O
Price	O
,	O
Mary	O
Williams	O
,	O
Ann	O
Lansdon	O
,	O
Mary	O
Friend	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Stanton	O
,	O
Mary	O
Savage	O
,	O
John	O
Callice	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
Judith	O
Hassard	O
,	O
Sarah	O
Jones	O
.	O
William	O
Scot	O
Fined	O
for	O
his	O
Trespass	O
6l	O
.	O
13s	O
.	O
4d	O
.	O
and	O
to	O
give	O
Security	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
for	O
3	O
Months	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENT	O
.	O
THis	O
is	O
to	O
give	O
Notice	O
,	O
That	O
any	O
Person	O
may	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
Ministers	O
Gowns	O
and	O
Cassocks	O
,	O
Silk	O
and	O
Sashes	O
,	O
Lawyers	O
Gowns	O
and	O
Hoods	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
Gowns	O
for	O
mayors	O
and	O
Aldermen	O
of	O
any	O
Corporation	O
in	O
Great	O
Britain	O
.	O
Sold	O
by	O
Anthony	O
Ingram	O
,	O
Robemaker	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Gown	O
and	O
Livery	O
Hand	O
in	O
Pater-Noster-Row	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
North-Gate	O
of	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church	O
,	O
who	O
hath	O
of	O
them	O
ready	O
made	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
at	O
reasonable	O
Prices	O
.	O
And	O
also	O
Black	O
Cloth	O
and	O
Franella	O
sold	O
for	O
Ministers	O
wear	O
.	O
RObert	O
Whitledge	O
,	O
who	O
formerly	O
lived	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
in	O
Creed	O
Lane	O
,	O
is	O
remov	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Bible	O
and	O
Bull	O
in	O
Ave-Mary	O
Lane	O
,	O
near	O
Ludgate	O
,	O
where	O
all	O
booksellers	O
and	O
others	O
may	O
be	O
furnish	O
'd	O
with	O
Bibles	O
and	O
Common	O
Prayers	O
of	O
all	O
sorts	O
nith	O
Cuts	O
or	O
without	O
,	O
Rul	O
'd	O
or	O
Unrul	O
'd	O
,	O
bound	O
in	O
Turkey	O
Leather	O
or	O
plain	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Sturt	O
's	O
Cuts	O
curiously	O
engraved	O
,	O
also	O
other	O
fine	O
Cuts	O
and	O
fitted	O
for	O
all	O
Sizes	O
of	O
Common	O
Prayer	O
The	O
Duty	O
of	O
Names	O
Works	O
of	O
all	O
Sizes	O
.	O
The	O
Duty	O
of	O
Man	O
in	O
Latin	O
,	O
Latin	O
and	O
French	O
Common	O
Prayers	O
,	O
Tate	O
and	O
Brady	O
's	O
New	O
version	O
of	O
Psalms	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
new	O
Suplements	O
.	O
D.	O
Gibson	O
on	O
the	O
Sacrement	O
.	O
The	O
Statutes	O
at	O
large	O
,	O
in	O
3	O
vols	O
.	O
Washington	O
and	O
Witgate	O
's	O
Abridgement	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Lord	O
Clarendon	O
's	O
History	O
of	O
the	O
rebellion	O
,	O
in	O
Folio	O
and	O
Octavo	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
new	O
Translation	O
of	O
Esopistables	O
.	O
All	O
which	O
Cuts	O
are	O
likewise	O
sold	O
by	O
J.	O
Baker	O
in	O
Mercer	O
Chapplen	O
Chastice	O
.	O
Also	O
Bp	O
.	O
Beveriages	O
Wares	O
in	O
5	O
Vol	O
.	O
Dean	O
Stanhope	O
on	O
the	O
Epistles	O
and	O
Gospels	O
in	O
4	O
Vol	O
.	O
THE	O
Charitable	O
Surgeon	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
the	O
best	O
Remedies	O
for	O
the	O
worst	O
Maladies	O
,	O
reveal	O
'd	O
.	O
Being	O
a	O
new	O
and	O
true	O
way	O
of	O
curing	O
without	O
Mercury	O
)	O
the	O
several	O
degrees	O
of	O
the	O
Venereal	O
Distemper	O
in	O
both	O
Sexes	O
,	O
whereby	O
all	O
Persons	O
,	O
even	O
the	O
meanest	O
Capacities	O
,	O
may	O
for	O
an	O
inconsiderable	O
Charge	O
,	O
without	O
confinement	O
or	O
knowledge	O
of	O
the	O
nearest	O
Relations	O
cure	O
themselves	O
easily	O
,	O
speedily	O
and	O
safely	O
,	O
by	O
The	O
without	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
any	O
Physician	O
,	O
Surgeon	O
or	O
Apothecary	O
;	O
to	O
the	O
hazardous	O
attempts	O
of	O
Quacks	O
and	O
Pretenders	O
.	O
To	O
discovery	O
of	O
the	O
true	O
Seat	O
of	O
Claps	O
in	O
Man	O
and	O
Women	O
,	O
different	O
from	O
the	O
commonly	O
received	O
Opinion	O
of	O
Authors	O
.	O
As	O
also	O
a	O
peculiar	O
Method	O
of	O
curing	O
their	O
Giects	O
and	O
Weaknesses	O
,	O
whether	O
Venereal	O
,	O
or	O
otherwise	O
;	O
with	O
some	O
other	O
pertinent	O
Observations	O
relating	O
thereto	O
,	O
never	O
being	O
taken	O
notice	O
of	O
.	O
Likewise	O
the	O
certain	O
easie	O
way	O
to	O
escape	O
Infection	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
never	O
so	O
often	O
accompanying	O
with	O
the	O
most	O
Companion	O
.	O
By	O
T.	O
C.	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
Printed	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
Edmund	O
Courle	O
at	O
the	O
Peacock	O
without	O
Temple	O
Bar	O
,	O
1708.	O
price	O
stitch	O
'd	O
1s	O
.	O
The	O
fam	O
'd	O
Canker	O
Water	O
.	O
WHich	O
so	O
perfectly	O
and	O
immediately	O
cures	O
all	O
Cankers	O
,	O
Sores	O
,	O
Pustules	O
,	O
Heats	O
and	O
Inflammations	O
in	O
the	O
Mouth	O
that	O
never	O
so	O
far	O
gone	O
,	O
even	O
to	O
the	O
loss	O
of	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Tongue	O
,	O
Cheeks	O
,	O
or	O
Lips	O
;	O
it	O
has	O
saved	O
the	O
Lives	O
of	O
several	O
both	O
Men	O
,	O
Women	O
and	O
Children	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
easily	O
to	O
be	O
had	O
at	O
Robins	O
Coffee-house	O
in	O
Exchange-alley	O
,	O
at	O
2s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
the	O
Bottle	O
,	O
with	O
Printed	O
Directions	O
.	O
Note	O
,	O
Its	O
vertue	O
decays	O
not	O
in	O
keeping	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
very	O
useful	O
and	O
much	O
esteemed	O
at	O
Sea	O
.	O
MArten	O
's	O
Treatise	O
being	O
the	O
Sixth	O
Edition	O
,	O
with	O
large	O
additions	O
on	O
all	O
the	O
Degrees	O
and	O
Symptoms	O
of	O
the	O
Venereal	O
Disease	O
,	O
in	O
both	O
Sexes	O
;	O
Explicating	O
Naturally	O
and	O
Mechanically	O
its	O
causes	O
,	O
Kinds	O
,	O
various	O
Ways	O
of	O
Infecting	O
;	O
the	O
Nature	O
of	O
Hereditary	O
Infection	O
,	O
Certainty	O
of	O
knowing	O
whether	O
Infected	O
or	O
not	O
;	O
Infallible	O
Way	O
to	O
prevent	O
Infection	O
;	O
Business	O
of	O
Cure	O
when	O
Infected	O
;	O
Reasons	O
why	O
so	O
many	O
miss	O
of	O
Cure	O
;	O
how	O
to	O
know	O
when	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
not	O
,	O
in	O
Skilful	O
Hands	O
for	O
Cure	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Use	O
and	O
Abuse	O
of	O
Mercury	O
in	O
the	O
Cure	O
.	O
Necessary	O
to	O
be	O
Read	O
and	O
Observe	O
'd	O
by	O
all	O
Persons	O
that	O
Now	O
have	O
,	O
Ever	O
had	O
,	O
(	O
many	O
other	O
Diseases	O
being	O
occasion	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Venereal	O
Taint	O
and	O
Mercury	O
,	O
)	O
or	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
May	O
have	O
the	O
Misfortune	O
of	O
that	O
Distemper	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
prevent	O
their	O
being	O
Ruin	O
'd	O
by	O
Ignorant	O
Pretenders	O
,	O
Quacks	O
,	O
Mountebanks	O
,	O
Impostors	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
whose	O
Notorious	O
Practices	O
are	O
clearly	O
evinc	O
'd	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
the	O
Cause	O
and	O
Cure	O
of	O
old	O
Gleets	O
,	O
and	O
Weaknesses	O
in	O
Men	O
and	O
Women	O
,	O
whether	O
Venereal	O
or	O
Seminal	O
,	O
briefly	O
describing	O
the	O
Use	O
and	O
Abuse	O
of	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
and	O
why	O
Gleets	O
(	O
as	O
sometimes	O
they	O
do	O
)	O
hinder	O
Procreation	O
causing	O
Impotency	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
Men	O
,	O
and	O
Sterility	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
Women	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
Remarkable	O
Cures	O
of	O
that	O
Kind	O
inserted	O
.	O
The	O
whole	O
interspersed	O
with	O
peculiar	O
Prescriptions	O
,	O
many	O
Pertinent	O
Observations	O
,	O
Histories	O
and	O
Letters	O
,	O
of	O
very	O
Remarkable	O
Cures	O
.	O
The	O
like	O
for	O
general	O
Advantage	O
never	O
Publish	O
'd	O
,	O
by	O
any	O
Author	O
,	O
Ancient	O
Modern	O
,	O
since	O
the	O
Disease	O
came	O
first	O
to	O
be	O
known	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
.	O
Sold	O
by	O
N.	O
Crouch	O
at	O
the	O
Bell	O
in	O
Cornhil	O
,	O
J.	O
Knapton	O
and	O
M.	O
Atkins	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church	O
yard	O
,	O
A.	O
Collins	O
at	O
the	O
Black	O
Boy	O
in	O
Fleetstreet	O
,	O
P.	O
Varenne	O
at	O
Saracen	O
's	O
Head	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
Ch	O
.	O
King	O
in	O
Westminster-Hall	O
;	O
Booksellers	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
Author	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
further	O
end	O
of	O
Hatton-Garden	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Left-hand	O
beyond	O
the	O
Chappel	O
,	O
John	O
Marten	O
Surgeon	O
writ	O
over	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
Price	O
Bound	O
4s	O
.	O
Speedily	O
will	O
be	O
Publish	O
'd	O
.	O
THe	O
Truth	O
of	O
the	O
Case	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
a	O
full	O
and	O
true	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
horrid	O
Murders	O
,	O
Robberies	O
and	O
Burnings	O
,	O
committed	O
at	O
Bradtorten	O
and	O
Upton	O
Snodsbury	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Worcester	O
;	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
Apprehension	O
,	O
Examination	O
,	O
Tryal	O
and	O
Conviction	O
,	O
of	O
John	O
Palmer	O
,	O
and	O
Tho	O
.	O
Symonds	O
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
William	O
Hobbins	O
and	O
John	O
Allen	O
,	O
Labourers	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Crimes	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
the	O
Bp	O
.	O
Of	O
Oxford	O
's	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
after	O
their	O
Condemnation	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
his	O
Lordship	O
's	O
whose	O
Transaction	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
written	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Bishop	O
.	O
Likewise	O
,	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
what	O
pass	O
'd	O
between	O
the	O
Ordinary	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
-	O
And	O
remarks	O
on	O
their	O
dying	O
Speeches	O
.	O
Publish	O
'd	O
on	O
Occasion	O
of	O
a	O
late	O
imperfect	O
,	O
false	O
and	O
scandalous	O
Libel	O
,	O
Entituled	O
the	O
Case	O
of	O
John	O
Palmer	O
and	O
Thomas	O
Symonds	O
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
who	O
were	O
executed	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
By	O
R.W	O
.	O
-	O
Printed	O
for	O
Jonah	O
Bowyer	O
at	O
the	O
Rose	O
in	O
Ludgate-street	O
,	O
1708	O
.	O
REmov	O
'd	O
from	O
the	O
three	O
Black-Birds	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
,	O
into	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
,	O
in	O
Widegate-Ally	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
White-Wing	O
and	O
Barbers-Pole	O
.	O
Is	O
to	O
be	O
Sold	O
,	O
a	O
never-failing	O
Ointment	O
that	O
Cures	O
the	O
Gout	O
,	O
although	O
the	O
Parties	O
be	O
reduc	O
'd	O
to	O
their	O
Crutches	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
time	O
,	O
having	O
often	O
been	O
found	O
true	O
by	O
Experience	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
great	O
Ease	O
and	O
Comfort	O
of	O
many	O
;	O
it	O
also	O
cures	O
Rheumatick	O
Pains	O
.	O
Likewise	O
a	O
certain	O
and	O
infallible	O
Cure	O
for	O
the	O
Tooth-Ache	O
,	O
without	O
Drawing	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
effectually	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Pain	O
will	O
never	O
return	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
only	O
so	O
,	O
but	O
makes	O
teeth	O
as	O
white	O
as	O
Ivory	O
,	O
and	O
fastens	O
those	O
that	O
are	O
loose	O
to	O
Admiration	O
.	O
THE	O
Arraignment	O
,	O
Tryal	O
and	O
Conviction	O
of	O
Robert	O
Fielding	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
for	O
Felony	O
in	O
Marrying	O
her	O
Grace	O
the	O
Dutchess	O
of	O
Cleeaveland	O
;	O
his	O
first	O
Wife	O
Mary	O
Wadsworth	O
being	O
then	O
alive	O
.	O
With	O
Copies	O
of	O
the	O
several	O
Letters	O
between	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fielding	O
and	O
his	O
first	O
Wife	O
Mrs	O
Wadsworth	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Anne	O
Countess	O
of	O
Fielding	O
.	O
As	O
also	O
all	O
the	O
Learned	O
Arguments	O
of	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Council	O
.	O
Perused	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Judges	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
Tryal	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Proceedings	O
against	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
spiritual	O
Court	O
at	O
Doctors	O
Commons	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Sentence	O
given	O
against	O
him	O
there	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
John	O
Morphew	O
near	O
Stationers-Hall	O
,	O
1708.	O
price	O
1s	O
.	O
ALL	O
Melancholly	O
and	O
Hypochondriacal	O
Distempers	O
of	O
Wind	O
,	O
with	O
strange	O
Fears	O
,	O
dismal	O
Apprehensions	O
,	O
great	O
Oppressions	O
and	O
Sinking	O
of	O
spirits	O
(	O
little	O
understood	O
,	O
and	O
seldom	O
Cured	O
by	O
any	O
common	O
Means	O
)	O
also	O
the	O
most	O
extreme	O
Giddinesses	O
,	O
and	O
Pains	O
in	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
Faintings	O
,	O
Tremblings	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
other	O
Disorders	O
arising	O
from	O
Vapours	O
;	O
are	O
successfully	O
cure	O
(	O
with	O
God	O
's	O
Blessing	O
)	O
by	O
a	O
Physician	O
well	O
experience	O
'd	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
more	O
than	O
20	O
Years	O
Practice	O
in	O
those	O
deplorable	O
Cases	O
:	O
who	O
also	O
Cures	O
Convulsions	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
the	O
most	O
strange	O
and	O
violent	O
Fits	O
,	O
if	O
curable	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
informs	O
on	O
sight	O
of	O
their	O
Water	O
,	O
Living	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
Shadwell	O
Coffee-House	O
,	O
in	O
upper-Shadwell	O
,	O
near	O
London	O
:	O
Where	O
those	O
that	O
have	O
occasion	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
remote	O
,	O
may	O
direct	O
their	O
Letters	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
shall	O
be	O
speedily	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
or	O
attended	O
on	O
if	O
desired	O
.	O
AN	O
Infallible	O
Cure	O
for	O
Ruptures	O
or	O
broken	O
Bellies	O
in	O
Men	O
,	O
Women	O
,	O
and	O
Children	O
,	O
with	O
much	O
Ease	O
and	O
Safety	O
,	O
by	O
wearing	O
of	O
easy	O
Spring-Trusses	O
,	O
the	O
finest	O
and	O
lightest	O
in	O
Great	O
Britain	O
or	O
Ireland	O
.	O
May	O
be	O
had	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Wigg	O
in	O
Whitegate-Ally	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
,	O
London	O
:	O
Being	O
made	O
by	O
one	O
that	O
has	O
had	O
great	O
Experience	O
.	O
