TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
Queen	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
Held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD	O
BAYLY	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
6th	O
,	O
7th	O
,	O
8th	O
and	O
9th	O
,	O
days	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
1710	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Ninth	O
Year	O
of	O
Her	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEfore	O
the	O
Rt	O
.	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
GARRARD	I-pers
,	O
Baronet	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
Peter	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
Her	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
John	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
John	B-pers
Walton	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Read	I-pers
William	B-pers
Floyd	I-pers
John	B-pers
Horn	I-pers
Nathaniel	B-pers
Chavet	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Unwinn	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Nelms	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Somes	I-pers
John	B-pers
Sherriff	I-pers
William	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Charles	B-pers
Munden	I-pers
Daniel	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
Benjamin	B-pers
Gascoign	I-pers
Nicholas	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
Jun	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Dicks	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
John	B-pers
Street	I-pers
Nathaniel	B-pers
Ravener	I-pers
Simon	B-pers
Ravener	I-pers
John	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Mary	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Debuke	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
were	O
both	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
,	O
a	O
silver	O
Watch	O
with	O
a	O
Tortois	O
Shell	O
Case	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
pick	O
'd	O
up	O
Elizabeth	O
Debuke	O
at	O
Green-Goose	O
Fair	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
her	O
into	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
;	O
that	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
there	O
together	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
his	O
Watch	O
privately	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Fob	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
clearly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
any	O
thing	O
upon	O
Lee	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Algate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
153	O
pound	O
of	O
Beef	O
,	O
value	O
34	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
our	O
Sovereign	O
Lady	O
the	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
some	O
Beef	O
had	O
been	O
missing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Stores	O
;	O
on	O
Tower-Hill	B-place
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
House	O
being	O
searcht	O
,	O
39	O
pieces	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Privy	O
,	O
weighing	O
some	O
pieces	O
3	O
pound	O
,	O
some	O
4	O
pound	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
after	O
the	O
manner	O
of	O
those	O
that	O
were	O
stol'n	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
giving	O
a	O
trifling	O
Account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Mordecai	B-pers
Witington	I-pers
,	O
by	O
driving	O
his	O
Horses	O
over	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
occasion	O
'd	O
one	O
mortal	O
Bruise	O
in	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
of	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
near	O
his	O
left	O
Temple	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languish	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
May	O
following	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
driving	O
his	O
Cart	O
and	O
Horses	O
in	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
High-way	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
being	O
then	O
on	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
was	O
push	O
'd	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
fore	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
receiv	O
'd	O
a	O
bruise	O
in	O
the	O
Head	O
from	O
the	O
Foot	O
of	O
the	O
2d	O
Horse	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
Surgeons	O
depos	O
'd	O
he	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
from	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drove	O
a	O
moderate	O
Pace	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
his	O
Horses	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
not	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Accident	O
happen	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
stop	O
'd	O
his	O
Horses	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
People	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
it	O
in	O
Chance	O
Medly	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Maw	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolphs	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
the	O
was	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
Pewter	O
and	O
wearing	O
Cloths	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
value	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
went	O
from	O
his	O
House	O
about	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
returning	O
about	O
6	O
found	O
it	O
broken	O
upon	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Goods	O
gone	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
same	O
Morning	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
as	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
'em	O
to	O
Sale	O
.	O
He	O
saying	O
little	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Proof	O
being	O
given	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
that	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Jacobs	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
River	O
of	O
Thames	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
High-way	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
silk	O
Hood	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Cap	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Holland	O
Apron	O
3	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Tyler	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hammersmith	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Damask	O
Napkins	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Hucka	O
bag	O
Napkin	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ayres	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
having	O
lost	O
some	O
Linnen	O
,	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
searching	O
her	O
Lodging	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolphs	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
a	O
Rug	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Blanket	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Darby	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
going	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Shop	O
,	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
snatch	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
the	O
Shop	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
pursu	O
'd	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Street	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Marrying	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Scarlet	I-pers
,	O
a	O
second	O
Wife	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
his	O
first	O
Wife	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
whom	O
he	O
Marry	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
1706.	O
being	O
living	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
substantially	O
prov	O
'd	O
the	O
1st	O
Marriage	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
appearing	O
no	O
Proof	O
of	O
the	O
2d	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Bragg	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Peters	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Denmare	I-pers
,	O
by	O
driving	O
the	O
near	O
Wheel	O
of	O
his	O
Coach	O
over	O
his	O
left	O
Leg	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languish	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
November	O
following	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
Indicted	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroners	O
inquest	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Manslaughter	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Denmare	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
being	O
an	O
under	O
Beadle	O
,	O
and	O
whose	O
business	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
regulate	O
the	O
standing	O
of	O
Coaches	O
in	O
Cornhill	B-place
,	O
observ	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Stand	O
,	O
order	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
drive	O
to	O
such	O
a	O
Place	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
refusing	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Horses	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
whipt	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
drove	O
them	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Wheels	O
ran	O
over	O
his	O
Leg	O
and	O
broke	O
it	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Hurt	O
the	O
Surgeons	O
depos	O
'd	O
he	O
died	O
.	O
It	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
any	O
premeditated	O
Malice	O
against	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Forest	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
her	O
Male	O
Bastard	O
Infant	O
,	O
by	O
strangling	O
it	O
with	O
both	O
Hands	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
of	O
which	O
it	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
Date	O
above	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
Child	O
was	O
found	O
Dead	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
near	O
Mile	O
End	O
,	O
and	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
It	O
further	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
born	O
about	O
5	O
that	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
calling	O
no	O
Person	O
to	O
her	O
Assistance	O
,	O
neither	O
had	O
she	O
made	O
any	O
Provision	O
for	O
the	O
Birth	O
of	O
the	O
Child	O
as	O
the	O
Law	O
requires	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
Still	O
born	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Proof	O
appearing	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Baldwin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
,	O
open	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Moletrap	I-pers
adjoining	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Ralph	B-pers
Winsor	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
12	O
Ells	O
of	O
Holland	O
value	O
24	O
s.	O
60	O
Yards	O
of	O
Ferrit	O
Ribbon	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Moletrap	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Miles	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
brown	O
Gelding	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
How	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
his	O
Gelding	O
from	O
a	O
Common	O
;	O
and	O
apprehending	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
saying	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Garret	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Gilot	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Olive	I-place
Silver-street	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Box	O
with	O
a	O
silk	O
Gowns	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
petticoats	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
wearing	O
Cloaths	O
value	O
25	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	B-pers
alighting	O
from	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
her	O
Goods	O
which	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Hay	O
Box	O
were	O
seen	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
from	O
thence	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
fled	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
pursu	O
'd	O
he	O
dropt	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
David	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Tims	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
2	O
pieces	O
of	O
Printed	O
Callicoe	O
containing	O
19	O
Yards	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
Jones	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Shop	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
one	O
Mr.	O
King	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
answer	O
'd	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
quick	O
about	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
the	O
Shop	O
Window	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
taken	O
going	O
off	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
saying	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
reaching	O
Tims	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Haddington	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Isleworth	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
gold	O
Ring	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Birket	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
his	O
Goods	O
from	O
his	O
Parlor	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
suspecting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Day	O
Labourer	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
caus	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
examin	O
'd	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
12	O
s.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
positive	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gouge	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Black	I-place
Friars	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Sheet	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Dimitty	O
Petticoat	O
3	O
s.	O
3	O
Diaper	O
Napkins	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
1	O
Guinea	O
,	O
2	O
gold	O
Rings	O
and	O
18	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Mony	O
of	O
Jacob	B-pers
Lesturgeon	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
going	O
out	O
left	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
alone	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
return	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
missing	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
aftewards	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
her	O
Examination	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
directed	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
the	O
Places	O
were	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
nothing	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
some	O
Linnen	O
,	O
Wearing	O
Cloths	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Briston	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Cambell	I-pers
.	O
This	O
Indictment	O
like	O
wise	O
being	O
clearly	O
proved	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
brass	O
Kettles	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Servant	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
the	O
Shop	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
pursu	O
'd	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Mary	B-pers
Weaver	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolphs	I-place
without	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Askew	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Herbert	B-pers
Smale	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
and	O
Ralph	B-pers
Wittingham	I-pers
,	O
were	O
as	O
three	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Riot	O
and	O
Fray	O
in	O
Black	B-place
Friars	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appealing	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Weaver	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Weaver	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cullen	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
the	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Cane	O
with	O
a	O
silver	O
Head	O
,	O
3	O
yards	O
of	O
Holland	O
Cloth	O
and	O
Sarcenet	O
Hood	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Cullen	I-pers
,	O
and	O
48	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elipholes	B-pers
Murry	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
Evans	O
was	O
a	O
Peruke	O
Makers	O
Apprentice	O
that	O
Lodg	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
Cullen	O
:	O
In	O
the	O
Night	O
aforesaid	O
he	O
run	O
away	O
from	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
missing	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
It	O
further	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
2	O
were	O
concern	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gratrix	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Surrupsal	I-pers
,	O
by	O
striking	O
and	O
bruiung	O
her	O
with	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Pot	O
upon	O
the	O
Head	O
and	O
right	O
side	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
languish	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
July	O
following	O
and	O
then	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
again	O
Indicted	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Sarah	O
Surupsal	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
,	O
were	O
at	O
Dinner	O
together	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
that	O
after	O
Dinner	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
arose	O
between	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
quart	O
Pewter	O
Pot	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
divers	O
Blows	O
upon	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
right	O
Side	O
,	O
which	O
by	O
the	O
Judgment	O
of	O
the	O
Surgeons	O
was	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
her	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cocoa	O
Nutshell	O
Cup	O
tip	O
'd	O
with	O
Silver	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
suit	O
of	O
lac	O
'd	O
Headcloths	O
8	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
destitute	O
of	O
a	O
Lodging	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	B-pers
out	O
of	O
kindness	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Lodging	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
returning	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
things	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
taken	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
William	B-pers
Cripp	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Babb	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Twittenham	I-place
,	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Roust	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
wooden	O
Staff	O
upon	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languish	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
June	O
following	O
and	O
then	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Babb	I-pers
,	O
for	O
being	O
aiding	O
and	O
assisting	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
likewise	O
Indicted	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Roust	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
came	O
by	O
his	O
Death	O
in	O
a	O
Fray	O
,	O
which	O
happen	O
'd	O
about	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
on	O
the	O
Date	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
and	O
occasion	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
young	O
Men	O
of	O
Twittenham	O
Fighting	O
with	O
those	O
of	O
Teddington	O
,	O
for	O
their	O
May	O
Pole	O
.	O
But	O
their	O
appearing	O
no	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
against	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wilder	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstans	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
being	O
Accessary	O
after	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
for	O
Harbouring	O
,	O
Receiving	O
,	O
Maintaining	O
and	O
Incouraging	O
Mary	B-pers
Cliff	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
made	O
her	O
Escape	O
from	O
the	O
Keeper	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
Convicted	O
for	O
Shop-Lifting	O
in	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
he	O
knowing	O
she	O
had	O
so	O
made	O
her	O
Escape	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
carrying	O
from	O
the	O
Old	O
Baily	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
she	O
made	O
her	O
Escape	O
through	O
the	O
Crowd	O
in	O
a	O
Riding	O
Hood	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
Rainy	O
Day	O
.	O
Upon	O
Enquiry	O
made	O
,	O
Information	O
was	O
given	O
to	O
the	O
Keeper	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
the	O
said	O
Cliff	O
,	O
and	O
declar	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
of	O
her	O
Escape	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
2	O
Guineas	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
before	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
;	O
he	O
by	O
Consent	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
he	O
saw	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
then	O
own	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
given	O
her	O
so	O
much	O
Mony	O
,	O
and	O
promis	O
'd	O
to	O
use	O
his	O
Endeavours	O
to	O
retake	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
Desir	O
'd	O
the	O
Keeper	O
to	O
be	O
Easy	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Man	O
should	O
have	O
his	O
Mare	O
again	O
;	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
consider	O
'd	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Court	O
being	O
of	O
opinion	O
that	O
some	O
point	O
of	O
Law	O
would	O
arise	O
,	O
directed	O
the	O
Jury	O
to	O
find	O
it	O
Special	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
did	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Housden	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Pitman	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Roach	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Counterfeiting	O
the	O
current	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
call	O
'd	O
Shillings	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
One	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Person	O
concern	O
'd	O
with	O
them	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
Date	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
the	O
3	O
Prisoners	O
with	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
were	O
all	O
Coining	O
together	O
at	O
Pitmans	O
House	O
:	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
made	O
this	O
Discovery	O
,	O
a	O
Warrant	O
was	O
granted	O
to	O
search	O
it	O
,	O
where	O
was	O
found	O
a	O
Flask	O
,	O
a	O
melting	O
Laddle	O
,	O
Mettle	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
fit	O
for	O
Counterfeit	O
Coining	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Housden	I-pers
was	O
likewise	O
apprehended	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
put	O
into	O
a	O
Boat	O
by	O
the	O
Constable	O
was	O
observed	O
to	O
drop	O
something	O
into	O
the	O
Water	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
Boy	O
,	O
being	O
sent	O
down	O
,	O
brought	O
up	O
5	O
l.	O
odd	O
Money	O
of	O
Counterfeit	O
Shillings	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
produced	O
inCourt	O
,	O
and	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
.	O
Housden	O
and	O
Pitman	O
saying	O
little	O
for	O
themselves	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
strong	O
enough	O
against	O
Roach	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
stuff	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
silk	O
Petticoat	O
Petticoat	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
silk	O
Gown	O
30	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
Stockings	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
,	O
on	O
July	O
13	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
,	O
so	O
uttering	O
2	O
K.	O
Charles	O
's	O
Shilling	O
gilt	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
French	O
Pistole	O
,	O
to	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Town	I-pers
,	O
on	O
May	O
20	O
last	O
,	O
he	O
knowing	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
gilt	O
Shilling	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ow	O
'd	O
Town	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
making	O
his	O
Boasts	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
both	O
Gold	O
and	O
Silver	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
Town	O
's	O
Wife	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
Then	O
pay	O
my	O
Husband	O
the	O
Mony	O
you	O
owe	O
him	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
produc	O
'd	O
the	O
gilt	O
Shilling	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
Pistole	O
,	O
and	O
giving	O
no	O
account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Trespass	O
.	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samuel	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
Quern	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
100	O
l.	O
weight	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bagnall	I-pers
,	O
on	O
September	O
2	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
clearly	O
prov	O
'd	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Mary	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
38	O
Yards	O
of	O
Drugget	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
,	O
on	O
July	O
12	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
and	O
cheapn	O
'd	O
Drugget	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
the	O
Servant	O
's	O
Back	O
was	O
turn	O
'd	O
,	O
Davis	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
under	O
her	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
discover	O
'd	O
and	O
brought	O
back	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
;	O
but	O
nothing	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
against	O
Wells	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Matthew	B-pers
Galpin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mildred	I-place
Poultry	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
,	O
on	O
June	O
18	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Ale	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
was	O
gone	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
where	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
,	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
with	O
it	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Salter	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
a	O
Razor-Case	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
10	O
Razors	O
1	O
l.	O
on	O
August	O
17	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Male	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
5	O
gold	O
Rings	O
3	O
l.	O
2	O
Guineas	O
and	O
40	O
s.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
on	O
July	O
7	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
while	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
with	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
Examined	O
,	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Marles	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cow	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
on	O
August	O
31	O
last	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
his	O
Cow	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
found	O
her	O
Hide	O
in	O
Leaden-hall	O
Market	O
;	O
the	O
Butcher	O
prov	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Cow	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
giving	O
no	O
account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elisabeth	B-pers
Cousins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Kettle	O
,	O
a	O
brass	O
Saucepan	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Bible	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Esther	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
on	O
August	O
6	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
privately	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
gone	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
missing	O
but	O
being	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
she	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
French	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
on	O
July	O
29	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
whether	O
such	O
a	O
Person	O
lodg	O
'd	O
there	O
?	O
but	O
being	O
answer	O
'd	O
no	O
,	O
she	O
desir	O
'd	O
the	O
Servant	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Privy	O
;	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
through	O
a	O
Wash-house	O
where	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
afterwards	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
making	O
no	O
defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Poddy	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
an	O
Assault	O
upon	O
John	B-pers
Sollars	I-pers
,	O
with	O
an	O
intention	O
to	O
commit	O
Sodomy	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
strong	O
enough	O
to	O
convict	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
gold	O
Chain	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
l.	O
3	O
gold	O
Rings	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
Mug	O
40	O
s.	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
value	O
,	O
and	O
40	O
s.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Mony	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Tumber	I-pers
,	O
on	O
August	O
1	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
known	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
on	O
the	O
Date	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
be	O
down	O
upon	O
his	O
Bed	O
;	O
and	O
leave	O
being	O
given	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
gone	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
being	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
,	O
most	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
making	O
an	O
ample	O
Confession	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Osney	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Winby	I-pers
,	O
on	O
August	O
10	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
carried	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
he	O
slipt	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joan	B-pers
Merryway	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Tickin	O
Apron	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Linen	O
Smock	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Travan	I-pers
,	O
on	O
August	O
20	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
proving	O
nothing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
good	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hartford	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Herbert	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cocoa	O
Nutshel	O
Box	O
,	O
tipt	O
with	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
laced	O
Headcloths	O
5	O
s.	O
another	O
of	O
plain	O
Headcloths	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
silk	O
Hoods	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Isabel	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
May	O
9	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
none	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Grimes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Evan	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Drugget	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Headcloaths	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Susannah	B-pers
Rowland	I-pers
,	O
on	O
August	O
11	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
provin	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sack	O
of	O
Wheat-Meal	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Alice	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
on	O
March	O
25	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Isleworth	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
200	O
l.	O
weight	O
of	O
Iron	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Birt	I-pers
,	O
on	O
July	O
9	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
his	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Barn	O
,	O
and	O
suspecting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Iron	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
confessing	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Richard	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
Bullar	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
3	O
pair	O
of	O
Womens	O
Shoes	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Morgan	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
on	O
June	O
13	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
Bullar	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
;	O
that	O
while	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
busie	O
in	O
trying	O
a	O
Pair	O
,	O
Brown	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
that	O
opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
those	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
off	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
discovered	O
,	O
was	O
pursued	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
taken	O
with	O
them	O
upon	O
him	O
:	O
Bullar	O
being	O
stopped	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
fell	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
beat	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
bit	O
her	O
upon	O
the	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
Escape	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
an	O
Argument	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
a	O
confederate	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Woolchurch	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
14	O
dozen	O
pair	O
of	O
wooden	O
Clogs	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Roger	B-pers
Penny	I-pers
,	O
on	O
August	O
26	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
having	O
lost	O
a	O
great	O
quantity	O
of	O
Clogs	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
two	O
Shops	O
;	O
to	O
fix	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
one	O
Soulthorp	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
bought	O
10	O
Pair	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
part	O
of	O
those	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
giving	O
no	O
account	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Martha	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Painter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dutton	I-pers
half	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
Shalon	O
scanes	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
and	O
15	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
on	O
September	O
5	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Markes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
dwelling-House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
4	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
on	O
September	O
6	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Daughter	O
going	O
from	O
her	O
Mothers	O
Shop	O
about	O
8	O
,	O
shut	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
returning	O
at	O
9	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Door	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
Goods	O
immediately	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cousins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Priscilia	B-pers
Begs	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
privately	O
away	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
,	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
James	B-pers
Goswell	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
25	O
Chickens	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Anne	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Bourn	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
upon	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
High-way	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
one	O
Guinea	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
:	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
Mary	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
being	O
a	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
Debt	O
,	O
a	O
Friend	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Guinea	O
which	O
she	O
gave	O
to	O
her	O
Son	O
,	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Collins	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
observing	O
it	O
,	O
followed	O
John	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
to	O
St.	B-place
Martins-lane	I-place
,	O
where	O
she	O
by	O
force	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hands	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
Positive	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
little	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sugg	I-pers
of	O
30	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
again	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Maunders	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Mantua	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Petticoat	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Cloath	O
Petticot	O
Laced	O
with	O
Silver	O
Orrace	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Catherine	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
any	O
thing	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Travalion	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Grace	B-pers
Hubbert	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Camlet	O
Riding	O
Hood	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Davison	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
very	O
poor	O
Woman	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
Hubbert	O
out	O
of	O
pity	O
took	O
her	O
into	O
her	O
House	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
there	O
long	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
away	O
privately	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
being	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
,	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
she	O
pawned	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Mary	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
24	O
Yards	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Callicoe	O
,	O
Night	O
Gown	O
5	O
s.	O
with	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Stanley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cutlar	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Wast	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shagg	O
Breeches	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
lac	O
'd	O
Neck-cloth	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Lunn	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
logded	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
date	O
aforesaid	O
she	O
stript	O
his	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Cloths	O
;	O
that	O
being	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
,	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Goddard	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Farthing	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
both	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
13	O
pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bilthon	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
observed	O
to	O
walk	O
to	O
and	O
fro	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
Goddard	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
over	O
the	O
Shop	O
Window	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
off	O
,	O
was	O
himself	O
taken	O
with	O
them	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
strong	O
enough	O
against	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Meekins	I-pers
and	O
Rodery	B-pers
Odery	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
12	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Mony	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Farren	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
date	O
aforesaid	O
at	O
Midnight	O
,	O
the	O
Watch	O
found	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Cellar	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
knocking	O
up	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
he	O
looked	O
to	O
see	O
whether	O
any	O
thing	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
but	O
finding	O
every	O
thing	O
safe	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
again	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Watch	O
finding	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
again	O
,	O
called	O
up	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
,	O
who	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Mony	O
mentioned	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Box	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
being	O
immediately	O
taken	O
,	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
both	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Charles	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Shipperton	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intention	O
to	O
Steal	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
Chattel	O
and	O
Mony	O
thereof	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
Queen	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
June	O
about	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
one	O
Crouch	O
entered	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Chamber	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
with	O
his	O
Wife	O
were	O
in	O
Bed	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
going	O
to	O
Cry	O
out	O
,	O
Dean	O
threatened	O
to	O
Stab	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
desisting	O
,	O
he	O
Bound	O
her	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
Bed	O
,	O
that	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
dragged	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Room	O
,	O
assaulting	O
him	O
after	O
a	O
very	O
Violent	O
manner	O
and	O
with	O
an	O
Iron	O
Crow	O
,	O
broke	O
his	O
Scull	O
in	O
divers	O
places	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
his	O
Life	O
is	O
dispaired	O
of	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
by	O
divers	O
of	O
the	O
Family	O
who	O
knew	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
positive	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
Day	O
coming	O
on	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
being	O
apprehended	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
without	O
taking	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
when	O
gone	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
that	O
an	O
Entry	O
was	O
made	O
in	O
the	O
Brick-wall	O
where	O
the	O
Sink	O
was	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Iron	O
Crow	O
aforesaid	O
:	O
Besides	O
this	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
Hat	O
and	O
peruke	O
,	O
was	O
left	O
behind	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
at	O
Brentford	O
by	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
without	O
those	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
pretended	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
met	O
with	O
Thieves	O
who	O
had	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
met	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
London	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
a	O
Hucabuck	O
Napkin	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
-	B-pers
Poole	I-pers
and	O
Katherine	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
apprehended	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Jane	B-pers
Jenkinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
15	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
2	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
from	O
Francis	B-pers
Pennington	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Door	O
being	O
left	O
open	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
slipt	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
apprehended	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Patience	B-pers
Gascoyne	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Fox	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tompion	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
Gascoyne	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Watch	O
and	O
Chain	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
Snuff	O
Box	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Cutbert	B-pers
Newbolt	I-pers
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
Tompion	O
for	O
being	O
adding	O
,	O
assisting	O
and	O
abetting	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Felony	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Thornbury	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Perjury	O
,	O
upon	O
an	O
Affidavit	O
taken	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
.	O
But	O
none	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
T	B-pers
-	I-pers
J	I-pers
-	I-pers
and	O
G	B-pers
-	I-pers
J	I-pers
-	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mildred	I-place
Poultry	I-place
,	O
were	O
both	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Rape	O
committed	O
by	O
them	O
upon	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Ruth	B-pers
Knot	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Virgin	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
strong	O
enough	O
to	O
convict	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
8.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Miles	I-pers
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Forrest	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Debuke	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Housden	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Pitman	I-pers
,	O
Ann	O
Goodwill	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
21.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Garret	I-pers
,	O
David	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Jacob	B-pers
Brag	I-pers
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Galpin	I-pers
,	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Gouge	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Geo	B-pers
.	I-pers
Bullar	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
Will	O
.	O
Markes	O
,	O
Will	O
.	O
Maw	O
,	O
Will	O
.	O
Haddington	O
,	O
Will	O
.	O
Weaver	O
,	O
Will	O
.	O
Evans	O
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Osney	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Mapleton	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gratrix	I-pers
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Male	I-pers
,	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Weaver	I-pers
Petty	O
Larcenies	O
16.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Brichard	I-pers
,	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Cutler	I-pers
,	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Tyler	I-pers
,	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Cousins	I-pers
,	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
French	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Jenkinson	I-pers
,	O
Anthony	B-pers
Goddard	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Goswell	I-pers
,	O
Will	O
.	O
Meckins	O
,	O
Roderick	B-pers
Oddery	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Travinian	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
to	O
stand	O
once	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
for	O
his	O
Trespass	O
.	O
