TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
Queen	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD	O
BAYLY	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
16th	O
,	O
17th	O
and	O
18th	O
Days	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
1711	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Tenth	O
Year	O
of	O
Her	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEfore	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
GILBERT	B-pers
HEATHCOTE	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
Trevor	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Powis	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Price	I-pers
;	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
Her	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Humphrey	B-pers
Thayre	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Fido	I-pers
John	B-pers
Benson	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Seewell	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
Stephen	B-pers
Cobbin	I-pers
Matthew	B-pers
Barwell	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Sone	I-pers
Mark	B-pers
Gwyn	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nicholls	I-pers
John	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
John	B-pers
Ilford	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Partridge	I-pers
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Mawson	I-pers
Hum	B-pers
.	I-pers
Newman	I-pers
John	B-pers
Marriot	I-pers
David	B-pers
Fifield	I-pers
John	B-pers
Millet	I-pers
Elias	B-pers
Hyrons	I-pers
James	B-pers
Odell	I-pers
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mottishell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
Instant	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
Date	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
Candlestick	O
to	O
a	O
Pawn-brokers	O
,	O
who	O
suspecting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
have	O
stolen	O
it	O
,	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
:	O
Upon	O
her	O
Examination	O
,	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
she	O
stole	O
it	O
from	O
a	O
House	O
near	O
the	O
7	O
Dials	O
;	O
Enquiry	O
being	O
made	O
,	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Candlestick	O
was	O
stolen	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Rushworth	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Place	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Mary	B-pers
Bordbanks	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Alhallows	I-place
Barkin	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Gold	O
Lockets	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Harrington	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
but	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
missing	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
afterwards	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Read	I-pers
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Alston	I-pers
.	O
To	O
both	O
which	O
Indictments	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Swift	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Box	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Box	O
of	O
Sweet	O
meats	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
clearly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Frankling	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Robbery	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Bingley	I-pers
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
High-way	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Bags	O
,	O
with	O
Bonds	O
,	O
Bills	O
,	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
Value	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
riding	O
along	O
Fleet-street	B-place
,	O
his	O
Leather	O
Bags	O
were	O
cut	O
from	O
behind	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Thief	O
made	O
his	O
Escape	O
,	O
that	O
applying	O
himself	O
afterwards	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
Thief	O
catcher	O
,	O
he	O
for	O
a	O
Sum	O
of	O
Money	O
help	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
Bags	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
apprehended	O
him	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
giving	O
no	O
Account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Hood	O
and	O
Scarf	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Wastecoat	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
Instant	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
enquir	O
'd	O
for	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Miller	O
,	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
down	O
from	O
the	O
said	O
Lodger	O
,	O
she	O
open	O
'd	O
a	O
Door	O
,	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
thence	O
:	O
that	O
going	O
down	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
observ	O
'd	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
Bundle	O
under	O
her	O
Ridinghood	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
apprehended	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
saying	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stent	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Macdoneld	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Silver	O
Tankards	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
l.	O
with	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Morrison	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Porringer	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Salt	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
.	O
To	O
both	O
which	O
Indictments	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Secillia	B-pers
Gourdon	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
in	O
counterfeiting	O
a	O
Certificate	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
Hands	O
of	O
Lieutenant	O
General	O
Harvey	O
,	O
and	O
Collonel	O
Bland	O
,	O
to	O
admit	O
William	B-pers
Arthur	I-pers
a	O
Pensioner	O
,	O
into	O
Chelsea	O
Hospital	O
:	O
William	B-pers
Arthur	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
Queen	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
the	O
Beginning	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
he	O
apply	O
'd	O
himself	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
admitted	O
a	O
Pensioner	O
into	O
Chelsea	O
Hospital	O
(	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
had	O
never	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
Army	O
in	O
his	O
Life	O
)	O
and	O
agreed	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
5	O
l.	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
:	O
l.	O
6	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
Clerks	O
Fees	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
He	O
paid	O
her	O
25	O
s.	O
in	O
part	O
thereof	O
:	O
Upon	O
which	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Collonel	O
Hales	O
,	O
Governor	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Hospital	O
,	O
and	O
inform	O
'd	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
the	O
Governor	O
order	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Crispe	O
to	O
pay	O
him	O
the	O
Six	O
Pounds	O
Six	O
Shillings	O
and	O
Six	O
Pence	O
,	O
to	O
further	O
such	O
his	O
Discovery	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
said	O
Arthur	O
receiv	O
'd	O
accordingly	O
,	O
and	O
procur	O
'd	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Certificate	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
counterfeit	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
her	O
Male	O
Infant	O
Bastard	O
Child	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
her	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Story	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
North	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Kensington	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Charlot	B-pers
,	I-pers
Countess	I-pers
of	I-pers
Warwick	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
2	O
Pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
Sheets	O
,	O
2	O
Table	O
Cloths	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Coach	O
Glasses	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
was	O
broken	O
(	O
but	O
whether	O
in	O
the	O
Day	O
time	O
or	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
)	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
were	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
andpawa	O
'd	O
by	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
William	B-pers
Room	I-pers
;	O
and	O
Walter	B-pers
Latten	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Hackney	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
,	O
in	O
receiving	O
and	O
buying	O
Goods	O
stolen	O
from	O
Charles	B-pers
Boddington	I-pers
,	O
by	O
Peter	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
:	O
They	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
not	O
the	O
least	O
Proof	O
given	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Aldridge	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Hester	B-pers
Aldridge	I-pers
his	O
Daughter	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
her	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
upon	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
of	O
her	O
Head	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
April	O
1710	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
;	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
falling	O
out	O
between	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
taking	O
,	O
up	O
a	O
Blunderbuss	O
charg	O
'd	O
,	O
swore	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
shoot	O
him	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
Child	O
being	O
by	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
receiv	O
'd	O
the	O
Blow	O
in	O
the	O
Scuffle	O
with	O
the	O
said	O
Blunderbuss	O
,	O
which	O
occasion	O
'd	O
a	O
Wound	O
in	O
her	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
depos	O
'd	O
she	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
brought	O
it	O
in	O
Chance-medley	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Burt	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
2	O
Pieces	O
of	O
broad	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Edmund	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
pick	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
St.	O
Hellens	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
home	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
made	O
him	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
by	O
him	O
:	O
He	O
further	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
put	O
one	O
Hand	O
in	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
parted	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Money	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
himself	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
scandalous	O
Person	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Evidence	O
not	O
strong	O
enough	O
to	O
convict	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Salter	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Chince	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
a	O
Chince	O
Petticoat	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Camblet	O
Petticoat	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
his	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
House	O
on	O
the	O
Date	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
carry	O
'd	O
by	O
Jane	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
to	O
a	O
Pawn-brokers	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
and	O
claim	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
Jane	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
was	O
apprehended	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
prov	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
her	O
Son	O
Salter	O
Herbert	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
charg	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
he	O
making	O
the	O
same	O
Confession	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
;	O
but	O
acquitted	O
Jane	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Oxford	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Chelsea	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
13	O
Holland	O
Caps	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
one	O
Muslin	O
Ruffle	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bickerstaff	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
March	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Jacculina	B-pers
Mountague	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
17	O
Pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bayley	I-pers
;	O
2	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Harlow	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
.	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
lodge	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Date	O
aforesaid	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
under	O
her	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
them	O
upon	O
her	O
before	O
she	O
could	O
get	O
off	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Millar	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stuff	O
Curtains	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Looking	O
Glass	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Vail	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Stotter	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
6	O
Silver	O
Buttons	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
2	O
Silver	O
Seals	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Head	O
Clothes	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lived	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
about	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
Days	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
time	O
she	O
went	O
privately	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
missing	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
with	O
them	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Margaret	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
a	O
Muslin	O
Hood	O
,	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
lac	O
'd	O
Head-clothes	O
,	O
a	O
Muslin	O
Pinner	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Josiah	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Harvey	O
sitting	O
in	O
his	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
heard	O
a	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
Entry	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
the	O
matter	O
was	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
Hill	O
's	O
Lodging	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Callico	O
Frock	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
17	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Brockton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Britton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
and	O
buying	O
Goods	O
,	O
stolen	O
from	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Christopher	I-pers
,	O
by	O
Thomas	B-pers
Alderson	I-pers
,	O
she	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
clearly	O
proved	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Peter	B-pers
Cartwright	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Pancrass	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Robert	B-pers
Short	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
High-way	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silver	O
hilted	O
sword	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
again	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
Joseph	B-pers
Ashton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
7	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Date	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutors	O
depos	O
'd	O
they	O
were	O
robb	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Queens	O
High-way	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Date	O
aforesaid	O
;	O
yet	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Thieves	O
;	O
but	O
Jewell	O
,	O
a	O
Person	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
(	O
and	O
who	O
had	O
formerly	O
convicted	O
another	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Robbery	O
)	O
plainly	O
proving	O
both	O
Facts	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Peter	B-pers
Bingham	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Millington	I-pers
(	O
his	O
Apprentice	O
)	O
in	O
April	O
last	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
any	O
thing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Josiah	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
Instant	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
observ	O
'd	O
to	O
stand	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
break	O
the	O
Show-Glass	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Watch	O
from	O
thence	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
an	O
Old	O
Offender	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Crow	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Gile	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
a	O
Cane	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
Instant	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Person	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Maunders	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
,	I-pers
Galloway	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminister	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
an	O
Indian	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Straw	O
Hat	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bore	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Plumber	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pauls	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
50	O
l	O
weight	O
of	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stiles	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bayley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Travallion	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
Instant	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
at	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Church	I-place
,	O
lost	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
apprehending	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
found	O
it	O
(	O
among	O
many	O
others	O
)	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
little	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	O
Haxton	O
,	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cantaline	O
Stuff	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Haxton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
Instant	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
with	O
others	O
to	O
buy	O
Clothes	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
to	O
shew	O
the	O
other	O
Women	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
staid	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Stuff	O
from	O
a	O
Shelf	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
was	O
discover	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
who	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Oliver	B-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Henry	I-pers
Lemon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Field	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Pewter	O
Castors	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
leaving	O
only	O
her	O
Child	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
another	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
enter	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
off	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Frances	I-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Frances	I-pers
Bauldwin	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Lodging	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Woodford	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Day	O
time	O
,	O
being	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
Dwelling-house	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Inhabitants	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
4	O
Gowns	O
and	O
4	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
a	O
Copper	O
Coffee-Pot	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
Things	O
of	O
Value	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Woodford	I-pers
;	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
and	O
8	O
Napkins	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lock	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
her	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
return	O
'd	O
,	O
found	O
it	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
gone	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
afterwards	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
giving	O
no	O
Account	O
of	O
her	O
Property	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
The	O
Jury	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Beer	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Smock	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Laruse	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
Smock	O
from	O
a	O
Line	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
pursu	O
'd	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Anne	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
Walter	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Mary	I-pers
Roods	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
and	O
Chain	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Coffee	O
Pot	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Snuffers	O
and	O
Snuff-pan	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Salver	O
5	O
l.	O
3	O
Silver	O
Casters	O
6	O
l.	O
with	O
other	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Plate	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Wade	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
personated	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Roods	I-pers
,	O
and	O
was	O
by	O
her	O
Name	O
and	O
Character	O
hired	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Service	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
in	O
her	O
Place	O
above	O
a	O
Week	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
privately	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
L	B-pers
-	I-pers
G	I-pers
-	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
25	O
yards	O
of	O
Damask	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Candlesticks	O
20	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Hayes	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
privately	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Damask	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
John	B-pers
Bateman	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Jacob	B-pers
Franingam	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
were	O
both	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Joyner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
4	O
Yards	O
of	O
Persian	O
Silk	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Remnant	O
of	O
green	O
and	O
red	O
Mantua	O
Silk	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
Instant	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
any	O
thing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Mugg	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Victualling-house	O
:	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Restow	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Matfellin	I-place
,	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
,	O
in	O
concealing	O
and	O
moving	O
away	O
his	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
500	O
l.	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
defraud	O
his	O
Creditors	O
(	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
declared	O
a	O
Bankrupt	O
)	O
contrary	O
to	O
an	O
Act	O
of	O
Parliament	O
made	O
in	O
the	O
5th	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
Queen	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
December	O
carried	O
on	O
the	O
Trade	O
of	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Draper	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
he	O
became	O
indebted	O
to	O
divers	O
Persons	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
legally	O
declared	O
a	O
Bankrupt	O
.	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
Date	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
being	O
Sunday	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
he	O
convey	O
'd	O
all	O
his	O
Effects	O
in	O
Carts	O
,	O
both	O
Shop	O
Goods	O
and	O
Houshold	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
value	O
500	O
l.	O
to	O
the	O
Water-side	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
Hoy	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
down	O
to	O
Lee	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Hoy	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
Sloop	O
that	O
was	O
prepared	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
to	O
some	O
Place	O
beyond	O
Sea	O
.	O
But	O
his	O
Creditors	O
having	O
early	O
Intelligence	O
of	O
his	O
Design	O
,	O
made	O
pursuit	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Sloop	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
not	O
denying	O
the	O
Fact	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Thornhill	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Sir	O
Cholmley	B-pers
Deering	I-pers
,	O
Baronet	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
under	O
the	O
Right	O
Pap	O
with	O
a	O
leaden	O
Bullet	O
discharg	O
'd	O
from	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
instant	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
soon	O
after	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
Indicted	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
Toy	O
at	O
Hampton	O
Court	O
with	O
about	O
15	O
other	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
April	O
:	O
That	O
there	O
they	O
dined	O
very	O
friendly	O
together	O
,	O
but	O
towards	O
the	O
Evening	O
some	O
Words	O
happen	O
'd	O
between	O
them	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
the	O
Deceased	O
struck	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
beat	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
arose	O
,	O
his	O
Lip	O
was	O
observ	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
swell	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
his	O
Teeth	O
out	O
.	O
A	O
Drawer	O
hearing	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
against	O
the	O
Wainscoat	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
but	O
immediately	O
parted	O
by	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
they	O
sat	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
friendly	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
look	O
'd	O
a	O
little	O
disturb	O
'd	O
.	O
This	O
Evidence	O
further	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
they	O
sat	O
together	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
Sir	O
Cholmley	O
,	O
you	O
know	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
me	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
Sir	O
Cholmley	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
you	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Lie	O
.	O
This	O
Witness	O
observed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Lip	O
much	O
swell	O
'd	O
before	O
the	O
giving	O
the	O
Lie	O
,	O
but	O
saw	O
not	O
the	O
Blows	O
given	O
.	O
It	O
further	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
seemed	O
to	O
beg	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Pardon	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
asking	O
of	O
Pardon	O
was	O
not	O
Satisfaction	O
for	O
the	O
Loss	O
of	O
his	O
Teeth	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
Fact	O
:	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
were	O
seen	O
in	O
Tuttle	B-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
about	O
12	O
Yards	O
distance	O
from	O
one	O
another	O
,	O
with	O
Pistols	O
in	O
their	O
Hands	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
advanced	O
very	O
boldly	O
toward	O
each	O
other	O
till	O
they	O
were	O
within	O
4	O
Yards	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
fir	O
'd	O
at	O
one	O
another	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
dropt	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lifting	O
up	O
his	O
Hands	O
in	O
token	O
of	O
Sorrow	O
,	O
willingly	O
surrender	O
'd	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
one	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
a	O
Half-Guinea	O
to	O
go	O
for	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
It	O
further	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
who	O
dress	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Wound	O
upon	O
the	O
Spot	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
to	O
a	O
Gardiner	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
He	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
by	O
several	O
of	O
his	O
Friends	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
others	O
,	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
the	O
Dewel	O
,	O
reply	O
'd	O
to	O
this	O
effect	O
:	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
Honour	O
,	O
and	O
acted	O
like	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
;	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
his	O
Friends	O
to	O
be	O
spoke	O
to	O
,	O
least	O
one	O
Misfortune	O
should	O
follow	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
heartily	O
forgave	O
him	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
It	O
further	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
challeng	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
gave	O
no	O
Account	O
after	O
what	O
manner	O
,	O
whether	O
by	O
Word	O
of	O
Mouth	O
or	O
by	O
Writing	O
.	O
Neither	O
did	O
it	O
appear	O
from	O
him	O
by	O
whom	O
he	O
was	O
challeng	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
his	O
Papers	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
a	O
Relation	O
of	O
his	O
had	O
receiv	O
'd	O
one	O
,	O
among	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
(	O
but	O
from	O
what	O
hand	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
)	O
which	O
he	O
put	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
read	O
after	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Challenge	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
as	O
follows	O
.	O
SIR	O
,	O
May	O
8th	O
,	O
1711	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
go	O
abroad	O
tomorrow	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
desire	O
you	O
will	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
Meeting	O
with	O
your	O
Sword	O
and	O
a	O
Brace	O
of	O
Pistols	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
insist	O
on	O
.	O
The	O
worthy	O
Gentleman	O
who	O
brings	O
this	O
will	O
concert	O
with	O
you	O
for	O
the	O
Time	O
and	O
Place	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
Tuttle	O
Fields	O
may	O
do	O
well	O
.	O
Hide	O
Park	O
is	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
of	O
Year	O
full	O
of	O
Company	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
Your	O
very	O
Humble	O
Servant	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Thornhill	I-pers
.	O
This	O
Challenge	O
being	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
Honour	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
intimate	O
Friends	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
seen	O
his	O
Hand	O
frequently	O
,	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
whether	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Hand	O
,	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
his	O
Knowledge	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
write	O
in	O
another	O
sort	O
of	O
Character	O
;	O
but	O
a	O
Foot-boy	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
the	O
Letter	O
shewn	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Writing	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
it	O
was	O
read	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
produc	O
'd	O
Evidence	O
,	O
to	O
prove	O
how	O
much	O
he	O
was	O
abus	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
;	O
how	O
that	O
from	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
his	O
Wounds	O
given	O
,	O
he	O
hath	O
lain	O
in	O
inexpressible	O
Pain	O
and	O
Anguish	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
take	O
only	O
Broth	O
and	O
small	O
Beer	O
,	O
for	O
almost	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
,	O
for	O
his	O
Sustenance	O
,	O
was	O
thrown	O
into	O
a	O
Fever	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Life	O
dispair	O
'd	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Jaw-bone	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
in	O
great	O
Danger	O
of	O
mortifying	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Necessity	O
of	O
loosing	O
more	O
of	O
his	O
Teeth	O
.	O
He	O
further	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Morning	O
the	O
Dewel	O
was	O
fought	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
sought	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
came	O
at	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
to	O
Kensington	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
formerly	O
lodg	O
'd	O
,	O
to	O
enquire	O
where	O
he	O
then	O
lodg	O
'd	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
7	O
to	O
his	O
Lodging	O
in	O
a	O
Hackney-Coach	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Brace	O
of	O
Pistols	O
in	O
his	O
Hands	O
;	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
let	O
into	O
his	O
Dining-Room	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
the	O
Servant	O
acquainted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
Sir	O
Chelmley	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
then	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
whether	O
he	O
would	O
drink	O
a	O
Dish	O
of	O
Tea	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
small	O
Beer	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
chose	O
the	O
latter	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
drank	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
dress	O
'd	O
,	O
they	O
both	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
same	O
Coach	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
directly	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
they	O
fought	O
the	O
Dewel	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
written	O
Challenge	O
,	O
the	O
Boy	O
that	O
swore	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
swore	O
likewise	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
write	O
in	O
all	O
his	O
Life	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
might	O
possibly	O
be	O
mistaken	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
likewise	O
produc	O
'd	O
a	O
great	O
Number	O
of	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
Men	O
of	O
Quality	O
,	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
his	O
intimate	O
Friends	O
and	O
Acquaintance	O
from	O
a	O
Boy	O
;	O
all	O
which	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
kind	O
,	O
affable	O
,	O
and	O
courteous	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
never	O
given	O
to	O
Quarrelling	O
in	O
the	O
least	O
:	O
And	O
on	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
produced	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
prov	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
unhappy	O
that	O
way	O
;	O
he	O
likewise	O
produc	O
'd	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
prov	O
'd	O
his	O
Serviceableness	O
to	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
Election	O
for	O
Member	O
of	O
Parliament	O
,	O
of	O
his	O
expending	O
several	O
Hundreds	O
of	O
Pounds	O
in	O
his	O
Service	O
,	O
and	O
procuring	O
about	O
800	O
Votes	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
an	O
entire	O
Friendship	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
till	O
this	O
sad	O
Accident	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
Trial	O
was	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
but	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
inform	O
'd	O
,	O
whether	O
there	O
was	O
two	O
,	O
or	O
four	O
Pistols	O
mentioned	O
by	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Witness	O
to	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
call	O
'd	O
up	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
four	O
Pistols	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Field	O
:	O
Upon	O
which	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
return	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Clift	I-pers
,	O
a	O
former	O
Convict	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
4.	O
Peter	B-pers
Cartwright	I-pers
,	O
Josia	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Restow	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Clift	I-pers
,	O
a	O
former	O
Convict	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
15.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Stent	I-pers
,	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Bordbanks	I-pers
,	O
Anne	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
Salter	O
Herbert	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Frankling	I-pers
,	O
Jacculina	O
Mountague	O
,	O
Oliver	B-pers
Lemon	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Swift	I-pers
,	O
Anne	B-pers
Britton	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Thornhill	I-pers
.	O
Petit	O
Larcinies	O
,	O
7.	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Mottishell	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bayley	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Beer	I-pers
,	O
L	O
-	O
G	O
-	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Story	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Stotter	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
Cecillia	B-pers
Gourdon	I-pers
,	O
fined	O
6	O
s.	O
8	O
d.	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
once	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
ALL	O
Mclancholy	O
,	O
Hysterical	O
and	O
Hypecondriack	O
Distempers	O
,	O
which	O
variously	O
after	O
the	O
Mind	O
,	O
with	O
strange	O
Fears	O
,	O
and	O
dismal	O
Apprehensions	O
;	O
saintings	O
and	O
sinkings	O
of	O
the	O
Spirits	O
,	O
great	O
Hurrys	O
,	O
Restlessness	O
and	O
Disquictment	O
,	O
(	O
little	O
understood	O
,	O
and	O
seldom	O
Cured	O
by	O
any	O
common	O
Means	O
)	O
also	O
Pains	O
and	O
Giddiness	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
Risings	O
to	O
the	O
Throat	O
,	O
Sickfits	O
,	O
Tremblings	O
,	O
Oppressions	O
of	O
the	O
Heart	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
other	O
Disorders	O
caus	O
'd	O
by	O
Vapours	O
are	O
successfully	O
Cured	O
(	O
with	O
God	O
's	O
Blessing	O
)	O
by	O
a	O
Physician	O
well	O
experienc	O
'd	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
more	O
than	O
20	O
Years	O
Practice	O
in	O
those	O
deplorable	O
Cases	O
;	O
who	O
also	O
Cures	O
all	O
kinds	O
of	O
Fits	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
strange	O
and	O
violent	O
,	O
if	O
Curable	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
informs	O
on	O
sight	O
of	O
their	O
Water	O
.	O
Living	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
Shadwell	O
Coffee-house	O
in	O
Upper	O
Shadwell	O
,	O
near	O
London	O
;	O
where	O
those	O
that	O
have	O
Occasion	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
remote	O
,	O
may	O
direct	O
their	O
Letters	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
shall	O
be	O
speedily	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
or	O
attended	O
on	O
if	O
desir	O
'd	O
.	O
Ldisworth	O
's	O
Record	O
Ink	O
Powder	O
,	O
it	O
made	O
and	O
sold	O
at	O
the	O
Golden	O
Ball	O
in	O
Cannon-street	O
,	O
London	O
.	O
Each	O
Six-Penny	O
Pater	O
of	O
3	O
Ounces	O
makes	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
the	O
best	O
Ink	O
,	O
or	O
Quart	O
,	O
as	O
by	O
Directions	O
,	O
sealed	O
up	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
same	O
in	O
proportion	O
,	O
for	O
greater	O
Quantities	O
)	O
Sold	O
by	O
the	O
Stationers	O
,	O
Booksellers	O
,	O
and	O
Haberdashers	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
chiefest	O
Cities	O
and	O
Towns	O
in	O
Great-Britain	O
and	O
Ireland	O
.	O
DR.	O
Gibson	O
on	O
the	O
Sacrament	O
,	O
at	O
1	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
per	O
Hundred	O
;	O
also	O
his	O
Exhortation	O
to	O
Family	O
Prayer	O
,	O
at	O
20	O
s.	O
per	O
Hundred	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Laws	O
relating	O
to	O
High	O
Treason	O
;	O
Printed	O
at	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Printing-House	O
:	O
Also	O
the	O
Statutes	O
at	O
large	O
,	O
in	O
3	O
Vol	O
.	O
Wingate	O
's	O
and	O
Washinton	O
's	O
Abridgement	O
;	O
and	O
all	O
sort	O
of	O
Bibles	O
and	O
Common	O
Prayers	O
,	O
rul	O
'd	O
and	O
unrul	O
'd	O
,	O
with	O
Cuts	O
and	O
without	O
;	O
also	O
Mr.	O
Sturt	O
's	O
Cuts	O
curiously	O
engraven	O
:	O
All	O
which	O
Book	O
and	O
Cuts	O
are	O
sold	O
by	O
Robert	B-pers
Whitledge	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
and	O
Ball	O
in	O
Ave	O
Mary	O
Lane	O
,	O
near	O
Ludgate	O
.	O
Two	O
excellent	O
Remedies	O
to	O
be	O
had	O
at	O
the	O
Peacock	O
in	O
Creed	O
Lane	O
,	O
by	O
Ludgate	O
.	O
First	O
,	O
A	O
Cordial	O
Anodine	O
Elixit	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
safe	O
and	O
immediate	O
Cure	O
for	O
the	O
Cholick	O
and	O
Gripes	O
,	O
Tooth-ach	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
all	O
other	O
Pains	O
of	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
or	O
Limbs	O
,	O
at	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Bottle	O
.	O
Secondly	O
,	O
A	O
Linament	O
for	O
outward	O
Use	O
,	O
for	O
Rickets	O
in	O
Children	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
a	O
sure	O
Cure	O
,	O
strengthening	O
them	O
to	O
Admiration	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
times	O
using	O
,	O
it	O
restores	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
perfect	O
Use	O
of	O
their	O
Limbs	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
never	O
so	O
weak	O
or	O
crooked	O
,	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Pot	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
.	O
Prepar	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
Physician	O
of	O
London	O
for	O
general	O
Good	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
Pretence	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Success	O
will	O
justify	O
:	O
He	O
therefore	O
desires	O
they	O
may	O
be	O
put	O
to	O
trial	O
by	O
those	O
that	O
have	O
occasion	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
will	O
soon	O
be	O
satisfy	O
'd	O
of	O
what	O
is	O
said	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
repent	O
their	O
Charge	O
.	O
A	O
Physician	O
of	O
eminent	O
and	O
great	O
Practice	O
in	O
Venereal	O
Diseases	O
,	O
in	O
Compassion	O
to	O
such	O
who	O
are	O
distemper	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
either	O
thro	O
'	O
Ignorance	O
or	O
Indigence	O
neglect	O
timely	O
Care	O
,	O
or	O
fall	O
into	O
unskilful	O
Hands	O
for	O
Cure	O
,	O
has	O
thought	O
fit	O
to	O
offer	O
some	O
gentle	O
Purging	O
Pills	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
Purchas	O
'd	O
at	O
a	O
small	O
Price	O
,	O
which	O
(	O
without	O
Hindrance	O
of	O
Business	O
,	O
or	O
Inconveniency	O
)	O
safely	O
and	O
compleatly	O
perform	O
the	O
Cure	O
of	O
any	O
Gonorrhea	O
or	O
Running	O
,	O
with	O
Heat	O
or	O
Sharpness	O
of	O
Urine	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
usually	O
in	O
10	O
or	O
12	O
Days	O
time	O
;	O
as	O
also	O
such	O
as	O
are	O
ill	O
cur	O
'd	O
they	O
clear	O
of	O
all	O
Relicts	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Disease	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
had	O
at	O
the	O
Waterman's-Arms	O
behind	O
Old	O
Round	O
Court	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
at	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
Box	O
,	O
containing	O
several	O
Doses	O
.	O
Sealed	O
up	O
with	O
full	O
Direction	O
,	O
for	O
Use	O
,	O
and	O
will	O
be	O
deliver	O
'd	O
to	O
any	O
Messenger	O
.	O
B.	O
LILBURN	O
,	O
that	O
formely	O
lived	O
on	O
Ludgate-hill	O
,	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms	O
Tavern	O
near	O
Fleet-Bridge	O
;	O
now	O
lives	O
at	O
the	O
Golden	O
Board	O
and	O
Ball	O
,	O
over	O
against	O
Prujean	O
's	O
Court	O
in	O
the	O
Great	O
Old	O
Baily	O
.	O
Who	O
makes	O
and	O
sells	O
the	O
WATER	O
(	O
and	O
has	O
near	O
Thirty	O
Years	O
)	O
for	O
taking	O
away	O
the	O
Freckles	O
,	O
Pimples	O
,	O
Worms	O
and	O
Morphew	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
.	O
Price	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Half	O
Pint	O
;	O
Sealed	O
with	O
the	O
3	O
Water-Budgens	O
.	O
and	O
B.	O
L.	O
on	O
the	O
Top	O
of	O
the	O
Seal	O
.	O
The	O
Antiscorbutick	O
,	O
Histerick	O
,	O
and	O
Head	O
Pill	O
,	O
being	O
likewise	O
good	O
for	O
Cancers	O
,	O
King	O
's	O
Evil	O
,	O
Gout	O
and	O
Rheumatisin	O
,	O
Dropsy	O
,	O
Agues	O
,	O
Surfeits	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Box	O
.	O
The	O
Elixir	O
for	O
the	O
Cholick	O
and	O
Gripes	O
,	O
being	O
good	O
for	O
Agues	O
,	O
Consumptions	O
,	O
or	O
Coughs	O
,	O
Colds	O
,	O
Stone	O
or	O
Gravel	O
,	O
Vomiting	O
,	O
and	O
Looseness	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Vial	O
,	O
or	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Half	O
Pint	O
.	O
An	O
Oyntment	O
for	O
sore	O
Nipples	O
,	O
the	O
Piles	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
Hair	O
grow	O
,	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Pot	O
.	O
An	O
Oyntment	O
for	O
a	O
red	O
Face	O
,	O
Tetters	O
,	O
Ring	O
worms	O
,	O
or	O
Scabs	O
one	O
Shilling	O
the	O
Pot	O
.	O
An	O
Oyntment	O
for	O
Bruises	O
,	O
Aches	O
,	O
Strains	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
dissolve	O
Swellings	O
&	O
c.	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Pot	O
;	O
and	O
cures	O
the	O
Itch	O
.	O
Printed	O
by	O
J.	O
Humfreys	O
in	O
Bartholomew-lane	O
,	O
behind	O
the	O
Royal-Exchange	O
,	O
(	O
where	O
Advertisements	O
are	O
taken	O
in	O
)	O
for	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
CROUCH	I-pers
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Popes	O
Head	O
Alley	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
;	O
And	O
Sold	O
by	O
A.	O
Baldwin	O
near	O
the	O
Oxford	O
Arms	O
in	O
Warwick-lane	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
d	O
.	O
