TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
Queen	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD	O
BAYLY	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
10th	O
,	O
11th	O
and	O
12th	O
Days	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
1711	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Tenth	O
Tear	O
of	O
Her	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEfore	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
GILBERT	B-pers
HEATHCOTE	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
Parker	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Tracey	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Bury	O
,	O
and	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
;	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
Her	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Jeremy	B-pers
Pierce	I-pers
Leonard	B-pers
Fitsbugh	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Fielder	I-pers
Clement	B-pers
Clearer	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Merrick	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
Christopher	B-pers
Garroway	I-pers
John	B-pers
Stepkins	I-pers
William	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Sadler	I-pers
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
William	B-pers
Hummerton	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Whitchand	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Hull	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Reamond	I-pers
Josiah	O
Tidmash	O
William	B-pers
Price	I-pers
William	B-pers
Seagour	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Adshead	I-pers
John	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Hazzard	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Tapper	I-pers
John	B-pers
Osgood	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Elford	I-pers
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Goodale	I-pers
,	O
Roddery	B-pers
Ordery	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Sweet	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Furnier	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Day	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
4	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
Value	O
40	O
s.	O
3	O
Silver	O
Forks	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Furnier	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
Date	O
aforesaid	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
observ	O
'd	O
to	O
sculk	O
about	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
That	O
Sweet	O
with	O
a	O
Hook	O
fasten	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
a	O
Stick	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
Window	O
(	O
they	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
Basket	O
)	O
and	O
made	O
his	O
Escape	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
strong	O
enough	O
against	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Britton	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
and	O
buying	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Proof	O
appearing	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Pickering	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
Value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samson	B-pers
Sago	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
asleep	O
in	O
his	O
Cabbin	O
,	O
was	O
awak	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
Noise	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
espy	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
jump	O
into	O
a	O
Boat	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
off	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
then	O
sent	O
his	O
Man	O
after	O
him	O
in	O
another	O
Boat	O
,	O
who	O
apprehended	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Watch	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
sound	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Nathanael	B-pers
Sturridge	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Plush	O
Coach	O
Seats	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ostler	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
Instant	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
his	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Coach	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
an	O
Upholder	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
stop	O
them	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
him	O
:	O
Accordingly	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
who	O
proving	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
giving	O
no	O
Account	O
of	O
his	O
Property	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Vedas	I-place
alias	I-place
Foster-lane	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
4	O
Yards	O
of	O
Canvass	O
,	O
Values	O
5	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Lingham	B-pers
Asterly	I-pers
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
three	O
Yards	O
and	O
Quarter	O
of	O
Stuff	O
Plad	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Tobias	B-pers
Wickar	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
Instant	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
and	O
cheapen	O
'd	O
some	O
Stuffs	O
,	O
but	O
bought	O
nothing	O
.	O
It	O
further	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Servants	O
saw	O
her	O
put	O
something	O
under	O
her	O
Riding-hood	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
off	O
;	O
but	O
immediately	O
pursuing	O
her	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Canvass	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
second	O
Indictment	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
Grate	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Wickar	O
's	O
Shop-window	O
.	O
The	O
Facts	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
nothing	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Alice	B-pers
Arthur	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pancrass	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
Value	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
3	O
l.	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Watkis	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
alone	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
broke	O
the	O
Chamber-door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Scrutoir	O
,	O
and	O
fled	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
apprehended	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Ewen	I-pers
of	O
S.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
22	O
Yards	O
of	O
Chyna	O
Stuff	O
,	O
Value	O
22	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
the	O
Younger	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
cheapen	O
'd	O
Stuffs	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
having	O
frequently	O
lost	O
Goods	O
had	O
a	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
And	O
watching	O
her	O
very	O
narrowly	O
,	O
he	O
observ	O
'd	O
her	O
Petticoats	O
to	O
stick	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
felt	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
dropt	O
from	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
proving	O
to	O
be	O
those	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
5	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
Value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
Silk	O
Petticoat	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Fairfax	I-pers
;	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Cripple-gate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
20	O
Ells	O
of	O
Garlick	O
Holland	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
being	O
in	O
her	O
Counting	O
House	O
,	O
miss	O
'd	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Cloth	O
from	O
the	O
Counter	O
;	O
and	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
:	O
She	O
saying	O
little	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Cumbers	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Coral	O
and	O
Chain	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Diggory	B-pers
Physicks	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pauls	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
5	O
l.	O
13	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Marlow	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
having	O
40	O
l.	O
in	O
a	O
Bag	O
,	O
missed	O
5	O
Pound	O
13	O
s.	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
and	O
charging	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
it	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
and	O
doing	O
the	O
same	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Lutestring	O
Silk	O
Hood	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
6	O
Yards	O
of	O
Bone	O
Lace	O
5	O
s.	O
The	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joan	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
leaving	O
a	O
little	O
Girl	O
in	O
her	O
Shop	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
returning	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
searching	O
him	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Bosom	O
the	O
above-mentioned	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
nothing	O
for	O
himself	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rodley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Cripple-gate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
40	O
Yards	O
of	O
Blew	O
Linnen	O
Cloth	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Toon	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
and	O
Chain	O
,	O
value	O
21	O
l.	O
a	O
Gold	O
locket	O
50	O
s.	O
a	O
Christal	O
Seal	O
set	O
in	O
Gold	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
S	B-pers
-	I-pers
W	I-pers
-	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
strong	O
enough	O
to	O
convict	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Boyle	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sattin	O
Gown	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
4	O
Pair	O
of	O
Womans	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Shooes	O
value	O
24	O
s.	O
2	O
Pair	O
of	O
Clogs	O
5	O
s.	O
4	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
4	O
Holland	O
Neckcloths	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Blanket	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
came	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
at	O
Knights-Bridge	B-place
,	O
and	O
enquir	O
'd	O
for	O
Lodgings	O
for	O
a	O
Colonel	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
the	O
Landlady	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
to	O
shew	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
the	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
Room	O
up	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
Tenanted	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Evans	O
's	O
Servant	O
with	O
his	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
thence	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
and	O
Susannah	B-pers
Burley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
both	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Draper	I-pers
from	O
his	O
Ware-house	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
strong	O
enough	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Fact	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Catharine	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Sallet	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Diaper	O
Napkins	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
6	O
Holland	O
Pillowbaers	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
Kenning	I-pers
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Riggell	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Pair	O
of	O
Spatter-dashes	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Minns	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
her	O
Goods	O
from	O
her	O
Shop	O
Window	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
afterwards	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
giving	O
no	O
Account	O
of	O
his	O
Property	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stansly	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
7	O
Muslin	O
Neckcloths	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hungerford	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2nd	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
22	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Miles	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gather	O
'd	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
for	O
a	O
Cook	O
,	O
and	O
us	O
'd	O
for	O
that	O
end	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
both	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Houses	O
,	O
they	O
lost	O
their	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
Suspition	O
,	O
who	O
upon	O
Examination	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Facts	O
;	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Challen	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
drawn	O
Sword	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
right	O
side	O
of	O
his	O
body	O
near	O
his	O
right	O
Pap	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
Indicted	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
been	O
Gaming	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
won	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
snatch	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
Stakes	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
demanding	O
as	O
his	O
right	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
threw	O
it	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
D	O
-	O
him	O
he	O
should	O
fight	O
him	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Fields	O
together	O
and	O
drew	O
their	O
Swords	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
several	O
Passes	O
at	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
mutually	O
should	O
Hands	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
wiped	O
the	O
Point	O
of	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
put	O
them	O
up	O
;	O
but	O
before	O
they	O
went	O
from	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
Words	O
arose	O
again	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
drew	O
the	O
2d	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
making	O
a	O
few	O
Passes	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
a	O
would	O
in	O
his	O
right	O
side	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Man	O
slaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Rivers	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
1710	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Sharlow	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Sharlow	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Hilted	O
Sword	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Edward	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
none	O
appearing	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Winnifred	B-pers
Shelley	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Duway	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
7	O
Yards	O
of	O
Muslin	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
Holland	O
Apron	O
18	O
d.	O
a	O
Towel	O
6	O
d.	O
3	O
Hand	O
kerchiefs	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Vallent	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
any	O
thing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Nun	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
8	O
l.	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Eustace	B-pers
Hermon	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
walking	O
in	O
Lambs	O
Conduit	O
Fields	O
,	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
into	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
together	O
and	O
play	O
'd	O
at	O
Cards	O
till	O
Two	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
going	O
out	O
first	O
was	O
overtaken	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
invited	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
Lodging	O
at	O
the	O
Cock	B-place
and	I-place
Dolphin	I-place
in	I-place
Grays	I-place
Inn	I-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
together	O
about	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
at	O
5	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
nothing	O
for	O
him	O
self	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Justice	I-pers
and	O
Lydia	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
both	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Thomas	B-pers
Trap	I-pers
upon	O
the	O
Queens	O
High-way	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Neckcloth	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
6	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Graves	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
8	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
;	O
but	O
none	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Maw	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White-Chapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taken	O
from	O
thence	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Frock	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Bradford	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
of	O
the	O
Date	O
aforesaid	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
abovementioned	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
One	O
Shales	O
a	O
Person	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
himself	O
and	O
Prisoner	O
committed	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
positive	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
nothing	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Avery	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
24	O
Pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Clogs	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Avery	I-pers
;	O
which	O
Fact	O
being	O
clearly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
3d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Charles	B-pers
Potts	I-pers
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Queens	O
High-way	O
.	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
a	O
Tortoise	O
Shell	O
Snuff-Box	O
20	O
s.	O
3	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Book	O
with	O
Silver	O
Clasps	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
30	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Charles	B-pers
Potts	I-pers
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
4th	O
Time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Anne	B-pers
Grover	I-pers
upon	O
the	O
Queens	O
High	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
5th	O
Time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Thomas	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
upon	O
the	O
Queens	O
High-way	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
Seal	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Penknife	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
on	O
the	O
Date	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
riding	O
about	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
between	O
Mile-end	B-place
and	O
Bow	B-place
,	O
were	O
assaulted	O
by	O
Three	O
Men	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
down	O
the	O
Lane	O
behind	O
the	O
Men	O
hanging	O
in	O
Chains	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictments	O
violently	O
taken	O
from	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Facts	O
being	O
clearly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
making	O
a	O
Trisling	O
Defence	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
an	O
Old	O
Offender	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Diter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Edgeway	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
5	O
Sheaves	O
of	O
Wheat	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Etheridge	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
strong	O
enough	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White-Chapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Porrige	O
Pot	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
16	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Handcock	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
proving	O
nothing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Burden	I-pers
.	O
But	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Temple	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Wearing	O
Clothes	O
,	O
Linnen	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Porringer	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
16	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Lydia	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
her	O
Goods	O
in	O
two	O
Trunks	O
with	O
a	O
Friend	O
of	O
hers	O
,	O
which	O
Friend	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
privately	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Hurd	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Weston	I-pers
,	O
39	O
Broad	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Weston	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
Hide	O
Park	O
Corner	O
,	O
was	O
met	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Harper	I-pers
,	O
who	O
perswaded	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
Tavern	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
Box	O
together	O
,	O
one	O
sat	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
pretended	O
to	O
keep	O
him	O
upright	O
;	O
it	O
further	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
held	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Arm	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
other	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
her	O
escape	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
positive	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
little	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cullingford	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Miles	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
,	I-pers
Adams	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Snuff	O
dish	O
,	O
Value	O
40	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Downing	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
West	I-pers
:	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joshua	B-pers
Holloway	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
several	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Houses	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
to	O
enquire	O
about	O
a	O
Maid	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
talking	O
with	O
the	O
Servants	O
,	O
would	O
ask	O
for	O
Small	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
divers	O
Ways	O
to	O
get	O
their	O
Backs	O
turn	O
'd	O
;	O
by	O
which	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
all	O
the	O
Indictments	O
.	O
The	O
Facts	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
last	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ralph	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
and	O
Grace	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Mitchell	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
9	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
2	O
Smocks	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
6	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
return	O
'd	O
at	O
7	O
,	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
the	O
Alley	O
where	O
she	O
liv	O
'd	O
;	O
That	O
coming	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
,	O
Grace	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
with	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
with	O
Picklocks	O
and	O
Chissels	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
two	O
Men	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
:	O
But	O
Grace	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
being	O
Wife	O
to	O
Ralph	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Pighells	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
Value	O
18	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Blackham	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Savoy	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
3	O
East	O
India	O
Bonds	O
300	O
l.	O
3	O
Broad	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Pighells	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
foul	O
and	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Davenant	I-pers
,	O
B	B-pers
-	I-pers
K	I-pers
-	I-pers
,	O
E	B-pers
-	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Caduggon	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
and	O
receiving	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
Value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Snuff	O
Box	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Broad	O
Gold	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Pighells	I-pers
.	O
This	O
being	O
likewise	O
a	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bethel	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
Value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Candlestick	O
12	O
d.	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Israel	B-pers
Child	I-pers
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ferrier	I-pers
,	O
Lewis	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Catharine	B-pers
Creek	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
indicted	O
for	O
taking	O
away	O
Margaret	B-pers
Delyle	I-pers
,	O
a	O
great	O
Fortune	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
Age	O
of	O
18	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Design	O
to	O
have	O
married	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Lewis	B-pers
West	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
Catharine	O
Creek	O
being	O
a	O
Teacher	O
to	O
a	O
Boarding-School	O
at	O
Bromley	O
,	O
where	O
Margaret	B-pers
Delyle	I-pers
boarded	O
,	O
went	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
September	O
to	O
Lewis	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Fleet	O
,	O
and	O
agreed	O
with	O
him	O
(	O
upon	O
the	O
Reward	O
of	O
a	O
Thousand	O
Pounds	O
)	O
to	O
assist	O
him	O
in	O
marrying	O
Mrs.	O
Delyle	O
,	O
a	O
Boarder	O
in	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
School	O
.	O
To	O
accomplish	O
which	O
a	O
Coach	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
brought	O
to	O
Mile-end	O
,	O
by	O
7	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
where	O
Creek	O
was	O
to	O
bring	O
Mrs.	O
Delyle	O
,	O
to	O
convey	O
her	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
the	O
Fleet	O
,	O
there	O
to	O
be	O
married	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
West	O
.	O
Accordingly	O
a	O
Coach	O
was	O
got	O
ready	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Cassal	O
and	O
Ferrier	O
went	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
the	O
Design	O
was	O
discover	O
'd	O
,	O
which	O
oblig	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
come	O
away	O
without	O
doing	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Clock	O
at	O
the	O
Boarding-School	O
going	O
an	O
Hour	O
too	O
fast	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Mrs.	O
Delyle	O
was	O
carryed	O
away	O
by	O
Creech	O
at	O
6	O
,	O
which	O
alarm	O
'd	O
the	O
School	O
;	O
and	O
Search	O
being	O
made	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
.	O
There	O
wanting	O
sufficient	O
Proof	O
of	O
the	O
Force	O
,	O
and	O
thePrisoner	O
West	O
proving	O
himself	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
Worth	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
:	O
But	O
Creech	O
for	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
betray	O
the	O
young	O
Gentlewoman	O
that	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
her	O
Care	O
,	O
was	O
order	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
to	O
find	O
Sureties	O
for	O
her	O
Good	O
Behaviour	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
22	O
Yards	O
of	O
Fustian	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
and	O
17	O
Yards	O
of	O
Scotch	O
Cloth	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Davison	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
which	O
Fact	O
being	O
clearly	O
prov	O
'd	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Garret	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
down	O
to	O
his	O
former	O
Judgment	O
.	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
3.	O
Mary	B-pers
Ewen	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Maw	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Anne	B-pers
Hurd	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Garret	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
down	O
to	O
his	O
former	O
Judgment	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
18.	O
Anne	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rodley	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cullingford	I-pers
,	O
Anne	B-pers
Cumbers	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Sweet	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Pickering	I-pers
,	O
Nathanael	O
Sturridge	O
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Mitchell	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stansley	I-pers
,	O
Alice	B-pers
Arthur	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Boyle	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
,	O
Ralph	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Mitchell	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Temple	I-pers
.	O
Petit	O
Larcinies	O
,	O
3.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Riggell	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Nun	I-pers
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
ALL	O
Melancholy	O
,	O
Hysterical	O
and	O
Hypocondriack	O
Distempers	O
,	O
which	O
variously	O
affect	O
the	O
Mind	O
,	O
with	O
strange	O
Fears	O
,	O
and	O
dismal	O
Apprehensions	O
;	O
faintings	O
and	O
sinkings	O
of	O
the	O
Spirits	O
,	O
great	O
Hurrys	O
,	O
Restlessness	O
and	O
Disquietment	O
,	O
(	O
little	O
understood	O
,	O
and	O
seldom	O
Cured	O
by	O
any	O
common	O
Means	O
)	O
also	O
Pains	O
and	O
Giddiness	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
Risings	O
to	O
the	O
Throat	O
,	O
Sickfits	O
,	O
Tremblings	O
,	O
Oppressions	O
of	O
the	O
Heart	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
other	O
Disorders	O
caus	O
'd	O
by	O
Vapours	O
are	O
successfully	O
Cured	O
(	O
with	O
God	O
's	O
Blessing	O
)	O
by	O
a	O
Physician	O
well	O
experienc	O
'd	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
more	O
than	O
20	O
Years	O
Practice	O
in	O
those	O
deplorable	O
Cases	O
;	O
who	O
also	O
Cures	O
all	O
kinds	O
of	O
Fits	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
strange	O
and	O
violent	O
,	O
if	O
Curable	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
informs	O
on	O
sight	O
of	O
their	O
Water	O
.	O
Living	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
Shadwell	O
Coffee-house	O
in	O
Upper	O
Shadwell	O
,	O
near	O
London	O
;	O
where	O
those	O
that	O
have	O
Occasion	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
remote	O
,	O
may	O
direct	O
their	O
Letters	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
shall	O
be	O
speedily	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
or	O
attended	O
on	O
if	O
desir	O
'd	O
.	O
Ldisworth	O
's	O
Record	O
Ink	O
Powder	O
,	O
is	O
made	O
and	O
sold	O
at	O
the	O
Golden	O
Ball	O
in	O
Cannon-street	O
,	O
London	O
.	O
Each	O
Six-Penny	O
Paper	O
of	O
3	O
Ounces	O
makes	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
the	O
best	O
Ink	O
,	O
or	O
Quart	O
,	O
as	O
by	O
Directions	O
,	O
sealed	O
up	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
same	O
in	O
proportion	O
,	O
for	O
greater	O
Quantities	O
)	O
Sold	O
by	O
the	O
Stationers	O
,	O
Booksellers	O
,	O
and	O
Haberdashers	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
chiefest	O
Cities	O
and	O
Towns	O
in	O
Great-Britain	O
and	O
Ireland	O
.	O
DR.	O
Gibson	O
on	O
the	O
Sacrament	O
,	O
at	O
1	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
per	O
Hundred	O
;	O
also	O
his	O
Exhortation	O
to	O
Family	O
Prayer	O
,	O
at	O
20	O
s.	O
per	O
Hundred	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Laws	O
relating	O
to	O
High	O
Treason	O
;	O
Printed	O
at	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Printing-House	O
:	O
Also	O
the	O
Statutes	O
at	O
large	O
,	O
in	O
3	O
Vol	O
.	O
Wagone	O
's	O
and	O
Washinton	O
's	O
Abridgement	O
;	O
and	O
all	O
sort	O
of	O
Bibles	O
and	O
Common	O
Prayers	O
,	O
rul	O
'd	O
and	O
unrul	O
'd	O
with	O
Cuts	O
and	O
without	O
;	O
also	O
Mr.	O
Smart	O
's	O
Cuts	O
curiously	O
engraven	O
:	O
All	O
which	O
Books	O
and	O
Cuts	O
are	O
sold	O
by	O
Robert	O
Whitedge	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
and	O
Ball	O
in	O
Ave	O
Mary	O
Lane	O
,	O
near	O
Ludgate	O
.	O
THO	O
.	O
Russell	B-pers
Chymist	I-pers
,	O
by	O
a	O
gentle	O
and	O
safe	O
Laxative	O
Medicine	O
,	O
gives	O
speedy	O
Ease	O
and	O
Relief	O
in	O
the	O
most	O
tormenting	O
Pains	O
of	O
the	O
Gout	O
and	O
Rheuntatism	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
short	O
Time	O
(	O
with	O
God	O
's	O
Blessing	O
)	O
perfects	O
the	O
Cure	O
of	O
those	O
Diseases	O
;	O
be	O
the	O
Joynts	O
never	O
so	O
much	O
knotted	O
,	O
or	O
Limbs	O
disabled	O
by	O
Pains	O
or	O
Weakness	O
;	O
perform	O
'd	O
without	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
any	O
external	O
Means	O
,	O
whose	O
ill	O
Effects	O
have	O
been	O
too	O
often	O
found	O
,	O
by	O
driving	O
the	O
Distemper	O
into	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
Stomach	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
vital	O
Parts	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
great	O
Hazard	O
of	O
Life	O
,	O
which	O
Danger	O
this	O
Medicine	O
secures	O
them	O
from	O
,	O
by	O
carrying	O
off	O
the	O
Morbisick	O
Humours	O
by	O
Stool	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
so	O
good	O
Effect	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Disease	O
is	O
seldom	O
known	O
to	O
return	O
;	O
divers	O
having	O
been	O
restor	O
'd	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
who	O
for	O
several	O
Years	O
lay	O
under	O
very	O
great	O
Sufferings	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
move	O
themselves	O
,	O
continuing	O
well	O
for	O
many	O
Years	O
after	O
;	O
Of	O
which	O
so	O
good	O
Testimonials	O
can	O
be	O
given	O
,	O
as	O
may	O
convince	O
the	O
most	O
Incredulous	O
and	O
Unbelieving	O
.	O
Let	O
none	O
therefore	O
despair	O
of	O
Help	O
,	O
be	O
their	O
Case	O
never	O
so	O
bad	O
(	O
either	O
from	O
the	O
common	O
Notion	O
of	O
the	O
Incurability	O
of	O
these	O
Diseases	O
,	O
or	O
Unsuccessfulness	O
of	O
other	O
Means	O
they	O
have	O
used	O
)	O
till	O
they	O
have	O
made	O
Trial	O
of	O
this	O
Remedy	O
,	O
which	O
with	O
God	O
's	O
Blessing	O
they	O
will	O
find	O
to	O
answer	O
their	O
Expectations	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
spoken	O
with	O
every	O
Day	O
till	O
Noon	O
,	O
at	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
at	O
a	O
Hatters	O
in	O
Beech-lane	O
near	O
Barbican	O
.	O
A	O
Friendly	O
and	O
compassionate	O
Exhortation	O
to	O
Vertue	O
:	O
In	O
five	O
short	O
Practical	O
Discourses	O
,	O
against	O
Profane	O
Swearing	O
,	O
Drunkenness	O
,	O
Gaming	O
,	O
Detraction	O
,	O
and	O
Immodesty	O
Wherein	O
the	O
Sinfulness	O
of	O
them	O
is	O
seriously	O
brought	O
home	O
to	O
every	O
Man	O
's	O
Conscience	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Means	O
of	O
avoiding	O
'em	O
plainly	O
and	O
familiarly	O
set	O
forth	O
.	O
By	O
G.	B-pers
R	I-pers
.	I-pers
B.	O
D.	O
Advice	O
to	O
the	O
Readers	O
of	O
the	O
Common-Prayer-Book	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
People	O
attending	O
the	O
same	O
:	O
Offer	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Consideration	O
of	O
those	O
who	O
are	O
for	O
promoting	O
Decency	O
in	O
the	O
service	O
of	O
God	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Usage	O
of	O
the	O
Cherish	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
Establish	O
'd	O
by	O
Law	O
.	O
With	O
a	O
Preface	O
of	O
Divine	O
Worship	O
in	O
general	O
.	O
By	O
T.	O
Seymor	O
,	O
Lay-man	O
.	O
The	O
Fourth	O
Edition	O
,	O
corrected	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
The	O
Art	O
of	O
Painting	O
in	O
Oil	O
.	O
Wherein	O
is	O
included	O
each	O
particular	O
Circumstance	O
relating	O
to	O
that	O
Art	O
and	O
Mystery	O
.	O
Containing	O
the	O
best	O
and	O
most	O
approved	O
Rules	O
for	O
preparing	O
,	O
mixing	O
,	O
and	O
working	O
of	O
Oil-Colours	O
.	O
The	O
whole	O
Treatise	O
being	O
so	O
full	O
,	O
compleat	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
exactly	O
fitted	O
to	O
the	O
meanest	O
Capacity	O
,	O
that	O
all	O
Persons	O
what	O
soever	O
,	O
may	O
be	O
able	O
by	O
these	O
Directions	O
,	O
to	O
paint	O
in	O
Oil-Colours	O
all	O
manner	O
of	O
Timber-work	O
;	O
such	O
as	O
Posts	O
,	O
Pails	O
,	O
Pallisadoes	O
,	O
Gates	O
,	O
Doors	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
that	O
requires	O
either	O
Use	O
,	O
Beauty	O
,	O
or	O
Preservation	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Violence	O
or	O
Injury	O
of	O
the	O
Weather	O
.	O
In	O
which	O
is	O
also	O
particularly	O
laid	O
down	O
,	O
all	O
the	O
several	O
Circumstances	O
required	O
in	O
Painting	O
of	O
Sun-Dials	O
,	O
printed	O
Pictures	O
,	O
Shash-Windows	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
Oily-Colours	O
.	O
The	O
Fourth	O
Impression	O
with	O
some	O
Alterations	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
Matters	O
added	O
,	O
which	O
are	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Three	O
former	O
Editions	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
the	O
whole	O
Art	O
and	O
Mystery	O
of	O
Colouring	O
Maps	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Prints	O
with	O
Water-Colours	O
.	O
By	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
C.	O
M.	O
These	O
three	O
sold	O
by	O
Samuel	B-pers
Crouch	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Popes-Head-Alley	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
.	O
Printed	O
by	O
J.	O
Humfreys	O
in	O
Bartholomew-lane	O
,	O
behind	O
the	O
Royal-Exchange	O
,	O
(	O
where	O
Advertisements	O
are	O
taken	O
in	O
)	O
for	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
CROUCH	I-pers
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Popes-Head-Alley	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
;	O
And	O
Sold	O
by	O
A.	O
Baldwin	O
near	O
the	O
Oxford-Arms	O
in	O
Warwick-lane	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
d	O
.	O
