TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
Queen	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD	O
BAYLY	O
,	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
10th	O
,	O
11th	O
,	O
and	O
12th	O
Days	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
1712	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Eleventh	O
Year	O
of	O
Her	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
BEfore	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
ROBERT	B-pers
BEACHCROFT	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Lovel	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
Richardson	O
;	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
Her	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Eyles	I-pers
.	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Flower	I-pers
.	O
Sam	B-pers
.	I-pers
Gleddow	I-pers
.	O
Geo	B-pers
Hurst	I-pers
.	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
Mich.	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Butcher	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Pullen	I-pers
.	O
Ja	B-pers
.	I-pers
Bedingfield	I-pers
.	O
Rich	B-pers
.	I-pers
Blagrave	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Brereton	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
John	B-pers
Page	I-pers
.	O
Cha	B-pers
.	I-pers
Munden	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Cass	I-pers
.	O
Dan	B-pers
.	I-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
.	O
Nath	B-pers
.	I-pers
Ravener	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Page	I-pers
.	O
Nich	B-pers
.	I-pers
Parker	I-pers
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Dicks	I-pers
.	O
Marmaduke	B-pers
Bromley	I-pers
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
John	B-pers
Colebach	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Coleblack	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Roan	O
Mare	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Jowers	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
Mare	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Grounds	O
at	O
Cotfield	B-place
in	I-place
Suffolk	I-place
;	O
and	O
putting	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
News	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bringing	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Castle	O
and	O
Faulcon	O
in	O
Aldersgate-street	O
,	O
was	O
suspected	O
,	O
and	O
stopt	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
sent	O
to	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
Town	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
her	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
strengthen	O
'd	O
by	O
another	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
he	O
bought	O
her	O
of	O
a	O
Yorkshire	O
Butcher	O
,	O
and	O
nam	O
'd	O
a	O
Woman	O
that	O
would	O
justifie	O
he	O
paid	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
appearing	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Elson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Magnes	I-place
the	I-place
Martyr	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Half-hundred	O
Weight	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
on	O
the	O
5th	O
Instant	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Nichols	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
following	O
him	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
hard	O
by	O
with	O
the	O
Weight	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
hide	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Pindar	I-pers
(	O
an	O
Infant	O
)	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
bruise	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
with	O
the	O
Off	O
wheel	O
of	O
a	O
Dray	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Dray	O
going	O
softly	O
along	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
a	O
Boy	O
set	O
the	O
Child	O
upon	O
the	O
hind	O
Plank	O
of	O
it	O
and	O
held	O
it	O
there	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Dray	O
giving	O
a	O
sudden	O
jog	O
,	O
the	O
Boy	O
let	O
go	O
his	O
hold	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Child	O
fell	O
between	O
the	O
Planks	O
and	O
was	O
kill	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
not	O
believing	O
the	O
Wheel	O
could	O
run	O
over	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Evidence	O
declaring	O
it	O
reasonable	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
dy	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
fall	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gines	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Wardrobe	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
22	O
Deal	O
Boards	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hose	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
declar	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
Waterman	O
,	O
brought	O
another	O
Man	O
in	O
his	O
Boat	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
to	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Covelt	O
's	O
Wharf	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
several	O
Boards	O
,	O
amongst	O
which	O
were	O
those	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
Boat	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
none	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cane	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Swancoat	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Grace	B-pers
Dowsing	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
Dowsing	O
and	O
another	O
being	O
washing	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
over	O
them	O
was	O
Lock	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Key	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
hearing	O
a	O
noise	O
in	O
that	O
Room	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
bolted	O
them	O
down	O
;	O
whereupon	O
they	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
stopt	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
pretended	O
a	O
Man	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Shilling	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
as	O
Frivolous	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Askew	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary-le-Bow	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Can	O
,	O
valued	O
40s	O
.	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
who	O
not	O
being	O
there	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
amusing	O
his	O
Wife	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Stories	O
and	O
Pretences	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Can	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Chamber	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
,	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
Satisfaction	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Hamlin	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Somerset	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Shifts	O
,	O
valued	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Shirt	O
valued	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Weaver	I-pers
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
she	O
having	O
been	O
formerly	O
try	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Robbery	O
,	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rolph	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Butolph	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Quarters	O
of	O
a	O
Pound	O
of	O
Silk	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Bouteau	I-pers
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary-le-Bow	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privily	O
stealing	O
from	O
Henry	B-pers
Hutchinson	I-pers
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
valued	O
3	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
along	O
Cheapside	B-place
about	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drew	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
saw	O
another	O
take	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
bidding	O
him	O
Lope	O
,	O
Jemmy	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
ran	O
too	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
stopt	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
matter	O
made	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Oshy	B-pers
Walton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Peters	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privily	O
stealing	O
10	O
Yards	O
of	O
Muslin	O
,	O
valued	O
50	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Coe	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
pretending	O
to	O
cheapen	O
Muslin	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
miss	O
'd	O
,	O
whereupon	O
she	O
was	O
pursu	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Evidence	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
so	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
9	O
Hogs	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Lambert	B-pers
Edmunds	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
September	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Hogs	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
8	O
in	O
Custody	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
swore	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
produced	O
one	O
Perry	O
,	O
who	O
sold	O
him	O
the	O
8	O
Hogs	O
at	O
Rumford	O
Market	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
bred	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
Sow	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
attested	O
by	O
several	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
;	O
and	O
divers	O
Persons	O
appearing	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Woolnoth	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
valued	O
1	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
6th	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
Lloyd	B-place
's	I-place
Coffee-house	I-place
,	O
where	O
the	O
Wig	O
was	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
further	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
;	O
and	O
lurking	O
about	O
a	O
while	O
,	O
was	O
observ	O
'd	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
off	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
stopt	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
search	O
,	O
two	O
Picklock	O
Keys	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
He	O
made	O
no	O
Defence	O
to	O
the	O
purpose	O
,	O
nor	O
had	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mildred	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Poultrey	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privily	O
Stealing	O
two	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Mony	O
from	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Opey	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Cheapside	B-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bustled	O
by	O
him	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Sleeve	O
;	O
whereupon	O
putting	O
his	O
Hand	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Mony	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
positive	O
he	O
had	O
just	O
before	O
,	O
She	O
said	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
wou	O
'd	O
have	O
pick	O
'd	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
refusing	O
,	O
he	O
accus	O
'd	O
her	O
maliciously	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
not	O
being	O
believ	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
none	O
appearing	O
to	O
speak	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Frances	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Alhallow	B-place
's	I-place
the	I-place
Wall	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Tea-Tongs	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Burnaby	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
open	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Hatch	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
the	O
Parlor-door	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Fuller	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Catharine	I-place
Coleman	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Side	O
,	O
a	O
Leg	O
,	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
Breast	O
of	O
Mutton	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
Instant	O
,	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davies	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Catharine	I-place
Coleman	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
valued	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Clayton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Lodger	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
of	O
a	O
sudden	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Clayton	O
swearing	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
.	O
After	O
some	O
enquiry	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
Purpool-lane	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
concurring	O
Circumstances	O
appearing	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
guilty	O
,	O
and	O
none	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
William	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Holloway	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Spurling	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
Instant	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
Breast	O
with	O
a	O
Leaden	O
Bullet	O
discharg	O
'd	O
from	O
a	O
Pistol	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
of	O
which	O
Wound	O
he	O
instantly	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
And	O
Jane	B-pers
Housden	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Aiding	O
,	O
Abetting	O
,	O
Comforting	O
and	O
Maintaining	O
the	O
said	O
Johnson	O
,	O
alias	O
Holloway	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
also	O
both	O
indicted	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Holloway	O
being	O
a	O
Convict	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Lord	O
Pierpoint	O
's	O
Horse	O
,	O
receiv	O
'd	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
Her	O
Majesty	O
's	O
late	O
gracious	O
Pardon	O
,	O
upon	O
condition	O
of	O
being	O
Transported	O
;	O
but	O
about	O
five	O
Weeks	O
ago	O
broke	O
out	O
of	O
Newgate	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
having	O
the	O
Confidence	O
to	O
come	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
,	O
(	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
drinking	O
within	O
the	O
Wall	O
by	O
the	O
Hole	O
)	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Turnkeys	O
went	O
with	O
a	O
Constable	O
and	O
a	O
Warrant	O
from	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
Parker	O
,	O
and	O
telling	O
him	O
he	O
must	O
take	O
him	O
into	O
Custody	O
,	O
he	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
surrender	O
himself	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Constable	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
his	O
Authority	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
also	O
refusing	O
to	O
obey	O
,	O
was	O
seiz	O
'd	O
upon	O
by	O
one	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Prison	O
,	O
with	O
whom	O
he	O
struggl	O
'd	O
a	O
pretty	O
while	O
'till	O
they	O
both	O
were	O
down	O
together	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
time	O
a	O
Pistol	O
(	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
before	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
)	O
was	O
beat	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
After	O
a	O
while	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
got	O
his	O
Pistol	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
still	O
held	O
fast	O
by	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
had	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
strong	O
and	O
unruly	O
;	O
whereupon	O
a	O
Prisoner	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
catch	O
'd	O
sold	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Arms	O
;	O
by	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
something	O
master	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
the	O
Hole	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Spurling	O
,	O
coming	O
to	O
help	O
the	O
others	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
quite	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
fir	O
'd	O
over	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
of	O
him	O
who	O
had	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
had	O
him	O
about	O
the	O
Middle	O
,	O
and	O
shot	O
the	O
Deceased	O
as	O
is	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
very	O
plain	O
and	O
full	O
in	O
all	O
particulars	O
.	O
And	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
sworn	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
kick	O
'd	O
and	O
beat	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
first	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
us	O
'd	O
all	O
violent	O
means	O
possible	O
to	O
procure	O
his	O
escape	O
;	O
and	O
also	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Pistol	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
she	O
convey	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
very	O
Pistol	O
which	O
kill	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceased	O
.	O
They	O
made	O
no	O
Defence	O
to	O
the	O
purpose	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
a	O
full	O
Hearing	O
,	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Wilful	O
Murder	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Carew	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstans	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
three	O
Perukes	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
from	O
Edward	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
his	O
Groom	O
,	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
his	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Burden	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
-	O
was	O
indicted	O
as	O
Principal	O
for	O
stealing	O
several	O
Goods	O
Value	O
15	O
s.	O
from	O
Lucy	B-pers
Marks	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Burden	I-pers
as	O
Accessary	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
In	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
being	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
,	I-pers
Jakeman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
large	O
quantity	O
of	O
Linnen	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
fast	O
at	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
found	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
(	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
)	O
about	O
a	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Neck	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
who	O
declar	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Marshalsea	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
did	O
also	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Johnson	O
.	O
At	O
her	O
Tryal	O
she	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
pretended	O
she	O
was	O
drunk	O
when	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
offer	O
'd	O
her	O
Mony	O
to	O
swear	O
it	O
upon	O
another	O
;	O
But	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
Evidence	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
Boy	O
)	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
forty	O
six	O
Yards	O
of	O
Callicoe	O
,	O
valued	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Molder	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
off	O
the	O
Shelf	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
plac	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Counter	O
ready	O
to	O
convey	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
discover	O
'd	O
,	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
He	O
pretended	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Boy	O
threw	O
his	O
Hat	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
fetch	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
meddle	O
with	O
the	O
Callicoe	O
;	O
which	O
not	O
being	O
believ	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
no	O
Witness	O
to	O
the	O
Reputation	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Flaxen	O
Shirt	O
,	O
valued	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Barns	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
sworn	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Shirt	O
hung	O
out	O
in	O
a	O
Court	O
a	O
drying	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
by	O
,	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
pursuit	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
He	O
pretended	O
he	O
came	O
under	O
the	O
Line	O
where	O
the	O
Linnen	O
hung	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Shirt	O
was	O
catch	O
'd	O
by	O
his	O
Button	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Peter	B-pers
Rosler	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Ewes	O
and	O
a	O
Weather	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Calcot	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Priner	O
having	O
stoln	O
the	O
Sheep	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Grounds	O
,	O
and	O
bringing	O
them	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Boat	O
,	O
a	O
Custom-house	O
Boat	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
three	O
Sheep	O
with	O
their	O
Heads	O
cut	O
off	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
they	O
brought	O
them	O
ashoar	O
,	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
Thieves	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Sheep	O
being	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
were	O
own	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
escap	O
'd	O
hir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
row	O
a	O
Boat	O
down	O
to	O
Greenwich	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
put	O
the	O
Sheep	O
aboard	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
told	O
him	O
were	O
their	O
Masters	O
:	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
either	O
to	O
that	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
as	O
Accessary	O
before	O
the	O
said	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Forest	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
seven	O
Yards	O
of	O
strip	O
'd	O
Muslin	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Walters	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
came	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
buying	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
being	O
gone	O
,	O
the	O
Muslin	O
was	O
found	O
under	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Feet	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
being	O
afterwards	O
fetch	O
'd	O
back	O
,	O
the	O
Handkerchiefs	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Mary	B-pers
Curtis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Tottenham-High-Cross	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Flaxen	O
Sheet	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Franklyn	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Witness	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
Sheet	O
off	O
a	O
Hedge	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
it	O
under	O
her	O
Ridinghood	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Silk	O
Patch	O
work	O
and	O
a	O
Snuff	O
Box	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
two	O
Years	O
ago	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
her	O
Servant	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Patchwork	O
had	O
been	O
seiz	O
'd	O
in	O
Execution	O
(	O
among	O
other	O
Goods	O
)	O
at	O
the	O
Suit	O
of	O
one	O
Brome	O
and	O
Ward	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
them	O
convey	O
'd	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Cross	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
to	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
did	O
also	O
Mrs.	O
Cross	O
,	O
the	O
Player	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
help	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
to	O
the	O
Snuff-box	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
several	O
credible	O
People	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
whom	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
knew	O
the	O
Patch	O
work	O
produc	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
help	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Pieces	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
Brome	O
and	O
Ward	O
's	O
Execution	O
was	O
set	O
aside	O
in	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
this	O
Prosecution	O
proceeded	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Patrick	B-pers
French	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Ingram	B-pers
Thwaits	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
under	O
the	O
right	O
Pap	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
.	O
and	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
six	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Wound	O
he	O
instantly	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
the	O
Deceased	O
and	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Thornton	O
being	O
at	O
Sadler	B-place
's	I-place
Wells	I-place
,	O
drank	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Cyder	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
their	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
soon	O
afterwards	O
returning	O
again	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
two	O
other	O
Gentlemen	O
in	O
the	O
Box	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
:	O
The	O
Deceased	O
thereupon	O
demanded	O
his	O
Place	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
readily	O
resign	O
'd	O
;	O
but	O
said	O
afterwards	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
his	O
Place	O
,	O
he	O
wou	O
'd	O
not	O
have	O
parted	O
with	O
it	O
so	O
easily	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Deceased	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
foolish	O
Fellow	O
to	O
think	O
he	O
'd	O
tell	O
him	O
a	O
Lye	O
;	O
immediately	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
Mr.	O
French	O
clapt	O
his	O
Hand	O
upon	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
drew	O
it	O
part	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Deceased	O
and	O
he	O
drew	O
both	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
Passes	O
at	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
fell	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
the	O
Deceased	O
drew	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
retreated	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
between	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
cou	O
'd	O
not	O
avoid	O
doing	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Defence	O
;	O
and	O
produc	O
'd	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
who	O
prov	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
passionate	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
addicted	O
to	O
Quarreling	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
quiet	O
honest	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
very	O
inoffensive	O
Conversation	O
.	O
Upon	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
gave	O
their	O
Verdict	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Defence	O
.	O
A	B-pers
-	I-pers
W	I-pers
-	I-pers
,	O
and	O
George	B-pers
Meal	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Hampstead	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
sworn	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
Sheets	O
off	O
the	O
Hedge	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
pursu	O
'd	O
,	O
dropt	O
'em	O
before	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
.	O
They	O
pretended	O
they	O
found	O
'em	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
some	O
who	O
said	O
they	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
harm	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Frocks	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
of	O
Hornsey	B-place
:	O
But	O
no	O
Prosecutor	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Delabeer	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Barnet	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Savoy	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
eleven	O
pair	O
of	O
Buckles	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Cutlery	O
Ware	O
and	O
Toys	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Boyce	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
he	O
lock	O
'd	O
his	O
Shop	O
with	O
four	O
Locks	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
broke	O
open	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
gone	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
that	O
Delabeer	O
sold	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
some	O
taken	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
had	O
Barnes	O
.	O
They	O
pretended	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
speak	O
English	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
an	O
Interpreter	O
allow	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
by	O
whom	O
they	O
made	O
a	O
very	O
trifling	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
were	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
Boyce	O
's	O
Shop	O
not	O
being	O
adjudg	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Mansion-house	O
of	O
Watkins	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Kuston	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Porringer	O
,	O
value	O
35	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
Basket-Woman	O
,	O
carry	O
'd	O
some	O
Fish	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Porringer	O
,	O
which	O
it	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
she	O
sold	O
to	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
her	O
Confession	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
whereupon	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
P	B-pers
-	I-pers
J	I-pers
-	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
Boy	O
)	O
of	O
-	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Linnen	O
,	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Welford	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
at	O
Dinner	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
stoln	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Garden	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
upon	O
pursuit	O
;	O
taken	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
'em	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
whereupon	O
be	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
,	O
valued	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
same	O
Place	O
and	O
Day	O
,	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Chalkley	I-pers
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
that	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Boyce	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
entring	O
the	O
Garden	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
break	O
into	O
his	O
House	O
:	O
but	O
there	O
wanting	O
sufficient	O
proof	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Battis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Fulham	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Auger	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
11	O
l.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
employ	O
'd	O
by	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
Garden	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
poor	O
;	O
but	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
after	O
the	O
Robbery	O
she	O
was	O
seen	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Mony	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
by	O
two	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
;	O
and	O
also	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
seen	O
asking	O
about	O
the	O
House	O
that	O
Night	O
it	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
having	O
consider	O
'd	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
her	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Capstick	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
a	O
Forbelow	O
Scarf	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Greenwood	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
sworn	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
pick	O
'd	O
the	O
Lock	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Archer	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Monk	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
insufficient	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Burroughs	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Stringer	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
stuff	O
Curtains	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Frederick	I-pers
Duplis	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
a	O
Room	O
furnish	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
opportunity	O
to	O
carry	O
off	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
pretended	O
her	O
Landlady	O
,	O
lent	O
her	O
some	O
in	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
no	O
proof	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
nor	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
so	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Silk	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
Value	O
40	O
s.	O
another	O
Silk	O
Petticoat	O
Value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Eden	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
a	O
decrepid	O
old	O
Woman	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
who	O
found	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Keys	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Mistriss	O
's	O
Pocket	O
,	O
rifled	O
her	O
Drawers	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
off	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
another	O
Woman	O
that	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Drawers	O
,	O
but	O
own	O
'd	O
her	O
being	O
privy	O
and	O
consenting	O
to	O
it	O
:	O
Whereupon	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Willoughby	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Chiswick	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Curtains	O
,	O
China	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Catherine	I-place
Coleman	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
ten	O
smocks	O
,	O
seven	O
Shirts	O
,	O
eight	O
Guineas	O
,	O
4	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
number	O
'd	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Abess	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
set	O
forth	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
Service	O
she	O
staid	O
but	O
three	O
Days	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
Goods	O
;	O
a	O
small	O
parcel	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
taken	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
Proof	O
full	O
enough	O
for	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Partridge	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
North	B-place
Hall	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Hogs	O
,	O
Value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
2	O
Sows	O
,	O
Value	O
3	O
l.	O
from	O
Charles	B-pers
Alston	I-pers
,	O
D.	O
D.	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
full	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Hogs	O
were	O
missing	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
search	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Custody	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Groom	O
in	O
Liquor-Pond-street	O
,	O
who	O
,	O
prov	O
'd	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
other	O
Person	O
sold	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
only	O
help	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
Chapman	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
Company	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
sold	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
being	O
positive	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
none	O
to	O
appear	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
Character	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Guest	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Garrard	I-pers
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Day-time	O
,	O
no	O
Person	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
Linen	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
she	O
went	O
a	O
milking	O
,	O
and	O
lock	O
'd	O
her	O
door	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
home	O
found	O
it	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Goods	O
gone	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
seiz	O
'd	O
before	O
she	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
with	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
was	O
had	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Johnson	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Felony	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Burglary	O
not	O
being	O
sufficiently	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
that	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Philont	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Davies	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Kensington	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Rodry	B-pers
Awdry	I-pers
,	O
and	O
another	O
Boy	O
,	O
did	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
steal	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Theophilus	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
a	O
Silver	O
Monteth	O
,	O
Value	O
30	O
l.	O
3	O
Casters	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
other	O
Plate	O
.	O
One	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
asking	O
about	O
Mr.	O
Butler	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
watching	O
at	O
a	O
distance	O
,	O
saw	O
a	O
Bundle	O
handed	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
of	O
a	O
lower	O
Room	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Boys	O
jump	O
'd	O
out	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Whereupon	O
she	O
pursu	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Man	O
assisting	O
her	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
dropt	O
the	O
Plate	O
.	O
He	O
pretended	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
2	O
Boys	O
well	O
dress	O
'd	O
,	O
who	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
Bundle	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
upon	O
the	O
Pursuit	O
they	O
got	O
off	O
and	O
left	O
him	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
only	O
as	O
a	O
Thief	O
's	O
common	O
Pretence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Jewers	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Pullen	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Sudworth	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Jewers	I-pers
and	O
another	O
Person	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
two	O
Silver	O
Tankards	O
,	O
Value	O
10	O
l.	O
from	O
Emanuel	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
but	O
circumstantial	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
John	B-pers
Jewers	I-pers
was	O
her	O
reputed	O
Husband	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Crowder	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Bed-Tickings	O
from	O
several	B-pers
People	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
sworn	O
by	O
one	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
sold	O
him	O
two	O
Ticks	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
being	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
was	O
sworn	O
to	O
be	O
Mr.	O
Hibbard	O
's	O
.	O
She	O
pleaded	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
brought	O
it	O
her	O
from	O
Flanders	O
;	O
but	O
cou	O
'd	O
neither	O
prove	O
that	O
nor	O
her	O
Reputation	O
:	O
Whereupon	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Stockdale	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
Mr.	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
And	O
Jane	B-pers
Revel	I-pers
as	O
Accessary	O
after	O
the	O
Fact	O
committed	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
three	O
Days	O
she	O
went	O
[	O
Pages	O
missing	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
