TOKEN	NE
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
Queen	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD	O
BAYLY	O
On	O
Friday	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
11th	O
and	O
12th	O
Days	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
1711	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Tenth	O
Year	O
of	O
Her	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEfore	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
ROBERT	B-pers
BEACHCROFT	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Lord	O
Chief	B-pers
Baron	I-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Dormer	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Ayres	O
,	O
and	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
;	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
Her	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Drake	I-pers
Simon	B-pers
Duncalf	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Toft	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Hoe	I-pers
William	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Parnel	I-pers
John	B-pers
Hanbury	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
John	B-pers
Houghton	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Forfeit	I-pers
John	B-pers
Wynn	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Aron	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Giles	B-pers
Riddle	I-pers
Jos	B-pers
.	I-pers
Spencer	I-pers
Jonathan	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
William	B-pers
Callow	I-pers
John	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
Jos	B-pers
.	I-pers
Partridge	I-pers
John	B-pers
Marriot	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Rhodes	I-pers
John	B-pers
Curtis	I-pers
John	B-pers
Meald	I-pers
William	B-pers
Pickard	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Jewet	I-pers
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Revel	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
from	O
the	O
Stall	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
11	O
Yards	O
and	O
half	O
of	O
Linsey-Wolsey	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
it	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
made	O
a	O
very	O
indifferent	O
Defence	O
;	O
only	O
brought	O
two	O
Persons	O
,	O
who	O
pretended	O
they	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
up	O
something	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Porter	O
cry	O
Halves	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
no	O
Evidence	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Talbot	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
her	O
Master	O
Richard	B-pers
Alwin	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
1	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Porringer	O
and	O
2	O
Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
Baker	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Salve-Box	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
:	O
And	O
,	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Ward	I-pers
and	O
Anne	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
as	O
Accessaries	O
after	O
the	O
Felony	O
committed	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
that	O
Ward	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
Talbot	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
Porringer	O
;	O
and	O
coming	O
to	O
sell	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Pritchard	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
stopt	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Constable	O
going	O
with	O
'em	O
to	O
Pritchard	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
found	O
Talbot	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Talbot	O
being	O
harbour	O
'd	O
there	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
no	O
body	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
,	O
but	O
Pritchard	O
alledg	O
'd	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
when	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
having	O
consider	O
'd	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
Ward	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
Pritchard	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rawson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
Woodstreet	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Box	O
of	O
Lace	O
of	O
about	O
3000	O
Yards	O
,	O
Value	O
100	O
l.	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
riding	O
through	O
Lad-lane	B-place
,	O
his	O
Box	O
was	O
cut	O
from	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
pursu	O
'd	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
Butcherhall-lane	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
Evidence	O
more	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
they	O
assisted	O
in	O
taking	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Penknife	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
't	O
is	O
suppos	O
'd	O
he	O
cut	O
off	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
threw	O
into	O
a	O
Cellar	O
when	O
taken	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
no	O
Person	O
to	O
appear	O
in	O
his	O
behalf	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Murphey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Magnes	I-place
the	I-place
Martyr	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockins	O
(	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
3	O
d	O
)	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Saunderson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
the	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
his	O
Master	O
left	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
'em	O
away	O
under	O
her	O
Ridinghood	O
;	O
and	O
another	O
took	O
her	O
just	O
by	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
over	O
London-bridge	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Stop	O
being	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
but	O
took	O
nothing	O
away	O
.	O
This	O
Defence	O
being	O
frivolous	O
,	O
and	O
none	O
appearing	O
to	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wingfield	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Lester	I-pers
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
2	O
Broad-pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
2	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
17	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Silver	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
took	O
her	O
at	O
Fleet-Ditch	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
dropt	O
the	O
Money	O
upon	O
a	O
Table	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
Examination	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
stole	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
Mistress	O
,	O
Lester	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
produc	O
'd	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
she	O
had	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
no	O
Witness	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Alice	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dennis	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Past-board	O
Box	O
,	O
12	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
16	O
s.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Dennis	O
's	O
Son	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
and	O
cheapen	O
'd	O
other	O
Goods	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
the	O
Box	O
was	O
miss	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
pursu	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
Aldersgate	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Proof	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
nor	O
of	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
being	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Rich	B-pers
.	I-pers
Cardwaker	I-pers
in	O
White-Friars	B-place
,	O
a	O
Stuff-Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joanne	B-pers
Cornish	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
was	O
Mrs.	O
Cornish	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
shelent	O
her	O
her	O
Key	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Fire	O
(	O
they	O
lodging	O
both	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Box	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
taken	O
at	O
three	O
several	O
Places	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lent	O
her	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
raise	O
Money	O
to	O
set	O
her	O
self	O
to	O
work	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
being	O
not	O
believ	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
body	O
saying	O
any	O
thing	O
on	O
her	O
behalf	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Murder	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
murdering	O
her	O
Female	O
Bastard	O
Child	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
instant	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
her	O
Mistress	O
,	O
a	O
Midwife	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
Dry	O
aforesaid	O
Nichols	O
being	O
up	O
earlier	O
than	O
usual	O
,	O
she	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
saw	O
an	O
Alteration	O
in	O
her	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
a	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
felt	O
her	O
Breasts	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
was	O
sure	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
newly	O
deliver	O
'd	O
of	O
a	O
Child	O
;	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
immediately	O
confess	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Box	O
in	O
her	O
Chamber	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
.	O
The	O
Child	O
was	O
at	O
its	O
full	O
growth	O
;	O
but	O
her	O
Mistress	O
,	O
with	O
another	O
Midwife	O
who	O
was	O
Evidence	O
,	O
gave	O
some	O
Reasons	O
why	O
in	O
their	O
Judgment	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
stillborn	O
;	O
nor	O
did	O
there	O
appear	O
any	O
Marks	O
of	O
Violence	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
When	O
her	O
Pains	O
came	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
Bed	O
,	O
but	O
fell	O
into	O
a	O
Swoon	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
call	O
for	O
Help	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
appearing	O
she	O
had	O
made	O
some	O
Provision	O
for	O
her	O
Bying-in	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Blunt	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Queen-hithe	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Sacks	O
,	O
4	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Pease	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Bushel	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Flower	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
a	O
Watchmen	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Pease	O
in	O
a	O
Wheel-barrow	O
selling	O
about	O
the	O
Streets	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
being	O
satisfied	O
he	O
was	O
Non	O
compos-mentis	O
,	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bow	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
in	O
speaking	O
false	O
,	O
seditious	O
and	O
dangerous	O
Words	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
Queen	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
afore-said	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
reading	O
the	O
Post-man	O
at	O
their	O
Master	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
Aldermanbury-Postern	O
,	O
they	O
there	O
found	O
that	O
Prince	O
Eugene	O
was	O
coming	O
for	O
England	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
cost	O
him	O
a	O
Shilling	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
the	O
Evidence	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
For	O
his	O
part	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
for	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
Queen	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
rather	O
see	O
her	O
;	O
where	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
utter	O
'd	O
these	O
Words	O
,	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
Queen	O
She	O
's	O
not	O
worthy	O
to	O
carry	O
Prince	O
Eugene	O
's	O
Shooes	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
Damn	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
wou	O
'd	O
sacrifice	O
Her	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
hundred	O
,	O
may	O
a	O
thousand	O
such	O
as	O
She	O
,	O
for	O
,	O
Prince	O
Eugene	O
;	O
for	O
She	O
's	O
but	O
a	O
Mechanick	O
,	O
the	O
Daughter	O
of	O
a	O
Collier	O
;	O
Her	O
Father	O
was	O
a	O
Rogue	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
better	O
born	O
than	O
She	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
sorry	O
for	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
said	O
;	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
No	O
;	O
Damn	O
her	O
,	O
what	O
I	O
said	O
was	O
true	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
testify	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
Words	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
little	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
;	O
but	O
called	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
he	O
was	O
enclining	O
to	O
Lunacy	O
;	O
one	O
particularly	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
distracted	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
said	O
all	O
the	O
Journey-men	O
Taylors	O
went	O
to	O
Hell	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
live	O
but	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
should	O
go	O
thither	O
too	O
;	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
mention	O
'd	O
other	O
extravagant	O
Expressions	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
Fore-man	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
thereby	O
went	O
through	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Business	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
declaring	O
he	O
frequently	O
spoke	O
ill	O
Words	O
against	O
the	O
Queen	O
and	O
Government	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
publishing	O
a	O
forg	O
'd	O
Will	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Cooke	I-pers
,	O
dated	O
March	O
14	O
,	O
1709	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
personated	O
Margaret	O
the	O
Widow	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Cooke	O
,	O
(	O
who	O
dy	O
'd	O
on	O
board	O
her	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Ship	O
Sunderland	O
)	O
and	O
making	O
Oath	O
before	O
the	O
Surrogate	O
,	O
had	O
Letters	O
of	O
Administration	O
;	O
and	O
thereupon	O
procur	O
'd	O
a	O
Ticket	O
for	O
the	O
Pay	O
of	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
marry	O
'd	O
to	O
Cooke	O
at	O
the	O
Nor	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
appearing	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
very	O
plain	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Daniel	B-pers
Tryant	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Tryant	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
publishing	O
a	O
forg	O
'd	O
Indenture	O
of	O
Apprenticeship	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hicks	I-pers
of	O
Abington	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Oxford	O
,	O
(	O
as	O
they	O
had	O
falsely	O
put	O
it	O
)	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
and	O
one	O
Weden	O
and	O
her	O
Father	O
(	O
who	O
went	O
for	O
her	O
Unkle	O
)	O
had	O
assign	O
'd	O
the	O
Indenture	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Power	O
upon	O
it	O
to	O
receive	O
the	O
Pay	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
Hicks	O
on	O
board	O
several	O
of	O
her	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Ships	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
serv	O
'd	O
,	O
to	O
one	O
Bailey	O
of	O
Deptford	O
for	O
27	O
d.	O
14	O
s.	O
which	O
being	O
discover	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Navy	O
board	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
apprehended	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
one	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anne	I-place
Black-Fryars	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Ware-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Child	I-pers
,	O
Justice	O
,	O
in	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
to	O
her	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
two	O
others	O
,	O
who	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Ware-house	O
;	O
and	O
another	O
Witness	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
3	O
of	O
the	O
Firkins	O
in	O
Black-Fryars	O
;	O
which	O
the	O
Woman	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
declar	O
'd	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
her	O
by	O
3	O
Men	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
for	O
Tallow	O
,	O
but	O
cou	O
'd	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
;	O
but	O
another	O
Witness	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
that	O
carr	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
Share	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
Another	O
Person	O
,	O
who	O
bought	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
Jones	O
help	O
'd	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
by	O
one	O
Draper	O
to	O
carry	O
'em	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
1	O
s.	O
for	O
his	O
Pains	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
some	O
Witness	O
,	O
who	O
not	O
being	O
credited	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Wedon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White-Chapel	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
publishing	O
a	O
forg	O
'd	O
indeatune	O
of	O
Apprenticeship	O
,	O
whereby	O
it	O
was	O
pretended	O
James	B-pers
Langmore	I-pers
,	O
Son	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Langmore	I-pers
of	O
Bristol	O
,	O
Weaver	O
,	O
was	O
bound	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
Blacksmith	O
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
4th	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
Queen	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Term	O
of	O
7	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Will	O
to	O
empower	O
the	O
said	O
Parker	O
to	O
receive	O
his	O
pretended	O
Apprentice	O
's	O
Pay	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Canterbury	O
;	O
which	O
said	O
Power	O
it	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
was	O
sold	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
for	O
22	O
l.	O
Wedon	O
being	O
present	O
,	O
and	O
justifying	O
that	O
Parker	O
was	O
the	O
real	O
Master	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Langmore	O
,	O
and	O
both	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
sign	O
'd	O
a	O
Bond	O
to	O
indemnify	O
the	O
Purchaser	O
.	O
Saunders	O
making	O
Enquiry	O
concerning	O
the	O
Payment	O
of	O
the	O
Ship	O
,	O
found	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
Indenture	O
;	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
the	O
Cheat	O
was	O
discover	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
were	O
seiz	O
'd	O
,	O
when	O
both	O
of	O
'em	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
Parker	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
Wedon	O
drew	O
him	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
same	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Frances	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
of	O
5	O
Sheets	O
(	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Barl	O
of	O
Ha	O
)	O
and	O
2	O
Shirts	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Marfield	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Marfield	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
Charewoman	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
to	O
help	O
her	O
wash	O
,	O
she	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Linnen	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confes	O
'd	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Gate-house	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
frightned	O
into	O
such	O
Confession	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
several	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
;	O
(	O
some	O
of	O
whom	O
said	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
a	O
vexations	O
Person	O
,	O
and	O
given	O
to	O
pawn	O
Linnen	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
unknown	O
to	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
whereupon	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Green	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Langton	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Stevens	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Francis	B-pers
Were	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
Mr	O
.	O
Were	O
being	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
,	O
left	O
a	O
Person	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
his	O
Chambers	O
,	O
(	O
No	O
2	O
in	O
Lions-Inn	B-place
)	O
who	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
going	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
heard	O
a	O
Noise	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Door	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
some	O
Help	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
going	O
up	O
,	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
one	O
after	O
another	O
upon	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
stopt	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
found	O
a	O
Trunk	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
China	O
pack	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Handbasket	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
over	O
it	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
Handkerchief	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Goodwin	O
,	O
whose	O
Chambers	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
not	O
long	O
before	O
)	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
ready	O
to	O
carry	O
away	O
.	O
Green	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
the	O
Inn	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
an	O
Outcry	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
and	O
Langton	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
there	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Harrison	O
of	O
that	O
Inn	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
have	O
him	O
put	O
a	O
Bond	O
in	O
sule	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
They	O
pretended	O
not	O
to	O
know	O
one	O
another	O
when	O
taken	O
;	O
but	O
at	O
their	O
Trial	O
they	O
own	O
'd	O
they	O
did	O
.	O
All	O
which	O
the	O
Court	O
taking	O
into	O
Consideration	O
,	O
were	O
of	O
Opinion	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
Garret	O
separate	O
from	O
the	O
Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
judg	O
'd	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Mansion-house	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
;	O
And	O
craving	O
Benefit	O
of	O
Clergy	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
deny	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
having	O
been	O
formerly	O
convicted	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
said	O
Benefit	O
,	O
which	O
none	O
ought	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
for	O
a	O
like	O
Offence	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
21	O
Yards	O
of	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
Shop	O
to	O
buy	O
half	O
a	O
Yard	O
of	O
Ribbon	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
24	O
Yards	O
was	O
miss	O
'd	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
pursu	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
privately	O
dropt	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
Drawer	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
also	O
prov	O
'd	O
by	O
another	O
Witness	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
;	O
but	O
none	O
appearing	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Bryan	B-pers
Cugley	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Camlet	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
other	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Dayley	B-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Chambers	O
in	O
Gray	O
's	O
Inn	O
were	O
rob	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
carried	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
alledg	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
time	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
granted	O
;	O
but	O
none	O
appearing	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Clements	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Fulham	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gelding	O
from	O
Ralph	B-pers
Sheldon	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
(	O
a	O
Servant	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Sheldon	O
's	O
)	O
depos	O
'd	O
That	O
the	O
Horse	O
was	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Grounds	O
at	O
Weston	O
in	O
Warwickshire	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
Walham-Green	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
Queen-street	O
,	O
where	O
both	O
the	O
Man	O
and	O
Gelding	O
were	O
taken	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
the	O
Horse	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Grounds	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Road	O
bridled	O
and	O
saddled	O
,	O
and	O
rode	O
him	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
intending	O
to	O
have	O
him	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
Evidence	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
frighted	O
into	O
a	O
Confession	O
:	O
But	O
that	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
induce	O
the	O
Jury	O
to	O
believe	O
him	O
innocent	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Horse-stealing	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Spring	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Cranfield	B-place
in	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
21	O
Weathers	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Westbrook	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
'em	O
in	O
the	O
Grounds	O
over-night	O
,	O
and	O
next	O
Morning	O
missing	O
'em	O
,	O
pursu	O
'd	O
the	O
Track	O
to	O
Kensington	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
found	O
'em	O
in	O
Possession	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
'em	O
upon	O
the	O
Road	O
of	O
one	O
who	O
had	O
sold	O
him	O
several	O
Sheep	O
before	O
,	O
one	O
Wild	O
a	O
Jobber	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
who	O
said	O
on	O
his	O
behalf	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Lunatick	O
about	O
a	O
Year	O
ago	O
;	O
but	O
could	O
say	O
nothing	O
since	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Budely	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
pretending	O
to	O
ask	O
for	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
West	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
Things	O
into	O
her	O
Apron	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joan	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hood	O
and	O
Scarf	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Whitwood	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Rachel	B-pers
Whitwood	I-pers
(	O
the	O
Mother	O
of	O
Mary	O
)	O
who	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
her	O
Window	O
was	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
another	O
Witness	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Box	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
Bed	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
when	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Jeremy	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Robert	B-pers
Hide	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
day-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
;	O
Silver	O
hafted	O
Knives	O
and	O
Forks	O
,	O
2	O
Salts	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
spoons	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
Witnesses	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Sash-window	O
was	O
open	O
'd	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
below	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
away	O
from	O
the	O
Side-board	O
in	O
the	O
Parlor	O
;	O
and	O
making	O
pursuit	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
'em	O
from	O
a	O
Boy	O
,	O
who	O
met	O
him	O
coming	O
from	O
Hide	O
Park	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
3	O
d.	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
Place	O
call	O
'd	O
Rose-Alley	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
believing	O
him	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Stubling	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
,	O
in	O
cutting	O
a	O
Trunk	O
from	O
behind	O
the	O
Cambridge	O
Stage-Coach	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
January	O
instant	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Sare	I-pers
junior	O
.	O
One	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
Trunk	O
from	O
behind	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
pursu	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Trunk	O
.	O
Another	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
behind	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
up	O
likewise	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
his	O
Master	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
angry	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
not	O
going	O
home	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
his	O
Trunk	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
haste	O
,	O
and	O
get	O
home	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Plastow	O
to	O
receive	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Trunk	O
in	O
the	O
Road	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
to	O
be	O
frivolous	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
stuff-Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Frances	B-pers
Sterry	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
her	O
Chamber-door	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Goods	O
gone	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
some	O
Information	O
concerning	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
took	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
having	O
no	O
body	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
reach	O
to	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Simons	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Amhurst	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
upon	O
two	O
several	O
Indictments	O
for	O
Cheating	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
not	O
having	O
sufficient	O
Matter	O
to	O
find	O
him	O
Guilty	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Frances	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Senock	I-pers
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
January	O
instant	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
two	O
Cloth	O
Coats	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
his	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
some	O
Lodgers	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Window	O
of	O
a	O
low	O
Room	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Casement	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Cloth	O
Coats	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
very	O
little	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
the	O
Burgarly	O
not	O
being	O
sufficiently	O
prov	O
'd	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
W	B-pers
-	I-pers
C	I-pers
-	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Wilful	O
Perjury	O
,	O
in	O
an	O
Affidavit	O
sworn	O
before	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
Parker	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Woodman	I-pers
and	O
Anne	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Linnen	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Waggon	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
they	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Jones	I-pers
being	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
her	O
former	O
Judgment	O
,	O
was	O
also	O
found	O
pregnant	O
The	O
Trials	O
bring	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Sentence	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
4.	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Price	O
,	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Langton	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Stevens	O
,	O
Alice	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Clements	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Women	O
pleaded	O
Pregnancy	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
being	O
impannell	O
'd	O
,	O
reported	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
with	O
Child	O
.	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Jones	I-pers
being	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
her	O
former	O
Judgment	O
,	O
was	O
also	O
found	O
pregnant	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
14	O
.	O
Jor	O
.	O
Clerk	O
,	O
Anne	B-pers
Talbot	I-pers
,	O
Anne	B-pers
Woodman	I-pers
,	O
Anne	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
Anne	B-pers
Walters	I-pers
,	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Stubling	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Spring	I-pers
,	O
Bryan	B-pers
Cagley	I-pers
,	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Rawson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Frances	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Wingfield	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
,	O
5.	O
Jane	B-pers
Revel	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Murphey	I-pers
,	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Anne	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
To	O
stand	O
on	O
the	O
Pillory	O
,	O
6.	O
Charles	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
fin	O
'd	O
13	O
s.	O
4	O
d.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Tryant	I-pers
,	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Tryant	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Wedon	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
All	O
Melancholy	O
,	O
Hysterical	O
and	O
Hypochondriacal	O
Distempers	O
,	O
which	O
variously	O
affect	O
the	O
Mind	O
,	O
with	O
strange	O
Fears	O
,	O
and	O
disposal	O
Apprehensions	O
;	O
Paintings	O
and	O
Sinkings	O
of	O
it	O
Spirits	O
,	O
great	O
Hurries	O
,	O
Restlessness	O
and	O
Disquietment	O
.	O
(	O
little	O
understood	O
,	O
and	O
seldom	O
cured	O
by	O
any	O
common	O
Means	O
)	O
also	O
Pain	O
,	O
and	O
Giddiness	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
Risings	O
to	O
the	O
Throat	O
,	O
Sick-fits	O
,	O
Tremblings	O
.	O
Oppressions	O
of	O
the	O
Heart	O
.	O
or	O
any	O
other	O
Disorders	O
caus	O
'd	O
by	O
Vapours	O
,	O
are	O
successfully	O
cured	O
(	O
with	O
God	O
's	O
Blessing	O
)	O
by	O
a	O
Physician	O
well	O
experienc	O
'd	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
more	O
than	O
20	O
Years	O
Practice	O
in	O
those	O
deplorable	O
Cases	O
;	O
who	O
also	O
cures	O
all	O
kinds	O
of	O
Fits	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
strange	O
and	O
violent	O
,	O
of	O
curable	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
information	O
sight	O
of	O
these	O
Water	O
.	O
Living	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
Shadwell	O
Coffee-House	O
in	O
Upper-Shadwell	O
,	O
near	O
London	O
;	O
where	O
those	O
that	O
have	O
occasion	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
remote	O
,	O
may	O
direct	O
their	O
Letters	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
shall	O
be	O
speedily	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
as	O
attended	O
on	O
,	O
if	O
desired	O
.	O
Ldisworth	O
's	O
Record	O
Ink	O
Powder	O
,	O
is	O
made	O
and	O
sold	O
at	O
the	O
Golden	O
Ball	O
in	O
Cannon-street	O
,	O
London	O
.	O
Each	O
Six-Penny	O
Paper	O
of	O
3	O
Ounces	O
makes	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
the	O
best	O
Ink	O
.	O
or	O
Quart	O
,	O
as	O
by	O
Directions	O
,	O
sealed	O
up	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
same	O
in	O
proposition	O
,	O
for	O
greater	O
Quantities	O
.	O
)	O
Sold	O
by	O
the	O
Stationers	O
,	O
Booksellers	O
,	O
and	O
Haberdashers	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
chiefest	O
Cities	O
and	O
Towns	O
in	O
Great-Britain	O
and	O
Ireland	O
.	O
An	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
Conversion	O
of	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Barville	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Barton	O
,	O
from	O
Popery	O
to	O
the	O
Reformed	O
Church	O
of	O
England	O
;	O
with	O
the	O
Form	O
of	O
his	O
solemn	O
Abjuration	O
of	O
the	O
Romish	O
Religion	O
.	O
Written	O
by	O
himself	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
are	O
added	O
,	O
a	O
Letter	O
of	O
the	O
Revetend	O
Dr.	O
Kennett	O
,	O
Dean	O
of	O
Peterborough	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Barville	O
,	O
upon	O
occasion	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
reconciled	O
to	O
the	O
Church	O
of	O
England	O
.	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Forms	O
of	O
Renouncing	O
Popery	O
,	O
made	O
by	O
some	O
other	O
late	O
Converts	O
.	O
Satyrical	O
Reflections	O
on	O
Clubs	O
;	O
in	O
29	O
Chapters	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
Of	O
Clubs	O
in	O
general	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
The	O
Vertuoso	O
's	O
Club	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
The	O
Knights	O
of	O
the	O
Golden	O
Fleece	O
.	O
4	O
.	O
The	O
No-Nose	O
Club	O
.	O
5	O
.	O
The	O
Man-killing	O
Club	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
The	O
Surly	O
Club	O
.	O
7	O
.	O
The	O
Atheistical-Club	O
8	O
.	O
The	O
Club	O
of	O
Ugly-Faces	O
.	O
9	O
.	O
Of	O
the	O
Split-Farthing	O
Club	O
.	O
10	O
.	O
The	O
Club	O
of	O
Broken	O
Shop-keepers	O
.	O
11	O
.	O
The	O
Man-Hunters	O
Club	O
.	O
12	O
.	O
The	O
Yorkshire	O
Club	O
.	O
13	O
.	O
The	O
Mock-Heroes	O
Club	O
.	O
14	O
.	O
The	O
Beauxe	O
Club	O
.	O
15	O
.	O
The	O
Wrangling	O
,	O
of	O
Hussel	O
Parthing	O
Club	O
.	O
16	O
.	O
The	O
Quack	O
's	O
Club	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
the	O
Physical	O
Society	O
.	O
17	O
.	O
The	O
Weekly	O
Dancing	O
Club	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
the	O
Buttock-Ball	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
.	O
18	O
.	O
The	O
Bird-Fanciers	O
Club	O
;	O
and	O
of	O
their	O
Annual	O
Feast	O
.	O
19	O
.	O
The	O
Lying	O
Club	O
;	O
and	O
how	O
it	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
establish	O
'd	O
.	O
20	O
.	O
The	O
Scatter-Wit	O
Club	O
.	O
21	O
.	O
The	O
Florists	O
Club	O
.	O
22	O
.	O
Buh	O
Weden	O
's	O
Cellar	O
Club	O
.	O
23	O
.	O
The	O
Mollies	O
Club	O
.	O
24	O
.	O
The	O
Bawds	O
initiating	O
Club	O
.	O
25.	O
Sam	B-pers
.	I-pers
Scot	I-pers
's	O
Smoaking	O
Club	O
.	O
26	O
.	O
The	O
Thieves	O
Club	O
.	O
27	O
.	O
The	O
Small-Coal	O
Man	O
's	O
Musick	O
Club	O
.	O
28	O
.	O
The	O
Kit-Cat	O
Club	O
.	O
29	O
.	O
The	O
Beef-Stake	O
Club	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
Author	O
of	O
the	O
London-Spy	O
.	O
Vol	O
.	O
IV	O
.	O
Politics	O
:	O
In	O
Select	O
Discourses	O
of	O
Monsieur	O
Bolzac	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
his	O
Aristippus	O
,	O
or	O
Wise	O
Scholar	O
.	O
Done	O
into	O
English	O
by	O
Basil	B-pers
Kennett	I-pers
,	O
Fellow	O
of	O
C.	B-pers
C.	I-pers
C.	I-pers
Oxford	I-pers
;	O
now	O
Chapter	O
in	O
a	O
British	O
Factory	O
abroad	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
are	O
added	O
,	O
An	O
Advertisement	O
of	O
the	O
Translation	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Life	O
and	O
Writings	O
of	O
the	O
Author	O
.	O
Sacramental	O
Exercises	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
The	O
Christian	O
's	O
Employment	O
Before	O
,	O
At	O
,	O
and	O
After	O
the	O
Lord	O
's	O
Supper	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
A	O
Discourse	O
of	O
Hearing	O
;	O
being	O
a	O
Farewell-Sermon	O
Preach	O
'd	O
in	O
Lime-Street	O
,	O
Sept.	O
29	O
,	O
1706	O
.	O
By	O
Jabex	O
Barle	O
.	O
All	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
Phillips	O
,	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
the	O
Fleece	O
.	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
.	O
Printed	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Humfreys	I-pers
in	O
Bartholomew-lane	O
,	O
behind	O
the	O
Royal-Exchange	O
,	O
(	O
where	O
Advertisements	O
are	O
taken	O
in	O
)	O
for	O
JOHN	B-pers
PHILLIPS	I-pers
at	O
the	O
Black	O
Bull	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
;	O
And	O
sold	O
by	O
A.	O
Buldwin	O
in	O
Warwick-lane	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
d	O
.	O
