TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
Queen	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
Held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD	O
BAYLEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
9th	O
,	O
and	O
10th	O
,	O
Days	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
1713	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Twelfth	O
Year	O
of	O
Her	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEfore	O
the	O
Rt	O
.	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	B-pers
HOARE	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Powis	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Eyre	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Price	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
Richardson	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
of	O
Her	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Roger	B-pers
Hitchcock	I-pers
Benjamin	B-pers
Eeles	I-pers
John	B-pers
Barnsley	I-pers
John	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
Nathaniel	B-pers
Hanwell	I-pers
John	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
William	B-pers
Kempster	I-pers
John	B-pers
Boyce	I-pers
Benjamin	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
John	B-pers
Whitehorn	I-pers
William	B-pers
Shippard	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Wyld	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Giles	B-pers
Riddle	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bavand	I-pers
John	B-pers
Curtis	I-pers
William	B-pers
Callow	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Roades	I-pers
Jonathan	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
Bruce	B-pers
Randall	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
How	I-pers
Jacob	B-pers
Pullen	I-pers
John	B-pers
Bull	I-pers
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Tomson	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
Muslen	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
15	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
and	O
cheapen	O
'd	O
Muslen	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
agreeing	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
when	O
gone	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
pursu	O
'd	O
and	O
brought	O
back	O
,	O
the	O
Muslen	O
drop	O
'd	O
from	O
Elizabeth	O
Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
saying	O
little	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
and	O
Catherine	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
two	O
Callico	O
Shirts	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Meers	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Kingston	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
Callico	O
;	O
that	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
Woman	O
came	O
in	O
for	O
her	O
Pot	O
;	O
and	O
while	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
turn	O
'd	O
her	O
Back	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
Jones	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
;	O
but	O
nothing	O
appearing	O
against	O
Parker	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cauldrey	I-pers
of	O
Alhallows	B-place
,	I-place
Lombard-street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Kettle	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Cambridge	I-pers
,	O
from	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Payne	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
Payne	O
's	O
Shop	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Kettle	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
cross	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
it	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Bartholomew	I-place
the	I-place
Less	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
60	O
Yards	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Drugget	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
Date	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
going	O
from	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
desir	O
'd	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
to	O
have	O
an	O
Eye	O
to	O
it	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
long	O
gone	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
and	O
come	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
,	O
being	O
suspected	O
to	O
have	O
stolen	O
something	O
,	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Callico	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edmund	B-pers
Lightfoot	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
and	O
cheapen	O
'd	O
Goods	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
reaching	O
some	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
take	O
those	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
under	O
his	O
great	O
Coat	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
upon	O
Search	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
ofDrugget	O
Breeches	O
,	O
a	O
Damask	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
a	O
Cloath	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Cloath	O
Breeches	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ordess	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Matthew	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictments	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Barbara	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
three	O
Silver	O
Castors	O
,	O
three	O
Silver	O
Salvers	O
,	O
12	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
pieces	O
of	O
Plate	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
60	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Catherine	B-pers
Priest	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Smithson	I-pers
of	O
four	O
Guineas	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Pocket	O
Pistols	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Arthur	B-pers
Birdwhistle	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
pursu	O
'd	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
White	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Best	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Susannah	B-pers
Thurley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Day	O
time	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
Person	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
a	O
Drugget	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
28	O
s.	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Ranger	I-pers
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Armstrong	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
four	O
Perukes	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Holland	O
Coif	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
Mony	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Drawer	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Mony	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Perukes	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sorrel	O
Gelding	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Twyford	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
his	O
Gelding	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Grounds	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
afterwards	O
found	O
in	O
Grays-Inn-Lane	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Possession	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
Apprehended	O
and	O
Examin	O
'd	O
before	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
but	O
giving	O
no	O
Account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Martha	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
Callico	O
Petticoat	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
Table	O
Cloth	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
were	O
both	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
six	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Thread-laces	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elias	B-pers
Oneby	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
Gartering	O
;	O
that	O
while	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
turn	O
'd	O
her	O
Back	O
to	O
reach	O
some	O
,	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Finch	I-pers
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
without	O
buying	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
brought	O
back	O
upon	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
he	O
drop	O
'd	O
the	O
Laces	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
but	O
nothing	O
appearing	O
against	O
the	O
Woman	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
White	I-pers
were	O
both	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
60	O
Yards	O
of	O
Persian	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
some	O
Persian	O
Silk	O
:	O
Several	O
Pieces	O
were	O
taken	O
down	O
and	O
shown	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
without	O
buying	O
any	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
came	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
whether	O
he	O
mist	O
nothing	O
;	O
upon	O
looking	O
over	O
his	O
Goods	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
above-mention	O
'd	O
;	O
immediate	O
pursuit	O
was	O
made	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
into	O
an	O
House	O
in	O
Black-fryars	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
deny	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
People	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Constable	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
a	O
Chamber	O
,	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
saying	O
nothing	O
for	O
themselves	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Walton	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
25	O
Yards	O
of	O
China	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
another	O
Woman	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
Blankets	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
carry	O
'd	O
the	O
said	O
other	O
Woman	O
into	O
the	O
back	O
Shop	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
loitered	O
behind	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
up	O
her	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
discover	O
'd	O
and	O
taken	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
positive	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
nothing	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elinor	B-pers
Ray	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Black	O
and	O
White	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
a	O
Black	O
Silk	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
work	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
but	O
on	O
the	O
Date	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
she	O
got	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
Chamber	O
where	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
,	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
took	O
them	O
and	O
fled	O
.	O
It	O
further	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Hope	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Richard	I-pers
Chapman	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Callico	O
Quilt	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Warehouseof	O
Will	B-pers
.	I-pers
Langbourn	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Oaks	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Warehouse	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Quilt	O
from	O
a	O
Pile	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
pursu	O
'd	O
,	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
it	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Corbet	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Faith	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
James	B-pers
Shippard	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
High-way	O
,	O
and	O
violently	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
Hat	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
James	B-pers
Shippard	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
going	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
by	O
the	O
Chapter-house	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Church	I-place
yard	I-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
suddenly	O
snatch	O
'd	O
off	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
down	O
Paul	O
's	O
Alley	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
being	O
pursu	O
'd	O
,	O
threw	O
them	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
immediately	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Eye	O
being	O
upon	O
him	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
making	O
a	O
frivolous	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
six	O
Rugs	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Armstrong	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
carrying	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
by	O
the	O
Watch	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
producing	O
no	O
Proof	O
of	O
his	O
Property	O
in	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Price	I-pers
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Revel	I-pers
were	O
both	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
a	O
Norwich	O
Crape-Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
with	O
other	O
Things	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Hebway	I-pers
;	O
a	O
Poplin	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Drugget	O
Coat	O
,	O
Wastecoat	O
and	O
Breeches	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Will	B-pers
.	I-pers
Hester	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Price	I-pers
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mary	O
Hill	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
he	O
got	O
into	O
Hester	O
's	O
Room	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
likewise	O
a	O
Lodger	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
stop	O
'd	O
near	O
Clerkenwell	O
by	O
a	O
Watchman	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
prov	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
;	O
but	O
nothing	O
more	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
against	O
Jane	B-pers
Revel	I-pers
,	O
than	O
her	O
being	O
in	O
Price	O
's	O
Company	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Alice	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Benj	B-pers
.	I-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
as	O
a	O
Visitor	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
the	O
Ring	O
was	O
missing	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Bason	O
;	O
being	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
;	O
upon	O
her	O
Examination	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Scot	I-pers
of	O
a	O
silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
going	O
thro	O
'	O
a	O
Croud	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Church-yard	I-place
,	O
found	O
a	O
twitch	O
given	O
to	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
seiz	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
found	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Twelves	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Drugget	O
Coat	O
and	O
Wastecoat	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Will	B-pers
.	I-pers
Careless	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
his	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
taken	O
upon	O
suspicion	O
,	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Wildman	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Yards	O
of	O
Garlick	O
Holland	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Abr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Ellis	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Yard	O
of	O
Muslen	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
agreeing	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
back	O
Shop	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Holland	O
from	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
going	O
along	O
it	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
drop	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
to	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
little	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
;	O
which	O
Fact	O
being	O
clearly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Gerrard	B-pers
Dennit	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
to	O
sell	O
an	O
old	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
she	O
went	O
backward	O
for	O
her	O
Journey-man	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
from	O
the	O
Shop-window	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
afterwards	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Isaacson	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Serge	O
Wastecoat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Predham	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Heley	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
taking	O
to	O
Wife	O
Catherine	B-pers
More	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
Anne	B-pers
Deton	I-pers
whom	O
he	O
married	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
being	O
then	O
alive	O
.	O
But	O
none	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cartwright	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Holland	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Burren	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Sheets	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
they	O
werehung	O
a	O
drying	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
taken	O
upon	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Tigget	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
23	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Slippers	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Boots	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Roger	B-pers
Edmunds	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
Intelligence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
sold	O
several	O
pair	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
Apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
his	O
Examination	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Wagstaff	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Floyd	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Tabby-Stays	O
,	O
Value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
Damask-gown	O
10	O
l.	O
a	O
Damask	O
Petticoat	O
trim	O
'd	O
with	O
Gold	O
10	O
l.	O
a	O
silver	O
Cup	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
4	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Moyl	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
April	O
1712	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Boarded	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
;	O
that	O
while	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Market	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bundled	O
up	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
privately	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Frances	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Sheet	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Alex	B-pers
.	I-pers
Minshall	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
losing	O
his	O
Goods	O
charg	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
who	O
upon	O
her	O
Examination	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anthony	B-pers
Dealmanza	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Perjury	O
,	O
upon	O
an	O
Affidavit	O
taken	O
before	O
the	O
Judges	O
of	O
the	O
Common-Pleas	O
;	O
that	O
one	O
Francis	B-pers
Bittilly	I-pers
was	O
indebted	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
24000	O
l.	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Coplady	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
by	O
shooting	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Leaden	O
Bullet	O
discharg	O
'd	O
from	O
a	O
Gun	O
,	O
which	O
occasion	O
'd	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
in	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
his	O
Stomach	O
near	O
his	O
Navel	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
Queen	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Evening	O
before	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
Murder	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Aunt	O
of	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
what	O
is	O
the	O
Matter	O
with	O
your	O
Nephew	O
,	O
he	O
does	O
nothing	O
but	O
asperce	O
me	O
?	O
Said	O
moreover	O
,	O
her	O
Nephew	O
was	O
all	O
for	O
Law	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
'll	O
take	O
another	O
Course	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
we	O
'll	O
have	O
a	O
Game	O
at	O
Loggerheads	O
,	O
he	O
shall	O
have	O
my	O
Blood	O
or	O
I	O
'll	O
have	O
his	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
that	O
he	O
actually	O
executed	O
what	O
he	O
threaten	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
produc	O
'd	O
divers	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
elsewhere	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fitz-Hugh	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
40	O
l.	O
Weight	O
of	O
Brass	O
,	O
Value	O
35	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Matthew	B-pers
Bagley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Horner	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Chelsea	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
5	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
Value	O
20	O
s.	O
24	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
24	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Crauford	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
strong	O
enough	O
to	O
convict	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Sparks	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bay	O
Mare	O
,	O
Value	O
6	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ralph	B-pers
Fryer	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
Date	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
put	O
his	O
Mare	O
in	O
the	O
Stable	O
about	O
10	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
lock	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Stable	O
about	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
his	O
Stable-door	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Mare	O
gone	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
giving	O
no	O
Account	O
of	O
his	O
Property	O
in	O
her	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Sandwell	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Precinct	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Catherines	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
60	O
Yards	O
of	O
Welch	O
Cotten	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Original	B-pers
Havers	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
going	O
thro	O
'	O
Bridge	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
was	O
suspected	O
by	O
some	O
Watermen	O
to	O
have	O
stolen	O
them	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
Apprehended	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
out	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
prov	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
from	O
his	O
Ware-house	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
giving	O
no	O
Account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Orton	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Fir-pole	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Burburrough	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
July	O
:	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
her	O
Request	O
granted	O
her	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Beswick	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
point	O
Pot	O
,	O
Value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
deficient	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Tooley	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
Sheets	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Lady	B-pers
Ann	I-pers
Mason	I-pers
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
12	O
Holland	O
Smocks	O
,	O
Value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
14	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Crowder	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
positive	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Fudg	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Higdell	I-pers
of	O
a	O
silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
Instant	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
in	O
Moorfields	B-place
to	O
see	O
the	O
Charity	O
Children	O
,	O
one	O
that	O
stood	O
by	O
him	O
observ	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
immediately	O
Apprehended	O
with	O
it	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Gladman	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brown	O
Gelding	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Lady	O
Ann	B-pers
Seabrook	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Horse	O
was	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Stable	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
2	O
Months	O
after	O
,	O
one	O
going	O
thro	O
'	O
Smithfield	O
that	O
knew	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
saw	O
him	O
there	O
set	O
to	O
Sale	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Servant	O
of	O
one	O
Morris	O
;	O
Morris	O
prov	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
giving	O
no	O
Account	O
of	O
his	O
Property	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Hannah	B-pers
Beck	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Shirts	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Will	B-pers
.	I-pers
Broadhurst	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
instant	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
a	O
Counter	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
Apprehended	O
by	O
a	O
Boy	O
,	O
with	O
them	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
nothing	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Major	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Dish	O
,	O
Value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
Brass	O
Sauce-pan	O
3	O
s.	O
10	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Worsted	O
20	O
d.	O
with	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Good	O
of	O
Rich	B-pers
.	I-pers
Beardsley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
losing	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
charg	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
who	O
upon	O
her	O
Examination	O
,	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Dean	B-place
and	I-place
Chapter	I-place
of	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
16	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
Value	O
16	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Flannel-smock	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
which	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Worsted	O
,	O
Value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Bromfield	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
two	O
others	O
came	O
to	O
a	O
Bookseller	O
's	O
Shop	O
and	O
enquir	O
'd	O
for	O
Valentine	O
and	O
Orson	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
away	O
without	O
buying	O
.	O
The	O
Bookseller	O
's	O
Servant	O
suspecting	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
Thieves	O
,	O
kept	O
his	O
Eye	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
them	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
lift	O
up	O
the	O
Sash	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
out	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
then	O
pursu	O
'd	O
them	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
got	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
bundle	O
of	O
wet	O
Linnen	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ingleby	B-pers
Thorp	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
and	O
bundled	O
up	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
off	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
them	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Hannah	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Wearing	O
Cloaths	O
and	O
Linnen	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hubbard	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Harris	O
,	O
but	O
left	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
of	O
her	O
Landlady	O
that	O
her	O
Trunk	O
of	O
Clothes	O
might	O
remain	O
there	O
for	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
:	O
It	O
further	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
same	O
Lodging	O
and	O
went	O
privately	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
afterwards	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Catherine	B-pers
Tanner	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Crowd	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
six	O
pound	O
Weight	O
of	O
Hair	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Greason	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
going	O
along	O
Church-Lane	O
in	O
Whitechappel	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
others	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
under	O
standing	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
that	O
dealt	O
in	O
Hair	O
,	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
would	O
sell	O
theirs	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
all	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
looking	O
upon	O
the	O
Hair	O
of	O
other	O
Women	O
in	O
Company	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
afterwards	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
Place	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
carry	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
little	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Ann	I-pers
Hazeman	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Constable	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
a	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
Value	O
6	O
l.	O
and	O
9	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Henry	B-pers
Constable	I-pers
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Facts	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cheese	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Shelton	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
18	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
Value	O
25	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Esther	B-pers
Dod	I-pers
,	O
and	O
three	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Silk	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
the	O
Elder	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Price	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
Value	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Southby	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Tankard	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
accordingly	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
there	O
long	O
,	O
before	O
he	O
sent	O
the	O
Maid	O
of	O
an	O
Errand	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Tankard	O
;	O
being	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
,	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
in	O
Hounsditch	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Day	I-pers
a	O
silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
Value	O
2	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
Poultrey	B-place
one	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
take	O
out	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
Bosom	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Decosta	I-pers
of	O
two	O
Guineas	O
,	O
a	O
Spanish	O
piece	O
of	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
Bell	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Joanna	B-pers
Chiswell	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
7	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mycock	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
Drinking	O
box	O
together	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
laid	O
down	O
,	O
which	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
up	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
privately	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
Value	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
proving	O
nothing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Hesson	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
,	O
1st	O
.	O
For	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Branch	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
nine	O
Ducks	O
and	O
seven	O
Pullets	O
.	O
The	O
2d	O
.	O
For	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
50	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
:	O
For	O
the	O
first	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
the	O
Window	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Poultry	O
were	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
gone	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
upon	O
Search	O
,	O
found	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
Apprehended	O
,	O
but	O
made	O
his	O
Escape	O
from	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
agen	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
stole	O
the	O
50	O
l.	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
second	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
Search	O
being	O
made	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
best	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
by	O
some	O
remarkable	O
Pieces	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
little	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
to	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Drew	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
16	O
Razors	O
,	O
Value	O
40	O
s.	O
4	O
Perukes	O
12	O
l.	O
with	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Humphreys	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
out	O
upon	O
Business	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
afterwards	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
C	B-pers
-	I-pers
J	I-pers
-	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Jacob	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
60	O
Yards	O
of	O
Durant	O
Stuff	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Shippard	I-pers
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
any	O
thing	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Edmund	B-pers
Dudley	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
's	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
by	O
shooting	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Musket	O
in	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
which	O
occasion	O
'd	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
Dyed	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
a	O
Hackney-Coach	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
standing	O
with	O
his	O
Coach	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
,	O
was	O
order	O
'd	O
by	O
an	O
Officer	O
of	O
the	O
Train	O
'd	O
Bands	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
Marching	O
with	O
his	O
Company	O
)	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
driving	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
the	O
said	O
said	O
Officer	O
directed	O
,	O
whip	O
'd	O
his	O
Horses	O
,	O
drove	O
violently	O
and	O
broke	O
the	O
Ranks	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Soldiers	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
stop	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
continuing	O
his	O
Violence	O
one	O
of	O
'em	O
flash	O
'd	O
the	O
Pan	O
of	O
his	O
Musket	O
at	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
likewise	O
level	O
'd	O
his	O
Piece	O
,	O
and	O
discharg	O
'd	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
fell	O
back	O
and	O
Dyed	O
:	O
It	O
further	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Musket	O
was	O
charg	O
'd	O
with	O
nothing	O
but	O
Powder	O
and	O
Paper	O
,	O
but	O
lighting	O
upon	O
his	O
Left	O
Eye	O
,	O
shot	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
enter	O
'd	O
into	O
his	O
Brain	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Soames	I-pers
of	O
Alhallows	B-place
the	I-place
Wall	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Riding-hood	O
and	O
a	O
Flasket	O
of	O
wet	O
Linen	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Tisdall	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
knew	O
not	O
who	O
was	O
the	O
Thief	O
;	O
that	O
about	O
six	O
Weeks	O
after	O
the	O
Robery	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
Riding-hood	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
who	O
giving	O
no	O
Proof	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Dionicious	B-pers
Carthy	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Carty	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
in	O
personating	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
Marriner	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
Her	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Ship	O
Drake	O
,	O
and	O
defrauding	O
him	O
of	O
12	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
due	O
as	O
Bounty-Money	O
for	O
taking	O
the	O
Royal	O
Colant	O
.	O
Which	O
being	O
clearly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Weigh	I-pers
,	O
Allen	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
were	O
all	O
Indicted	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bath-mettle	O
Seal	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Buckles	O
;	O
which	O
Facts	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Simms	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Stears	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
his	O
Stears	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Grounds	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
driven	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
Rosemary-lane	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
stop	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
own	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
nothing	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
11.	O
Robert	B-pers
Hope	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Walton	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Corbet	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Sparkes	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Gladman	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Simms	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
to	O
hard	O
Labour	O
,	O
22.	O
Catherine	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Cauldry	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
,	O
Barbara	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
,	O
Martha	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Herbert	O
,	O
George	B-pers
Sandwell	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Drew	I-pers
,	O
Edmund	O
Dudley	O
,	O
Will	O
.	O
Isaacson	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Wagstaff	I-pers
,	O
Frances	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
Catharine	O
Tannar	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
Hannah	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
,	O
Joanna	O
Chiswell	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
,	O
23	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Hall	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Tomson	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
,	O
Elinor	B-pers
Ray	I-pers
,	O
Alice	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Wildman	I-pers
,	O
Hannah	B-pers
Beck	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Major	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Fudg	I-pers
,	O
Gerrard	O
Dennit	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Cartwright	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Tiggel	I-pers
,	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Weigh	I-pers
,	O
Allen	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Armstrong	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cheese	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Twelves	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Soames	I-pers
.	O
Dionicious	O
Carthy	O
alias	O
Carty	O
,	O
Fined	O
for	O
his	O
Offence	O
10	O
Nobles	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
ALL	O
Melancholly	O
,	O
Hysterical	O
and	O
Hypocondriacal	O
Distempers	O
which	O
variously	O
affect	O
the	O
Mind	O
with	O
strange	O
Fears	O
and	O
dismal	O
Apprehensions	O
;	O
Faintings	O
,	O
and	O
Sinkings	O
of	O
the	O
Spirits	O
,	O
great	O
Hurries	O
,	O
Restlessness	O
and	O
Disquietment	O
(	O
little	O
understood	O
,	O
and	O
seldom	O
cured	O
by	O
any	O
common	O
Means	O
)	O
also	O
Pains	O
and	O
Giddiness	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
Risings	O
to	O
the	O
Throat	O
.	O
Sick	O
Fits	O
,	O
Tremblings	O
,	O
Oppressions	O
of	O
the	O
Heart	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
other	O
Disorders	O
caus	O
'd	O
by	O
Vapours	O
,	O
are	O
succesfully	O
cured	O
(	O
with	O
God	O
's	O
Blessing	O
)	O
by	O
a	O
Physician	O
well	O
Experienc	O
'd	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
more	O
than	O
20	O
years	O
Practice	O
in	O
those	O
deplorable	O
Cases	O
;	O
who	O
also	O
cures	O
all	O
kind	O
of	O
Fits	O
,	O
the	O
strange	O
and	O
violent	O
,	O
if	O
curable	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
informs	O
on	O
sight	O
of	O
their	O
Water	O
.	O
Now	O
living	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
the	O
Shears	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Chambers	O
street	O
in	O
Goodman	O
's	O
Fields	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Minories	O
;	O
where	O
those	O
that	O
have	O
Occasion	O
,	O
and	O
Lives	O
remote	O
,	O
may	O
direct	O
their	O
Letters	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
shall	O
be	O
speedily	O
Answer	O
'd	O
or	O
attended	O
on	O
if	O
desir	O
'd	O
.	O
THat	O
Excellent	O
Remedy	O
for	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
Children	O
in	O
the	O
painful	O
breeding	O
or	O
cutting	O
of	O
their	O
Teeth	O
,	O
is	O
still	O
prepar	O
'd	O
by	O
me	O
D.	O
Perronet	O
,	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
in	O
Dvot-street	O
,	O
near	O
Bloomsbury	O
;	O
whereby	O
multitudes	O
of	O
Infants	O
labouring	O
under	O
the	O
greatest	O
Agony	O
of	O
Pain	O
,	O
Fevers	O
,	O
Convulsions	O
,	O
and	O
tho	O
'	O
Numbers	O
of	O
'em	O
expos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
utmost	O
peril	O
of	O
Life	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
Cause	O
;	O
yet	O
thro	O
God	O
's	O
Goodness	O
have	O
instantly	O
been	O
relieved	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
restored	O
to	O
perfect	O
Ease	O
and	O
Safety	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Application	O
of	O
this	O
admirable	O
Medicine	O
,	O
which	O
for	O
its	O
Pleasantness	O
of	O
Use	O
,	O
and	O
constant	O
Success	O
,	O
far	O
exceeds	O
all	O
other	O
Means	O
whatsoever	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
in	O
these	O
deplorable	O
Cases	O
:	O
The	O
Truth	O
where	O
of	O
will	O
evidently	O
appear	O
by	O
the	O
many	O
Certificates	O
given	O
under	O
the	O
Hands	O
of	O
sundry	O
Reputable	O
Persons	O
,	O
of	O
whom	O
the	O
Scrupulous	O
are	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
further	O
Inquiry	O
for	O
their	O
better	O
Satisfaction	O
.	O
The	O
said	O
Certificates	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
Gratis	O
where	O
this	O
Remedy	O
is	O
Sold	O
,	O
at	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
per	O
Viol	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
in	O
Dyot-street	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Alcraft	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bleu-coat-boy	O
against	O
the	O
Rayal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
Cornhill	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Lillie	O
,	O
Persumer	O
,	O
next	O
Beauford	O
Buildings	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Watkins	O
,	O
Tobacconist	O
,	O
in	O
King-street	O
,	O
Westminster	O
.	O
