TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
Queen	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
Held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
,	O
On	O
Thursday	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
13th	O
and	O
14th	O
Days	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
1714	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Thirteenth	O
Tear	O
of	O
Her	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
BEfore	O
the	O
Rt	O
.	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
STANIER	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
Richardson	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
Her	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Tale	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Dobson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Trigg	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Bonwick	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barwell	I-pers
,	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Tooke	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Burlace	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Hurst	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Pannet	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Ilford	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Newland	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Robertson	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Sanders	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hinton	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Burchet	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Odell	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Roderick	B-pers
Awdry	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Lothbury	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
11	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
2	O
Salvers	O
,	O
2	O
Salts	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Plate	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
having	O
been	O
abroad	O
,	O
at	O
his	O
return	O
he	O
saw	O
White	O
standing	O
at	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
in	O
,	O
found	O
Awdry	O
sitting	O
in	O
the	O
Parlour	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
his	O
Lady	O
sent	O
him	O
thither	O
on	O
an	O
Errand	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Servant	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
Assistance	O
secur	O
'd	O
White	O
also	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
a	O
Salver	O
taken	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Plate	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
Awdry	O
.	O
The	O
Matter	O
was	O
very	O
plain	O
;	O
and	O
tho	O
'	O
Awdry	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
excuse	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
by	O
saving	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Salver	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
a	O
Place	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
upon	O
the	O
new	O
Satute	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Amram	B-pers
Fordham	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
7	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
were	O
two	O
Watchmen	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
hearing	O
a	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
put	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Bag	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Padlock	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
broke	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Stock-lock	O
pick	O
'd	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Stranger	O
come	O
from	O
Bristol	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Shop	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
lye	O
there	O
,	O
having	O
no	O
Lodging	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Burglary	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Pantile	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bartholomew	I-place
the	I-place
Less	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Gown	O
and	O
Pettycoat	O
,	O
a	O
Hood	O
and	O
Headcloaths	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
been	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
miss	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
being	O
taken	O
up	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
own	O
'd	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
dispos	O
'd	O
of	O
the	O
Gown	O
and	O
Pettycoat	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
Cap	O
and	O
Handkerchief	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
gave	O
'em	O
her	O
to	O
pawn	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
not	O
being	O
believ	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Still	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Esther	B-pers
Partridge	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Camblet	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lownes	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
set	O
forth	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
standing	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
together	O
,	O
he	O
thought	O
them	O
suspicious	O
Persons	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
observing	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
say	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
three	O
go	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
two	O
will	O
stay	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
.	O
This	O
increasing	O
his	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
he	O
watch	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
three	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
hanker	O
about	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Shop	O
over-against	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
what	O
he	O
suspected	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
a	O
while	O
seeing	O
the	O
three	O
come	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
another	O
seiz	O
'd	O
them	O
all	O
five	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
made	O
her	O
Escape	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
plain	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
Confederates	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
his	O
Goods	O
again	O
,	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
of	O
Petty	O
Larceny	O
only	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Savin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Duke	I-place
's	I-place
Place	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Maurice	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
Instant	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
11	O
Pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Breeches	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
his	O
Shop	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
seeing	O
a	O
Man	O
with	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Breeches	O
on	O
,	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
look	O
on	O
'em	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
'em	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
own	O
;	O
by	O
which	O
Means	O
he	O
discover	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
another	O
Pair	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
4	O
Pair	O
more	O
.	O
In	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
he	O
pretended	O
he	O
bought	O
'em	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
turn	O
'd	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
Person	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
sold	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
false	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Rachel	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
the	O
Holy	B-place
Trinity	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Gold	O
Ear-rings	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
being	O
a	O
Milkwoman	O
,	O
had	O
some	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Proctor	O
in	O
the	O
Poultry	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
being	O
out	O
of	O
Place	O
,	O
she	O
prevail	O
'd	O
to	O
stay	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
till	O
she	O
could	O
get	O
in	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
April	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
pretended	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
Place	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
was	O
seen	O
about	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
next	O
Day	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
miss	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
being	O
taken	O
up	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
Street	O
Door	O
away	O
before	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
also	O
found	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
'em	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Ear-rings	O
with	O
a	O
Cunning-Woman	O
in	O
Ratcliff	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
them	O
to	O
tell	O
her	O
some	O
News	O
of	O
her	O
Sweetheart	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
Joyce	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
very	O
plain	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Burglary	O
.	O
Katherine	B-pers
Kirk	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Alhallows	B-place
Lombard-Street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Can	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Dry	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Mrs.	O
Dry	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
came	O
from	O
one	O
Madam	O
Hill	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
help	O
her	O
to	O
a	O
good	O
Place	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Can	O
and	O
Spoon	O
were	O
brought	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
She	O
deny	O
'd	O
herself	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
mistake	O
,	O
another	O
being	O
accus	O
'd	O
before	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
of	O
Truth	O
in	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
whereupon	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Lace	O
,	O
a	O
Holland	O
Frock	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
.	O
It	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
manner	O
to	O
a	O
Servant	O
there	O
,	O
pretending	O
one	O
Madam	O
Johnson	O
sent	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
help	O
her	O
to	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Place	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Servant	O
going	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
miss	O
'd	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
This	O
being	O
very	O
plain	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
also	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Twelves	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloath	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Oakley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Riding-hood	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Stamper	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Stamper	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
that	O
were	O
mended	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
going	O
back	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
to	O
put	O
them	O
on	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
positive	O
were	O
there	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
nothing	O
material	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
John	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bridget	I-place
,	I-place
alias	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Bateman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
Ludgate-Hill	B-place
,	O
with	O
the	O
Shirt	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
justled	O
him	O
a	O
pretty	O
while	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
got	O
clear	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
Pursuit	O
,	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Apron	O
.	O
He	O
pretended	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
believ	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Weston	I-pers
,	O
(	O
two	O
little	O
Boy	O
s	O
)	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dionis	I-place
Backchurch	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Priscilla	B-pers
Birch	I-pers
,	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
standing	O
ata	O
Poulterer	O
's	O
Stall	O
in	O
Leadenhall-Market	B-place
to	O
pay	O
for	O
Butter	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Pork	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
miss	O
'd	O
her	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
being	O
taken	O
upon	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
one	O
of	O
'em	O
;	O
whereupon	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Wilmot	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Hurdesly	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
an	O
Earthen	O
Mug	O
,	O
tip	O
'd	O
with	O
Silver	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Paper	O
Book	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
That	O
being	O
in	O
his	O
Counting-House	O
about	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
suspected	O
some-body	O
was	O
under	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
where-upon	O
he	O
remov	O
'd	O
some	O
Money	O
he	O
had	O
there	O
,	O
into	O
another	O
Place	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
making	O
some	O
Search	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Sash	O
thrown	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Mug	O
and	O
Book	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
A	O
Gold-smith	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
coming	O
to	O
sell	O
him	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tip	O
,	O
he	O
suspected	O
and	O
stopt	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
it	O
was	O
given	O
him	O
by	O
one	O
Richardson	O
;	O
but	O
had	O
no	O
Proof	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Mary	B-pers
Skinner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
,	O
2	O
Shifts	O
,	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
2	O
Pettycoats	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Hanna	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
Instant	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
sworn	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
employed	O
in	O
winding	O
Silk	O
;	O
and	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
miss	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
taken	O
about	O
10	O
Days	O
after	O
,	O
with	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
pretended	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lent	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Aid	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Perjury	O
in	O
swearing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Behalf	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lynn	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
indicted	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
up	O
a	O
Purse	O
(	O
which	O
it	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
he	O
pick	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Dorcas	O
Roberts	O
;	O
)	O
and	O
also	O
that	O
she	O
liv	O
'd	O
at	O
one	O
Wood	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
Carpenter	O
in	O
Houndsditch	O
,	O
whereas	O
no	O
such	O
Person	O
was	O
found	O
to	O
live	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
Indictment	O
being	O
faulty	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Proby	B-pers
Phesaunt	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
secretly	O
stealing	O
47	O
Yards	O
of	O
Mantua	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
l.	O
7	O
s.	O
17	O
Ells	O
of	O
Lustring	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
Yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Sarsnet	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bellamy	I-pers
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Frances	B-pers
Larkin	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Larkin	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
being	O
entrusted	O
by	O
her	O
Master	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
going	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
shewing	O
'em	O
to	O
a	O
Lady	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
into	O
Dunning	B-place
's	I-place
Alley	I-place
in	I-place
Bishopsgate-street	I-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
getting	O
Help	O
,	O
took	O
her	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
bargain	O
'd	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Bellamy	O
for	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
Bill	O
of	O
Parcels	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Maid	O
was	O
appointed	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
Mugwell	O
Street	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
sold	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Maid	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
afterwards	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
too	O
late	O
to	O
shew	O
'em	O
to	O
a	O
Lady	O
she	O
had	O
design	O
'd	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
near	O
her	O
own	O
Lodging	O
,	O
she	O
bid	O
the	O
Maid	O
give	O
them	O
her	O
to	O
carry	O
home	O
.	O
The	O
Person	O
to	O
whom	O
she	O
sold	O
that	O
Part	O
in	O
Mugwell	O
street	O
,	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Bill	O
of	O
Parcels	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
was	O
written	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Bellamy	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
,	O
directed	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
S	B-pers
-	I-pers
R	I-pers
-	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Masterman	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
with	O
Intention	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Henry	B-pers
Masterman	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
being	O
waiting	O
on	O
his	O
Master	O
at	O
Supper	O
at	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
Noise	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Sash	O
at	O
the	O
Stair-head	O
thrown	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
the	O
Stairs	O
;	O
who	O
going	O
to	O
throw	O
himself	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
over	O
a	O
Wall	O
,	O
the	O
Servant	O
catch	O
'd	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
fell	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
To	O
defend	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
thro	O
'	O
a	O
Court	O
joyning	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
a	O
drunken	O
Man	O
,	O
who	O
threw	O
his	O
Hat	O
upon	O
the	O
Ledge	O
over	O
the	O
Window	O
at	O
the	O
Stairs-head	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Window	O
to	O
fetch	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
very	O
positive	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Burglary	O
.	O
R	B-pers
-	I-pers
A	I-pers
-	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
2	O
Holland	O
Smocks	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Linnen	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Gooding	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
one	O
Bray	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
.	O
Upon	O
her	O
Trial	O
she	O
said	O
Bray	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
persuaded	O
her	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
upon	O
her	O
self	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
being	O
a	O
frivolous	O
Excuse	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cotes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
126	O
Yards	O
of	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Roger	B-pers
Hasketh	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
meeting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
she	O
pretended	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
a	O
Ferret-Weaver	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
be	O
search	O
'd	O
threw	O
the	O
Ribbon	O
on	O
theFloor	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
Pick-lock	O
keys	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Harper	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
upon	O
4	O
Indictments	O
,	O
for	O
robbing	O
upon	O
the	O
Highway	O
;	O
viz	O
.	O
the	O
two	O
first	O
for	O
robbing	O
Michael	B-pers
Biddulph	I-pers
of	O
8	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
Francis	B-pers
Woodhouse	I-pers
of	O
14	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
in	O
the	O
Cirencester	O
Stage-Coach	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
about	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Woodhouse	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
the	O
Coach	O
was	O
just	O
driving	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Wise	O
's	O
Gates	O
on	O
this	O
Side	O
Kensington	B-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
rode	O
up	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
his	O
pistol	O
in	O
,	O
demanded	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
some	O
Silver	O
given	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Passengers	O
,	O
demanded	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
looking	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Coach-Window	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
stop	O
the	O
Glocester-Coach	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
two	O
for	O
robbing	O
William	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
of	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
George	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Glocester	O
Coach	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Lloyd	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
Pistol	O
into	O
the	O
Coach	O
as	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
Silver	O
given	O
him	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
must	O
have	O
Gold	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
thrust	O
his	O
Hand	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
two	O
half	O
Guineas	O
.	O
And	O
Mr.	O
Cook	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
while	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
rifling	O
Mr.	O
Lloyd	O
,	O
he	O
snapt	O
a	O
Pistol	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
miss	O
'd	O
Fire	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
rifled	O
him	O
also	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
Watch	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
rode	O
off	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
he	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
pursu	O
'd	O
him	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
rais	O
'd	O
a	O
Cry	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
follow	O
'd	O
thro	O
'	O
Knights-bridge	O
,	O
up	O
Tyburn-line	O
,	O
and	O
quite	O
to	O
the	O
Soil-pond	O
in	O
Mary	O
bone	O
Fields	O
,	O
where	O
his	O
Horse	O
being	O
mir	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
oblig	O
'd	O
to	O
quit	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
at	O
length	O
taken	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
dropt	O
Mr.	O
Cook	O
's	O
Watch	O
in	O
the	O
Road	O
by	O
Knightsbridge	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
He	O
pretended	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Portsmouth	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
from	O
Godlyman	O
that	O
Morning	O
;	O
and	O
riding	O
very	O
peaceably	O
along	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
Cry	O
of	O
Highway-men	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
upon	O
a	O
Grey	O
Horse	O
ride	O
by	O
him	O
(	O
that	O
being	O
the	O
Colour	O
of	O
the	O
Horse	O
be	O
rode	O
himself	O
;	O
)	O
and	O
the	O
Outcry	O
coming	O
forward	O
,	O
he	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
for	O
Fear	O
he	O
should	O
fare	O
the	O
worse	O
for	O
having	O
been	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
.	O
The	O
Proof	O
being	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Defence	O
frivolous	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Walter	B-pers
Cantwell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bible	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Tennis-Balls	O
,	O
Glass-Necklaces	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Bearing	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
Evidence	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
a	O
Stall	O
in	O
Holbourn	B-place
,	O
and	O
a	O
Person	O
coming	O
by	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
saw	O
it	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
watching	O
him	O
,	O
saw	O
him	O
come	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
drop	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
rest	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Picklock-Keys	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
nothing	O
material	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
William	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
and	O
Humphry	B-pers
Clements	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripple-gate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
,	O
two	O
Shifts	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Linnen	O
(	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
several	O
Persons	O
)	O
from	O
Mary	B-pers
Draper	I-pers
a	O
Washerwoman	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Griffin	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
Clements	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
John	B-pers
Greycroft	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Greycroft	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Tortoise-shell	O
Snuff	O
Box	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Gold	O
Hinge	O
and	O
Rim	O
,	O
and	O
17	O
Diamonds	O
on	O
the	O
Lid	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
two	O
Silvers	O
Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
Salt	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Adrian	B-pers
Metcalf	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
sworn	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Woman	O
liv	O
'd	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
Year	O
as	O
a	O
Cook-maid	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Hether	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Metcalf	O
finding	O
his	O
Drawer	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Snuff-Box	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
gone	O
,	O
made	O
Enquiry	O
among	O
his	O
Family	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
inform	O
'd	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
lie	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
a	O
strict	O
Search	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
that	O
he	O
carried	O
the	O
Snuff-Box	O
to	O
a	O
Friend	O
to	O
sell	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
left	O
him	O
by	O
an	O
Uncle	O
at	O
Nottingham	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutors	O
Stockins	O
,	O
Shirts	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
were	O
also	O
found	O
at	O
his	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Proof	O
was	O
very	O
full	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Woman	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
his	O
Wife	O
.	O
She	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
but	O
deny	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
ever	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Guy	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Acton	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
Chich	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
being	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
would	O
not	O
swear	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Confession	O
was	O
sufficient	O
for	O
the	O
Jury	O
to	O
find	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
James	B-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Precinct	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Katherine	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
a	O
Drawer	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
12	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
privately	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Katherine	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
A	O
Witness	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
without	O
his	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
reach	O
over	O
the	O
Counter	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
got	O
him	O
pursu	O
'd	O
and	O
taken	O
.	O
He	O
dropt	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
Drawer	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
his	O
Shoes	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cotterel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Wound	O
with	O
an	O
Iron	O
Poker	O
on	O
the	O
third	O
Finger	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Hand	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
January	O
[	O
Pages	O
missing	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
