TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
Held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
9th	O
,	O
10th	O
and	O
11th	O
Days	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
1714	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
First	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEfore	O
the	O
Rt	O
.	O
Hon	O
Sir	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
STANIER	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Littleton	B-pers
Powis	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Dormer	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Pennystone	O
,	O
Sir	O
Peter	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
Nathanael	B-pers
Chavet	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Blagrave	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Horn	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Norris	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Davies	I-pers
,	O
Matthias	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Meylin	I-pers
,	O
Nathanael	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
Andrew	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Chadwell	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Munden	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Greenhill	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Street	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	O
Nathanael	B-pers
Ravener	I-pers
,	O
Simon	B-pers
Ravener	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Butteridge	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Dix	I-pers
,	O
Marmaduke	B-pers
Branley	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Obadiah	B-pers
Leman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mildred	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Poultry	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
l.	O
(	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Bridgman	I-pers
)	O
privately	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Hodgkins	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
Hodgkins	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
from	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
House	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
Wig	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bridgman	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
met	O
and	O
thrust	O
him	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
lost	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Box	O
;	O
and	O
another	O
Witness	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
Wig	O
out	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
Box	O
being	O
open	O
'd	O
by	O
squeezing	O
)	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
Bosom	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
when	O
Hodgkins	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
of	O
stealing	O
3	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
;	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Graves	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2nd	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
sworn	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
run	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
Bell-Court	B-place
in	I-place
Mincing-Lane	I-place
;	O
and	O
being	O
pursu	O
'd	O
,	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Spoons	O
found	O
dropt	O
in	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
She	O
pretended	O
it	O
was	O
another	O
Woman	O
ran	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
beat	O
her	O
down	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
not	O
being	O
believ	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hoskins	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bow	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
,	O
3	O
pair	O
of	O
Thread	O
Stockins	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Pooley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
Value	O
28	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Holiday	I-pers
.	O
It	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
going	O
to	O
visit	O
Holiday	O
's	O
Wife	O
sent	O
her	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Drink	O
;	O
and	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
stole	O
the	O
Ring	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Window	O
where	O
it	O
lay	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anthony	B-pers
Elson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
Value	O
3	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
swore	O
That	O
going	O
through	O
Bishopsgate	B-place
,	O
he	O
felt	O
something	O
press	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
putting	O
his	O
Hand	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Denford	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
Woodstreet	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Silver	O
Forks	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Spoon	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Eggleston	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Snuff	O
Box	O
from	O
Margaret	B-pers
Hewetson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Chearwoman	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
which	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
when	O
taken	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
Fork	O
for	O
7	O
s.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Stephen	B-pers
Nott	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Geese	O
,	O
Value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Simon	B-pers
Sylvester	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Witness	O
was	O
one	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
he	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
lifted	O
up	O
a	O
Board	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Stall	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Geese	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
shar	O
'd	O
amongst	O
'em	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Gregory	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
Value	O
20	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Barret	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
very	O
full	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
Value	O
10	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Dudley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Box	O
taken	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Daniel	B-pers
Ryder	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Christophers	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
Value	O
3	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Gardener	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
walking	O
on	O
the	B-place
Exchange	I-place
,	O
he	O
felt	O
a	O
Hand	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
and	O
turning	O
quick	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
have	O
his	O
Handkerchief.The	O
Fact	O
being	O
so	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
Boy	O
)	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
26	O
Yards	O
of	O
Norwich	O
Crape	O
,	O
Value	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Witness	O
swore	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
across	O
the	O
Shop	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Katherine	B-pers
Priest	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bow	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
19	O
s	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
going	O
along	O
Cheapside	B-place
about	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
,	O
who	O
catch	O
'd	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
pretended	O
to	O
kiss	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
very	O
familiar	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
he	O
found	O
his	O
Pocket	O
cut	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Money	O
gone	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
seize	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
assaulted	O
by	O
two	O
Men	O
,	O
and	O
prevented	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
,	O
understanding	O
who	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
frequently	O
walk	O
'd	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
he	O
afterwards	O
took	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
She	O
us	O
'd	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Words	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
to	O
the	O
Purpose	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Homby	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Christ-Church	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Basket	O
,	O
and	O
100	O
Eggs	O
,	O
Value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Byway	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Witness	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
Oxford-Arms	B-place
Yard	I-place
in	I-place
Newgate-street	I-place
,	O
and	O
take	O
away	O
the	O
Eggs	O
,	O
and	O
follow	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
no	O
Proof	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samuel	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
Value	O
2	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Rodriguez	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
going	O
down	O
Cornhill	B-place
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
throw	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Penelope	B-pers
Darket	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Christ-Church	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
Two	O
Guineas	O
and	O
27	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Humphry	B-pers
Witby	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
going	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
into	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
(	O
no	O
Person	O
being	O
in	O
his	O
Company	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
and	O
that	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
some	O
Stir	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
50	O
s.	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
keeping	O
a	O
publick	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
drink	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
seeing	O
he	O
had	O
too	O
much	O
before	O
,	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
any	O
;	O
whereupon	O
Words	O
arose	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
swore	O
she	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
:	O
But	O
being	O
perswaded	O
to	O
pull	O
off	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
the	O
Mony	O
dropp	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
She	O
also	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
compound	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
People	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Diaper	O
Table	O
Cloth	O
,	O
a	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Napkins	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Scot	O
at	O
the	O
Dolphin	B-place
Tavern	I-place
in	I-place
Tower	I-place
Street	I-place
;	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
lost	O
several	O
Things	O
,	O
at	O
length	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
began	O
to	O
be	O
suspected	O
;	O
whereupon	O
a	O
Box	O
of	O
hers	O
,	O
which	O
stood	O
at	O
another	O
House	O
,	O
being	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
there	O
found	O
:	O
She	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
when	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
wou	O
'd	O
have	O
denied	O
it	O
at	O
her	O
Trial	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
O	B-pers
-	I-pers
H	I-pers
-	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
Wastcoat	O
and	O
Breeches	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
38	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Mitchell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Mitchell	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
late	O
dreadful	O
Fire	O
in	O
Houndsditch	B-place
being	O
very	O
near	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
remov	O
'd	O
his	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Hurry	O
,	O
amongst	O
those	O
who	O
came	O
to	O
assist	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
;	O
who	O
having	O
got	O
a	O
Bundle	O
,	O
went	O
into	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
in	O
Narrow-Alley	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
follow	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
Friend	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
seeing	O
where	O
he	O
plac	O
'd	O
what	O
he	O
carried	O
;	O
put	O
hers	O
there	O
too	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
more	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Hurry	O
was	O
over	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Mitchell	O
was	O
inform	O
'd	O
by	O
her	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
carried	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
,	O
found	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
Intelligence	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
upon	O
his	O
Back	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
work	O
all	O
Night	O
is	O
assisting	O
at	O
the	O
Engine	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
left	O
his	O
own	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
wet	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
put	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
on	O
,	O
but	O
intended	O
to	O
carry	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
But	O
that	O
being	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
as	O
a	O
forg	O
'd	O
Story	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
and	I-place
Agnes	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Ward	I-place
of	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
Value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Broad-piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
12	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Low	I-pers
)	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Wey	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
Low	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
till	O
't	O
was	O
late	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
prevail	O
'd	O
to	O
lye	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
That	O
when	O
he	O
(	O
the	O
Witness	O
)	O
rose	O
,	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
search	O
found	O
'em	O
under	O
a	O
Bench	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
Watch	O
and	O
Money	O
gone	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
search	O
'd	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
some	O
Days	O
taken	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
according	O
to	O
his	O
Direction	O
.	O
He	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
at	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
alledging	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
ill	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
wanted	O
to	O
get	O
Money	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thought	O
fit	O
to	O
bring	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Mug	O
,	O
Value	O
3	O
l.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Walford	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
Pint	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
Drunk	O
,	O
wou	O
'd	O
have	O
a	O
Silver	O
Mug	O
to	O
drink	O
out	O
of	O
,	O
some	O
other	O
Customers	O
being	O
drinking	O
out	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
one	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
a	O
while	O
(	O
the	O
other	O
Company	O
being	O
gone	O
)	O
he	O
found	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
carry	O
off	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Mugs	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
believ	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
cou	O
'd	O
not	O
swear	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
sworn	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
Restitution	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
being	O
satisfy	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
3d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Can	O
,	O
Value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
day	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
12th	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
Queen	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
sworn	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
once	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
some	O
Sausages	O
dress	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
coming	O
again	O
a	O
while	O
after	O
,	O
had	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Drink	O
in	O
a	O
Silver	O
Can	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
watch	O
'd	O
his	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Comins	I-pers
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Noble	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Vedast	I-place
,	I-place
alias	I-place
Foster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
179	O
Yards	O
of	O
Silk	O
Ferret	O
,	O
Value	O
24	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
Comins	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
amusing	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
Noble	O
convey	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Ferret	O
into	O
her	O
Lap	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
others	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
let	O
them	O
go	O
a	O
little	O
away	O
,	O
Comins	O
was	O
coming	O
back	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
Bundle	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
both	O
stopt	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
dropt	O
by	O
Noble	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Bundle	O
being	O
open	O
'd	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
to	O
contain	O
12	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockins	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
some	O
who	O
gave	O
them	O
a	O
pretty	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
but	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
12	O
pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockins	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
12	O
pair	O
of	O
Stocking	O
being	O
stopt	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Fletcher	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
enquiry	O
was	O
made	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Dawson	O
own	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
sworn	O
in	O
Court	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
give	O
a	O
good	O
Account	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
by	O
'em	O
,	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Alhallows	B-place
Barkin	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
Wrist	O
of	O
his	O
Left-hand	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languish	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stepping	O
on	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Hoy	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
go	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Hatches	O
broke	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
high	O
Words	O
happen	O
'd	O
betwixt	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stepping	O
on	O
Shoar	O
again	O
,	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Shove	O
,	O
who	O
return	O
'd	O
it	O
by	O
a	O
Blow	O
on	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Nose	O
bleed	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
Blow	O
at	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Witness	O
stept	O
in	O
and	O
wrench	O
'd	O
the	O
Sword	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
receiv	O
'd	O
any	O
Wound	O
:	O
That	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
so	O
taken	O
away	O
the	O
Sword	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
it	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
all	O
was	O
over	O
.	O
Another	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
coming	O
over	O
Tower	O
Wharf	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
(	O
with	O
whom	O
he	O
was	O
well	O
acquainted	O
)	O
between	O
whom	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
understood	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
perswaded	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
Friends	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Wine	O
together	O
;	O
and	O
all	O
seem'dto	O
be	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
not	O
knowing	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
hurt	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
did	O
go	O
and	O
drink	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
Company	O
seeing	O
some	O
Blood	O
about	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Hand	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
wounded	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
't	O
was	O
some	O
of	O
Thompson	O
's	O
Blood	O
which	O
issu	O
'd	O
from	O
his	O
Nose	O
,	O
however	O
,	O
upon	O
looking	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
small	O
kind	O
of	O
a	O
Hurt	O
a	O
little	O
above	O
the	O
left	O
Wrist-bone	O
,	O
but	O
made	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
Witness	O
(	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
)	O
and	O
he	O
found	O
his	O
Arm	O
swell	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
out	O
of	O
order	O
,	O
and	O
applied	O
proper	O
Remedies	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
Day	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
dy	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
otherwise	O
an	O
infirm	O
Man	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
deny	O
'd	O
he	O
push	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
;	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
came	O
peaceably	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Button	O
,	O
asking	O
him	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
so	O
much	O
ill	O
Language	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
thereupon	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
violent	O
Blow	O
on	O
the	O
Face	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
Blood	O
gush	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Nose	O
,	O
which	O
did	O
provoke	O
him	O
to	O
draw	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
sensible	O
he	O
struck	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
also	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
first	O
assaulted	O
and	O
struck	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
knew	O
not	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
his	O
Hurt	O
in	O
the	O
Scuffle	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
Surgeons	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
it	O
upon	O
their	O
Oaths	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
believ	O
'd	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
ill	O
Habit	O
of	O
Body	O
,	O
and	O
frequently	O
ailing	O
before	O
.	O
Upon	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
Ludgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hair-Trunk	O
,	O
3	O
Wooden	O
Boxes	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Gorget	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hale	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
kind	O
of	O
a	O
brangling	O
Business	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Proof	O
of	O
Felony	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Revel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mark	B-pers
Lambert	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
several	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
swore	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Accomplice	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
Two	O
more	O
,	O
broke	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
carried	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
The	O
last	O
Witness	O
swore	O
against	O
him	O
for	O
spight	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
help	O
him	O
with	O
what	O
Subsistance	O
he	O
desired	O
in	O
the	O
Marshalsea	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
entirely	O
giving	O
credit	O
to	O
that	O
Witness	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Peter	I-place
's	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Seal	O
Value	O
2	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hillyard	I-pers
on	O
the	O
9th	O
Instant	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
sworn	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Seal	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Drawer	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Pearson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Alhallows	B-place
Barking	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Boat	O
,	O
2	O
Oars	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Cuts	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Boat	O
from	O
Somer's-Key	B-place
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
Hole	O
near	O
the	O
Bridge	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Oars	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Another	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
rowing	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Boat	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
spoke	O
to	O
each	O
other	O
.	O
The	O
Matter	O
was	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Dalton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cunningham	I-pers
,	O
but	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
foolish	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
speaking	O
scandalous	O
Words	O
relating	O
to	O
her	O
late	O
Majesty	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
God	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
the	O
Queen	O
,	O
she	O
may	O
kiss	O
my	O
A	O
-	O
se	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
raving	O
and	O
swearing	O
along	O
the	O
Street	O
late	O
at	O
Night	O
;	O
and	O
among	O
others	O
,	O
us	O
'd	O
the	O
Words	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
thought	O
it	O
his	O
Duty	O
to	O
secure	O
him	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
upon	O
his	O
Trial	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
somewhat	O
Lunatick	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
under	O
Cure	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Stable	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Steed	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
thence	O
a	O
Saddle	O
,	O
Value	O
10	O
s.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
work	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
some	O
Time	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
he	O
suspected	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
immediately	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Saddle	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
3	O
Shillings	O
.	O
He	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
at	O
his	O
Trial	O
,	O
but	O
deny	O
'd	O
breaking	O
the	O
Stable	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Clare	I-pers
and	O
T	B-pers
-	I-pers
E	I-pers
-	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Hampstead	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Feather-Bed	O
,	O
Value	O
40	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Baily	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
E	O
-	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
(	O
a	O
Window	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
opening	O
to	O
Hampstead	B-place
Heath	I-place
)	O
that	O
she	O
put	O
the	O
Bed	O
out	O
at	O
Noon	O
Day	O
,	O
where	O
Clare	O
was	O
ready	O
to	O
receive	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
afterwards	O
found	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
.	O
They	O
neither	O
of	O
them	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
but	O
each	O
wou	O
'd	O
have	O
clear	O
'd	O
her	O
self	O
by	O
accusing	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
,	O
considering	O
the	O
Master	O
,	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Seth	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
2	O
Guineas	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
Prisoner	O
quarrell	O
'd	O
about	O
their	O
Workmanship	O
(	O
being	O
Cooper	O
s	O
)	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
little	O
Scuffle	O
together	O
,	O
wherein	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
he	O
lost	O
2	O
Guineas	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
.	O
it	O
as	O
a	O
frivolous	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
accquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Neale	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Hull	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
in	O
counterfeiting	O
the	O
current	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
6	O
Pieces	O
of	O
counterfeit	O
Money	O
call	O
'd	O
Guineas	O
,	O
one	O
5	O
s.	O
Piece	O
,	O
5	O
Half-Crowns	O
,	O
and	O
10	O
Shil	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
the	O
2	O
Former	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
also	O
indicted	O
for	O
procuring	O
and	O
knowingly	O
having	O
in	O
their	O
Custody	O
Tools	O
or	O
Instruments	O
for	O
coining	O
,	O
contrary	O
to	O
a	O
Statute	O
in	O
that	O
Case	O
made	O
and	O
provided	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Neal	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Two	O
putting	O
themselves	O
upon	O
their	O
Trial	O
,	O
the	O
Fact	O
appear	O
'd	O
thus	O
:	O
Upon	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Rodam	O
(	O
a	O
Captain	O
in	O
the	O
Tower	O
Hamblets	O
)	O
receiving	O
Orders	O
to	O
make	O
Search	O
for	O
suspected	O
Persons	O
and	O
Arms	O
,	O
was	O
inform	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Beadle	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
Two	O
Men	O
who	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
come	O
by	O
the	O
Watch	O
late	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
Three-Colt-street	B-place
at	I-place
Limehouse	I-place
about	O
6	O
Months	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Captain	O
took	O
a	O
Constable	O
and	O
what	O
Force	O
he	O
thought	O
proper	O
;	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
upon	O
Search	O
found	O
the	O
counterfeit	O
Money	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
a	O
Fire	O
lighted	O
,	O
some	O
melted	O
Metal	O
,	O
4	O
Flasks	O
(	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
Warm	O
)	O
2	O
Edgers	O
,	O
a	O
Press	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
other	O
Instruments	O
for	O
Coining	O
;	O
all	O
Three	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
being	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
Barker	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
his	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
the	O
Tools	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
his	O
Wife	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
it	O
appear	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
;	O
and	O
had	O
she	O
known	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
being	O
in	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
were	O
of	O
Opinion	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
Guilty	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Tayler	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
White	B-place
Chapel	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
160	O
Diamonds	O
,	O
Value	O
40	O
l.	O
4	O
Diamond	O
Rings	O
,	O
Value	O
24	O
l.	O
some	O
other	O
small	O
Diamonds	O
and	O
Jewels	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
being	O
much	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
by	O
Stocks-Market	O
late	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
Tayler	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
Dram	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
perswaded	O
by	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
which	O
drove	O
to	O
her	O
Lodging	O
;	O
where	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
,	O
she	O
got	O
half	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
drank	O
it	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
put	O
him	O
to	O
Bed	O
;	O
and	O
about	O
Ten	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
he	O
wak	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
himself	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
all	O
his	O
Money	O
and	O
Moveables	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
made	O
what	O
Enquiry	O
he	O
could	O
of	O
the	O
Passages	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
over	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
Search	O
found	O
Tayler	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
nothing	O
material	O
to	O
alledge	O
against	O
Richardson	O
.	O
Tayler	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
meet	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
pick	O
'd	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
did	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
rob	O
him	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
upon	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
,	O
were	O
pleas	O
'd	O
to	O
acquit	O
them	O
both	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Mantle	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Alice	B-pers
and	I-pers
Susannah	I-pers
Kepburn	I-pers
,	I-pers
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
40	O
Yards	O
of	O
Calliminco	O
,	O
Value	O
40	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
Instant	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
sworn	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
break	O
a	O
Square	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
thrust	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
out	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
also	O
taken	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
being	O
satisfied	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
(	O
it	O
being	O
about	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
)	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Cane	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Trevor	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
a	O
great	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Linnen	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Stevens	O
swore	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
not	O
open11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
3	O
the	O
Cellar	O
Door	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
gone	O
.	O
Another	O
Witness	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
(	O
being	O
a	O
Baker	O
)	O
he	O
was	O
up	O
about	O
his	O
Work	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
a	O
Boy	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
suspecting	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
ill	O
People	O
,	O
he	O
follow	O
'd	O
them	O
at	O
some	O
Distance	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
got	O
some	O
Help	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
forward	O
in	O
the	O
Pursuit	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
Trevor	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
upon	O
his	O
Back	O
,	O
which	O
afterwards	O
he	O
gave	O
to	O
Cane	O
,	O
and	O
Cane	O
carrying	O
it	O
a	O
little	O
Way	O
,	O
threw	O
it	O
over	O
into	O
a	O
Garden	O
,	O
and	O
jump	O
'd	O
after	O
it	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Pursuers	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Garden	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
Bundle	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
the	O
Linnen	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Stevens	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
Trevor	O
for	O
that	O
Time	O
made	O
his	O
Escape	O
,	O
but	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
following	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
seeing	O
him	O
by	O
chance	O
,	O
dog	O
'd	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
convenient	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
Cane	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Bundle	O
to	O
carry	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
't	O
was	O
run	O
Muslin	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
very	O
plain	O
against	O
them	O
both	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Hans	I-pers
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Kensington	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Shirts	O
and	O
a	O
Shift	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Garden	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Walsh	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
Hans	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
Evans	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Hans	O
:	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joyce	B-pers
Hodgkis	I-pers
,	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Hodgkis	I-pers
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
on	O
the	O
Left	O
Thigh	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Groin	O
,	O
or	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
lodging	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
a	O
great	O
Noise	O
and	O
Scolding	O
between	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
at	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
saw	O
Blood	O
run	O
out	O
at	O
his	O
Breeches	O
.	O
Another	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
liv	O
'd	O
over	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
an	O
Out-Cry	O
,	O
ran	O
over	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
heard	O
the	O
Man	O
groaning	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Blood	O
run	O
violently	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
asking	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
how	O
it	O
came	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
cursed	O
Knife	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
(	O
shewing	O
her	O
an	O
old	O
Butcher	O
's	O
carving	O
Knife	O
)	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
stab	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
cursed	O
Wretch	O
had	O
been	O
the	O
Ruin	O
of	O
her	O
and	O
himself	O
too	O
.	O
When	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
asking	O
her	O
how	O
it	O
came	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
himself	O
.	O
In	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
had	O
Words	O
about	O
keeping	O
his	O
Mother	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Knife	O
threatning	O
to	O
stab	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
running	O
away	O
to	O
avoid	O
it	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
turn	O
'd	O
back	O
again	O
saw	O
him	O
bleed	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
himself	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Petit-Treason	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Dobbins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
upon	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
Stabbing	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Blount	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Pap	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Breadth	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
3	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
set	O
forth	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
other	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
King	B-place
's	I-place
Arms	I-place
Tavern	I-place
near	I-place
Hungerford-Market	I-place
,	O
till	O
between	O
3	O
and	O
4	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
talk	O
'd	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
of	O
his	O
Pedigree	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
advis	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
leave	O
off	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
he	O
need	O
not	O
talk	O
so	O
much	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
his	O
Mother	O
sold	O
Ale	O
in	O
Ireland	O
.	O
This	O
caus	O
'd	O
other	O
Words	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
(	O
the	O
Deceas'd	O
's	O
hanging	O
upon	O
a	O
Peg	O
)	O
which	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
Company	O
saw	O
,	O
they	O
interpos	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
wound	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
who	O
soon	O
fell	O
down	O
and	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
Being	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
had	O
any	O
Cane	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
they	O
cou	O
'd	O
not	O
say	O
he	O
had	O
;	O
but	O
were	O
sure	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Sword	O
drawn	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
.	O
A	O
Drawer	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
hearing	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
between	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
had	O
a	O
Cane	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
saw	O
none	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
having	O
given	O
him	O
ill	O
Language	O
,	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
good	O
as	O
he	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
struck	O
him	O
several	O
times	O
with	O
a	O
Cane	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
draw	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
make	O
any	O
Push	O
,	O
and	O
believes	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
might	O
in	O
his	O
Eagerness	O
run	O
upon	O
the	O
Point	O
.	O
To	O
prove	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
cau	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Evans	O
made	O
Oath	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
lives	O
just	O
over-against	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms	O
Tavern	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
up	O
in	O
her	O
Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
a	O
great	O
Noise	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
from	O
thence	O
the	O
Sashes	O
being	O
up	O
)	O
she	O
could	O
plainly	O
see	O
and	O
hear	O
all	O
that	O
pass	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Gentlemen	O
were	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
a	O
Room	O
upon	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
hear	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
(	O
as	O
she	O
since	O
understood	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
)	O
give	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
hard	O
words	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
saw	O
him	O
strike	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
say	O
nothing	O
to	O
the	O
drawing	O
the	O
Sword	O
.	O
Another	O
Woman	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
Street	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
she	O
heard	O
a	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
strike	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
Cane	O
or	O
a	O
Stick	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
was	O
sworn	O
by	O
a	O
Watchman	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Words	O
into	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
strike	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
3	O
times	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
also	O
several	O
who	O
had	O
look	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
the	O
Accident	O
happen	O
'd	O
,	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Evan	O
's	O
Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
high	O
Words	O
might	O
be	O
heard	O
,	O
and	O
Persons	O
distinguish	O
'd	O
from	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
Places	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
several	O
Gentlemen	O
who	O
said	O
their	O
Meeting	O
was	O
accidental	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
and	O
he	O
never	O
had	O
the	O
least	O
Disagreement	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
at	O
all	O
times	O
behav	O
'd	O
himself	O
after	O
a	O
very	O
ineffective	O
and	O
courteous	O
Manner	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
born	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
his	O
Grandfather	O
and	O
Father	O
being	O
both	O
Justices	O
of	O
Peace	O
in	O
Ireland	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Hague	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bow	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Milton	I-pers
,	I-pers
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Randal	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
seiz	O
'd	O
upon	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
being	O
satisfy	O
'd	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Alice	B-pers
Cotton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
White	B-place
Chapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Badnage	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
being	O
in	O
drink	O
,	O
she	O
pick	O
'd	O
him	O
up	O
in	O
Well-Close	B-place
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
drank	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
also	O
he	O
lay	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Money	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Plunket	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
by	O
cutting	O
his	O
Throat	O
with	O
a	O
Razor	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
Day	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Witness	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
lodg	O
'd	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
down	O
Stairs	O
in	O
some	O
haste	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
heard	O
a	O
Noise	O
above	O
,	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
fighting	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
believe	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
being	O
(	O
as	O
she	O
thought	O
)	O
at	O
work	O
by	O
himself	O
:	O
That	O
a	O
while	O
afterwards	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
came	O
down	O
with	O
both	O
Hands	O
at	O
his	O
Throat	O
,	O
bleeding	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
People	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
laid	O
upon	O
a	O
Bench	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
.	O
Another	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
while	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
lay	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
some	O
Keys	O
and	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
speak	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
being	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
dress	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
him	O
on	O
a	O
Bed	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
by	O
farther	O
Application	O
,	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
Speech	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
describ	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
knew	O
not	O
his	O
Name	O
;	O
only	O
said	O
't	O
was	O
he	O
that	O
came	O
over	O
from	O
Ostend	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Reignard	O
(	O
which	O
it	O
,	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
)	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
pull	O
'd	O
back	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
him	O
twice	O
on	O
the	O
Throat	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Sword	O
and	O
Gloves	O
were	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
murder	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
bespoke	O
a	O
Wig	O
of	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
who	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
7	O
l.	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
came	O
to	O
6	O
l.	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
bidding	O
him	O
4	O
l.	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Passion	O
,	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
Razor	O
that	O
lay	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
cut	O
his	O
Throat	O
first	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
accordingly	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
because	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
Custom	O
in	O
France	O
(	O
in	O
which	O
Country	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
born	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
which	O
he	O
fled	O
for	O
killing	O
a	O
Man	O
)	O
that	O
whoever	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
a	O
Man	O
is	O
kill	O
'd	O
,	O
shall	O
answer	O
for	O
his	O
Blood	O
:	O
But	O
this	O
being	O
look	O
'd	O
on	O
as	O
a	O
very	O
weak	O
Defence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
wilful	O
Murther	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Steel	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Humphry	B-pers
Clements	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Hammond	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
3	O
Leather	O
Jacks	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Tipt	O
Mug	O
.	O
The	O
Burglary	O
being	O
sufficiently	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
White	B-place
Chapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
her	O
Husband	O
Will	B-pers
.	I-pers
Fisher	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
Side	O
of	O
his	O
Body	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Pap	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languish	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
Evidence	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
said	O
to	O
a	O
Person	O
who	O
had	O
heard	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
kill	O
'd	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
going	O
up	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
wounded	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
his	O
Wife	O
very	O
great	O
Provocation	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
Mischief	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
A	O
Woman	O
who	O
nurs	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
Illness	O
,	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
had	O
misus	O
'd	O
and	O
beat	O
his	O
Wife	O
to	O
a	O
great	O
Degree	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
thereupon	O
she	O
catch	O
'd	O
up	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
cut	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Boots	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
prevent	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Scuffle	O
the	O
Knife	O
struck	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Breast	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Purpose	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
beat	O
her	O
with	O
a	O
Horse-whip	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
the	O
small	O
End	O
would	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
that	O
she	O
in	O
her	O
Rage	O
did	O
attempt	O
to	O
cut	O
his	O
Boots	O
;	O
but	O
knew	O
not	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
his	O
Hurt	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
Surgeons	O
who	O
open	O
'd	O
his	O
Body	O
,	O
and	O
depos	O
'd	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
die	O
of	O
the	O
Wound	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
it	O
had	O
not	O
penetrated	O
the	O
Trunk	O
of	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
an	O
infirm	O
Man	O
for	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
before	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
two	O
Brass	O
Kettles	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
G	B-pers
-	I-pers
P	I-pers
-	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Dudley	B-pers
Moor	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
of	O
the	O
Breadth	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
10	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languish	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
September	O
and	O
then	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
being	O
at	O
Young	B-place
Man	I-place
's	I-place
Coffee-House	I-place
about	O
9	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
his	O
Acquaintance	O
,	O
a	O
Discourse	O
arose	O
concerning	O
the	O
Lords	O
Address	O
in	O
Ireland	O
in	O
Favour	O
of	O
Sir	O
Constantine	O
Phipps	O
,	O
then	O
Lord	O
Chancellor	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Lords	O
Justices	O
of	O
that	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
Whether	O
the	O
Address	O
was	O
made	O
upon	O
the	O
Examination	O
of	O
Witnesses	O
?	O
And	O
Mr.	O
Moor	O
then	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
his	O
Opinion	O
of	O
the	O
Address	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
It	O
was	O
without	O
Examination	O
into	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
and	O
added	O
,	O
That	O
Sir	O
Constantine	O
Phipps	O
was	O
a	O
Rascal	O
and	O
a	O
Villain	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
much	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
to	O
hear	O
any	O
Gentleman	O
so	O
forward	O
to	O
condemn	O
a	O
Person	O
in	O
so	O
high	O
a	O
Station	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
taking	O
the	O
Power	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Legislature	O
,	O
and	O
fixing	O
it	O
in	O
himself	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
tell	O
him	O
as	O
much	O
to	O
his	O
Face	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
seem	O
'd	O
much	O
to	O
be	O
displeased	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
said	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
under	O
the	O
Protection	O
of	O
the	O
Coffee-House	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
him	O
in	O
another	O
Place	O
he	O
would	O
use	O
him	O
scurrily	O
;	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
answer	O
'd	O
he	O
would	O
endeavour	O
to	O
return	O
his	O
Usage	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
bid	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
hold	O
his	O
prating	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
Puppy	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
Words	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Silence	O
in	O
the	O
Coffee-Hose	O
for	O
a	O
while	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Friends	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
a	O
Supper	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
and	O
order	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
repeated	O
twice	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
going	O
out	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
,	O
clashing	O
of	O
Swords	O
was	O
heard	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Company	O
ran	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
wounded	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
how	O
it	O
came	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
Fair	O
,	O
fair	O
,	O
very	O
fair	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Bateman	I-pers
swore	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
pass	O
at	O
one	O
another	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
who	O
drew	O
first	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Moor	O
being	O
carry	O
'd	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
said	O
Mr.	O
G	O
P.	O
had	O
done	O
very	O
fairly	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
ill	O
Language	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
acknowledg	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
on	O
both	O
Sides	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
pretended	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
order	O
Supper	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
look	O
'd	O
him	O
full	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
expected	O
he	O
should	O
follow	O
him	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Passage	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
Face	O
towards	O
the	O
Coffee-House	O
Door	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
advanc	O
'd	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
drawn	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drew	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
several	O
Passes	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
receiv	O
'd	O
two	O
slight	O
Wounds	O
before	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
got	O
his	O
.	O
A	O
Minster	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
being	O
sent	O
for	O
by	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
wounded	O
,	O
to	O
administer	O
the	O
Sacrament	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
sorry	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
such	O
provoking	O
Language	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
bespeak	O
Supper	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
thoughts	O
he	O
would	O
follow	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
what	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
done	O
was	O
very	O
fair	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
the	O
Law	O
might	O
be	O
dispens	O
'd	O
with	O
,	O
he	O
wou	O
'd	O
not	O
have	O
him	O
Prosecuted	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
he	O
recover	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
shou	O
'd	O
have	O
as	O
great	O
a	O
Value	O
and	O
Esteem	O
for	O
him	O
as	O
for	O
any	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
Nation	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Witness	O
asking	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
if	O
he	O
might	O
declare	O
this	O
,	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
It	O
is	O
my	O
desire	O
you	O
should	O
if	O
there	O
be	O
Occasion	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Gentlemen	O
to	O
his	O
Character	O
,	O
who	O
upon	O
their	O
Oaths	O
declar	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
modest	O
,	O
courteous	O
,	O
inoffensive	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
so	O
behav	O
'd	O
himself	O
in	O
several	O
Stations	O
,	O
Civil	O
and	O
Military	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
appearing	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
were	O
Strangers	O
to	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Peter	B-pers
Letune	I-pers
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Edminton	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Daytime	O
,	O
no	O
Person	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheers	O
,	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
Pettycoat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
Palmer	O
'	O
Wife	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
3	O
found	O
her	O
Window	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
gone	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
being	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
as	O
suspicious	O
Persons	O
,	O
were	O
follow	O
'd	O
cross	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
Letune	O
wou	O
'd	O
have	O
taken	O
it	O
upon	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
hired	O
Williamson	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Matter	O
appearing	O
plainly	O
to	O
be	O
otherwise	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tinsley	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
South	B-place
Mims	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Black-brown	O
Mare	O
,	O
Value	O
4l	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Goddard	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
Mare	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Grounds	O
;	O
and	O
hearing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Crowns	O
at	O
Bow	O
,	O
being	O
put	O
there	O
by	O
one	O
Cole	O
at	O
Limehouse	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
Sold	O
her	O
for	O
50s	O
.	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
)	O
found	O
her	O
there	O
accordingly	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Black	O
Mare	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Grounds	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
prov	O
's	O
that	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
this	O
Fact	O
also	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Man	O
he	O
did	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
accordingly	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
upon	O
3	O
several	O
Indictments	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
Linnen	O
from	O
several	O
Hedges	O
near	O
Rumford	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
taken	O
upon	O
him	O
near	O
Bow	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
nothing	O
Material	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
all	O
Three	O
felonies	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
sett	O
with	O
an	O
Emerald	O
and	O
4	O
Diamonds	O
,	O
Value	O
25l	O
.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Cooling	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
Barber	O
's	O
Servant	O
)	O
coming	O
to	O
Trim	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
his	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
having	O
some	O
suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
swore	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
:	O
But	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
afterwards	O
he	O
deliver	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Ross	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
to	O
buy	O
it	O
for	O
30s	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Excuse	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
amongst	O
his	O
Linnen	O
unknown	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Martha	B-pers
Harwood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Dowlas	O
Shirt	O
and	O
Smock	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Linnen	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bonner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Andirons	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Spit	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Cornelius	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
having	O
lost	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Custody	O
of	O
one	O
Kendrick	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Rule	O
,	O
an	O
Iron-Adds	O
,	O
a	O
Hatchet	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Tools	O
,	O
from	O
Edward	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Isaac	B-pers
Ray	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Cane	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
dwelling-House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lord	I-pers
Brereton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
a	O
Pendulum	O
Clock	O
,	O
Value	O
30l	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Tipping	I-pers
;	O
a	O
Buckle	O
set	O
with	O
Diamonds	O
,	O
Value	O
40l	O
.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
Lord	O
Brereton	O
.	O
The	O
Clock	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
sworn	O
to	O
be	O
brought	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
one	O
Matthews	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
were	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Burglary	O
not	O
being	O
sufficiently	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Rag	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Howel	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Calimancoe	O
Pettycoat	O
,	O
Value	O
12s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
the	O
Fire	O
was	O
in	O
Houndsditch	B-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
stopt	O
in	O
White-Chapel	O
with	O
the	O
Coat	O
,	O
which	O
upon	O
Enquiry	O
was	O
found	O
to	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Howel	O
(	O
who	O
had	O
the	O
Coat	O
)	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
working	O
hard	O
all	O
Night	O
at	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Person	O
going	O
along	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
of	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Coat	O
slipt	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
bid	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
up	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
not	O
seeing	O
him	O
afterwards	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
whom	O
to	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
not	O
being	O
believ	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
and	O
Perry	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hewen	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
White-Chapel	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Pot	O
,	O
Value	O
15s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Widowson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
:	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Proof	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
and	I-pers
Mary	I-pers
and	O
Mary	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
were	O
both	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sheep	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Grounds	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
How	I-pers
at	O
Hampsted	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
Sheep	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
Watchman	O
that	O
he	O
stopt	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
with	O
a	O
Sack	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
part	O
of	O
2	O
Sheep	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
had	O
the	O
Skin	O
on	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Mark	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
said	O
they	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
Ditch	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
being	O
miserably	O
Poor	O
,	O
were	O
carrying	O
it	O
home	O
to	O
their	O
Three	O
Children	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
creditable	O
People	O
who	O
gave	O
them	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Pavior	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
Value	O
25	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Clements	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
But	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
strong	O
enough	O
to	O
satisfy	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stoke-Newington	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Eew	O
Sheep	O
,	O
Value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
seen	O
with	O
a	O
Sack	O
upon	O
his	O
Back	O
,	O
was	O
suspected	O
and	O
taken	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Carcas	O
of	O
a	O
Sheep	O
in	O
the	O
Sack	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Isaac	B-pers
Cordell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Ware	I-pers
on	O
the	O
1st	O
Instant	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Linnen	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
stopt	O
selling	O
them	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Fonner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
White-Chapel	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
Value	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
Brass	O
Pot	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
insufficient	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
3	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
5	O
Plates	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Witness	O
was	O
an	O
Accomplice	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Gardener	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
about	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
pretty	O
light	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Lewis	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Le	I-place
Bone	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Whitfield	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
a	O
Frize-Coat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
about	O
11	O
Weeks	O
he	O
sent	O
him	O
of	O
an	O
Errand	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
no	O
more	O
;	O
but	O
soon	O
after	O
his	O
Cellar	O
Window	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
gone	O
;	O
and	O
hearing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Marshalsea	O
for	O
robbing	O
another	O
Master	O
,	O
went	O
thither	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Breeches	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Burglary	O
not	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Deverell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Heston	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wayt	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
Bottle-Screw	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Proof	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
Sarah	B-pers
Holgate	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Box	O
of	O
Linnen	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
:	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
deliver	O
'd	O
the	O
Box	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
carry	O
,	O
the	O
Indictment	O
was	O
not	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Pinner	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
Dowlas	O
Smocks	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Tyse	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
been	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Entry	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
stolen	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
in	O
the	O
Chamber	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Flannel	O
Pettycoat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
Henry	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
without	O
Warning	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Things	O
were	O
miss	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
2	O
Days	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
them	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
whereupon	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Annesly	I-pers
in	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
Two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
All	O
that	O
appear	O
'd	O
in	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
a	O
Scuffle	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
his	O
Rings	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
immediately	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
who	O
had	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
consider	O
'd	O
it	O
as	O
a	O
very	O
trifling	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
being	O
Accessary	O
with	O
Frances	B-pers
Dye	I-pers
after	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
in	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Fountaine	I-pers
,	O
but	O
the	O
Indictment	O
was	O
faulty	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
acquitted	O
.	O
L	B-pers
-	I-pers
D	I-pers
-	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
marrying	O
a	O
second	O
Wife	O
,	O
his	O
former	O
being	O
still	O
living	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Gerald	B-pers
Fitz-Gibbons	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
speaking	O
dangerous	O
and	O
seditious	O
Words	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
one	O
Averal	O
,	O
a	O
Taylor	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
us	O
'd	O
these	O
Words	O
,	O
God	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
the	O
Whigs	O
,	O
the	O
Pretender	O
is	O
King	O
James	O
the	O
Third	O
,	O
and	O
right	O
Heir	O
to	O
the	O
Crown	O
of	O
England	O
.	O
To	O
disprove	O
this	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
that	O
Averal	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
us	O
'd	O
provoking	O
Words	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
calling	O
him	O
Irish	O
Papist	O
,	O
and	O
saying	O
such	O
as	O
he	O
would	O
bring	O
in	O
the	O
Pretender	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
God	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
all	O
the	O
Whigs	O
in	O
England	O
,	O
and	O
God	O
bless	O
the	O
Queen	O
and	O
all	O
her	O
Mothers	O
Children	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
such	O
Words	O
as	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Enoch	B-pers
Bradley	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
in	O
personating	O
Richard	B-pers
Moreton	I-pers
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
receive	O
his	O
Prize-Money	O
at	O
the	O
Office	O
on	O
Tower-Hill	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
pass	O
Sentence	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
10.	O
Katherine	B-pers
Priest	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Neal	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Cann	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Trevor	I-pers
,	O
Joyce	B-pers
Hodgkis	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Plunket	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Leinne	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tinsley	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
22.	O
John	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
Dorothy	O
Hall	O
,	O
O	O
-	O
H	O
-	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Stove	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Commins	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Noble	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Clare	I-pers
,	O
T	O
-	O
E	O
-	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Mantle	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Dobbins	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hague	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Steel	I-pers
,	O
Humphry	O
Clements	B-pers
,	I-pers
G	I-pers
-	O
P	O
-	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
Martha	B-pers
Harwood	I-pers
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Rag	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Cordelt	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
Lewis	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
whipt	O
,	O
19	O
.	O
Obediah	O
Leman	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hoskins	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Pooly	I-pers
,	O
Anthony	B-pers
Elson	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Denford	I-pers
,	O
Stephen	B-pers
Nott	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Ryder	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hornby	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	O
Ellis	O
,	O
William	O
Stevens	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Pearson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Hans	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bonner	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Howell	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Herbet	O
,	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Roberts	O
.	O
Enoch	B-pers
Bradley	I-pers
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Neal	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
to	O
be	O
drawn	O
upon	O
Sledges	O
,	O
and	O
Executed	O
as	O
in	O
Cases	O
of	O
High-Treason	O
;	O
and	O
Joyes	O
Hodgkis	O
to	O
be	O
burnt	O
to	O
Ashes	O
.	O
Katherine	B-pers
Priest	I-pers
and	O
Joyce	B-pers
Hodgkis	I-pers
pleaded	O
their	O
Bellies	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
being	O
impannell	O
'd	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
first	O
to	O
be	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
last	O
not	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENT	O
.	O
THE	O
most	O
excellent	O
Spirit	O
of	O
Ground-lvy	O
,	O
distill	O
'd	O
to	O
its	O
Perfection	O
:	O
which	O
infallibly	O
cools	O
and	O
sweetens	O
the	O
Blood	O
,	O
and	O
keeps	O
the	O
Stomach	O
in	O
order	O
.	O
It	O
hath	O
a	O
more	O
than	O
ordinary	O
Effect	O
upon	O
the	O
Lungs	O
,	O
by	O
preventing	O
and	O
wearing	O
off	O
short	O
husking	O
Coughs	O
;	O
immediately	O
stops	O
any	O
violent	O
Fit	O
of	O
Coughing	O
.	O
In	O
any	O
Case	O
where	O
the	O
Blood	O
wants	O
rectifying	O
,	O
(	O
especially	O
Consumptions	O
)	O
it	O
is	O
of	O
great	O
Benefit	O
.	O
It	O
easeth	O
all	O
griping	O
Pains	O
,	O
windy	O
and	O
cholerick	O
Humours	O
in	O
the	O
Stomach	O
,	O
Spleen	O
,	O
or	O
Belly	O
,	O
helps	O
against	O
the	O
Yellow-Jaundice	O
and	O
Melancholy	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
taken	O
according	O
to	O
Directions	O
given	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Seal	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Scotch	O
Sold	O
Wholesale	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Garway	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
Gate	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
,	O
and	O
Retail	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Stone	O
,	O
Stationer	O
,	O
next	O
to	O
Gate	O
on	O
London-bridge	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Deard	O
,	O
Toyshop	O
,	O
under	O
it	O
.	O
Dunstan's-Church	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Lovell	O
,	O
Toyshop	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Parish	O
against	O
Great	O
Suffolk-street	O
End	O
,	O
near	O
Charing-Cross	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Goddard	O
,	O
Bookseller	O
at	O
Norwich	O
,	O
Mr.	O
White	O
,	O
chandler	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Black-Boy	O
without	O
the	O
Bart	O
at	O
White-chapel	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Gills	O
,	O
next	O
Hercules-Pillars-Alley	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
at	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
Bottle	O
.	O
