TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
Queen	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
Held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
7th	O
,	O
8th	O
,	O
and	O
9th	O
,	O
Days	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
1714	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Twelfth	O
Tear	O
of	O
Her	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEfore	O
the	O
Rt	O
Hon	O
Sir	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
STANIER	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
Parker	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Tracy	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Bury	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
Richardson	O
,	O
Sir	O
Peter	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
Her	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
,	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Keeble	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Grimsted	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Swinbow	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dowell	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Terriot	I-pers
,	I-pers
Ichabod	B-pers
Dawks	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Kimber	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Kelson	I-pers
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Finchwait	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Mawl	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Caldecott	I-pers
,	O
Arthur	B-pers
Osborne	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Legg	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Orbell	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
How	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Beckington	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Jackman	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Millet	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Croker	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Drew	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Cash	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Higgins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Magnes	I-place
the	I-place
Martyr	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
10	O
Silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
valu	O
'd	O
14	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Warkman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
.	O
instant	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Warkman	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
Shop	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
about	O
,	O
mov	O
'd	O
6	O
which	O
lay	O
upon	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
:	O
But	O
being	O
stopp	O
'd	O
and	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
dropp	O
'd	O
them	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
4	O
others	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Bosom	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
stoln	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
Window	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
his	O
Goods	O
again	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Abigal	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
18	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
valu	O
'd	O
18	O
s.	O
2	O
Table	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
a	O
Brass	O
Ladle	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Riding-hood	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Frances	B-pers
Ayres	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
hir	O
'd	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
missing	O
.	O
Being	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
,	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
at	O
her	O
Trial	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
given	O
her	O
by	O
her	O
Master	O
(	O
Mrs.	O
Ayres	O
's	O
Son	O
)	O
and	O
some	O
Circumstances	O
appear	O
'd	O
which	O
induc	O
'd	O
the	O
Jury	O
to	O
believe	O
her	O
so	O
far	O
as	O
to	O
acquit	O
her	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lynn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Swithin	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
3	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
16	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Dorcas	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
Meeting	O
at	O
Salters-Hall	B-place
,	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Money	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
in	O
a	O
Green	O
Silk	O
Purse	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
;	O
and	O
her	O
Footman	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
just	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
stepping	O
into	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brush	O
'd	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Purse	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
who	O
said	O
they	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
do	O
an	O
ill	O
thing	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Ayd	I-pers
,	O
who	O
swore	O
she	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
up	O
the	O
Purse	O
at	O
a	O
little	O
distance	O
from	O
the	O
Meeting-house	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
being	O
catch	O
'd	O
in	O
several	O
Falsities	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
committed	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anthony	B-pers
Gery	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Laurence	I-place
Jury	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Porringer	O
,	O
value	O
45	O
s.	O
(	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Fotherby	I-pers
)	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Whaley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Whaley	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
having	O
been	O
to	O
fetch	O
some	O
Oysters	O
in	O
a	O
Porringer	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
,	O
she	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
;	O
and	O
while	O
the	O
other	O
catch	O
'd	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
pretending	O
to	O
kiss	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
snatch	O
'd	O
the	O
Porringer	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
pursu	O
'd	O
and	O
taken	O
,	O
threw	O
it	O
under	O
a	O
Stall	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
.	O
The	O
Matter	O
wasvery	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
(	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
having	O
receiv	O
'd	O
Her	O
Majesty	O
's	O
most	O
Gracious	O
Pardon	O
but	O
last	O
Summer	O
)	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Warrel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Peter	I-place
Cheap	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Boult	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
,	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Boult	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
Shop	O
on	O
pretence	O
of	O
buying	O
a	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
about	O
to	O
look	O
the	O
Scales	O
,	O
the	O
Box	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
it	O
just	O
then	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
about	O
a	O
Month	O
afterwards	O
to	O
sell	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Buckles	O
he	O
stopp	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
where	O
the	O
Box	O
was	O
pawn	O
'd	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
accordingly	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bolson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Zachary	I-place
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tobacco-Box	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Cornock	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
Bolson	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
Shop	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Buckles	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
opening	O
the	O
Shew-Glass	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
out	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
weighing	O
them	O
,	O
Walker	O
(	O
who	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
)	O
found	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Box	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
miss	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
taken	O
to	O
be	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
Walker	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
lay	O
it	O
down	O
slily	O
.	O
The	O
matter	O
was	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
no	O
Defence	O
to	O
make	O
,	O
whereupon	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Leech	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
from	O
Sarah	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
Street	O
about	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pass	O
'd	O
by	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
snatch	O
'd	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
off	O
her	O
Neck	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
help	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
two	O
others	O
in	O
his	O
Company	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
thought	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
positive	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Thornbury	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Cecil	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Foster	I-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Mugg	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
2	O
silver	O
Casters	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Fawdry	I-pers
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servants	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
got	O
behind	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
do	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
Breakfast	O
)	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
there	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Mugg	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Casters	O
he	O
had	O
thrown	O
down	O
.	O
He	O
made	O
many	O
frivolous	O
Excuses	O
,	O
as	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
an	O
Arrest	O
,	O
and	O
deny	O
'd	O
his	O
meddling	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Proof	O
being	O
very	O
full	O
and	O
clear	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Shop-lifting	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Hardy	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bartholomew	I-place
the	I-place
Great	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Shurlow	I-pers
:	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Gardener	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Vedast	I-place
alias	I-place
Foster	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
182	O
Yards	O
of	O
Silk	O
Ferret	O
,	O
value	O
21	O
s.	O
19	O
Yards	O
of	O
black	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
19	O
Yards	O
of	O
Silk	O
Galloon	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
come	O
frequently	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
seem	O
'd	O
very	O
difficult	O
to	O
be	O
pleas	O
'd	O
in	O
Goods	O
she	O
pretended	O
to	O
buy	O
,	O
but	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
she	O
was	O
narrowly	O
watch	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
seen	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
dropp	O
'd	O
and	O
part	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
spoke	O
well	O
of	O
her	O
former	O
Behaviour	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
herself	O
could	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
present	O
Fact	O
,	O
whereupon	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
52	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Heron	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
Depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
being	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Coachman	O
,	O
whose	O
Coach-house	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
Green-Yard	B-place
,	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
4	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
return	O
'd	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
suspecting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
an	O
idle	O
Person	O
lurking	O
about	O
the	O
Yard	O
)	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
before	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Withers	I-pers
,	O
before	O
whom	O
a	O
Constable	O
swore	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ralph	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bartholomew	I-place
the	I-place
Less	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cheshire	O
Cheese	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
;	O
on	O
the	O
19	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
swore	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
tasted	O
several	O
Cheeses	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
she	O
miss	O
'd	O
one	O
,	O
but	O
cou	O
'd	O
not	O
say	O
who	O
took	O
it	O
:	O
But	O
one	O
who	O
was	O
an	O
Accomplice	O
with	O
him	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
in	O
on	O
purpose	O
to	O
amuse	O
her	O
with	O
Tasting	O
and	O
Talk	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
Cheese	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
got	O
3	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
swear	O
he	O
was	O
sick	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
them	O
faltering	O
in	O
her	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
examin	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
confess	O
'd	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
hir	O
'd	O
to	O
Swear	O
for	O
5	O
s.	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
latter	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
bound	O
in	O
Regonizance	O
to	O
give	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
Holland	O
Shifts	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Broxton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
sent	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
Wash	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
lost'em	O
off	O
the	O
Lines	O
;	O
and	O
Hull	O
(	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Accomplices	O
)	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
going	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
Evans	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stood	O
watching	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
stood	O
at	O
a	O
further	O
distance	O
,	O
to	O
give	O
Notice	O
when	O
any	O
body	O
was	O
coming	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Evans	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sold	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
but	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
for	O
his	O
share	O
.	O
The	O
matter	O
being	O
thus	O
plain	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
3d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
90	O
l.	O
weight	O
of	O
Soap	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
prove	O
which	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Vaughan	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
her	O
shop	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
Pound	O
of	O
Raisins	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
her	O
busie	O
in	O
talk	O
,	O
finding	O
fault	O
with	O
the	O
Weight	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
while	O
she	O
lost	O
her	O
Soap	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
telling	O
her	O
somebodyhad	O
robb	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stood	O
betwixt	O
her	O
and	O
the	O
Shop-door	O
,	O
to	O
hinder	O
her	O
getting	O
out	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
had	O
the	O
Soap	O
(	O
viz	O
.	O
Hull	O
the	O
Evidence	O
)	O
being	O
taken	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
also	O
secur	O
'd	O
.	O
All	O
this	O
was	O
justify	O
'd	O
by	O
Hull	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
drawn	O
him	O
into	O
that	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Robberies	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Podger	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Best	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Fulham	B-place
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cock	O
and	O
Coulter	O
of	O
a	O
Plough	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
Podger	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Accomplice	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
Podger	O
and	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
but	O
cou	O
'd	O
say	O
nothing	O
against	O
Best	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coulter	O
and	O
a	O
Harrow	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
from	O
George	B-pers
Swetenham	I-pers
.	O
Podger	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
as	O
before	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
3d	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Harrows	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Cock	O
of	O
a	O
Plough	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Hackman	I-pers
on	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
.	O
To	O
this	O
also	O
Podger	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
affecting	O
Best	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
all	O
3	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Stable	O
of	O
the	O
Honourable	O
James	B-pers
Bridges	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Bridges	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
having	O
lost	O
his	O
Coat	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Coach-box	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
it	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
much	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
not	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
Coat	O
;	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
Witness	O
who	O
swore	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
drop	O
the	O
Coat	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
deficient	O
in	O
his	O
Story	O
,	O
and	O
rather	O
expos	O
'd	O
than	O
excus	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Whale	I-pers
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Pancrass	B-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
10	O
Ells	O
of	O
Flaxen	O
Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Douglas	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
together	O
in	O
a	O
Ditch	O
near	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
husling	O
something	O
between	O
'em	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
afraid	O
to	O
venture	O
on	O
them	O
by	O
himself	O
,	O
went	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
his	O
Dog	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
running	O
away	O
,	O
he	O
pursu	O
'd	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
Price	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
swore	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
stoln	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Garden	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
not	O
full	O
enough	O
against	O
Whale	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
accquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Price	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kerny	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
Silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Frances	B-pers
Gain	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
:	O
But	O
no	O
Prosecutor	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margeret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
2	O
Seals	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bruce	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
Bruce	O
Swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
Room	O
to	O
ask	O
him	O
a	O
Question	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
Bed	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
getting	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
left	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
while	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Watch	O
was	O
hanging	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Buckles	O
lying	O
on	O
a	O
Table	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
coming	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
the	O
Necessary	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
at	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
she	O
us	O
'd	O
.	O
She	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
brought	O
Witnesses	O
who	O
swore	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
all	O
that	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
charg	O
'd	O
another	O
Woman	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
fled	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
also	O
several	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Lydia	B-pers
Cane	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Cayler	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Wade	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Gilpin	I-pers
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
day-time	O
(	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
Gilpin	O
being	O
then	O
therein	O
,	O
)	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Wastcoat	O
and	O
Breeches	O
,	O
a	O
Quilted	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
not	O
sufficient	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hatchet	I-pers
on	O
the	O
21st	O
.	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
day-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Drugget	O
Suit	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bugg	I-pers
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
being	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
Hatchet	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Sarah	B-pers
Barnet	I-pers
(	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
an	O
Accomplice	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
)	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
in	O
Spittle-fields	B-place
,	O
Cane	O
pitch	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
her	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
with	O
a	O
Picklock-key	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
Wade	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
standing	O
upon	O
the	O
Watch	O
to	O
give	O
Notice	O
when	O
any	O
body	O
came	O
.	O
A	O
Constable	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
taking	O
up	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
the	O
Witness	O
as	O
suspicious	O
Persons	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
Bunch	O
of	O
Picklock	O
keys	O
in	O
Cane	O
's	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
Barnet	O
confess	O
'd	O
this	O
and	O
the	O
former	O
Robbery	O
.	O
They	O
deny	O
'd	O
they	O
ever	O
had	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
the	O
Witness	O
,	O
yet	O
Cane	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Picklock	O
keys	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margery	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Dempster	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
left	O
her	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
door	O
lock	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
of	O
hers	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
seeing	O
Thompson	O
come	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
she	O
suspected	O
and	O
stop	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
the	O
Stairs	O
.	O
Thompson	O
said	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
meddle	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
some	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
affecting	O
Dempster	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
she	O
only	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
Thompson	O
for	O
Company	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Doughty	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Livery	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
great	O
Coat	O
,	O
Wastcoat	O
and	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Gore	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
been	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
in	O
his	O
Gardens	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
London	O
to	O
do	O
the	O
same	O
Office	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Gore	O
intending	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
into	O
his	O
House	O
as	O
a	O
Domestick	O
Servant	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
telling	O
the	O
Maid	O
his	O
Master	O
had	O
order	O
d	O
him	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
Livery	O
Suit	O
which	O
he	O
knew	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
his	O
ways	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
his	O
Master	O
order	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Livery	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
his	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
her	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Bruise	O
with	O
a	O
Rolling	O
Pin	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
her	O
Head	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
languish	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
several	O
Persons	O
who	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
by	O
whole	O
Evidence	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
hearing	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
Noise	O
,	O
ran	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
Floor	O
as	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
'em	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
strike	O
her	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Blows	O
with	O
the	O
Rolling-Pin	O
as	O
she	O
lay	O
;	O
and	O
catching	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
why	O
he	O
kill	O
'd	O
his	O
Wife	O
?	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
answered	O
because	O
she	O
wou	O
'd	O
have	O
kill	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
afterwards	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
Question	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
Devil	O
lay	O
under	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
very	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
;	O
but	O
several	O
People	O
appearing	O
to	O
prove	O
him	O
Non	O
compos	O
mentis	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Woman	O
particularly	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
was	O
afraid	O
to	O
be	O
with	O
him	O
because	O
of	O
his	O
Distemper	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
agreed	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
for	O
a	O
white	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquited	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ralph	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
2	O
Tumblers	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
12	O
Silver	O
spoons	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Ladle	O
,	O
a	O
Porringer	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Robins	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
It	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
about	O
10	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
5	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
Printed	O
Bills	O
being	O
given	O
about	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
at	O
Plastow	O
in	O
Essex	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
upon	O
the	O
new	O
Statute	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Timothy	B-pers
Dunn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
Chain	O
and	O
Seal	O
,	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Smart	I-pers
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
through	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
Park	O
about	O
7	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
a	O
Woman	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
clasp	O
'd	O
her	O
Hand	O
about	O
his	O
Middle	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Man	O
came	O
and	O
jostled	O
him	O
from	O
one	O
to	O
th	O
'	O
other	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
hearing	O
,	O
something	O
jingle	O
,	O
cast	O
his	O
Eye	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Hand	O
go	O
from	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
clapt	O
his	O
Hand	O
upon	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
swearing	O
he	O
wou	O
'd	O
kill	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
follow	O
'd	O
;	O
however	O
,	O
he	O
still	O
pursu	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
go	O
up	O
close	O
to	O
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
he	O
gave	O
something	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
for	O
help	O
,	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
secur	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Centinel	O
Box	O
with	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
might	O
take	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
some	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
very	O
positive	O
in	O
his	O
Evidence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
privately	O
stealing	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Wade	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Weight	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Samuel	B-pers
Slap	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Queens	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
Slap	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
coming	O
from	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
to	O
Mile-End	B-place
about	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
two	O
others	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
set	O
upon	O
by	O
6	O
Men	O
,	O
3	O
of	O
whom	O
were	O
Executed	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
made	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
accus	O
'd	O
Wade	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
likewise	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
hearing	O
Wade	O
was	O
in	O
New-Prison	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
:	O
But	O
James	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
swearing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
Man	O
he	O
accus	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Suits	O
of	O
Cloths	O
,	O
a	O
Riding-Coat	O
,	O
Linnen	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Stables	O
of	O
the	O
Lord	B-pers
Paget	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
depos	O
'd	O
That	O
about	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
the	O
stables	O
being	O
found	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Man	O
seen	O
go	O
by	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
pursu	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
drew	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
and	O
fir	O
'd	O
at	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Pursuers	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
down	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Chelsea	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
were	O
given	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
deliver	O
'd	O
'em	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
own	O
'd	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Matter	O
being	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
-	O
Note	O
,	O
This	O
pretended	O
J.	O
Johnson	O
is	O
Cullum	O
who	O
kill	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Perry	O
the	O
Turnkey	O
of	O
New-Prison	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
,	O
in	O
Marrying	O
Mary	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
.	O
of	O
June	O
1710	O
his	O
former	O
Wife	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Millisent	I-pers
being	O
then	O
alive	O
.	O
He	O
own	O
'd	O
his	O
last	O
Marriage	O
,	O
but	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
first	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
being	O
very	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Mohair	O
Gown	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
(	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
)	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Whitfield	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
an	O
Apprentice	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Gown	O
being	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Trunk	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
suspected	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
own	O
'd	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
for	O
10	O
s.	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
at	O
her	O
Tryal	O
;	O
but	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
some	O
of	O
her	O
Mother	O
's	O
Mony	O
,	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
Gown	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
for	O
the	O
present	O
,	O
intending	O
to	O
restore	O
it	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
had	O
several	O
People	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Rebekah	B-pers
Tayler	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
8	O
plain	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
a	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
,	O
a	O
Ring	O
with	O
a	O
Turquois	O
Stone	O
,	O
and	O
70	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
at	O
the	O
earnest	O
request	O
of	O
Tayler	O
(	O
who	O
is	O
her	O
Neighbour	O
)	O
she	O
permitted	O
Morgan	O
to	O
lodge	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
Tayler	O
came	O
frequently	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Man	O
;	O
but	O
after	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
were	O
miss	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Dressing-Box	O
wherein	O
they	O
were	O
being	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
broken	O
to	O
pieces	O
upon	O
his	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Money-Bags	O
over	O
the	O
Tester	O
.	O
Being	O
thus	O
gone	O
,	O
upon	O
Intelligence	O
they	O
pursu	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
Reading	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Rings	O
,	O
some	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
that	O
he	O
receiv	O
'd	O
the	O
Things	O
from	O
Tayler	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
other	O
Proof	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
privately	O
stealing	O
,	O
and	O
accquitted	O
her	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Macmullen	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ashburn	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Holland	O
Shifts	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Witnesses	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
Ashburn	O
was	O
seen	O
walking	O
about	O
by	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
Macmullen	O
came	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
out	O
a	O
Bundle	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
pursu	O
'd	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
,	O
Ashburn	O
having	O
the	O
Linen	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
nothing	O
material	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Hackney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
(	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Marryweather	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
)	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
Lodging	O
,	O
pretending	O
it	O
was	O
for	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Cass	I-pers
's	O
Nieces	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
the	O
Spoon	O
was	O
miss	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
fetch	O
'd	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
when	O
sitting	O
down	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
,	O
after	O
she	O
got	O
up	O
the	O
Spoon	O
was	O
found	O
under	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
intended	O
to	O
come	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
having	O
left	O
her	O
Handbasket	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
search	O
'd	O
when	O
taken	O
:	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
very	O
positive	O
the	O
Spoon	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
Chair	O
before	O
she	O
sate	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
such	O
Persons	O
appearing	O
as	O
she	O
pretended	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Lodging	O
for	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Boyle	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary-le	I-place
Bone	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Suits	O
of	O
Head	O
Cloaths	O
a	O
Bible	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Whitfield	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Witnesses	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
not	O
sit	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
pretending	O
she	O
had	O
sore	O
Eyes	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Room	O
was	O
too	O
light	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
was	O
had	O
into	O
another	O
Room	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
open	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Whitfield	O
having	O
Notice	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
presently	O
fell	O
a	O
Swearing	O
at	O
her	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
come	O
for	O
her	O
Bible	O
?	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
she	O
valu	O
'd	O
her	O
things	O
at	O
,	O
She	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
all	O
at	O
her	O
Tryal	O
,	O
and	O
behav	O
'd	O
her	O
self	O
very	O
rudely	O
;	O
but	O
cou	O
'd	O
say	O
nothing	O
to	O
the	O
purpose	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
,	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Lambert	I-pers
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
a	O
Lodging	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
it	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
following	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
came	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
betimes	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
Being	O
describ	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
enquir	O
'd	O
after	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Betty	O
the	O
Cook	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
3	O
hours	O
time	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
nothing	O
material	O
to	O
offer	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
and	O
is	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
notorious	O
Offender	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
also	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Daniel	B-pers
Lovet	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Harrow	B-place
on	I-place
the	I-place
Hill	I-place
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Weather-sheep	O
and	O
6	O
Ewes	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Corbet	I-pers
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
mark	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
one	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
at	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
drawn	O
aside	O
by	O
a	O
Master	O
he	O
had	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Alexander	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
and	O
Francis	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
And	O
stealing	O
thence	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Drugget	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Leathern	O
Breeches	O
,	O
an	O
Iron	O
Goose	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
his	O
Shop	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
being	O
taken	O
upon	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
Stone	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
he	O
carried	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Jackson	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Lovet	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
,	O
the	O
Shop	O
that	O
was	O
broke	O
not	O
being	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Mansion	O
house	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
H	B-pers
-	I-pers
J	I-pers
-	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
7	O
Yards	O
of	O
Sattin	O
value	O
41	O
s.	O
(	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Emerson	I-pers
)	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
a	O
Dyer	O
,	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
off	O
his	O
Lines	O
;	O
and	O
giving	O
Notice	O
amongst	O
the	O
Dyers	O
and	O
Calenders	O
,	O
found	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
carry	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Mother	O
keeps	O
a	O
Broker	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
Customer	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
Callender	O
'd	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
prove	O
by	O
another	O
Witness	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Woman	O
of	O
ill	O
fame	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Martha	B-pers
Holt	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Camblet	O
Riding-Hood	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
diver	O
other	O
Goods	O
belonging	O
to	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Jordan	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
been	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Jordan	O
about	O
3	O
Weeks	O
,	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
taken	O
upon	O
her	O
and	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
Justice	O
Clare	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
now	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
an	O
extravagant	O
Husband	O
,	O
who	O
coming	O
to	O
her	O
for	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
She	O
having	O
none	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
'em	O
her	O
to	O
make	O
Money	O
of	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Pool	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
(	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Curstal	I-pers
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
.	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
,	O
who	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
gave	O
them	O
in	O
Ford	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
laid	O
his	O
Watch	O
upon	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
afterwards	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
in	O
lieu	O
of	O
a	O
Crown	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
not	O
being	O
believ	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Penlington	I-pers
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
thence	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Stockins	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecution	O
was	O
after	O
the	O
same	O
manner	O
with	O
that	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
try	O
'd	O
last	O
Sessions	O
for	O
the	O
like	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Daughter	O
letting	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
also	O
prov	O
'd	O
she	O
did	O
this	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Stockins	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Graves	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
101	O
l.	O
of	O
Iron	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kirby	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Iron	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
quantity	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
who	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
hir	O
'd	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
for	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
was	O
carrying	O
the	O
last	O
piece	O
when	O
taken	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
none	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Blundel	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
)	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Harrow	B-place
on	I-place
the	I-place
Hill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
8	O
Yards	O
of	O
Lustring	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Silk	O
Hood	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Saucer	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
Parish	O
Child	O
of	O
St.	O
Andrews	O
Holborn	O
,	O
was	O
nurs	O
'd	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
who	O
fancying	O
the	O
Boy	O
,	O
took	O
him	O
upon	O
liking	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
were	O
abroad	O
he	O
was	O
left	O
at	O
home	O
to	O
look	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
threatning	O
to	O
bring	O
him	O
to	O
London	O
to	O
a	O
Cunning	O
Man	O
,	O
he	O
run	O
away	O
to	O
his	O
Nurse	O
,	O
who	O
protected	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Boy	O
upon	O
his	O
Trial	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Cock	I-pers
his	O
Nurse	O
's	O
Grandson	O
,	O
who	O
stole	O
the	O
Silk	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
it	O
home	O
to	O
his	O
Grandmother	O
,	O
who	O
receiv	O
'd	O
whatever	O
they	O
stole	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
order	O
'd	O
to	O
proceed	O
against	O
his	O
Nurse	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Wapping	B-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
not	O
taken	O
;	O
did	O
steal	O
5	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Red	O
Lisbon	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Stone	O
Bottles	O
from	O
Captain	O
Samuel	B-pers
Moody	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
;	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Green	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Captain	O
Moody	O
having	O
lost	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Wine	O
from	O
on	O
Board	O
his	O
Ship	O
was	O
inform	O
'd	O
that	O
his	O
Servant	O
had	O
sold	O
some	O
to	O
Green	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Green	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
who	O
readily	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Buying	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
12	O
s.	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
Freeman	O
and	O
not	O
of	O
Hopkins	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
its	O
being	O
stole	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
customary	O
to	O
buy	O
such	O
parcels	O
of	O
Wine	O
of	O
Sailors	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Hopkins	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Gunter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Boot	O
Legs	O
,	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Upper	O
Leather	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Plush	O
Breeches	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
and	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Pincers	O
and	O
other	O
Tools	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
with	O
Turner	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
taken	O
,	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
upon	O
his	O
Trial	O
,	O
That	O
Turner	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
the	O
Boots	O
to	O
make	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
pawn	O
'd	O
'em	O
to	O
buy	O
Wax	O
and	O
Thread	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
2	O
s.	O
for	O
the	O
Breeches	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Tools	O
,	O
't	O
was	O
customary	O
for	O
'em	O
to	O
use	O
one	O
another	O
's	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Clap	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
into	O
the	O
Chamber	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
on	O
the	O
3d	O
instant	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
3	O
Perukes	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
;	O
That	O
being	O
at	O
Work	O
in	O
his	O
Chamber	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
broke	O
in	O
upon	O
him	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
arresting	O
him	O
for	O
6	O
s.	O
8	O
d.	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
his	O
Wigs	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
produc	O
'd	O
a	O
Writ	O
in	O
Court	O
to	O
arrest	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
Witness	O
that	O
he	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
thrust	O
in	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
and	O
arrested	O
him	O
.	O
Another	O
Witness	O
who	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
swore	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Wig	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
.	O
The	O
matter	O
appearing	O
plain	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
behalf	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Gill	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Feather	O
Bolster	O
and	O
Pillow	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Blankets	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Holland	O
Pillowber	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Willington	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
swore	O
she	O
let	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
her	O
Husband	O
a	O
Room	O
furnish	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
lay	O
there	O
3	O
Weeks	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
.	O
But	O
her	O
Husband	O
taking	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
lodging	O
there	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Sophia	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
Counterfeiting	O
the	O
current	O
Coyn	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Prosecution	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Plunket	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Moor	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Body	O
near	O
the	O
Groin	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
breath	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
two	O
inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
first	O
day	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Moor	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
at	O
the	O
Horn	O
and	O
Horse	O
shoe	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Chancery-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
enquir	O
'd	O
for	O
one	O
Mr.	O
O	O
Hara	O
,	O
who	O
being	O
there	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Plunket	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Moor	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
Saluted	O
the	O
Company	O
all	O
round	O
after	O
a	O
very	O
friendly	O
manner	O
,	O
but	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
sit	O
down	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
having	O
drank	O
very	O
plentifully	O
before	O
.	O
After	O
mutual	O
Salutations	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
Mr.	O
Plunket	O
aside	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
talk	O
'd	O
together	O
a	O
while	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
gone	O
sometime	O
before	O
the	O
Company	O
miss	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
concluded	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
past	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
;	O
but	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
Sword	O
and	O
Cane	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
telling	O
them	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
Mr.	O
Moor	O
was	O
hurt	O
.	O
Bass	O
,	O
the	O
Beadle	O
of	O
that	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
,	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
as	O
he	O
went	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
him	O
bleeding	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
and	O
led	O
him	O
home	O
;	O
and	O
asking	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
that	O
Condition	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
't	O
was	O
an	O
old	O
Grudge	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
not	O
say	O
who	O
did	O
it	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Lodging	O
,	O
the	O
Maid	O
asking	O
him	O
where	O
his	O
Sword	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
in	O
Bream	O
's	O
Buildings	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
likewise	O
that	O
one	O
who	O
ow	O
'd	O
him	O
an	O
old	O
Grudge	O
had	O
paid	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
who	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
barbarously	O
us	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Sword	O
being	O
in	O
his	O
Body	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
upon	O
his	O
Guard	O
,	O
his	O
Cane	O
hanging	O
upon	O
his	O
Wrist	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
.	O
[	O
Here	O
the	O
Beadle	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
light	O
enough	O
for	O
one	O
Man	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
another	O
did	O
at	O
some	O
distance	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
]	O
Mr.	O
Adrian	O
Moor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
he	O
dy	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
told	O
him	O
Mr.	O
Plunket	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Humphreys	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
being	O
at	O
a	O
Coffee	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
City	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
asking	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
heard	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Moor	O
's	O
Misfortune	O
of	O
being	O
wounded	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
Unfortunate	O
Man	O
that	O
did	O
it	O
.	O
By	O
which	O
Evidence	O
it	O
plainly	O
appear	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
kill	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
.	O
To	O
prove	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
premeditated	O
Quarrel	O
,	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
that	O
they	O
fell	O
out	O
and	O
fought	O
together	O
about	O
20	O
Months	O
ago	O
at	O
the	O
Swan	O
Ale-house	O
in	O
the	O
Butcher-row	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Sword	O
being	O
broke	O
,	O
they	O
parted	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
declar	O
'd	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Moor	O
had	O
divers	O
times	O
us	O
'd	O
very	O
hard	O
words	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Plunket	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
such	O
a	O
Skirmish	O
with	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
all	O
was	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
reconcil	O
'd	O
long	O
ago	O
;	O
to	O
prove	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
declar	O
'd	O
that	O
since	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
even	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
before	O
their	O
last	O
unhappy	O
meeting	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
extraordinary	O
friendly	O
,	O
and	O
us	O
'd	O
the	O
most	O
endearing	O
expressions	O
that	O
could	O
be	O
to	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
help	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
into	O
several	O
Causes	O
,	O
and	O
once	O
particularly	O
favour	O
'd	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
Chancery	O
,	O
when	O
by	O
mistake	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
himself	O
liable	O
to	O
a	O
Penalty	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
Crime	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
calling	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Tavern	O
,	O
they	O
walk	O
'd	O
up	O
Chancery-Lane	O
together	O
(	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
his	O
way	O
home	O
)	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
began	O
to	O
talk	O
of	O
a	O
Bill	O
of	O
Costs	O
to	O
be	O
paid	O
by	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Talbot	I-pers
in	O
a	O
Cause	O
wherein	O
he	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
he	O
fell	O
into	O
such	O
a	O
Passion	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
first	O
struck	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
with	O
his	O
Cane	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
drew	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
parrying	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
got	O
,	O
his	O
Wound	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
strengthen	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
Witness	O
who	O
swore	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
he	O
dy	O
'd	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
fault	O
.	O
He	O
further	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
heard	O
Mr.	O
Moor	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
he	O
surrender	O
'd	O
himself	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Le	O
Neve	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
never	O
absconded	O
from	O
his	O
Lodging	O
during	O
the	O
whole	O
time	O
of	O
his	O
Illness	O
.	O
He	O
also	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Persons	O
of	O
Distinction	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
peaceable	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
readier	O
to	O
appease	O
,	O
than	O
create	O
Quarrels	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
summing	O
up	O
the	O
Evidence	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
impartial	O
and	O
judicious	O
Manner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Sentence	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
10.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lynn	I-pers
,	O
Anthony	B-pers
Gery	I-pers
,	O
Richard	O
Thandbury	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Ralph	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Williams	O
,	O
Lydia	B-pers
Cane	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Wade	I-pers
,	O
Timothy	B-pers
Dun	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Boyle	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
14	O
.	O
Mary	O
Gardener	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Podger	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
William	O
Doughty	O
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Plunket	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
Ralph	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Levet	I-pers
,	O
Alexander	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
,	O
H	O
-	O
J	O
-	O
Martha	B-pers
Holt	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Pool	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
,	O
12.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Higgins	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Warrel	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	O
B	O
,	O
Richard	O
Leeche	O
Inn	O
Hall	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Macmullen	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ashburn	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Graves	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Gunter	I-pers
.	O
Lydia	B-pers
Cane	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Wade	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Boyle	I-pers
,	O
severally	O
pleaded	O
their	O
Bellies	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
being	O
empannell	O
'd	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
first	O
to	O
be	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
Quick	O
;	O
the	O
Second	O
with	O
Quick	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Third	O
not	O
with	O
Child	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
sold	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
Penny-worth	O
.	O
TWO	O
very	O
good	O
new	O
Brick-houses	O
,	O
well	O
Tenanted	O
,	O
with	O
large	O
Gardens	O
,	O
Fish	O
ponds	O
and	O
other	O
Conveniences	O
thereto	O
belonging	O
,	O
Scituate	O
in	O
Holloway	O
next	O
High-gate	O
.	O
Enquire	O
at	O
the	O
Blue-Bodice	O
in	O
the	O
Long-walk	O
next	O
Christ's-Hospital	O
.	O
ALL	O
Melancholly	O
,	O
Hysterical	O
and	O
Hypocondriacal	O
Distempers	O
which	O
variously	O
affect	O
the	O
with	O
strange	O
Fears	O
and	O
dismal	O
Apprehensions	O
;	O
Faintings	O
and	O
Sinkings	O
of	O
the	O
Spirits	O
,	O
great	O
Hurries	O
,	O
Restlessness	O
and	O
Disquietment	O
(	O
little	O
understood	O
,	O
and	O
seldom	O
cured	O
by	O
any	O
common	O
Means	O
also	O
Pains	O
and	O
Giddiness	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
Risings	O
to	O
the	O
Throat	O
Sick	O
Fits	O
,	O
Tremblings	O
,	O
Oppressions	O
of	O
the	O
Heart	O
or	O
any	O
other	O
Disorders	O
caus	O
'd	O
by	O
Vapours	O
,	O
are	O
successfully	O
cured	O
(	O
with	O
God	O
Blessing	O
)	O
by	O
a	O
Physician	O
well	O
Experienc	O
'd	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
more	O
than	O
20	O
Years	O
Practice	O
in	O
those	O
deplorable	O
Cases	O
;	O
who	O
also	O
cured	O
all	O
kind	O
of	O
Fits	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
strange	O
and	O
violent	O
,	O
if	O
curable	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
informs	O
on	O
sight	O
of	O
their	O
Water	O
.	O
Now	O
living	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
the	O
Shears	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
Chambers-street	O
in	O
Goodman	O
's	O
Fields	O
the	O
Minories	O
;	O
where	O
those	O
that	O
have	O
Occasion	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
may	O
direct	O
their	O
Letters	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
shall	O
be	O
speedliy	O
Answer	O
'd	O
attended	O
on	O
,	O
if	O
desir'sd	O
.	O
Printed	O
by	O
S.	O
KEIMER	O
at	O
the	O
Printing-Press	O
in	O
Black-Fryars	O
,	O
for	O
J.	O
PHILLIPS	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Black	O
Bull	O
in	O
Cornhil	O
;	O
and	O
Sold	O
by	O
J.	O
BAKER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Black	O
Boy	O
in	O
Pater-Noster-Row	O
.	O
Where	O
Advertisements	O
are	O
taken	O
in	O
.	O
