TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
9th	O
,	O
10th	O
,	O
11th	O
,	O
and	O
13th	O
,	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
1714	O
is	O
the	O
First	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HUMFREYS	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
and	O
Bart	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Sir	O
Peter	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
of	O
the	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Eyres	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
Richardson	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
Jacob	B-pers
Brent	I-pers
James	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
John	B-pers
Cookson	I-pers
John	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Eland	I-pers
Jonas	B-pers
Wheatly	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Garrett	I-pers
William	B-pers
Clackson	I-pers
Nath	B-pers
Guillam	I-pers
David	B-pers
Rawbotham	I-pers
William	B-pers
Trindal	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
John	B-pers
Outing	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hargrave	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
John	B-pers
Meards	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Ingram	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Cutbert	I-pers
Daniel	B-pers
Croker	I-pers
Guy	B-pers
Stave	I-pers
William	B-pers
Ashman	I-pers
James	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Duck	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bolton	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
upon	O
2	O
several	O
indictments	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
Cocks	O
and	O
Hens	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
being	O
not	O
sufficient	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Perkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Catherine	I-place
Coleman	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
8	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Moss	I-pers
,	O
Dr.	O
of	O
Physick	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
with	O
whom	O
she	O
had	O
some	O
Acquaintance	O
formerly	O
)	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
asking	O
her	O
Advice	O
as	O
to	O
a	O
young	O
Woman	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
marry	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
invite	O
her	O
to	O
his	O
Wedding	O
;	O
and	O
coming	O
again	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
above	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
sent	O
the	O
Boy	O
with	O
a	O
Message	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
took	O
the	O
Spoons	O
.	O
She	O
coming	O
down	O
soon	O
after	O
miss	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
purs	O
'd	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
for	O
43	O
s.	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
accordingly	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
offer	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
his	O
Goods	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
only	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
35	O
s.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
and	I-pers
Mary	I-pers
Thurland	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Undershaft	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
132	O
Yards	O
of	O
Ruffel	O
,	O
and	O
400	O
Yards	O
of	O
Tamarine	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Sare	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Sharpeless	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
Warehouse	B-place
at	I-place
the	I-place
Kings-Arms	I-place
Inn	I-place
in	I-place
Leaden-hall-street	I-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
lodge	O
as	O
Man	O
and	O
Wife	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
adjoining	O
to	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
continued	O
five	O
Nights	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
not	O
having	O
occasion	O
to	O
be	O
open	O
'd	O
in	O
that	O
time	O
)	O
but	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
miss	O
'd	O
;	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
upon	O
search	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
a	O
Pawn-Broker	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
The	O
Man	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
at	O
Colchester	O
,	O
and	O
dealt	O
in	O
such	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
these	O
;	O
but	O
having	O
no	O
Proof	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
appearing	O
the	O
Woman	O
was	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susan	B-pers
Shelton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Stuff	O
Gowns	O
and	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
Hannah	B-pers
Gibbs	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
having	O
been	O
abroad	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
home	O
she	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
going	O
to	O
pawn	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
met	O
a	O
Woman	O
in	O
Moorfields	O
,	O
who	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
pawn'em	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
having	O
no	O
Proof	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Bowman	I-pers
and	O
Jane	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Catherine	I-place
Creechurch	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
12	O
Yards	O
of	O
Callico	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Mayhew	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
very	O
full	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
prisoners	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
with	O
another	O
Woman	O
,	O
to	O
look	O
upon	O
Muslins	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
did	O
buy	O
half	O
a	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
while	O
Bowman	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
give'em	O
to	O
White	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
them	O
under	O
the	O
Tail	O
of	O
her	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
his	O
Goods	O
again	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cotes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Stephen	I-place
Walbrook	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
14	O
Muffs	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Bellamy	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
with	O
something	O
in	O
her	O
Lap	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
pursu	O
'd	O
,	O
was	O
immediately	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
stealing	O
whereof	O
she	O
presently	O
confess	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
at	O
her	O
Tryal	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Hugh	B-pers
Oatly	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Fiander	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Christ-Church	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Humphry	B-pers
Bodman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
going	O
along	O
Newgate-street	B-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
Oatly	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
pretending	O
he	O
would	O
see	O
him	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
Way	O
home	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
by	O
the	O
Way	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Watch	O
and	O
Ring	O
.	O
Oatly	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
coming	O
over	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Rotherhith	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
Assistance	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
leading	O
him	O
down	O
Aldersgate-street	O
,	O
it	O
rain	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
got	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
promis	O
'd	O
to	O
gratify	O
'em	O
both	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
come	O
to	O
Queenhith	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
talking	O
of	O
their	O
Reward	O
,	O
he	O
quarrel	O
'd	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
accus	O
'd	O
them	O
of	O
robbing	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Landlord	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
they	O
drank	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecuter	O
was	O
very	O
drunk	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
promise	O
them	O
a	O
Reward	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Alexander	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Dowlas	O
Shirts	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Linen	O
,	O
from	O
Miriam	B-pers
Britt	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
one	O
Night	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
in	O
Expectation	O
of	O
an	O
Aunt	O
coming	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
that	O
Opportunity	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
which	O
,	O
being	O
taken	O
,	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
at	O
her	O
Trial	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Stone	O
Bottle	O
,	O
and	O
21	O
lib	O
.	O
of	O
Currans	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Westfield	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servants	O
being	O
very	O
busie	O
in	O
putting	O
up	O
Currans	O
and	O
Raisins	O
into	O
Bottles	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
West	O
Indies	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
that	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Fowls	I-pers
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Gammon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
Ironmonger-lane	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Fustian	O
Frock	O
and	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
3	O
Shirts	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Smedley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
sworn	O
,	O
That	O
Fowls	O
having	O
work	O
'd	O
some	O
time	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
(	O
a	O
Glazier	O
)	O
and	O
the	O
Shop	O
being	O
open	O
'd	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
miss	O
'd	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
suspected	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
some	O
Search	O
,	O
taken	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appear	O
'd	O
against	O
Gam-mon	O
,	O
only	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
after	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
Fowls	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
Gammon	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Stephen	B-pers
Mead	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Lewis	I-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
forging	O
and	O
publishing	O
a	O
Bill	O
of	O
Exchange	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
Hand	O
of	O
Derrick	B-pers
Van	I-pers
Slicker	I-pers
,	O
Merchant	O
of	O
Amsterdam	O
,	O
and	O
endeavouring	O
there	O
by	O
to	O
defraud	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Atwell	I-pers
(	O
a	O
Banker	O
)	O
of	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
200	O
l.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Atwell	O
's	O
Shop	O
pretending	O
to	O
be	O
acquainted	O
with	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Hart	O
of	O
Bristol	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
take	O
such	O
a	O
Bill	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
Money	O
when	O
received	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
consented	O
to	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Atwell	O
sent	O
the	O
Bill	O
to	O
Mess	O
.	O
Appleby	O
and	O
Dematrius	O
(	O
who	O
were	O
Correspondents	O
of	O
Van	O
Slicker	O
,	O
and	O
frequently	O
paid	O
his	O
Bills	O
,	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
pay	O
it	O
in	O
Honour	O
to	O
the	O
Drawer	O
;	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
something	O
inclin	O
'd	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
till	O
having	O
some	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
the	O
Bill	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
answering	O
it	O
was	O
he	O
was	O
again	O
question	O
'd	O
how	O
he	O
receiv	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
from	O
one	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
at	O
Cork	O
in	O
Ireland	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
it	O
was	O
directed	O
by	O
the	O
pretended	O
Drawer	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
him	O
indors	O
'd	O
;	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
also	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Atwell	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
counterfeit	O
Name	O
of	O
Lewis	O
Jackson	O
.	O
His	O
account	O
of	O
himself	O
and	O
the	O
Bill	O
appearing	O
doubtful	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
secur	O
'd	O
and	O
then	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
one	O
Hannam	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Fleet	O
,	O
who	O
employ	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
40	O
s.	O
for	O
his	O
Pains	O
.	O
He	O
made	O
a	O
very	O
frivolous	O
Defence	O
at	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Forgery	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Knapp	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bridget	I-place
alias	O
Brides	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
in	O
filing	O
and	O
diminishing	O
27	O
Guineas	O
,	O
taking	O
from	O
each	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Jackson	O
,	O
to	O
change	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
which	O
having	O
been	O
observed	O
to	O
do	O
at	O
several	O
other	O
Shops	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
stop	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Guinea	O
weigh	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
8	O
Grains	O
too	O
light	O
,	O
as	O
were	O
also	O
those	O
he	O
had	O
chang	O
'd	O
before	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
who	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
Custody	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
more	O
Guineas	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
denied	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
search	O
26	O
more	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Bosom	O
;	O
by	O
all	O
which	O
,	O
his	O
putting	O
,	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
counterfeit	O
,	O
was	O
very	O
plain	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
filing	O
not	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
dark	O
grey	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
l.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Grounds	O
of	O
George	B-pers
More	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Horse	O
was	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Grounds	O
at	O
Newark	B-place
upon	I-place
Trent	I-place
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	B-place
Greyhound-Ind	I-place
in	I-place
in	I-place
Smithfield	I-place
;	O
and	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
give	O
an	O
Account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Laurence	B-pers
Singleton	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Singleton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Noblet	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Ware	O
house	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Ives	I-pers
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
15	O
Foot	O
of	O
Wallnut-Tree-Plank	O
,	O
60	O
Foot	O
of	O
Wainscot	O
,	O
and	O
100	O
Foot	O
of	O
Deal	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
Noblet	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
and	O
store	O
was	O
an	O
Evidence	O
who	O
Swore	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
bring	O
said	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Board	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
(	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
half	O
a	O
Yard	O
long	O
)	O
and	O
burn	O
them	O
at	O
Singleton	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
which	O
not	O
being	O
thought	O
sufficient	O
Cause	O
for	O
an	O
Indictment	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Andrew	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
)	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Macolcos	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
instant	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
do	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
taken	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Edling	I-pers
(	O
an	O
Infant	O
)	O
with	O
intention	O
to	O
rob	O
on	O
the	O
2nd	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Child	O
coming	O
from	O
School	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
her	O
Arms	O
:	O
and	O
the	O
Child	O
crying	O
,	O
she	O
us	O
'd	O
it	O
very	O
roughly	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
Notice	O
of	O
by	O
some	O
Neighbours	O
and	O
the	O
she	O
set	O
the	O
Child	O
down	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
was	O
seiz	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Child	O
ran	O
home	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Gold	O
Chain	O
she	O
had	O
about	O
her	O
Neck	O
was	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
Loosen	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Child	O
up	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
Cart	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
carrying	O
it	O
towards	O
its	O
own	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
a	O
contrary	O
way	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Assault	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Hopgood	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
she	O
for	O
personating	O
and	O
he	O
for	O
counselling	O
and	O
perswading	O
her	O
to	O
personate	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
the	I-pers
Widow	I-pers
of	I-pers
Henry	I-pers
Car	I-pers
,	O
late	O
a	O
Mariner	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Salisbury-Prize	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
they	O
defrauded	O
George	B-pers
Veale	I-pers
of	O
the	O
sum	O
of	O
39	O
l.	O
14	O
s.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
very	O
plainly	O
proved	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Misdemeanor	O
.	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
conspiring	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	O
to	O
defraud	O
Abraham	B-pers
Campbel	I-pers
of	O
3	O
lib	O
.	O
2	O
oz	O
.	O
of	O
Human	O
Hair	O
,	O
Value	O
8	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
12th	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
Queen	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
William	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	O
being	O
a	O
Barber	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
buy	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
him	O
upon	O
Credit	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
his	O
Debtor	O
in	O
about	O
26	O
l.	O
before	O
,	O
he	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
trust	O
him	O
;	O
whereupon	O
Arnold	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
bring	O
his	O
Uncle	O
John	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	O
who	O
would	O
give	O
his	O
Word	O
for	O
the	O
Payment	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
having	O
heard	O
a	O
Character	O
of	O
John	O
Arnold	O
,	O
consented	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
Word	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
personated	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
Arnold	O
,	O
and	O
promis	O
'd	O
Payment	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
trusted	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
above-mentioned	O
.	O
The	O
Matter	O
was	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Misdemeanor	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Savil	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Tibbs	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Andrews	B-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Hughs	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
4	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
and	O
10	O
Plates	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
indictment	O
Savil	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
;	O
and	O
Tibbs	O
putting	O
himself	O
upon	O
his	O
Trial	O
,	O
one	O
Woodfield	O
,	O
an	O
Accomplice	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Cellar-Window	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
handed	O
them	O
out	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
Savil	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Graves	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Pratt	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Rebekah	B-pers
Whitrow	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Whitrow	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Day-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
hence	O
a	O
Silk	O
and	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Door	O
latch	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
home	O
about	O
3	O
,	O
found	O
it	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
gone	O
;	O
and	O
another	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
saw	O
Graves	O
lurking	O
about	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
knowing	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
ill	O
Person	O
,	O
Suspected	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
out	O
.	O
She	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Matter	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
where	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
were	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
At	O
their	O
Trials	O
neither	O
of	O
them	O
disown	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
lay	O
the	O
Blame	O
upon	O
one	O
another	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
all	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Kennedy	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Clarkson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
thence	O
2	O
Copper	O
Pots	O
,	O
a	O
Brass	O
Pot	O
,	O
12	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
afterwards	O
informed	O
by	O
one	O
Bonner	O
,	O
(	O
a	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Newgate	O
)	O
that	O
Mills	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
doing	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
apprehended	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
Kennedy	O
,	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Robery	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
Confession	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
other	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Kennedy	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stanmore	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
an	O
Ax	O
upon	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Collar-bone	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languish	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
witness	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
coming	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Door	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
an	O
Alehouse	B-place
in	I-place
Edgware	I-place
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
without	O
wounded	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
cut	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
broad	O
Ax	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
going	O
thereupon	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
asking	O
him	O
how	O
it	O
came	O
,	O
he	O
answered	O
If	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
miss	O
'd	O
my	O
Blow	O
,	O
I	O
'd	O
have	O
cut	O
of	O
his	O
Head	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
'd	O
have	O
died	O
a	O
more	O
honourable	O
Death	O
than	O
s	O
're	O
a	O
Scotchman	O
in	O
England	O
;	O
mine	O
is	O
a	O
Corporation	O
House	O
I	O
hang	O
,	O
draw	O
and	O
quarter	O
,	O
within	O
my	O
self	O
.	O
The	O
like	O
Word	O
were	O
sworn	O
to	O
by	O
another	O
Witness	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
none	O
swore	O
to	O
the	O
Wound	O
given	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
behalf	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
sworn	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
and	O
another	O
Man	O
,	O
being	O
drinking	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
let	O
them	O
have	O
any	O
more	O
till	O
they	O
had	O
paid	O
for	O
what	O
they	O
had	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
him	O
give	O
him	O
2s	O
.	O
saying	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
in	O
Truth	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
nothing	O
;	O
whereupon	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
happen	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
struck	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
throu	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ran	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
the	O
Ax	O
to	O
frighten	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
how	O
the	O
Wound	O
came	O
.	O
Others	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Wound	O
had	O
but	O
just	O
cut	O
the	O
skin	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
often	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
agreed	O
it	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
a	O
Guinea	O
.	O
And	O
two	O
Surgeons	O
,	O
who	O
viewed	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
swore	O
that	O
the	O
Wound	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
but	O
he	O
died	O
of	O
an	O
Ague	O
and	O
Fever	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
having	O
fully	O
consider	O
'd	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Hale	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
of	O
stealing	O
a	O
Table-Cloth	O
,	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Leman	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
work	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
suspected	O
,	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
15	O
lib	O
.	O
of	O
Feathers	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Clavering	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
she	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
who	O
lodg	O
'd	O
there	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
take	O
the	O
Feathers	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Bed	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
't	O
was	O
the	O
Witness	O
stole	O
the	O
Feathers	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
believ	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Isaac	B-pers
Dale	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Pot	O
,	O
Value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
drink	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
Pot	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Yard	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
was	O
stop	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
confess	O
'd	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
put	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
another	O
Man	O
carry	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
back	O
to	O
tell	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
which	O
not	O
being	O
believ	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Corbet	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Page	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
30	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Colestock	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
from	O
whence	O
they	O
were	O
stolen	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Proof	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stole'em	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lightfoot	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Whitechappel	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Nagg	B-place
's	I-place
Head	I-place
and	I-place
Woolpack	I-place
in	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
,	O
and	O
making	O
use	O
of	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Name	O
,	O
lodg	O
'd	O
there	O
a	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Coat	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
stopt	O
for	O
another	O
Robbery	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
selling	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
Monmouth-street	O
,	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Dowlas	O
Shirts	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Aloffe	I-pers
;	O
which	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
again	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Savil	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Tibbs	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Maurice	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
a	O
Brass	O
Porridge	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
Brass	O
Sawse-pans	O
,	O
val	O
10	O
s.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Savil	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
Confession	O
in	O
Newgate	O
when	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
a	O
Robbery	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
he	O
thought	O
to	O
make	O
himself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
Evidence	O
to	O
affect	O
Tibbs	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Savil	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
and	O
robbing	O
Thomas	B-pers
Trenoweth	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
over	O
the	O
Fields	B-place
to	I-place
Marybone	I-place
Park	I-place
,	O
at	O
five	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
Savil	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Lanthorn	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
light	O
him	O
along	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
a	O
while	O
,	O
one	O
Moses	B-pers
Whitefield	I-pers
(	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
struck	O
up	O
his	O
Heels	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
down	O
,	O
Tibbs	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
35	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Lancets	O
in	O
a	O
Box	O
.	O
They	O
neither	O
of	O
them	O
could	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
but	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
accuse	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
whereupon	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Field	I-pers
,	I-pers
and	I-pers
Mary	I-pers
his	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Hillendon	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
he	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
,	I-pers
the	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Gabriel	I-pers
Randal	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
House	O
25	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
25	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
as	O
an	O
Accessary	O
to	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
by	O
receiving	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
so	O
stoln	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Randal	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Pipe-maker	O
by	O
Trade	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
his	O
Journey-man	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
carry	O
out	O
some	O
Pipes	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
only	O
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
and	O
returning	O
again	O
in	O
about	O
2	O
Hours	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
String	O
of	O
the	O
Door-latch	O
out	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
sometime	O
before	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
in	O
;	O
which	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
going	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
his	O
Wife	O
lying	O
a-cross	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
with	O
her	O
Hands	O
and	O
Legs	O
tied	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Neighbours	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
who	O
found	O
a	O
Clout	O
thrust	O
down	O
her	O
Throat	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
tied	O
round	O
her	O
Head	O
before	O
her	O
Mouth	O
;	O
which	O
when	O
they	O
had	O
remov	O
'd	O
,	O
Blood	O
issued	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
discover	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
murder	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
about	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
his	O
Chest	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Hammer	O
lying	O
by	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
Work-shop	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
also	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Apron	O
bloody	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Randal	O
sending	O
him	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
what	O
had	O
pass	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
strict	O
search	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
found	O
at	O
last	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
Ship	O
bound	O
for	O
Virginia	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
searching	O
him	O
,	O
found	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Purse	O
was	O
also	O
taken	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
frequently	O
carried	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
.	O
He	O
deny	O
'd	O
his	O
Name	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
John	O
Gardener	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
his	O
Trial	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
while	O
John	O
Gardener	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
Murder	O
.	O
This	O
being	O
all	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Murder	O
and	O
Felony	O
;	O
but	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
being	O
accessary	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
of	O
her	O
Coverture	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Hoskins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Downs	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
80	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Stockins	O
,	O
40	O
Pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
Value	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
Shop	O
was	O
broke	O
by	O
boring	O
Holes	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
out	O
some	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Board	O
on	O
the	O
Side	O
of	O
his	O
Shop	O
next	O
a	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
thereby	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Goods	O
.	O
Another	O
Witness	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
searching	O
for	O
other	O
stolen	O
Goods	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Lodging	O
.	O
One	O
Chance	O
,	O
an	O
Accomplice	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
Chance	O
was	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
and	O
drew	O
him	O
in	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Burglary	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
Linen	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
5	O
l.	O
Mrs.	O
Smith	O
swore	O
,	O
Her	O
Shop	O
was	O
broke	O
by	O
boring	O
as	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
away	O
:	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
other	O
Evidence	O
but	O
Chance	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
concern	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Barrow	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Daintry	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
with	O
Intent	O
to	O
steal	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wynn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
9	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
from	O
Mary	B-pers
Chislet	I-pers
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
her	O
Ring	O
and	O
Money	O
were	O
in	O
her	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
a	O
Boy	O
)	O
being	O
her	O
Fellow-Servant	O
,	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
He	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Cornish	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Harley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
3	O
Perukes	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Hays	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
Value	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
Jane	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
going	O
up	O
stairs	O
in	O
her	O
Master	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Garret	O
,	O
and	O
crying	O
out	O
for	O
Help	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Precinct	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Katherine	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Wherry	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sculls	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Tilt	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
three	O
several	O
Persons	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
having	O
their	O
Goods	O
again	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Joscelin	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Haythorn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Weather-Sheep	O
,	O
value	O
of	O
26	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
Sheep	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Grounds	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Joscelin	O
being	O
in	O
Leadenhall-market	O
,	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
Carcass	O
,	O
was	O
suspected	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
presently	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
Haythorn	O
;	O
who	O
being	O
also	O
taken	O
,	O
discover	O
'd	O
where	O
the	O
Skin	O
was	O
hid	O
.	O
This	O
Proof	O
being	O
so	O
very	O
full	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Giles	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Firkin	O
of	O
Butter	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Slater	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
instant	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
back	O
Room	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
Firkin	O
and	O
go	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
pursuing	O
,	O
took	O
it	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Precinct	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Katherines	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Kettle	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Blount	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
Octobe	O
r	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
a	O
while	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
a	O
Crown	O
told	O
him	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
sold	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
Enquiry	O
at	O
that	O
place	O
,	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
erson	O
who	O
sold	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
from	O
a	O
Sailor	O
;	O
but	O
having	O
no	O
proof	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
nor	O
of	O
her	O
Reputation	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
Crowd	O
in	O
the	O
Church	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
of	O
the	O
Bishop	O
of	O
London	O
's	O
Confirming	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
searching	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
found	O
that	O
and	O
5	O
more	O
in	O
his	O
Breeches	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Drew	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
27	O
Yards	O
of	O
Stuff	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Bonivier	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
sworn	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
her	O
left	O
Arm	O
and	O
carry	O
it	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
calling	O
out	O
for	O
Help	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
it	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Stuff	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
she	O
only	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Shop-door	O
to	O
look	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
intend	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
false	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Awdry	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Awdry	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
he	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
6	O
Firkins	O
of	O
Butter	O
,	O
300	O
Weight	O
of	O
Cheese	O
,	O
and	O
30	O
lib	O
.	O
of	O
Bacon	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
Goods	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stoln	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Fisher	O
swore	O
his	O
Shop	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Goods	O
gone	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
John	O
Awdry	O
being	O
in	O
Custody	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Robbery	O
and	O
Burglary	O
;	O
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Awdry	I-pers
swore	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
his	O
Brother	O
bring	O
some	O
Firkins	O
of	O
Butter	O
to	O
his	O
Mother	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
turn	O
'd	O
out	O
again	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
kill	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
them	O
in	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
who	O
fix	O
'd	O
strong	O
Circumstances	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
that	O
his	O
Mother	O
knew	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stoln	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Banks	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Chelsea	B-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
of	O
the	O
Breadth	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
5	O
Inches	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languish	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
25th	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Trial	O
,	O
That	O
some	O
words	O
happening	O
between	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
(	O
being	O
both	O
Pensioners	O
of	O
Chelsea	O
College	O
)	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
went	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
a	O
Sword	O
under	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
threatned	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
A	O
Witness	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
them	O
fight	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
parted	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
;	O
but	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
they	O
put	O
up	O
their	O
Swords	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
both	O
together	O
into	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
dress	O
'd	O
and	O
drank	O
,	O
and	O
smoak	O
'd	O
a	O
Pipe	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
with	O
much	O
Difficulty	O
perswaded	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
his	O
Chamber	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
Bed	O
all	O
Night	O
.	O
Before	O
he	O
died	O
he	O
forgave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
Heat	O
of	O
Passion	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Circumstances	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Man-Slaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Trunk	O
with	O
several	O
Clothes	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Pullen	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
.	O
Instant	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
these	O
were	O
three	O
Men	O
seen	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
(	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
describ	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
)	O
and	O
afterwards	O
come	O
out	O
again	O
with	O
a	O
Trunk	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
pursu	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
were	O
overtaken	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
dropping	O
a	O
Bundle	O
,	O
wherein	O
were	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seiz	O
'd	O
.	O
He	O
brought	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
another	O
Place	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
not	O
being	O
satisfactory	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Coxhead	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Shadwell	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Walter	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
a	O
Canvas	O
Bag	O
and	O
9	O
lib	O
.	O
of	O
Hops	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Proof	O
being	O
insufficient	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Old	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Body	O
near	O
the	O
Pap	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Breadth	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
18	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
being	O
in	O
Company	O
together	O
,	O
fell	O
into	O
Talk	O
about	O
Bravery	O
;	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
affirming	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
any	O
Man	O
who	O
at	O
first	O
entering	O
upon	O
Action	O
,	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
Coldness	O
or	O
Apprehension	O
;	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
a	O
brave	O
Man	O
was	O
never	O
capable	O
of	O
Apprehension	O
or	O
Fear	O
.	O
That	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
argu	O
'd	O
this	O
Matter	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
seeming	O
Reservedness	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
hot	O
Words	O
;	O
And	O
that	O
after	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Tavern	O
,	O
the	O
Decceas	O
'd	O
not	O
going	O
homewards	O
,	O
but	O
turning	O
down	O
York	O
Buildings	O
,	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
Company	O
with'em	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
Walk	O
at	O
the	O
Water-side	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
perswade	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
vain	O
,	O
yet	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
told	O
him	O
upon	O
his	O
Word	O
and	O
Honour	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Design	O
to	O
quarrel	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
left	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
back	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
going	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
Heat	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
prevented	O
from	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
Passion	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
hear	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
small	O
Time	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Swords	O
clash	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
in	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
kill	O
'd	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
who	O
swore	O
they	O
heard	O
the	O
Swords	O
clash	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
fall	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
positive	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
brought	O
out	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pull	O
his	O
Sword	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Body	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
plain	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
kill	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Malice	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Michael	B-pers
Plunket	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Feather-Bed	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Furniture	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
deliver	O
'd	O
the	O
Bed	O
to	O
another	O
Person	O
to	O
carry	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
Said	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
sent	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
swore	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
his	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
run	O
away	O
from	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
regarded	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Bellingham	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Holland	O
and	O
2	O
Doulas	O
Shirts	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Staples	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
instant	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
Sworn	O
that	O
the	O
Shirts	O
were	O
stolen	O
from	O
the	O
Hedge	O
where	O
they	O
hung	O
a	O
drying	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
Pursuit	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
them	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
whereupon	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cane	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Precinct	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Katherine	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
30	O
Yards	O
of	O
Fustian	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Hammon	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
Evidence	O
who	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
come	O
out	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
seiz	O
'd	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Apron	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
from	O
Mary	B-pers
Burges	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
;	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
not	O
satisfactory	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
having	O
several	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Tayler	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
were	O
all	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
,	O
putting	O
in	O
bodily	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
Thomas	B-pers
Edward	I-pers
Frederick	I-pers
Slade	I-pers
of	O
6	O
s	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
Novembe	O
r	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
went	O
to	O
Gilbert	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
drank	O
Wine	O
and	O
Brandy	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
fetch	O
'd	O
the	O
other	O
three	O
Women	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
staid	O
there	O
a	O
while	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
young	O
Men	O
who	O
were	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
Gilbert	O
observing	O
him	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
stopt	O
him	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
till	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
what	O
she	O
demanded	O
to	O
her	O
self	O
and	O
the	O
Women	O
;	O
and	O
Bailey	O
threaten	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
comply	O
;	O
nor	O
could	O
he	O
get	O
away	O
till	O
a	O
Constable	O
came	O
who	O
was	O
sent	O
by	O
his	O
2	O
Companions	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
found	O
them	O
all	O
guilty	O
of	O
Petty-Larceny	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Price	I-pers
and	O
Martha	B-pers
Hare	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
as	O
Accessaries	O
to	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Graves	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Prat	I-pers
and	O
Rebekah	O
Whitrow	O
,	O
in	O
receiving	O
and	O
buying	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Whitrow	I-pers
,	O
by	O
them	O
stoln	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
insufficient	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hubbub	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Rod	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
several	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Linnen	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
instant	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
pretty	O
plain	O
against	O
Hubbub	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
so	O
against	O
Hall	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jasper	B-pers
Du	I-pers
Lac	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Canby	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Spicer	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Spicer	O
swore	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
Wig	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
offer	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
Sale	O
.	O
But	O
he	O
proving	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
another	O
Person	O
who	O
absconds	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Pistols	O
,	O
and	O
30	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Katharine	B-pers
Whitfield	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2nd	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
intrusted	O
with	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
Closet	O
where	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
were	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
up	O
by	O
Chance	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
to	O
New	O
Prison	O
,	O
his	O
Master	O
had	O
notice	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
cousels	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
at	O
his	O
Trial	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Duncan	I-pers
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Evet	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Hackney	B-place
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
Duncan	O
for	O
stealing	O
and	O
Evet	O
for	O
receiving	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
Value	O
34	O
s.	O
The	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Bever	I-pers
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Duncan	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
hir	O
'd	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bever	O
and	O
the	O
Candlestick	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
Means	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
thereupon	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
against	O
Evet	O
that	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
Sale	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
he	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Cord	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
he	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
for	O
receiving	O
19	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Foreign	O
Gold	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
that	O
Cord	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
on	O
Shipboard	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
satisfactory	O
Evidence	O
that	O
Thomas	O
knew	O
they	O
were	O
stolen	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Loftus	I-pers
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Elwood	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
he	O
as	O
Principal	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
as	O
Accessary	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Drugget	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2nd	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
that	O
Loftus	O
stole	O
the	O
Clothes	O
from	O
on	O
Ship-board	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
Elwood	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
saying	O
,	O
and	O
Loftus	O
acknowledging	O
that	O
he	O
deliver	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
get	O
them	O
mended	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Adamson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
;	O
15	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
Value	O
4	O
l.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
Stephen	B-pers
Hemings	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
his	O
Servant	O
was	O
entrusted	O
with	O
his	O
Linnen	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
several	O
Times	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
was	O
also	O
depos	O
'd	O
by	O
his	O
Daughter	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Things	O
from	O
her	O
Master	O
's	O
Daughter	O
to	O
pawn	O
for	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
maliciously	O
prosecuted	O
;	O
however	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Milner	B-pers
Wilder	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwel	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Haggard	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
abroad	O
,	O
broke	O
her	O
Lodging	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
She	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
at	O
her	O
Trial	O
,	O
whereupon	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Manley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchre	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
7	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Roger	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
an	O
the	O
8th	O
instant	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Gilt	O
Spoon	O
,	O
Value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Gifford	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Gifford	O
's	O
Daughter	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
laid	O
the	O
Spoon	O
upon	O
a	O
Plate	O
in	O
a	O
low	O
Room	O
;	O
and	O
while	O
she	O
turn	O
'd	O
her	O
Back	O
she	O
heard	O
something	O
click	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
follow	O
'd	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
Help	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Spoon	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
no	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stains	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
White-chappel	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Hood	O
and	O
Scarf	O
,	O
and	O
9	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Everet	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
,	O
one	O
for	O
robbing	O
her	O
Lodging	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
another	O
Room	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
stolen	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
taken	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
whereupon	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Matth.ew	B-pers
Read	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
White-chappel	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Drugget	O
Coat	O
,	O
Wastcoat	O
and	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
47	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Southin	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
and	O
Money	O
were	O
stolen	O
from	O
on	O
Ship	O
board	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
selling	O
the	O
Coat	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Ship	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Arthur	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Hackney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Flaxen	O
Sheet	O
Value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Pope	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Sheet	O
was	O
hanging	O
on	O
a	O
Hedge	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Pope	O
's	O
Garden	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
seen	O
to	O
come	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
was	O
pursu	O
'd	O
and	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Sheet	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
drop	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
This	O
being	O
a	O
plain	O
Proof	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Franklin	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
Hughs	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
instant	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
against	O
Hall	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
but	O
Franklin	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Atwood	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
and	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Bed	O
about	O
8	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
a-sleep	O
,	O
was	O
wak	O
'd	O
and	O
heard	O
some	O
body	O
in	O
his	O
Room	O
;	O
whereupon	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
Garret	O
,	O
having	O
remov	O
'd	O
several	O
things	O
with	O
Intention	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Felony	O
was	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Burglary	O
not	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Linen	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Hare	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
being	O
Irroning	O
near	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
threw	O
up	O
the	O
Sash	O
,	O
thrust	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
Snatch	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
pursu	O
'd	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Tibbs	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Giles	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Briggs	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-times	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
20	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
safe	O
over	O
night	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Cellar-Window	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
gone	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
who	O
was	O
an	O
Accomplice	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
Tibbs	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
handed	O
out	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
Stevens	O
was	O
by	O
and	O
helped	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
away	O
;	O
whereupon	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Savil	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Tibbs	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Nath	B-pers
Windsor	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
a	O
Brass	O
Kettle	O
,	O
a	O
Sawce-pan	O
,	O
and	O
7	O
lib	O
.	O
of	O
Cheese	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
Savil	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
;	O
but	O
Tibbs	O
and	O
Windsor	O
putting	O
themselves	O
upon	O
their	O
Trial	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Burglary	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Friend	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
,	O
putting	O
in	O
bodily	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Pridley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Loaf	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
desirous	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
Silver	O
Groat	O
in	O
change	O
;	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Daughter	O
saying	O
she	O
had	O
never	O
a	O
one	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
importunate	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
look	O
among	O
her	O
Money	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
did	O
pull	O
out	O
her	O
Money	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
sooner	O
done	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
thrust	O
her	O
Hand	O
into	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
it	O
all	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
young	O
Woman	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
finding	O
the	O
Matter	O
plain	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Hoskins	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
190	O
Yards	O
of	O
Spanish	O
Poplin	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Hans	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cambrick	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
,	O
2	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Chace	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
instant	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Chace	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Church	I-place
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Hand	O
moving	O
from	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
seized	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Norris	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
7	O
iron-hoop	O
'd	O
Pails	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mary	I-pers
on	O
the	O
11th	O
instant	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
Hall	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
and	O
take	O
out	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
deliver	O
part	O
of	O
'em	O
to	O
Norris	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
watch	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
Goods	O
were	O
both	O
taken	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Spell	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
50	O
oz	O
.	O
of	O
Grain	O
Silver	O
from	O
James	B-pers
Grammar	I-pers
:	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Lardell	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Rothbon	I-pers
the	O
5th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Prosecution	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
8	O
Thomas	B-pers
Thurland	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Savil	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Tibbs	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Field	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Awdrey	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
29.	O
Robert	B-pers
Perkins	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Bowman	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cotes	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Graves	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Pratt	I-pers
,	O
Rebekah	B-pers
Whitrow	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Josceline	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Loftus	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Haythorn	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
alias	O
Drew	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Banks	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wills	I-pers
,	O
Michael	B-pers
Plunket	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cane	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hubbub	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Cord	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Adamson	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Read	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Friend	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Norris	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whip	O
'd	O
26.	O
Susan	B-pers
Sheldon	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Alexander	I-pers
,	O
S	O
-	O
D	O
-	O
John	B-pers
Fowle	I-pers
,	O
Andrew	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Catherine	B-pers
Hale	I-pers
;	O
Isaac	B-pers
Dale	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Lightfoot	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wynn	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Hays	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Giles	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Bellingham	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
,	O
Martha	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Duncan	I-pers
,	O
Milner	B-pers
Wilder	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stains	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
Arthur	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Hans	I-pers
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Mead	I-pers
fin	O
'd	O
100	O
l.	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
3	O
times	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
fin	O
'd	O
6	O
s.	O
8	O
d.	O
John	B-pers
James	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Hopwood	I-pers
,	O
to	O
stand	O
3	O
times	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
.	O
C	O
-	O
L	O
-	O
fin	O
'd	O
20	O
l.	O
For	O
the	O
Good	O
of	O
the	O
Publick	O
.	O
Whereas	O
several	O
goodwomen	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
that	O
sex	O
in	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
have	O
contracted	O
an	O
evil	O
Habit	O
of	O
body	O
,	O
wherein	O
the	O
vicious	O
Humours	O
at	O
first	O
dispersed	O
through	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
coming	O
at	O
length	O
to	O
be	O
lodged	O
in	O
one	O
part	O
or	O
another	O
,	O
for	O
Causes	O
too	O
long	O
here	O
to	O
be	O
mentioned	O
,	O
are	O
thrown	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Womb	O
,	O
occasioning	O
a	O
dangerous	O
Weakness	O
in	O
that	O
Part	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
neglected	O
at	O
last	O
turns	O
cancerous	O
,	O
and	O
often	O
proves	O
fatal	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
to	O
acquaint	O
all	O
such	O
as	O
may	O
have	O
Occasion	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
speedy	O
Relief	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
had	O
,	O
from	O
an	O
experienced	O
Midwife	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Queens-Arms	O
,	O
A	O
Goldsmith	O
's	O
near	O
Exeter-Exchange	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
who	O
perform	O
'd	O
a	O
Care	O
upon	O
a	O
Lady	O
at	O
the	O
Bath	O
,	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
given	O
over	O
by	O
Physicians	O
and	O
since	O
has	O
bred	O
several	O
Gentlewomen	O
and	O
others	O
in	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
Suburbs	O
of	O
London	O
.	O
I	O
Do	O
publickly	O
declare	O
,	O
That	O
my	O
Child	O
having	O
for	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
been	O
reduc	O
'd	O
to	O
extreme	O
Sufferings	O
and	O
Danger	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
hard	O
Breeding	O
of	O
Teeth	O
was	O
(	O
by	O
good	O
Providence	O
)	O
immediately	O
reliev	O
'd	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Use	O
of	O
a	O
Remedy	O
Trial	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Perronet	O
,	O
Surgeon	O
;	O
Witness	O
my	O
Hand	O
,	O
Mar	O
.	O
Adams	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
Eating	O
House	O
in	O
Shoe-lane	O
,	O
Within	O
one	O
door	O
of	O
Fleetstreet	O
.	O
This	O
Remedy	O
is	O
sold	O
for	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
per	O
Vial	O
,	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alcraft	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Blue-Coat	O
Boy	O
against	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
;	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Author	O
Mr.	O
Perronet	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Surgeons-Arms	O
against	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
Dorset-street	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
;	O
whose	O
Wife	O
effectually	O
cures	O
all	O
kinds	O
of	O
Ruptures	O
in	O
young	O
Children	O
.	O
Note	O
,	O
At	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Places	O
may	O
also	O
be	O
had	O
Sire	O
Kenelm	O
Digby	O
's	O
famous	O
Apoplectick	O
Snuff	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Remedy	O
for	O
all	O
Pains	O
,	O
Dizziness	O
,	O
Vapours	O
,	O
Sleapiness	O
,	O
and	O
Imposthumes	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
;	O
cures	O
Rhuem	O
upon	O
the	O
Eyes	O
;	O
Dimness	O
of	O
Sight	O
,	O
and	O
Thickness	O
of	O
Hearing	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
per	O
Paper	O
.	O
