TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
'S	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
7th	O
,	O
8th	O
,	O
and	O
9th	O
,	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
1715	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Second	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEfore	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HUMFREYS	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
and	O
Bart	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
;	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Mosely	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Devis	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cooke	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Uphold	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hymore	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Hales	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Ballard	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Blye	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hartshorn	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wyton	I-pers
,	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Dix	I-pers
,	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Ravenor	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Arnor	I-pers
,	O
Marmaduke	B-pers
Bramley	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Ashworth	I-pers
.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Magdalen	I-place
New-Fish	I-place
street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
145	O
Yards	O
of	O
Silk	O
and	O
Worsted	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Thorpe	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
Bowden	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
some	O
Buckram	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
pleasing	O
,	O
Bowden	O
search	O
'd	O
for	O
more	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
put	O
the	O
Lace	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
also	O
swore	O
to	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
hitch	O
'd	O
upon	O
his	O
Buttons	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
his	O
carrying	O
it	O
away	O
;	O
which	O
not	O
being	O
satisfactory	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
Coat	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Hat	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Cockley	I-pers
:	O
and	O
a	O
few	O
other	O
odd	O
Things	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Katharine	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
very	O
evident	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
her	O
Lap	O
bundled	O
up	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
carry	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
detected	O
,	O
she	O
dropt	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
but	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
behalf	O
;	O
and	O
therefore	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Nicholls	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Undershaft	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Long	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Tomms	I-pers
swore	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
wanting	O
a	O
Lodging	O
,	O
she	O
having	O
a	O
Room	O
to	O
lett	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
been	O
up	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
,	O
coming	O
down	O
again	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
Chamber	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
Story	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Wig	O
;	O
but	O
going	O
down	O
the	O
last	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
it	O
was	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Tomms	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
Knots	O
appearing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Basket	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
challeng	O
'd	O
she	O
threw	O
the	O
Wig	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Now	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
of	O
yours	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
coming	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
the	O
Wig	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
Basket	O
and	O
therefore	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
and	O
Robbing	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Boy	O
about	O
5	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
stuff	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
lac	O
'd	O
Hat	O
value	O
2	O
s	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Evidence	O
was	O
the	O
Maid	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
,	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Sister	O
were	O
together	O
in	O
Moorfields	O
drying	O
Clothes	O
,	O
but	O
wanting	O
a	O
Line	O
,	O
she	O
sent	O
the	O
Girl	O
home	O
for	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
return	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
miss	O
'd	O
her	O
Brother	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
brought	O
soon	O
after	O
by	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
without	O
his	O
Coat	O
and	O
Hat	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Boy	O
said	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
by	O
a	O
Girl	O
;	O
whom	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
after	O
in	O
Long-Alley	O
,	O
where	O
his	O
Mother	O
(	O
having	O
been	O
inform	O
'd	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Character	O
)	O
was	O
searching	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
knew	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
accus	O
'd	O
her	O
of	O
the	O
Charge	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
The	O
Mother	O
and	O
Sister	O
's	O
Evidence	O
agreed	O
with	O
what	O
has	O
been	O
already	O
depos	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
before	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Abney	I-pers
.	O
She	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Rebecca	B-pers
David	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Wild	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
David	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Wild	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Catharine	I-place
Creed-Church	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Sampson	I-pers
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
a	O
Pearl	O
Necklace	O
,	O
a	O
Diamond	O
Anchor	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
1200	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Eleanor	O
Sampson	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
Several	O
Evidences	O
appear	O
'd	O
in	O
behalf	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
appearing	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
some	O
malicious	O
Grudges	O
between	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
who	O
made	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
and	O
at	O
their	O
Request	O
,	O
were	O
order	O
'd	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
their	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Twifort	B-pers
Twyford	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
,	O
stealing	O
several	O
pair	O
of	O
Yarn	O
Stockings	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
val	O
.	O
of	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Tough	I-pers
.	O
An	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
Stockings	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Grate	O
upon	O
the	O
Stall	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
informing	O
Tough	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
.	O
She	O
saying	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Bolton	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
as	O
Rioters	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
and	O
Wounding	O
Thomas	B-pers
Morton	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
a	O
great	O
Mob	O
came	O
into	O
Basing-hall	B-place
street	I-place
about	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
hollowing	O
,	O
and	O
breaking	O
the	O
Windows	O
that	O
were	O
illuminated	O
,	O
and	O
committing	O
other	O
Disorders	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Morton	O
went	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
peaceable	O
and	O
quiet	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
good	O
Words	O
;	O
whereupon	O
they	O
fell	O
upon	O
him	O
and	O
abus	O
'd	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
barbarous	O
Manner	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Blow	O
upon	O
the	O
Forehead	O
,	O
which	O
laid	O
it	O
open	O
to	O
the	O
Skull	O
.	O
Freeman	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
this	O
Mob	O
,	O
and	O
hollowed	O
;	O
and	O
Page	O
,	O
that	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Constable	O
's	O
Blood	O
was	O
upon	O
his	O
Clothes	O
;	O
but	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Post-house	O
and	O
fell	O
into	O
the	O
Mob	O
by	O
Chance	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
;	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Dish	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Graves	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
An	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
in	O
and	O
a	O
Man	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
they	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
Time	O
the	O
Woman	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
enquired	O
for	O
Ball	O
Alley	O
,	O
in	O
Gravel-Lane	O
,	O
(	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
such	O
Place	O
)	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
sometime	O
after	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Man	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
which	O
caus	O
'd	O
Suspicion	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Maid	O
looking	O
thro	O
'	O
a	O
Hole	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Woman	O
was	O
alone	O
,	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
some	O
Pewter	O
off	O
the	O
Shelf	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
her	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
cover	O
'd	O
all	O
with	O
her	O
Riding-hood	O
,	O
which	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
challeng	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
slipt	O
from	O
her	O
upon	O
the	O
Bench	O
she	O
sat	O
on	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
did	O
take	O
down	O
a	O
Plate	O
,	O
admiring	O
it	O
's	O
Brightness	O
,	O
and	O
desiring	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
the	O
Letter	O
X	O
was	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
having	O
heard	O
that	O
those	O
Plates	O
which	O
have	O
that	O
Mark	O
are	O
made	O
of	O
the	O
best	O
Pewter	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
intend	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
left	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
to	O
consider	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
possible	O
to	O
disengage	O
her	O
self	O
so	O
easily	O
from	O
it	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
that	O
Care	O
to	O
hide	O
it	O
which	O
was	O
sworn	O
against	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
brought	O
some	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
:	O
But	O
one	O
Evidence	O
deposing	O
that	O
the	O
Man	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
was	O
some	O
Minutes	O
with	O
her	O
after	O
they	O
found	O
themselves	O
discover	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Hammond	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.Giles	B-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
some	O
Holland	O
Shifts	O
,	O
Aprons	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Linnen	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Linnen	O
hung	O
up	O
in	O
his	O
Yard	O
to	O
dry	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Clothes	O
off	O
the	O
Lines	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
chancing	O
to	O
break	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Onion	O
,	O
the	O
Washer-Woman	O
,	O
swore	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
same	O
she	O
had	O
hung	O
upon	O
the	O
Line	O
;	O
and	O
another	O
Evidence	O
saw	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
who	O
saying	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
Boy	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Frasier	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Todd	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stanwell	I-pers
,	O
(	O
together	O
with	O
Isaac	B-pers
Rag	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
Checques	O
,	O
Hollands	O
,	O
Gawzes	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
8	O
l.	O
odd	O
Money	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Stanwell	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
being	O
inform	O
'd	O
where	O
some	O
Persons	O
were	O
that	O
she	O
suspected	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
an	O
Officer	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
secure	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
,	O
the	O
Beadle	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
Isaac	O
Rag	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Frasier	O
took	O
a	O
Pistol	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
held	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Beadle	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
he	O
would	O
shoot	O
him	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Beadle	O
struck	O
the	O
Pistol	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
Isaac	O
Ragg	O
got	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Beadle	O
swore	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Purpose	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
more	O
aided	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Frasier	O
in	O
the	O
Rescue	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
other	O
Evidences	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
plain	O
that	O
Todd	O
was	O
in	O
Frasier	O
's	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
an	O
Apron	O
on	O
which	O
was	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Goods	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
Todd	O
was	O
heard	O
to	O
say	O
by	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
known	O
he	O
would	O
discover	O
'em	O
when	O
he	O
stood	O
by	O
at	O
the	O
Skittle	O
Place	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
stick	O
a	O
Pinn	O
in	O
his	O
Wind	O
Pipe	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
swore	O
a	O
great	O
Oath	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
her	O
Company	O
had	O
been	O
rul	O
'd	O
by	O
her	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
never	O
been	O
discover	O
'd	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
other	O
Circumstances	O
to	O
the	O
Disadvantage	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
;	O
who	O
made	O
a	O
very	O
incredible	O
Defence	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
speak	O
in	O
their	O
Behalf	O
confronting	O
their	O
own	O
Evidence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
Todd	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
;	O
but	O
Frasier	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
this	O
Robbery	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Alexander	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Mullins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anne	I-place
,	I-place
Black	I-place
Fryars	I-place
,	O
Labourers	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
38	O
Yards	O
of	O
Silk	O
Camblet	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mess	B-pers
.	I-pers
Coleman	I-pers
and	I-pers
Clay	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Hen	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Parish	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
Murray	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
some	O
Camblet	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
he	O
saw	O
another	O
Piece	O
of	O
blue	O
Camblet	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
agreeing	O
about	O
the	O
Price	O
,	O
he	O
bid	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
take	O
the	O
Camblet	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Paul	O
's	O
Head	O
Ale-house	O
,	O
where	O
was	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
that	O
would	O
pay	O
for	O
as	O
much	O
of	O
it	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
agree	O
for	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
Mullins	O
,	O
he	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
like	O
the	O
great	O
Piece	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
the	O
Servant	O
carry	O
home	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
send	O
his	O
Master	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
Money	O
;	O
as	O
accordingly	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Coleman	O
came	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
Murray	O
being	O
gone	O
before	O
pretending	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
Taylor	O
)	O
was	O
gone	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
Mr.	O
Coleman	O
went	O
immediately	O
to	O
the	O
Water-side	O
,	O
and	O
enquir	O
'd	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
learnt	O
of	O
a	O
Waterman	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
Boat	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
with	O
his	O
Servant	O
took	O
another	O
to	O
pursue	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Waterman	O
coming	O
back	O
:	O
who	O
,	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
where	O
he	O
landed	O
his	O
Passenger	O
,	O
said	O
at	O
the	O
Horse	O
Ferry	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
White	O
Heart	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
Information	O
they	O
landed	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
search	O
was	O
made	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
Mullins	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
secur	O
'd	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Evidence	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
White	O
Heart	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
Murray	O
was	O
above	O
Stairs	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
wherein	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
lock	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
open	O
'd	O
,	O
found	O
Murray	O
shut	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Closer	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
under	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
without	O
the	O
Mark	O
,	O
which	O
Murray	O
at	O
last	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Murray	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
He	O
thought	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
paid	O
for	O
;	O
And	O
Mullins	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
't	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
fright	O
;	O
for	O
seeing	O
two	O
Bailiffs	O
almost	O
at	O
the	O
Paul	O
's	O
Head	O
Door	O
,	O
he	O
thought	O
they	O
wanted	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
him	O
slip	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
his	O
hast	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Burnet	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Pollocks	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Mitchell	I-pers
,	O
were	O
both	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
in	O
taking	O
up	O
a	O
false	O
Letter	O
of	O
Administration	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
erasing	O
and	O
altering	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Pollocks	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
administer	O
to	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Jonas	B-pers
Pollocks	I-pers
(	O
who	O
she	O
said	O
was	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
that	O
died	O
on	O
Board	O
the	O
Mary	O
Gally	O
Man	O
of	O
War	O
)	O
and	O
accordingly	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
Letter	O
of	O
Administration	O
in	O
that	O
Name	O
,	O
his	O
true	O
Name	O
being	O
James	O
,	O
and	O
altering	O
it	O
to	O
James	O
afterwards	O
,	O
to	O
enable	O
one	O
Chapman	O
by	O
Letters	O
of	O
Attorney	O
to	O
receive	O
Money	O
,	O
due	O
(	O
for	O
the	O
Services	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Pollocks	I-pers
,	O
and	O
his	O
Servant	O
on	O
Board	O
the	O
said	O
Ship	O
)	O
by	O
proper	O
Powers	O
,	O
to	O
another	O
.	O
An	O
Attorney	O
swore	O
that	O
Pollocks	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
Letters	O
of	O
Attorney	O
drawn	O
up	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
accordingly	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
received	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Chapman	O
.	O
'T	O
was	O
also	O
prov	O
'd	O
Brown	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
eras	O
'd	O
the	O
Name	O
Jonas	O
and	O
put	O
in	O
James	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
pillory	O
'd	O
if	O
he	O
should	O
ever	O
be	O
discover	O
'd	O
.	O
They	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cotton	I-pers
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Labourers	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
yet	O
unknown	O
,	O
did	O
Assault	O
in	O
a	O
riotous	O
and	O
tumultuous	O
Manner	O
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
and	O
several	O
others	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
The	O
Council	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Charge	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
the	O
following	O
Evidence	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
Night	O
aforesaid	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Fountain	B-place
Tavern	I-place
in	I-place
Stocks	I-place
market	I-place
;	O
that	O
a	O
Bonfire	O
being	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
he	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
more	O
Gentlemen	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
to	O
drink	O
King	O
George	O
's	O
Health	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
Mob	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
abus	O
'd	O
several	O
that	O
drank	O
it	O
;	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
Ormond	O
,	O
High	O
Church	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
and	O
nam	O
'd	O
some	O
particular	O
Injuries	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
One	O
Gentleman	O
had	O
his	O
Jaw-Bone	O
broke	O
,	O
another	O
had	O
his	O
Arm	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
receiv	O
'd	O
a	O
very	O
desperate	O
Wound	O
in	O
his	O
Head	O
;	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
other	O
unsufferable	O
Affronts	O
and	O
Abuses	O
which	O
he	O
thought	O
too	O
tedious	O
to	O
mention	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Bell	O
's	O
Hand	O
had	O
receiv	O
'd	O
a	O
great	O
Contusion	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
bloody	O
.	O
Another	O
depos	O
'd	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
same	O
Cry	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
hiss	O
'd	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Health	O
,	O
threw	O
Firebrands	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
almost	O
murder	O
'd	O
several	O
who	O
were	O
about	O
the	O
Bonfire	O
.	O
One	O
Bucknal	O
depos	O
'd	O
he	O
took	O
Charles	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
out	O
of	O
the	O
Mob	O
with	O
a	O
Stick	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
Lanthorn	O
which	O
hung	O
over	O
the	O
Tavern	O
Door	O
was	O
broke	O
to	O
Pieces	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Rogers	O
the	O
Constable	O
also	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
being	O
at	O
the	O
Bonfire	O
to	O
keep	O
Peace	O
and	O
Order	O
,	O
a	O
Man	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
have	O
a	O
Care	O
of	O
your	O
selves	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
are	O
some	O
here	O
,	O
will	O
be	O
about	O
your	O
House	O
by	O
and	O
by	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
he	O
went	O
home	O
to	O
put	O
on	O
his	O
Cap	O
and	O
Gown	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
force	O
done	O
but	O
down	O
came	O
the	O
Mob	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
first	O
Man	O
he	O
laid	O
his	O
Hand	O
on	O
that	O
was	O
among	O
them	O
,	O
was	O
Cotton	O
;	O
(	O
who	O
had	O
a	O
Pole	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
a	O
Foot	O
longer	O
than	O
his	O
own	O
Staff	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
rough	O
and	O
shagged	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
,	O
fit	O
for	O
desperate	O
Attempts	O
)	O
hollowing	O
and	O
crying	O
out	O
High	O
Church	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
secur	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
what	O
Hast	O
he	O
could	O
to	O
the	O
R.	O
Exchange	O
,	O
to	O
desire	O
the	O
commanding	O
Officer	O
to	O
assist	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Detachment	O
of	O
the	O
Train	O
'd	O
Bands	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Atkins	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
being	O
at	O
the	O
Place	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
and	O
drinking	O
King	O
George	O
's	O
Health	O
,	O
a	O
Man	O
that	O
stood	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
hiss	O
'd	O
at	O
it	O
aloud	O
:	O
and	O
drinking	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
spit	O
in	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Damn	O
ye	O
,	O
drink	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
;	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
?	O
(	O
he	O
replied	O
)	O
so	O
I	O
do	O
;	O
pray	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
?	O
Mean	O
(	O
says	O
he	O
)	O
I	O
mean	O
Jemmy	O
;	O
and	O
immediately	O
retir	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Mob	O
.	O
Warren	O
brought	O
some	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
civil	O
lad	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Stocks-market	O
was	O
his	O
way	O
home	O
from	O
the	O
Place	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
.	O
Cotton	O
also	O
brought	O
the	O
Master	O
he	O
serv	O
'd	O
his	O
Time	O
with	O
,	O
who	O
spoke	O
well	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
they	O
could	O
say	O
nothing	O
to	O
the	O
Behaviour	O
they	O
were	O
charg	O
'd	O
with	O
in	O
the	O
Riot	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
one	O
Whiston	O
's	O
Astronomy	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
Brown	O
swore	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
Shop	O
enquiring	O
for	O
some	O
Mathematical	O
Books	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Book	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
afterwards	O
sold	O
to	O
one	O
Chapman	O
in	O
Chancery-lane	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Book	O
was	O
found	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
again	O
to	O
offer	O
another	O
Book	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
secur	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
one	O
Mohun	O
,	O
a	O
Scholar	O
of	O
his	O
;	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samuel	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
hilted	O
Sword	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Bartlington	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
going	O
thro	O
'	O
Hide-Park	B-place
Gate	I-place
,	O
he	O
was	O
oppos	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
great	O
Crowd	O
of	O
People	O
,	O
and	O
getting	O
thro	O
'	O
he	O
missed	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Hand	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
;	O
and	O
held	O
it	O
up	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Minutes	O
,	O
enquiring	O
for	O
the	O
Owner	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
readily	O
restor	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Hackney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
her	O
Bastard	O
Male	O
Child	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Second	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
hearing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
who	O
answering	O
nothing	O
;	O
she	O
look	O
'd	O
under	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
Cloth	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
it	O
a	O
dead	O
Child	O
:	O
The	O
Midwife	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Women	O
saw	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
but	O
believ	O
'd	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
born	O
in	O
the	O
after	O
Birth	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
made	O
some	O
Provision	O
for	O
the	O
Birth	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
born	O
dead	O
;	O
and	O
no	O
Body	O
proving	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
Anne	B-pers
Cousey	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
7th	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
Reign	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
upon	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
fact	O
was	O
committed	O
before	O
the	O
late	O
Act	O
of	O
Grace	O
of	O
Queen	O
Anne	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
immediately	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
1	O
Neckcloth	O
,	O
1	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
6	O
Yards	O
of	O
Bone	O
Lace	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
Joseph	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knight	O
depos	O
'd	O
she	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
missing	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
he	O
challeng	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
'em	O
,	O
who	O
confess	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Trolly	B-pers
Lolly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Hurt	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
1	O
Pair	O
of	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
from	O
the	O
said	O
Christopher	O
Hurt	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
being	O
in	O
Bed	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
House	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
ran	O
out	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
.	O
A	O
Lodger	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
being	O
obliged	O
to	O
rise	O
early	O
on	O
the	O
Account	O
of	O
his	O
Business	O
that	O
Morning	O
,	O
he	O
lock	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
Key	O
under	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
a	O
Hay-making	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Door	O
wide	O
open	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
a	O
very	O
poor	O
one	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Whigley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Holdeway	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
1	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
35	O
s.	O
no	O
body	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
1	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
2	O
Shirts	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
42	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
Holdeway	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Door	O
being	O
left	O
lock	O
'd	O
.	O
Freeman	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
which	O
his	O
Wife	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
having	O
Notice	O
of	O
some	O
suspicious	O
Persons	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
Picklock	O
Keys	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Holdeway	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
some	O
of	O
her	O
Goods	O
too	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
desired	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
for	O
another	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Rowland	B-pers
Humphreys	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Seager	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
down	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
jump	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Parlour	O
Window	O
with	O
the	O
Cup	O
.	O
His	O
Maid	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
just	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Shutters	O
at	O
6	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
turning	O
about	O
to	O
do	O
other	O
Business	O
,	O
she	O
heard	O
a	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
tumble	O
over	O
the	O
Pails	O
with	O
the	O
Cup	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
he	O
lifted	O
up	O
the	O
Shash	O
.	O
He	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
Maid	O
would	O
have	O
sworn	O
it	O
to	O
another	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Mackentosh	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Randal	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
,	O
no	O
body	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
coming	O
to	O
Town	O
late	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
home	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
two	O
Watchmen	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
House	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
Search	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Chissel	O
,	O
a	O
Dark	O
Lanthorn	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Bundle	O
of	O
Matches	O
.	O
The	O
Watchmen	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Purpose	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
only	O
saying	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
by	O
,	O
fell	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Burglary	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Mackentosh	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Cowper	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anne	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Chetwind	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Silver	O
Embroider	O
'd	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
l.	O
a	O
Gold	O
embroider	O
'd	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
Value	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
Chetwind	O
Esq	O
;	O
no	O
Person	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
with	O
some	O
Assistants	O
were	O
walking	O
about	O
the	O
7	O
Dials	O
to	O
scower	O
the	O
Gang	O
(	O
as	O
they	O
call	O
'd	O
it	O
)	O
'	O
and	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
10	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
who	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
'em	O
,	O
answer	O
'd	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
'em	O
;	O
but	O
watching	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stop	O
'd	O
at	O
one	O
Ireton	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
who	O
coming	O
down	O
and	O
opening	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
threw	O
in	O
the	O
Bundle	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Woman	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
said	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
about	O
him	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
a	O
Chissel	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Things	O
of	O
that	O
suspicious	O
Sort	O
.	O
This	O
Evidence	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
three	O
others	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
was	O
the	O
Woman	O
who	O
kept	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
in	O
the	O
Family	O
's	O
Absence	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
left	O
the	O
Door	O
fast	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
10	O
a	O
Clock	O
was	O
inform	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
Esquire	O
Chetwind	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
Watchman	O
came	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Doors	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
gone	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
he	O
heard	O
Mr.	O
Chetwind	O
's	O
Door	O
shut	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
two	O
Men	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
one	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
without	O
;	O
they	O
bid	O
one	O
another	O
good	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
saying	O
nothing	O
to	O
him	O
he	O
suspected	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
his	O
Neighbour	O
.	O
A	O
Servant	O
of	O
Esquire	O
Chetwind	O
's	O
saw	O
the	O
Goods	O
at	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
which	O
she	O
knew	O
to	O
be	O
her	O
Master	O
's	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
up	O
Holborn	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
two	O
Men	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
Drink	O
sitting	O
at	O
a	O
Door	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Bundle	O
on	O
the	O
Stall	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
this	O
Bundle	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
doing	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
at	O
some	O
distance	O
,	O
but	O
ran	O
away	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
Time	O
indicted	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
John	O
Mackentosh	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Labourer	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Mary	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Parish	O
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
Bart	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
an	O
Iron	O
Chest	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
1	O
Diamond	O
Necklace	O
,	O
value	O
200	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Sir	O
Richard	O
Reynolds	O
.	O
Sir	O
Richard	O
's	O
Servant	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
House	O
about	O
4	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Day	O
and	O
double	O
lock	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
about	O
1	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
(	O
being	O
Moon-light	O
)	O
he	O
saw	O
4	O
Persons	O
carrying	O
along	O
an	O
Iron	O
Chest	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Newton	O
's	O
Lane	O
,	O
2	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
inform	O
'd	O
a	O
Constable	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
who	O
coming	O
with	O
some	O
Assistants	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
could	O
not	O
perswade	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
Mary	O
Powell	O
)	O
whose	O
Voice	O
they	O
heard	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
but	O
breaking	O
it	O
open	O
found	O
the	O
Chest	O
there	O
.	O
After	O
which	O
they	O
had	O
it	O
cry	O
'd	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Seymour	O
(	O
who	O
kept	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
in	O
the	O
Family	O
's	O
Absence	O
)	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
an	O
Iron	O
Chest	O
was	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
her	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
Sir	O
Richard	O
Reynolds	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
into	O
his	O
House	O
found	O
the	O
Chest	O
gone	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
the	O
Chest	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
Sir	O
Richard	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
,	O
coming	O
to	O
Town	O
,	O
open	O
'd	O
it	O
with	O
the	O
Key	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
making	O
a	O
very	O
trifling	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Smith	O
:	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Powell	O
:	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Royston	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
strip	O
'd	O
Satin	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Crape	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
Opportunities	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Goods	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
keeping	O
an	O
Apple-stall	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
for	O
an	O
Half-penny	O
worth	O
of	O
Codlings	O
,	O
giving	O
her	O
6	O
Pence	O
,	O
and	O
telling	O
her	O
she	O
would	O
presently	O
come	O
for	O
her	O
Change	O
,	O
desiring	O
her	O
to	O
hold	O
that	O
Peticoat	O
for	O
her	O
till	O
she	O
came	O
again	O
;	O
but	O
heard	O
nothing	O
from	O
her	O
till	O
a	O
Messenger	O
came	O
from	O
her	O
at	O
Newgate	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
having	O
left	O
her	O
Mistress	O
immediately	O
from	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
to	O
the	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
whereupon	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Punford	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
Peticoat	O
,	O
some	O
Shifts	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
Punford	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecuter	O
swore	O
his	O
wife	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
a	O
Milking	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Door	O
upon	O
the	O
Latch	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Goods	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
5	O
that	O
Morning	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
coming	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
threw	O
them	O
down	O
.	O
Another	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
watch	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
she	O
cried	O
out	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
threw	O
them	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
Man	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
supposing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
threw	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
,	O
the	O
Breadth	O
of	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
5	O
Inches	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
he	O
languish	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Month	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
Wine	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
always	O
good	O
Friends	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
respectful	O
to	O
one	O
another	O
:	O
That	O
their	O
Conversation	O
that	O
Night	O
was	O
chiefly	O
in	O
Welch	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
growing	O
suddenly	O
uneasie	O
,	O
told	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
in	O
English	O
)	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Puppy	O
,	O
and	O
turn	O
'd	O
him	O
round	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
again	O
repeated	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
replied	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
shew	O
'd	O
a	O
Desire	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
they	O
both	O
drew	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
saw	O
'em	O
thrusting	O
at	O
one	O
another	O
with	O
the	O
utmost	O
Fury	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
lay	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Deceas'd	O
's	O
Sword	O
,	O
but	O
made	O
no	O
Offer	O
afterwards	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Griffith	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
done	O
my	O
Business	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
replied	O
,	O
No	O
:	O
By	O
G	O
-	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
for	O
all	O
the	O
World	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
too	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
wounded	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
desir	O
'd	O
of	O
every	O
body	O
that	O
saw	O
him	O
afterwards	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
might	O
come	O
to	O
no	O
Trouble	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
fairly	O
done	O
;	O
and	O
particularly	O
told	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Evidences	O
.	O
That	O
Esq	O
.	O
Griffith	O
was	O
his	O
very	O
good	O
Friend	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
heartily	O
forgave	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
since	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
Laws	O
must	O
have	O
their	O
Course	O
,	O
he	O
earnestly	O
beg	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
do	O
his	O
Friend	O
all	O
the	O
Service	O
he	O
could	O
upon	O
his	O
Trial	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Carr	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
in	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
Labourer	B-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Ounces	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
of	O
Human	O
Hair	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Sparrow	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
Aug.	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Susan	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Dowlas	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
small	O
Value	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
.	O
The	O
Felony	O
not	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gowen	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Pewterer	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pauls	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Brigham	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
1	O
Silk	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
74	O
Yards	O
of	O
Gnewring	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Linnen	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Robert	O
Brigham	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
Aug.	O
last	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Brigham	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
her	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Parcels	O
and	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Linnen	O
were	O
stole	O
.	O
An	O
Headborough	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
going	O
into	O
Whitechapel	O
Fields	O
,	O
to	O
cut	O
Tuffs	O
for	O
his	O
Larks	O
,	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
very	O
busy	O
together	O
upon	O
a	O
Spot	O
of	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
up	O
to	O
'em	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
about	O
,	O
Gowen	O
threw	O
1	O
Piece	O
of	O
Linnen	O
into	O
a	O
Ditch	O
,	O
and	O
examining	O
the	O
Place	O
they	O
were	O
so	O
busy	O
at	O
,	O
found	O
30	O
Yards	O
of	O
Linnen	O
buried	O
in	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
with	O
the	O
Help	O
of	O
some	O
Persons	O
coming	O
over	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
secur	O
'd	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
looking	O
about	O
,	O
found	O
more	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Goods	O
buried	O
in	O
3	O
other	O
Places	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
is	O
being	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
many	O
Pieces	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Linnen	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
their	O
Bosoms	O
and	O
other	O
Places	O
about	O
them	O
.	O
They	O
made	O
no	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Ayers	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Simon	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
High-way	O
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
him	O
of	O
a	O
Hat	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Tortoise-shell	O
Snuff-box	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
an	O
Handkerchief	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Simon	O
Thompson	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
Thompson	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
he	O
going	O
the	O
same	O
way	O
together	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
scrap	O
'd	O
acquaintance	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
drank	O
together	O
,	O
with	O
one	O
Okely	O
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
went	O
along	O
,	O
just	O
by	O
Windmill-hill	B-place
,	O
about	O
10	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Okely	O
assaulted	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Company	O
,	O
but	O
left	O
him	O
with	O
Okely	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
going	O
over	O
Moorfields	O
;	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
some	O
Persons	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
having	O
consider	O
'd	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Susan	B-pers
Carpenter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Quart	O
Pots	O
,	O
2	O
Brass	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brunet	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
Brunet	O
swore	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
Weeks	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
Time	O
the	O
Goods	O
aforesaid	O
were	O
lost	O
;	O
and	O
examining	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Trinity	B-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Minories	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
1	O
Muslin-Pillow-bear	O
,	O
1	O
Holland	O
Shift	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
Judith	B-pers
Marks	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Diana	B-pers
Levi	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Proof	O
not	O
being	O
full	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
20	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
1	O
Dish	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Attsy	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
in	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
1	O
Drugget	O
Coat	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
1	O
Drugget	O
Wastcoat	O
10	O
s.	O
1	O
Pair	O
of	O
Drugget	O
Breeches	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Porton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Maid	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
coming	O
home	O
from	O
an	O
Errand	O
she	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Stairs	O
Foot	O
with	O
her	O
Lap	O
full	O
of	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
to	O
her	O
Mistress	O
,	O
ran	O
up	O
Stairs	O
.	O
Her	O
Mistress	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
Stairs	O
Foot	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
before	O
her	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
there	O
for	O
a	O
Midwife	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminister	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
1	O
Silver	O
hilted	O
Sword	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ferdinando	B-pers
Richard	I-pers
Hastings	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Catherine	B-pers
Hastings	I-pers
.	O
A	O
Footman	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
hearing	O
somebody	O
on	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
who	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
ran	O
into	O
the	O
Street	O
;	O
hereupon	O
this	O
Evidence	O
cried	O
out	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Servant	O
of	O
my	O
Lord	O
Peterborow	O
's	O
stop	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
threw	O
away	O
a	O
pick-lock	O
Key	O
and	O
a	O
Chissel	O
;	O
which	O
Key	O
,	O
upon	O
Trial	O
,	O
could	O
open	O
almost	O
all	O
the	O
Doors	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
.	O
A	O
large	O
Sack	O
was	O
also	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Parlour	O
:	O
But	O
nothing	O
being	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
when	O
taken	O
;	O
nor	O
the	O
Fact	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
Humphry	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pocket-book	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
Hunt	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Pocket-book	O
in	O
his	O
Way	O
from	B-place
Lawrence	I-place
Lane	I-place
to	I-place
Smithfield	I-place
,	O
and	O
with	O
it	O
two	O
Bank-Notes	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
35	O
l.	O
the	O
other	O
of	O
15	O
l.	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
stop	O
'd	O
Payment	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Note	O
of	O
35	O
l.	O
coming	O
in	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
trac	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
brought	O
it	O
,	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
who	O
said	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
she	O
dealt	O
in	O
old	O
Clothes	O
,	O
and	O
received	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
Chapman	O
for	O
10	O
l.	O
(	O
10	O
l.	O
having	O
been	O
already	O
paid	O
off	O
and	O
endors	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Bank	O
)	O
to	O
whom	O
she	O
gave	O
a	O
Token	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Return	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
remaining	O
15	O
l.	O
to	O
the	O
Bearer	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
accordingly	O
received	O
her	O
Token	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
but	O
knew	O
not	O
her	O
Chapman	O
's	O
Name	O
,	O
nor	O
where	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hope	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Second	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
Perriwig	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Hole	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
Window	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
in	O
hopes	O
he	O
might	O
catch	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Second	O
Attempt	O
,	O
he	O
let	O
the	O
Hole	O
remain	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
Boxes	O
along	O
the	O
Window	O
as	O
before	O
;	O
accordingly	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
following	O
,	O
about	O
1	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
saw	O
the	O
Boxes	O
move	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Wig	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
;	O
and	O
according	O
to	O
his	O
Direction	O
the	O
Wig	O
was	O
found	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
he	O
was	O
making	O
Water	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Door	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
secur	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Wig	O
;	O
but	O
told	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
where	O
Persons	O
liv	O
'd	O
that	O
bought	O
such	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
found	O
him	O
,	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Wanderson	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Goddard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Purse	O
of	O
13	O
Guineas	O
,	O
3	O
Broad	O
Pieces	O
,	O
and	O
1	O
Pistol	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Epiphenius	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
instant	O
.	O
Spencer	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
coming	O
down	O
Holborn	B-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
clap	O
'd	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Countryman	O
,	O
how	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
?	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
answerapos	O
;	O
d	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
you	O
.	O
Do	O
n't	O
you	O
?	O
replied	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
very	O
go	O
and	O
drink	O
a	O
Pot	O
together	O
,	O
that	O
we	O
may	O
be	O
better	O
I	O
tell	O
you	O
,	O
said	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
we	O
must	O
have	O
a	O
Pot	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
just	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
we	O
'll	O
have	O
there	O
but	O
going	O
forward	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stop	O
'd	O
at	O
a	O
publick	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
she	O
was	O
acquainted	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
went	O
in	O
:	O
after	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Brandy	O
;	O
and	O
seeming	O
very	O
fond	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
him	O
about	O
the	O
Neck	O
to	O
kiss	O
him	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
handsome	O
enough	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
however	O
she	O
did	O
kiss	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
took	O
away	O
his	O
Purse	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
ye	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
fetch	O
you	O
the	O
handsomest	O
Woman	O
in	O
England	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
greatest	O
Precipitation	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
liv	O
'd	O
very	O
honestly	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
all	O
Shifts	O
for	O
an	O
honest	O
Livelihood	O
.	O
But	O
being	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
loose	O
Person	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Ursula	I-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
1	O
Yard	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
green	O
and	O
white	O
Ribbond	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Straw	O
Hat	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Gabriel	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
Aug	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
Lawrence	O
swore	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Ribbond	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
two	O
Days	O
after	O
it	O
was	O
stole	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
asking	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
first	O
one	O
thing	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
another	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
Woman	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
not	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
she	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Leaver	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
an	O
Holland	O
Apron	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
about	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
having	O
been	O
a	O
Servant	O
at	O
the	O
Red	O
Lion	O
in	O
Thames-street	O
,	O
upon	O
a	O
Difference	O
between	O
him	O
and	O
his	O
Mistress	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
his	O
Wages	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
turn	O
'd	O
away	O
:	O
That	O
going	O
along	O
Stepney	O
Causeway	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
some	O
Fritters	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
out	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
put	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
'em	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
observ	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Wright	O
,	O
who	O
afterwards	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
tir	O
'd	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
Account	O
of	O
his	O
Discharge	O
,	O
melancholy	O
and	O
dejected	O
,	O
he	O
laid	O
himself	O
down	O
to	O
consolidate	O
his	O
Spirits	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
prevent	O
his	O
being	O
rob	O
'd	O
,	O
should	O
he	O
fall	O
asleep	O
,	O
put	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
that	O
held	O
the	O
Money	O
under	O
his	O
Head	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
wak	O
'd	O
,	O
found	O
himself	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
A	O
little	O
while	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
complaining	O
of	O
his	O
Misfortunes	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
told	O
,	O
the	O
Persons	O
were	O
known	O
who	O
had	O
his	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
inform	O
'd	O
where	O
they	O
might	O
be	O
found	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
an	O
Officer	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Leaver	O
with	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
above	O
mentioned	O
about	O
his	O
Neck	O
.	O
Wright	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
a	O
Shop	O
selling	O
the	O
Apron	O
;	O
and	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
:	O
but	O
Leaver	O
said	O
Wright	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
to	O
fell	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
taking	O
all	O
things	O
into	O
Consideration	O
,	O
found	O
Wright	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
Leaver	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
Francis	B-pers
Latham	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
full	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
saying	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
two	O
Boys	O
dropt	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
10th	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
Queen	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Spokeman	I-pers
.	O
Spokeman	O
depos	O
'd	O
he	O
made	O
himself	O
a	O
Watch	O
for	O
his	O
own	O
Use	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
afterwards	O
borrow	O
'd	O
by	O
his	O
Mother	O
in	O
law	O
,	O
who	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Odell	O
,	O
since	O
dead	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
apprehended	O
on	O
the	O
Accounts	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Latham	O
's	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
this	O
Watch	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Coat	O
Pocket	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Maker	O
's	O
Name	O
(	O
Spokeman	O
)	O
as	O
usual	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
own	O
'd	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Odell	O
's	O
Kinsman	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Watch	O
at	O
his	O
Uncle	O
's	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
give	O
no	O
Account	O
of	O
it	O
since	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
a	O
Hawker	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
she	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
ary	O
'd	O
Halves	O
,	O
but	O
contented	O
her	O
self	O
with	O
10	O
s.	O
And	O
it	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Watch	O
some	O
Years	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Excuse	O
upon	O
his	O
Trial	O
of	O
his	O
finding	O
it	O
very	O
lately	O
,	O
not	O
agreeing	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
1	O
Pair	O
of	O
flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
of	O
small	O
Value	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
Prisoner	O
have	O
been	O
very	O
intimate	O
since	O
the	O
time	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
appearing	O
malicious	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Bromley	B-place
,	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
Indian	O
Carpets	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dod	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Grounds	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
some	O
Part	O
of	O
them	O
upon	O
a	O
young	O
Woman	O
,	O
made	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
trac	O
'd	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
sold	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Hornsey	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Stuff	O
Lining	O
of	O
a	O
Shaize	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fish	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
making	O
no	O
Defence	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Gaton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Cashaw	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
instant	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
:	O
After	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
miss	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
found	O
broke	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
directly	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
confronting	O
themselves	O
in	O
point	O
of	O
Time	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Carr	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Scarlet	O
Hood	O
,	O
some	O
Head	O
Cloths	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
Lieutenant	B-pers
Sadler	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Kempster	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
Aug.	O
last	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Kempster	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
having	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
formerly	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
perswaded	O
by	O
her	O
to	O
admit	O
her	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
till	O
such	O
time	O
she	O
could	O
get	O
another	O
Place	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Things	O
before	O
,	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Kempster	O
's	O
Order	O
,	O
without	O
the	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
her	O
Husband	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Pawn-broker	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
Mrs.	O
Kempster	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
might	O
deal	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
was	O
her	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
another	O
time	O
said	O
,	O
She	O
hop	O
'd	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
no	O
Notice	O
to	O
her	O
Husband	O
of	O
what	O
had	O
pass	O
'd	O
between	O
them	O
in	O
Dealing	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
durst	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
know	O
anything	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Spavin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
1	O
Pair	O
of	O
flaxen	O
Sheets	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
2	O
Pillows	O
,	O
2	O
Pillow	O
Cases	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Man	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
Man	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
a	O
Room	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
which	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
carried	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
her	O
Husband	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
forc	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
help	O
him	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
over	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
,	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
11.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
,	O
Alexander	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Mullins	I-pers
,	O
Trolly	B-pers
Lolly	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Whigley	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
alias	O
Mackentish	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gowen	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Pewterer	I-pers
,	O
Anne	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
12.	O
Eliz	B-pers
Nicholls	I-pers
,	O
Anne	B-pers
Todd	I-pers
,	O
Rowland	B-pers
Humphries	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Hayston	I-pers
,	O
Tho	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Attsy	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hope	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
Esq	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Clarks	I-pers
,	O
H	O
-	O
E	O
-	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whip	O
'd	O
,	O
7.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
Twifort	B-pers
Twyford	I-pers
,	O
T	O
-	O
S	O
-	O
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
Susan	B-pers
Carpenter	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Page	I-pers
and	O
Bolton	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
fin	O
'd	O
10	O
Marks	O
each	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cotton	I-pers
fin	O
'd	O
20	O
Marks	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
fin	O
'd	O
15	O
Marks	O
.	O
John	O
Brown	O
alias	O
Burnet	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Pollocks	I-pers
alias	O
Mitchell	O
,	O
fin	O
'd	O
5	O
Marks	O
each	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
once	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
near	O
the	O
Pay	O
Office	O
in	O
Broadstreet	O
.	O
Trolly	B-pers
Lolly	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Whigley	I-pers
,	O
Anne	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
,	O
pleaded	O
their	O
Bellies	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
being	O
impanell	O
'd	O
,	O
Whigley	O
,	O
Smith	O
and	O
Powell	O
,	O
were	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
Quick	O
,	O
with	O
Child	O
;	O
but	O
Trolly	O
Lolly	O
was	O
found	O
not	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Good	O
of	O
the	O
Publick	O
.	O
WHereas	O
several	O
Gentlewomen	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
that	O
Sex	O
in	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
have	O
contracted	O
an	O
evil	O
Habit	O
of	O
Body	O
,	O
wherein	O
the	O
vicious	O
Humours	O
,	O
at	O
first	O
dispersed	O
through	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
come	O
at	O
length	O
to	O
be	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
one	O
Part	O
or	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
times	O
(	O
for	O
Causes	O
too	O
long	O
to	O
be	O
here	O
mentioned	O
)	O
are	O
thrown	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Womb	O
,	O
occasioning	O
a	O
dangerous	O
Weakness	O
in	O
that	O
Part	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
neglected	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
turns	O
cancerous	O
,	O
and	O
often	O
proves	O
fatal	O
.	O
I	O
cure	O
the	O
Diabetes	O
when	O
given	O
over	O
by	O
all	O
other	O
Persons	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
to	O
acquaint	O
all	O
such	O
as	O
may	O
have	O
occasion	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
speedy	O
Relief	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
had	O
from	O
an	O
experienced	O
Midwife	O
,	O
dwelling	O
now	O
at	O
the	O
Queens	O
Arms	O
,	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
near	O
Exeter	O
Change	O
in	O
the	O
strand	O
,	O
who	O
perform	O
'd	O
a	O
Cure	O
upon	O
a	O
Lady	O
at	O
the	O
Bath	O
,	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
given	O
over	O
by	O
Physicians	O
;	O
and	O
since	O
has	O
cured	O
several	O
Gentle	O
women	O
and	O
others	O
in	O
the	O
City	O
and	O
Suburbs	O
of	O
London	O
.	O
BOOKS	O
printed	O
for	O
Andrew	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Cross	O
Keys	O
and	O
Bible	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
.	O
The	O
History	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
Remarkable	O
Trails	O
in	O
Court	O
Britain	O
and	O
Ireland	O
in	O
Capital	O
Cases	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Hereby	O
,	O
Treason	O
,	O
Incest	O
,	O
Adultery	O
,	O
Rapes	O
,	O
Sodomy	O
,	O
Perjury	O
,	O
Murder	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
faithfully	O
extracted	O
from	O
Records	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
authentick	O
Authorities	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
Manuscript	O
as	O
printed	O
.	O
Price	O
6	O
d.	O
Where	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
the	O
present	O
State	O
of	O
Great	O
Britain	O
and	O
Ireland	O
.	O
In	O
Three	O
Parts	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
the	O
present	O
State	O
of	O
King	O
George	O
's	O
Dominoes	O
in	O
Germany	O
Continuing	O
an	O
exact	O
Description	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
few	O
Map	O
of	O
them	O
all	O
.	O
The	O
Third	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
6	O
s.	O
The	O
Life	O
and	O
Posrhumous	O
Works	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
famous	O
Arthur	B-pers
Manwaring	I-pers
;	O
Esq	O
;	O
pr	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
The	O
History	O
of	O
the	O
Wars	O
of	O
the	O
present	O
King	O
of	O
Sweeden	O
,	O
pr	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
The	O
Third	O
Edition	O
of	O
Memoits	O
of	O
the	O
Affairs	O
of	O
Scotland	O
;	O
in	O
which	O
is	O
the	O
whole	O
Secret	O
of	O
the	O
Pretender	O
's	O
Invasion	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
pr	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
Fourteen	O
Sermons	O
on	O
several	O
Occassions	O
by	O
his	O
Grace	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Daws	I-pers
,	O
Lord	O
Archbishop	O
of	O
York	O
pr	O
.	O
1	O
s	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
A	O
Collection	O
of	O
the	O
best	O
Odes	O
and	O
Imitations	O
of	O
Heracs	O
.	O
pr	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
The	O
Life	O
of	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Marlborough	O
and	O
Prince	O
Engine	O
;	O
with	O
both	O
their	O
Effigies	O
,	O
pr	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
The	O
Arabian	O
Nights	O
Entertainments	O
,	O
consisting	O
of	O
1001	O
Stories	O
.	O
In	O
Eight	O
Vols	O
.	O
pr	O
.	O
11	O
s.	O
The	O
diverting	O
Works	O
of	O
the	O
Countess	O
D'Amiot	O
,	O
Author	O
of	O
the	O
Ladies	O
Travels	O
into	O
Spain	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
the	O
Tales	O
of	O
the	O
Falries	O
.	O
With	O
Several	O
new	O
Cuts	O
.	O
pr	O
.	O
6	O
s.	O
The	O
Art	O
of	O
Memory	O
.	O
pr	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
The	O
History	O
of	O
pr	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
The	O
of	O
the	O
Waterside	O
;	O
Or	O
,	O
General	O
Practice	B-pers
of	O
the	O
Customs	O
.	O
Pride	O
stitch	O
'd	O
2	O
s.	O
Bound	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d	O
.	O
Just	O
publish	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Works	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Edmund	B-pers
Hickeringill	I-pers
,	O
Containing	O
the	O
History	O
of	O
Priests	O
and	O
Priestcroft	O
.	O
The	O
Black	O
New-conformist	O
.	O
The	O
Ceremony	O
Monger	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
his	O
other	O
Works	O
collected	O
into	O
3	O
Vols	O
.	O
Sold	O
by	O
J.	O
Baker	O
,	O
J	O
.	O
Brown	O
,	O
Temple	O
;	O
J.	O
Simons	O
,	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
;	O
and	O
J	O
.	O
Marshal	O
,	O
Newgate-street	O
.	O
Where	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
Brown	O
's	O
Works	O
in	O
3	O
Vols	O
.	O
in	O
Prose	O
and	O
Verse	O
.	O
Luchen	O
's	O
Works	O
from	O
the	O
Greek	O
,	O
in	O
4	O
Vols	O
Butler	O
's	O
Works	O
:	O
With	O
a	O
Key	O
to	O
Hudibres	O
by	O
Sir	O
Roger	O
L'Estrange	O
.	O
Also	O
the	O
Third	O
Edition	O
of	O
the	O
History	O
of	O
the	O
Highway-men	O
,	O
Foot-pads	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
By	O
Capt	O
.	O
Smith	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
CROUCH	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Pope's-hand	O
Alley	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
;	O
And	O
Sold	O
by	O
J.	O
Baker	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Black	O
Bay	O
in	O
Pater-noster-row	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
2	O
d.	O
)	O
Advertisements	O
are	O
taken	O
in	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Humfreys	I-pers
,	O
Printer	O
,	O
in	O
Bartholomew-lane	O
,	O
behind	O
the	O
R.	O
Exchange	O
.	O
