TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
'S	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
.	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
During	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
the	O
Rt	O
.	O
Honble	O
Sir	O
Charles	O
Peers	O
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
2d	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
'S	O
Reign	O
.	O
1716	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
PHILLIPS	O
,	O
by	O
M.	O
Jenour	O
,	O
against	O
St.	O
Sepulchre	O
's	O
Back	O
Gate	O
,	O
in	O
Gilt	O
Spur	O
Street	O
,	O
near	O
Newgate	O
.	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
'S	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
7th	O
,	O
8th	O
,	O
9th	O
,	O
and	O
10th	O
,	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
1715	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Second	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEfore	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
CHARLES	B-pers
PEERS	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
King	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Eyres	O
,	O
Sir	O
Williams	O
Thompson	O
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
;	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
John	B-pers
Low	I-pers
William	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
Abraham	B-pers
Pettyfer	I-pers
Nathanael	B-pers
Spinlove	I-pers
William	B-pers
Cowley	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
John	B-pers
Blackburn	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Gardiner	I-pers
Peregrine	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
John	B-pers
Wolf	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cliff	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rathpole	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Pike	I-pers
John	B-pers
Pashly	I-pers
Mathew	B-pers
Hopkinson	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Billing	I-pers
Benjamin	B-pers
Boltby	I-pers
Daniel	B-pers
Croker	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Chace	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Argus	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
George	B-pers
Poole	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
30	O
Canvas	O
Bags	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
the	O
Owner	O
of	O
the	O
Bags	O
dealt	O
in	O
Nails	O
,	O
and	O
such	O
sorts	O
of	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
them	O
in	O
Bags	O
from	O
Bromingham	O
to	O
his	O
Customers	O
in	O
London	O
,	O
who	O
usually	O
sent	O
them	O
(	O
when	O
empty	O
)	O
to	O
one	O
Inn	O
;	O
from	O
whence	O
when	O
their	O
Number	O
was	O
thought	O
sufficient	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
sworn	O
to	O
be	O
lost	O
from	O
a	O
Shed	O
in	O
the	O
Inn	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
them	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
who	O
then	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
denied	O
it	O
upon	O
his	O
Trial	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Attsy	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Thomas	I-place
the	I-place
Apostle	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Dark	I-pers
,	O
between	O
the	O
Hours	O
of	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
(	O
some	O
Persons	O
being	O
therein	O
)	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
4	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Exeter	O
Long	O
Ells	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Dark	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Servant	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
that	O
Time	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
leaving	O
the	O
Door	O
which	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
lock	O
'd	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Key	O
(	O
without	O
which	O
it	O
was	O
never	O
open	O
'd	O
)	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Goods	O
upon	O
a	O
Press	O
within	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
and	O
his	O
Goods	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
Some	O
Neighbours	O
who	O
had	O
taken	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
when	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
another	O
Robbery	O
,	O
observ	O
'd	O
him	O
loitering	O
about	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
aforesaid	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
saw	O
him	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
Mr	O
.	O
Dark	O
's	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
of	O
Goods	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
a	O
foggy	O
Morning	O
,	O
miss	O
'd	O
of	O
apprehending	O
him	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
making	O
use	O
of	O
their	O
Description	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
found	O
him	O
out	O
and	O
secur	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
who	O
they	O
were	O
very	O
positive	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
they	O
had	O
before	O
observ	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
willing	O
to	O
surrender	O
himself	O
to	O
Justice	O
;	O
but	O
brought	O
none	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
Outwich	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
40	O
Yards	O
of	O
Fustian	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bow	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
3	O
pair	O
of	O
Black	O
Silk	O
Gloves	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Mess	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
and	I-pers
Joseph	I-pers
Marriot	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
plain	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
some	O
Gloves	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
some	O
were	O
shewn	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
not	O
pleasing	O
,	O
whilst	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
was	O
looking	O
for	O
others	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
suspecting	O
her	O
Design	O
,	O
stop	O
'd	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
found	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
the	O
Gloves	O
thrust	O
up	O
her	O
Arm	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
was	O
search	O
'd	O
further	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
pair	O
was	O
drop	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Search	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
She	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
Gloves	O
hitch	O
'd	O
unfortunately	O
upon	O
her	O
Sleeve	O
:	O
Some	O
Persons	O
being	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
for	O
her	O
past	O
Behaviour	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
say	O
nothing	O
to	O
the	O
Matter	O
in	O
hand	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
and	O
Hannah	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
1	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
2	O
Silver	O
Salts	O
27	O
s.	O
1	O
Silver	O
Snuff-box	O
8	O
s.	O
3	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
said	O
Alex	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
,	O
no	O
Person	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
had	O
a	O
Room	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
House	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
Rented	O
of	O
the	O
Landlord	O
,	O
as	O
Mr.	O
Holland	O
did	O
his	O
(	O
the	O
first	O
Story	O
;	O
)	O
and	O
whilst	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
were	O
abroad	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
John	O
Wild	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
one	O
end	O
of	O
his	O
Poker	O
to	O
burn	O
the	O
Wood	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Lock	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
back	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
enter	O
'd	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
pass	O
'd	O
for	O
his	O
Wife	O
.	O
He	O
only	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Poker	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Days	O
before	O
;	O
but	O
brought	O
no	O
Witnesses	O
:	O
Whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Woman	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Weit	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bow	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
1	O
Perriwig	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Dixon	O
swore	O
.	O
That	O
going	O
home	O
about	O
12	O
a-Clock	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drew	O
his	O
Wigg	O
'	O
off	O
behind	O
,	O
pass	O
'd	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
for't	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
and	O
pursu	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Heels	O
chancing	O
to	O
fly	O
up	O
within	O
a	O
few	O
Yards	O
of	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
between	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
Wigg	O
was	O
found	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
heard	O
somebody	O
cry	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
that	O
pass	O
'd	O
by	O
him	O
threw	O
him	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
sworn	O
to	O
be	O
false	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Volumes	O
of	O
Dryden	O
's	O
Plays	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
Woodward	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
his	O
Stall	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
afterwards	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
Petty	O
France	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
they	O
were	O
trac	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
who	O
gave	O
a	O
very	O
different	O
Account	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
'em	O
,	O
from	O
what	O
she	O
said	O
upon	O
her	O
Trial	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
consider	O
'd	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Seat	O
of	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ostrum	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
One	O
Mr.	O
Henly	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
thrust	O
his	O
Head	O
and	O
Shoulders	O
into	O
the	O
Coach	O
(	O
it	O
being	O
empty	O
)	O
and	O
take	O
out	O
the	O
Seat	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
secur	O
'd	O
him	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
very	O
positive	O
to	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
who	O
having	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
but	O
a	O
flat	O
Denial	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smout	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Hill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdeameanor	O
,	O
in	O
speaking	O
traiterous	O
and	O
devilish	O
Words	O
of	O
His	O
most	O
excellent	O
Majesty	O
King	B-pers
GEORGE	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
King	O
G	O
-	O
e	O
;	O
I	O
'll	O
fight	O
for	O
another	O
Man	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
An	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
with	O
a	O
Friend	O
to	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Mug	O
of	O
Ale	O
,	O
he	O
there	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
Soldiers	O
who	O
made	O
a	O
great	O
Disturbance	O
,	O
and	O
affronted	O
all	O
Companies	O
;	O
insomuch	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
quiet	O
and	O
peaceable	O
,	O
and	O
behave	O
themselves	O
like	O
King	O
George	O
's	O
Subjects	O
to	O
all	O
such	O
as	O
lov	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
since	O
they	O
wore	O
his	O
Cloth	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
replied	O
in	O
the	O
abovesaid	O
Expression	O
,	O
and	O
drew	O
his	O
Bayonet	O
with	O
great	O
Passion	O
,	O
as	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
murder	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
prevented	O
.	O
Other	O
Evidence	O
confirm	O
'd	O
their	O
rude	O
Behaviour	O
;	O
and	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
much	O
in	O
Drink	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
Soldiers	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
quite	O
contrary	O
Character	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
not	O
being	O
credited	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Philip	B-pers
Storey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Magnus	I-place
by	I-place
the	I-place
Bridge	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
white	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cormell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cooke	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Gregory	I-place
by	I-place
St.	I-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Cheat	O
,	O
in	O
endorsing	O
two	O
Notes	O
,	O
of	O
50	O
l.	O
each	O
,	O
payable	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bateman	I-pers
,	O
with	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Thomas	O
Bateman	O
,	O
without	O
his	O
Leave	O
or	O
Order	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
Intent	O
to	O
defraud	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
Bateman	O
of	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Notes	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
from	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bateman	O
,	O
the	O
Receiver	O
of	O
the	O
Coal-Duty	O
for	O
building	O
of	O
Churches	O
,	O
about	O
6	O
Years	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
entrusted	O
with	O
the	O
Management	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Bateman	O
's	O
Affairs	O
;	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Bateman	O
being	O
to	O
account	O
with	O
the	O
Commissioners	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Cooke	O
found	O
himself	O
short	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
goes	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Robinson	O
,	O
who	O
sign	O
'd	O
the	O
Notes	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
make	O
himself	O
Debtor	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bateman	O
235	O
l.	O
upon	O
Condition	O
to	O
return	O
him	O
all	O
his	O
Notes	O
in	O
their	O
Hands	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
agreed	O
to	O
,	O
Cooke	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
taken	O
up	O
150	O
l.	O
of	O
one	O
Gudger	O
for	O
his	O
private	O
Affairs	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
often	O
sollicited	O
for	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
endorses	O
two	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Robinson	O
's	O
Notes	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Bateman	O
's	O
Name	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
with	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
Gudger	O
:	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Robinson	O
informing	O
Bateman	O
,	O
that	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Notes	O
were	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Cooke	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
who	O
found	O
means	O
to	O
get	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
Gudger	O
's	O
Hands	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bateman	O
who	O
looking	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
saw	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
endors	O
'd	O
with	O
his	O
Name	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
how	O
he	O
durst	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
replied	O
,	O
'T	O
was	O
no	O
Harm	O
.	O
Cooke	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
sole	O
Management	O
of	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Business	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
transacted	O
by	O
verbal	O
Order	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
never	O
defrauded	O
,	O
nor	O
intended	O
to	O
defraud	O
Mr.	O
Bateman	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
many	O
thousand	O
Pounds	O
had	O
pass	O
'd	O
through	O
his	O
Hands	O
for	O
him	O
:	O
That	O
upon	O
a	O
Difference	O
between	O
the	O
Commissioners	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Bateman	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Mint	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Bateman	O
was	O
in	O
Danger	O
of	O
losing	O
his	O
Place	O
;	O
which	O
brought	O
upon	O
him	O
this	O
Prosecution	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
very	O
much	O
reduc	O
'd	O
his	O
Debt	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bateman	O
:	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
endors	O
'd	O
the	O
Notes	O
having	O
a	O
regard	O
to	O
Mortality	O
only	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
least	O
to	O
injure	O
his	O
Master	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
7	O
English	O
Guineas	O
,	O
1	O
French	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
12	O
l.	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Nath	B-pers
.	I-pers
Spurling	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
upon	O
Wright	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
Chapman	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
;	O
and	O
Wright	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Nicholls	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Gregory	I-place
by	I-place
St.	I-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hut	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
35	O
Yards	O
of	O
Callicoe	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Day	O
time	O
,	O
some	O
Persons	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lift	O
up	O
a	O
Sash	O
in	O
the	O
Parlour	O
,	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
crying	O
out	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
threw	O
down	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
he	O
fell	O
on	O
his	O
Knees	O
,	O
and	O
beg	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Pardon	O
.	O
He	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
several	O
Persons	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
beg	O
'd	O
Pardon	O
,	O
and	O
promis	O
'd	O
Satisfaction	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
fear	O
of	O
a	O
Prison	O
;	O
and	O
not	O
as	O
an	O
Acknowledgement	O
of	O
the	O
Guilt	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Flood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
Basishaw	I-place
,	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
upon	O
an	O
Inquisition	O
taken	O
before	O
the	O
Coroner	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
wilful	O
Neglect	O
of	O
proper	O
Physick	O
and	O
Nourishment	O
for	O
the	O
Preservation	O
of	O
the	O
Life	O
of	O
Susan	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Lunatick	O
,	O
under	O
her	O
Charge	O
;	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
said	O
Susan	O
Shepherd	O
miserably	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Substance	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
herself	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Shepherd	O
at	O
Maidstone	O
,	O
and	O
persuaded	O
her	O
to	O
come	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
London	O
most	O
part	O
by	O
Water	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
then	O
in	O
a	O
weak	O
Condition	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
took	O
two	O
Rooms	O
.	O
That	O
during	O
that	O
Time	O
she	O
took	O
but	O
little	O
Care	O
of	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
for	O
the	O
last	O
Fortnight	O
of	O
her	O
Life	O
she	O
kept	O
Fire	O
,	O
Candle	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
Necessaries	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
having	O
an	O
Estate	O
.	O
of	O
about	O
80	O
l.	O
per	O
Annum	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
deluded	O
her	O
to	O
sell	O
one	O
half	O
for	O
620	O
l.	O
which	O
Money	O
remains	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Hands	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
People	O
who	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
observing	O
no	O
Meat	O
,	O
Drink	O
,	O
or	O
other	O
Necessaries	O
administred	O
as	O
usual	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
appear	O
'd	O
no	O
more	O
at	O
her	O
wonted	O
Times	O
,	O
going	O
into	O
her	O
Chamber	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
Point	O
of	O
Death	O
.	O
That	O
an	O
Apothecary	O
being	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
he	O
declar	O
'd	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Fever	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
to	O
live	O
.	O
That	O
being	O
dead	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
bury	O
her	O
as	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
had	O
desir	O
'd	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
the	O
Searchers	O
should	O
visit	O
her	O
Body	O
.	O
That	O
being	O
buried	O
privately	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
12	O
Days	O
after	O
by	O
Order	O
of	O
the	O
Coroner	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
viewed	O
by	O
two	O
Surgeons	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
of	O
Opinion	O
she	O
died	O
of	O
a	O
Fever	O
,	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
proper	O
Advice	O
and	O
Remedies	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
Power	O
over	O
her	O
late	O
dear	O
Friend	O
Mrs.	O
Shepherd	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
in	O
the	O
least	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
afflicted	O
beyond	O
what	O
was	O
usual	O
at	O
the	O
Return	O
of	O
her	O
Fits	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
Respect	O
for	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
griev	O
'd	O
at	O
her	O
Death	O
.	O
She	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
credible	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Mrs.	O
Shepherd	O
was	O
frequently	O
subject	O
to	O
Fits	O
;	O
in	O
which	O
Condition	O
,	O
one	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
drank	O
hut	O
two	O
Draughts	O
of	O
warm	O
Ale	O
in	O
four	O
Days	O
:	O
And	O
another	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
knew	O
her	O
to	O
have	O
Fits	O
ten	O
Days	O
together	O
to	O
such	O
a	O
Degree	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
neither	O
eat	O
nor	O
drank	O
any	O
thing	O
all	O
that	O
Time	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
often	O
importan	O
'd	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Advice	O
of	O
Physicians	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
always	O
refus	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
tried	O
them	O
too	O
much	O
already	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
nothing	O
more	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
That	O
during	O
the	O
Intervals	O
of	O
her	O
Fits	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
frequently	O
express	O
herself	O
kindly	O
of	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Flood	O
and	O
seem	O
'd	O
very	O
desirous	O
of	O
making	O
her	O
Satisfaction	O
for	O
the	O
Civility	O
,	O
Care	O
and	O
Tenderness	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
she	O
was	O
always	O
treated	O
by	O
her	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
always	O
complained	O
of	O
her	O
Relations	O
,	O
who	O
she	O
said	O
had	O
been	O
very	O
rude	O
and	O
uncivil	O
That	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Flood	O
had	O
done	O
her	O
great	O
Services	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
always	O
chose	O
Privacy	O
and	O
Retirement	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Motives	O
were	O
Malice	O
and	O
Revenge	O
,	O
being	O
Heir	O
at	O
Law	O
to	O
the	O
Deceas'd	O
's	O
Estate	O
.	O
Several	O
Persons	O
of	O
great	O
Note	O
and	O
Distinction	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
an	O
excellent	O
Character	O
,	O
And	O
the	O
jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mildred	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Poultry	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
50	O
Ounces	O
of	O
China	O
,	O
and	O
14	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Tea	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Tobias	B-pers
Isham	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
Instant	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Day-Servant	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
Nights	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
home	O
,	O
took	O
Opportunities	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
suspecting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
search	O
'd	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
and	O
found	O
his	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
to	O
send	O
to	O
his	O
Relations	O
in	O
Wales	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
Persons	O
of	O
Note	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Whole	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Vineyard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Pounds	O
of	O
Sugar	O
value	O
8d	O
.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hyton	I-pers
on	O
the	O
7th	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Gill	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
3	O
Pound	O
Weight	O
of	O
Camblet	O
Warp	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Pound	O
Weight	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Warp	O
,	O
Value	O
28	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
and	O
Tho	B-pers
Eades	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
as	O
a	O
Journeyman	O
Weaver	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
to	O
make	O
Camblet	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
frequent	O
occasion	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
for	O
Materials	O
,	O
took	O
Opportunities	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
that	O
gave	O
out	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White-Chappel	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
with	O
the	O
Blows	O
of	O
his	O
Fists	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
no	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Soldier	O
,	O
were	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
Drink	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
quarell	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
having	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
two	O
Blows	O
with	O
his	O
Fist	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
him	O
another	O
over	O
the	O
other	O
Soldier	O
's	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Deceased	O
fell	O
:	O
But	O
it	O
not	O
being	O
believed	O
that	O
that	O
One	O
Blow	O
occasion	O
'd	O
his	O
Death	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Katherine	B-pers
Carr	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anne	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
9	O
Dowlas	O
Shirts	O
,	O
9	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
1	O
Apron	O
,	O
1	O
Holland	O
Pillowbear	O
,	O
5	O
Neckloths	O
,	O
5	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
6	O
Holland	O
Caps	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Linnen	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
50	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
he	O
heard	O
somebody	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
House	O
about	O
6	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
and	O
following	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
abovementioned	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
seiz	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
he	O
saw	O
her	O
drop	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
waited	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
for	O
a	O
sight	O
of	O
her	O
Mistress	O
,	O
to	O
borrow	O
a	O
Crown	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
consider	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Day	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White-Chappel	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
an	O
Iron	O
Handle	O
of	O
a	O
Grindstone	O
,	O
Value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
Iron	O
Hoops	O
,	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
1	O
Head	O
of	O
a	O
Hatchet	O
,	O
6	O
d.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Head	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
9	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Bar-Iron	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
1	O
Iron	O
Screw-Plate	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Work-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Stevenson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Facts	O
were	O
both	O
proved	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
each	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Coulson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
3	O
Pair	O
of	O
Women	O
's	O
Bodice	O
,	O
Value	O
20	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
,	I-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
set	O
forth	O
,	O
That	O
her	O
Sister	O
being	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
under	O
a	O
Pretence	O
of	O
Shifting	O
herself	O
;	O
four	O
Days	O
after	O
she	O
miss	O
'd	O
some	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
accidentally	O
with	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
the	O
Bodice	O
under	O
her	O
arm	O
;	O
and	O
challenging	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
but	O
afterwards	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
from	O
her	O
Sister	O
:	O
Upon	O
her	O
Trial	O
she	O
said	O
her	O
Sister	O
gave	O
them	O
her	O
to	O
pawn	O
for	O
Money	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Shift	O
,	O
but	O
thought	O
her	O
Sister	O
had	O
bought	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Hillingham	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bay	O
Mare	O
,	O
Value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Good	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Heddington	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
Islington	B-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
stopped	O
at	O
Uxbridge	O
upon	O
the	O
Mare	O
,	O
without	O
Bridle	O
or	O
Saddle	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
several	O
false	O
Accounts	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
carried	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
as	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
He	O
made	O
no	O
Defence	O
upon	O
his	O
Trial	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Bowcher	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
with	O
Intent	O
to	O
steal	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
5	O
Shop-Books	O
,	O
Value	O
20	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Langton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Powell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
South-Mimms	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
an	O
assault	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Maddocks	I-pers
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
her	O
of	O
2s	O
.	O
6	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
7	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Maddocks	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
between	B-place
Barnet	I-place
and	I-place
Kicks-end	I-place
the	O
Prisoner	O
met	O
her	O
Sister	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
?	O
Give	O
me	O
your	O
Money	O
;	O
who	O
replied	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
none	O
.	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
ye	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
have	O
Money	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
I	O
'll	O
shoot	O
you	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
offer	O
'd	O
him	O
some	O
Farthing	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
dash	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
ye	O
,	O
I	O
want	O
Gold	O
and	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
Gold	O
and	O
Silver	O
I	O
will	O
have	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
came	O
to	O
herself	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
ye	O
,	O
must	O
I	O
wait	O
here	O
all	O
Night	O
?	O
Give	O
me	O
your	O
Money	O
;	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
she	O
had	O
but	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
.	O
Give	O
it	O
me	O
quickly	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
into	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
they	O
describ	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
some	O
Labourers	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
both	O
very	O
positive	O
in	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
He	O
denied	O
it	O
upon	O
his	O
Trial	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Pistol	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
but	O
5	O
s	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
when	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Behn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
I	O
Callicoe	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
1	O
Callicoe	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
some	O
Shirts	O
and	O
other	O
Linnen	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Coulson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
Mrs.	O
Coulson	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
Stairs	O
and	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
doing	O
above	O
Stairs	O
;	O
No	O
harm	O
(	O
replied	O
she	O
)	O
I	O
only	O
come	O
to	O
ask	O
a	O
Civil	O
Question	O
.	O
But	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
above	O
mention	O
'd	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
,	O
and	O
bundled	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Maid	O
's	O
Apron	O
,	O
that	O
hung	O
upon	O
the	O
Rails	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Floor	O
.	O
The	O
Maid	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
A	O
Pick-lock	O
Key	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
.	O
She	O
made	O
a	O
frivolous	O
Defence	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Heston	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Whitlock	B-pers
Bulstrode	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
1	O
Livery	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
and	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Buck-skin	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
1	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Felony	O
was	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
;	O
but	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Daniel	B-pers
Ayres	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Mellitony	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Day-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
1	O
Plod	O
Stuff	O
Night-Gown	O
,	O
2	O
Perriwigs	O
,	O
1	O
Deal	O
Box	O
,	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Neck-cloths	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Francis	B-pers
Mellitony	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Felony	O
was	O
plain	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Burglary	O
being	O
doubtful	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anne	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
Cloth	O
Wastcoat	O
and	O
Breeches	O
,	O
1	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
1	O
Flannel	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
40	O
s.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Nixon	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Woodruffe	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Yards	O
of	O
Silver	O
Fringe	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
3	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Viner	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Belgrave	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
13th	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
Queen	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Cowley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
Anderson	O
as	O
Principal	O
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
Christopher	B-pers
Banister	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
;	O
and	O
Cowley	O
and	O
Fletcher	O
,	O
as	O
Accessories	O
,	O
in	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
Richard	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
Holland	O
Apron	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
1	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
9	O
d.	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
Boots	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Christian	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
Norwich	O
Crape	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
1	O
Apron	O
,	O
2	O
Shifts	O
,	O
1	O
Child	O
's	O
Frock	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Headcloths	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Chipping	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Alice	I-pers
Marsh	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Savoy	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
Guinea	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Clever	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
;	O
But	O
the	O
Proof	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cammel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
Pounds	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
David	B-pers
Macdonald	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
Instant	O
.	O
Macdonald	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Trunk	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
continually	O
drunk	O
after	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
gave	O
him	O
Cause	O
to	O
suspect	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
lodging	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
searching	O
her	O
Room	O
,	O
found	O
4	O
1.16	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
an	O
Oatmeal	O
Barrel	O
in	O
her	O
Bed	O
,	O
cover	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
Water	O
amongst	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
2	O
Guineas	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
'em	O
being	O
.	O
Queen	O
Anne	O
's	O
Guinea	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
particularly	O
knew	O
.	O
She	O
only	O
said	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Prosector	O
ow	O
'd	O
her	O
a	O
Spite	O
.	O
The	O
jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
16	O
Sheep	O
,	O
value	O
41.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Grounds	O
of	O
Sir	O
Roger	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
at	O
Denham	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Katherine	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
38	O
Yards	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Camblet	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
1	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
1	O
Sagathie	O
Coat	O
30	O
s	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Preston	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
King	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
Coats	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
Williams	O
denied	O
being	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Stranger	O
to	O
the	O
Design	O
:	O
Upon	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
King	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
1	O
Cloth	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
1	O
Scarf	O
,	O
1	O
Suit	O
of	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Headcloths	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Proof	O
not	O
being	O
satisfactory	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Still	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Steel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Stolwood	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
4	O
Diaper	O
Table-Cloths	O
,	O
2	O
Holland	O
Smocks	O
,	O
4	O
Diaper	O
Napkins	O
,	O
3	O
Knives	O
,	O
2	O
Silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
3	O
Cambrick	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
with	O
Aprons	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Linnen	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
Value	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Proof	O
being	O
full	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Mower	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Kelley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
;	O
she	O
,	O
as	O
Principal	O
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
great	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Plate	O
,	O
Houshold	O
and	O
Wearing	O
Linnen	O
,	O
and	O
Apparel	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
Value	O
;	O
and	O
28	O
Lottery	O
Tickets	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Year	O
1710	O
,	O
value	O
224	O
l	O
some	O
Rings	O
,	O
2	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
71	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
;	O
and	O
he	O
,	O
as	O
Accessory	O
,	O
in	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stoln	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
This	O
Trial	O
was	O
very	O
long	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Substance	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
may	O
be	O
reduc	O
'd	O
to	O
this	O
:	O
That	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
was	O
as	O
follows	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
swore	O
,	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
above-mention	O
'd	O
;	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
a	O
Year	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
as	O
his	O
Housekeeper	O
,	O
persuaded	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Chiswick	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
his	O
Grand	O
Children	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
the	O
Advantage	O
of	O
his	O
Health	O
;	O
as	O
accordingly	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
him	O
:	O
But	O
she	O
failing	O
of	O
her	O
Promise	O
,	O
he	O
grew	O
uneasie	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
Town	O
,	O
found	O
his	O
Doors	O
fast	O
and	O
his	O
House	O
empty	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
breaking	O
it	O
open	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
gone	O
.	O
Immediately	O
he	O
goes	O
in	O
Exchange-Alley	O
,	O
and	O
puts	O
up	O
his	O
Lottery	O
Tickets	O
;	O
by	O
which	O
Means	O
he	O
discover	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
who	O
sold	O
them	O
there	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
he	O
made	O
it	O
his	O
Business	O
to	O
find	O
them	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
inform	O
'd	O
Kelly	O
was	O
at	O
Hull	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Post	O
of	O
a	O
Lieutenant	O
in	O
that	O
Garrison	O
,	O
he	O
employ	O
'd	O
a	O
Person	O
with	O
a	O
Warrant	O
to	O
apprehend	O
him	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
done	O
with	O
great	O
Caution	O
and	O
Respect	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Mower	O
being	O
taken	O
before	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Place	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
kept	O
Kelly	O
Company	O
.	O
One	O
Beatknife	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
search	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
Hair	O
Trunk	O
found	O
a	O
great	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
most	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
sworn	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
his	O
Daughter	O
to	O
be	O
theirs	O
,	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
by	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Kelly	O
manag	O
'd	O
the	O
selling	O
of	O
the	O
Tickets	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Mower	O
gave	O
the	O
Receipts	O
;	O
And	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Three	O
Cups	O
in	O
Aldersgate-street	O
,	O
to	O
bespeak	O
a	O
place	O
in	O
the	O
Lincoln	O
Coach	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
designing	O
for	O
Hull	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
however	O
fill	O
'd	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Mower	O
;	O
That	O
they	O
lay	O
together	O
at	O
the	O
said	O
Inn	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
there	O
taken	O
for	O
Man	O
and	O
Wife	O
;	O
That	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
carried	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Coach	O
in	O
Kelly	O
's	O
Portmanteau	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
himself	O
went	O
down	O
with	O
her	O
on	O
Horseback	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Mower	O
said	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
had	O
made	O
a	O
Bargain	O
with	O
her	O
in	O
his	O
Wife	O
's	O
Life-time	O
,	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
live	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
his	O
Wife	O
should	O
die	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
his	O
Bedfellow	O
:	O
That	O
after	O
his	O
Wife	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
he	O
claim	O
'd	O
her	O
Promise	O
,	O
and	O
She	O
went	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
put	O
her	O
into	O
Possession	O
of	O
all	O
he	O
had	O
:	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
Child	O
by	O
him	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
order	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
Room	O
on	O
t'other	O
side	O
the	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
Lottery	O
Tickets	O
for	O
her	O
Security	O
:	O
After	O
this	O
her	O
Husband	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
from	O
Berbadoes	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
been	O
inform	O
'd	O
of	O
her	O
late	O
Course	O
of	O
Life	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
forc	O
'd	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
the	O
Tickets	O
to	O
appease	O
him	O
.	O
To	O
prove	O
all	O
this	O
,	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
was	O
acquainted	O
with	O
her	O
in	O
his	O
Wife	O
's	O
Life-time	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
her	O
civil	O
Visits	O
;	O
that	O
once	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
Mower	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
Mourning	O
,	O
and	O
claim	O
'd	O
her	O
Promise	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
away	O
;	O
That	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
she	O
appear	O
'd	O
very	O
fine	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Alteration	O
,	O
Mower	O
said	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
gave	O
them	O
her	O
as	O
a	O
Reward	O
for	O
her	O
Services	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
also	O
depos	O
'd	O
by	O
one	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
Seem	O
'd	O
very	O
loth	O
to	O
Prosecute	O
Mrs.	O
Mower	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
done	O
it	O
,	O
if	O
Mr.	O
Kelly	O
would	O
have	O
given	O
him	O
a	O
Bond	O
not	O
to	O
prosecute	O
him	O
for	O
false	O
imprisonment	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
tender	O
of	O
her	O
while	O
in	O
Newgate	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
others	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
they	O
heard	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
say	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
well	O
satisfy	O
'd	O
as	O
to	O
her	O
being	O
with	O
Child	O
.	O
Some	O
there	O
were	O
also	O
who	O
spoke	O
well	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Mower	O
's	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Kelly	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Mower	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Husband	O
)	O
sent	O
for	O
him	O
about	O
two	O
Months	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
enquir	O
'd	O
for	O
his	O
Wife	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
inform	O
'd	O
him	O
how	O
she	O
liv	O
'd	O
:	O
That	O
after	O
this	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Mower	O
,	O
and	O
inform	O
'd	O
her	O
of	O
her	O
Husband	O
's	O
Arrival	O
;	O
which	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
disturb	O
her	O
,	O
because	O
of	O
her	O
familiarity	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
.	O
But	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Mower	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
sent	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
some	O
Lottery	O
Tickets	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
which	O
accordingly	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
not	O
doubting	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
own	O
:	O
That	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
they	O
all	O
met	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Mower	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
married	O
another	O
Wife	O
in	O
Berbadoes	O
;	O
but	O
was	O
now	O
resolv	O
'd	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
his	O
Wife	O
Jane	O
,	O
in	O
Holland	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
Effects	O
;	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
see	O
his	O
Wife	O
safe	O
at	O
Hull	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
possible	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
her	O
Embarkment	O
there	O
for	O
that	O
Voyage	O
;	O
for	O
he	O
having	O
a	O
Kinsman	O
of	O
his	O
other	O
Wife	O
's	O
in	O
Town	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
some	O
small	O
Business	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
Holland	O
,	O
he	O
durst	O
not	O
carry	O
her	O
with	O
him	O
lest	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
disoblig	O
'd	O
.	O
To	O
confirm	O
all	O
this	O
,	O
he	O
produced	O
a	O
Letter	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
in	O
Town	O
(	O
where	O
this	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
Wife	O
and	O
Family	O
)	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Mower	O
in	O
Holland	O
,	O
desiring	O
him	O
to	O
dispatch	O
the	O
Business	O
of	O
his	O
last	O
Request	O
;	O
for	O
that	O
now	O
all	O
Things	O
were	O
ready	O
for	O
his	O
Wife	O
's	O
Reception	O
.	O
He	O
also	O
called	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Circumstances	O
of	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
;	O
who	O
did	O
him	O
but	O
little	O
Service	O
:	O
And	O
two	O
Evidences	O
call	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
gave	O
them	O
both	O
the	O
work	O
of	O
Characters	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Mower	O
:	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Kelley	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
and	O
Anne	B-pers
Body	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
thence	O
1	O
Silver	O
Saucepan	O
,	O
Value	O
50	O
s.	O
5	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
3	O
l.	O
2	O
Diaper	O
Table-Cloths	O
,	O
16	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
Body	O
,	O
who	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
discovered	O
her	O
Confederate	O
Walker	O
,	O
who	O
also	O
con-fess	O
'd	O
it	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
.	O
They	O
made	O
a	O
very	O
mean	O
Defence	O
upon	O
Trial	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
Bay	O
Gelding	O
,	O
Value	O
41.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Miles	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
Wood	O
swore	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Gelding	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Grounds	O
at	O
Munner	B-place
's	I-place
-End	I-place
in	I-place
Essex	I-place
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
afterwards	O
in	O
one	O
Powell	O
's	O
Custody	O
on	O
Tower-Hill	O
.	O
Powell	O
depos	O
'd	O
he	O
bought	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
he	O
took	O
for	O
a	O
Grazier	O
,	O
for	O
31	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
swopp	O
'd	O
his	O
own	O
Chesant	O
Mare	O
for	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Man	O
he	O
met	O
accidentally	O
on	O
the	O
Road	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
Defence	O
not	O
being	O
of	O
any	O
Weight	O
with	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Martha	B-pers
Moor	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
in	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
Value	O
6	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
Napkin	O
,	O
4	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Cooke	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
very	O
plain	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
was	O
in	O
Drink	O
:	O
Whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
only	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.10	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Daniel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Marribone	B-place
was	O
indicted	O
upon	O
two	O
indictments	O
,	O
for	O
assaulting	O
and	O
putting	O
in	O
bodily	O
Fear	O
,	O
Austin	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
each	O
a	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
Value	O
2	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
Drink	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Action	O
seem	O
'd	O
more	O
like	O
a	O
Drunken-Frolick	O
,	O
than	O
the	O
Effect	O
of	O
a	O
real	O
Intent	O
to	O
do	O
Mischief	O
;	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
considering	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
aquitted	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Salter	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Salter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
in	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
Value	O
3	O
l.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
Barker	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
coming	O
up	O
Grays-Inn-Lane	O
,	O
a	O
Woman	O
clap	O
'd	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
drink	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
consenting	O
to	O
,	O
she	O
carried	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
Time	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Watch	O
.	O
Frances	B-pers
Strickland	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
That	O
she	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Barker	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Brandy	O
which	O
was	O
brought	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Salter	O
,	O
who	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
shew	O
'd	O
her	O
the	O
Watch	O
behind	O
his	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
receiv	O
'd	O
10	O
s.	O
for	O
her	O
Service	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Strickland	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
their	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
not	O
known	O
by	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
ill	O
Person	O
be-fore	O
;	O
That	O
she	O
called	O
Mr.	O
Barker	O
Cousin	O
and	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
private	O
;	O
but	O
denied	O
they	O
ever	O
saw	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
or	O
know	O
anything	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
he	O
has	O
Robb	O
'd	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
both	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Eastgate	I-pers
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Cannon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
upon	O
3	O
indictments	O
;	O
For	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
5	O
Chair-Curtains	O
,	O
Value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bullion	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Stringer	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Facts	O
were	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
Eastgate	O
;	O
but	O
Cannon	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
found	O
Eastgate	O
Guilty	O
of	O
each	O
Indictment	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Graves	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Cloth	O
Coats	O
,	O
Value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Adam	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
Smith	O
depos	O
'd	O
be	O
lost	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Coats	O
in	O
Monmouth	O
Street	O
,	O
at	O
one	O
Rowland	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sold	O
it	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
bought	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Walter	B-pers
Onby	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Onby	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
Silk	O
Hood	O
and	O
Scarf	O
,	O
Value	O
16	O
s.	O
1	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
1	O
Cap	O
,	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Merrifield	I-pers
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
but	O
the	O
Woman	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Cape	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
30	O
Yards	O
of	O
Stuff	O
,	O
Value	O
20	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Pigg	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Precinct	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Katherines	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
Pair	O
of	O
Watermen	O
's	O
Sculls	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Christopher	I-pers
;	O
which	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ralph	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Felony	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Rape	O
upon	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Phebe	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Virgin	O
,	O
under	O
14	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
Phebe	O
Shaw	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
before	O
,	O
the	O
House	O
being	O
clear	O
,	O
her	O
Master	O
follow	O
'd	O
her	O
down	O
Stairs	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
draw	O
her	O
Mistress	O
some	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
shew	O
'd	O
her	O
something	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
was	O
frightned	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
up	O
Stairs	O
:	O
That	O
the	O
Thursday-Night	O
after	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
about	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
leaving	O
her	O
Master	O
and	O
Mistress	O
with	O
some	O
Company	O
below	O
Stairs	O
,	O
who	O
sate	O
up	O
all	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
whilst	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
sleep	O
,	O
about	O
5	O
a-Clock	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
her	O
Master	O
put	O
his	O
cold	O
Hands	O
into	O
her	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
wak	O
'd	O
her	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
tell	O
her	O
Mistress	O
,	O
who	O
thereupon	O
replied	O
,	O
Hold	O
your	O
Tongue	O
,	O
you	O
Toad	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
crept	O
to	O
Bed	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
stop	O
'd	O
her	O
Mouth	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
upon	O
her	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
;	O
in	O
which	O
Time	O
he	O
entered	O
and	O
had	O
Carnal	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
her	O
Body	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
her	O
wet	O
between	O
the	O
Legs	O
after	O
which	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
sore	O
,	O
but	O
durst	O
not	O
tell	O
her	O
Mother	O
till	O
some	O
Time	O
after	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
made	O
some	O
persons	O
aquainted	O
with	O
it	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
it	O
reach	O
'd	O
her	O
Eare	O
,	O
who	O
immediately	O
got	O
a	O
Midwife	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Wings	O
of	O
her	O
Womb	O
were	O
t	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Neck	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
turn	O
'd	O
quite	O
out	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
thought	O
must	O
be	O
done	O
by	O
a	O
too	O
early	O
Copulation	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
Phebe	O
Shaw	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
her	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
thereupon	O
her	O
Mother	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
poor	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
maintain	O
her	O
,	O
put	O
her	O
Daughter	O
upon	O
this	O
Prosecution	O
.	O
That	O
his	O
Wife	O
had	O
also	O
taken	O
a	O
Warrant	O
out	O
against	O
the	O
said	O
Phebe	O
Shaw	O
.	O
And	O
some	O
Persons	O
were	O
call	O
'd	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
they	O
heard	O
the	O
Mother	O
say	O
,	O
That	O
since	O
they	O
had	O
put	O
out	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
Daughter	O
's	O
Eyes	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
put	O
out	O
both	O
theirs	O
.	O
One	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
had	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
a	O
Country-man	O
lay	O
with	O
her	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
Road	O
in	O
her	O
Way	O
to	O
London	O
:	O
And	O
several	O
others	O
gave	O
Evidence	O
that	O
made	O
it	O
look	O
like	O
a	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Whitby	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
as	O
an	O
Accessory	O
in	O
receiving	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
privately	O
stole	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
;	O
for	O
which	O
the	O
Principal	O
(	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jefferies	I-pers
)	O
was	O
convicted	O
last	O
Sessions	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
Proof	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Fear	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
Value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Floyd	I-pers
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Proof	O
not	O
being	O
satisfactory	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
making	O
a	O
good	O
Defence	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Godsell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
17	O
Yards	O
of	O
Green	O
Cloth	O
,	O
Value	O
7	O
1	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
15	O
Yards	O
of	O
Scarlet	O
Cloth	O
,	O
Value	O
16	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Goodwyn	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Briggs	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
Goods	O
stoln	O
by	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
William	B-pers
Godsell	I-pers
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stoln	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
reaching	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cooke	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
1	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
,	O
upon	O
Trial	O
,	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
done	O
in	O
Kent	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White-Chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
1	O
Apron	O
,	O
3	O
Yards	O
of	O
Gold	O
Lace	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Huson	I-pers
;	O
which	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Felix	B-pers
Rainsford	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Peter	I-place
le	I-place
Chaine	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
7	O
Purbeck	O
Stones	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Churchill	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
The	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
1	O
Drugget	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Micklethwait	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
,	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
13.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Bowcher	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Brown	O
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Powell	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cammel	I-pers
,	O
Katherine	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Still	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Steel	O
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Mower	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
Anne	B-pers
Body	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
10.	O
John	B-pers
Attsy	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Godsell	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Behn	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Ayres	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Kelly	I-pers
,	O
Martha	B-pers
Moor	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Cape	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whip	O
'd	O
,	O
19.	O
George	B-pers
Poole	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
Phillip	B-pers
Storey	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Nicholls	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Vineyard	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Day	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Gill	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Coulson	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Eastgate	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Graves	I-pers
,	O
Walter	B-pers
Onby	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smout	I-pers
,	O
fin	O
'd	O
5	O
Marks	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cammel	I-pers
,	O
Katherine	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Still	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Mower	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Body	I-pers
,	O
pleaded	O
their	O
Bellies	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
being	O
impanell	O
'd	O
,	O
found	O
Cammell	O
,	O
King	O
,	O
and	O
Mower	O
,	O
Quick	O
with	O
Child	O
;	O
but	O
Still	O
,	O
and	O
Body	O
not	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
Lately	O
Publish	O
'd	O
,	O
THE	O
Pen	O
's	O
Dexterity	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
The	O
Ingenious	O
and	O
Useful	O
Art	O
of	O
writing	O
Short-Hand	O
.	O
Containing	O
Twenty	O
Copper	O
Plates	O
(	O
curiously	O
engraved	O
in	O
the	O
Author	O
's	O
Life-time	O
for	O
the	O
Use	O
of	O
his	O
Scholars	O
)	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Letters	O
,	O
Characters	O
and	O
Contractions	O
used	O
therein	O
.	O
With	O
Rules	O
and	O
Directions	O
explaining	O
the	O
same	O
on	O
the	O
meanest	O
Capacity	O
.	O
Whereunto	O
are	O
added	O
,	O
Law	O
Terms	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
Discourses	O
,	O
as	O
on	O
War	O
,	O
Trade	O
,	O
Birds	O
,	O
Beasts	O
,	O
Fruits	O
,	O
Vermin	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Seventh	O
Edition	O
.	O
By	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Rich	I-pers
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
Maximum	O
in	O
Minimo	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Jeremiah	O
Rich	O
's	O
Pens	O
Dexterity	O
Completed	O
Being	O
the	O
plainest	O
and	O
easiest	O
Method	O
of	O
writing	O
Short-Hand	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
are	O
added	O
the	O
Terms	O
of	O
the	O
Law	O
compleat	O
in	O
Characters	O
at	O
Length	O
.	O
Never	O
done	O
till	O
now	O
.	O
By	O
Samuel	B-pers
Botley	I-pers
.	O
The	O
whole	O
curiously	O
engrav	O
'd	O
on	O
Thirty	O
Copper-Plates	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Both	O
printed	O
for	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
Edmund	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
and	O
Crown	O
in	O
Lombard-street	O
,	O
near	O
Stocks-Market	O
.	O
The	O
Volatile	O
Spirit	O
of	O
BOHEE-TEA	O
,	O
THE	O
first	O
of	O
this	O
Kind	O
that	O
ever	O
was	O
made	O
in	O
England	O
,	O
which	O
hath	O
been	O
found	O
the	O
most	O
absolute	O
Care	O
for	O
Consumptions	O
,	O
inward	O
Wastings	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
Decays	O
of	O
Nature	O
whatsoever	O
,	O
incident	O
to	O
Mankind	O
:	O
Being	O
infinitely	O
more	O
Balsamick	O
,	O
healing	O
to	O
the	O
Lungs	O
,	O
and	O
fattening	O
the	O
whole	O
Constitution	O
,	O
than	O
the	O
common	O
Infusion	O
of	O
the	O
Leaf	O
in	O
Water	O
;	O
insomuch	O
that	O
15	O
or	O
20	O
Drops	O
taken	O
twice	O
a	O
Day	O
in	O
Ale	O
,	O
Wine	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
Dish	O
of	O
Bohee-Tea	O
,	O
sweetened	O
with	O
the	O
finest	O
Loaf-Sugar	O
,	O
shall	O
do	O
more	O
Service	O
to	O
weak	O
Consumptive	O
People	O
in	O
one	O
Week	O
,	O
than	O
all	O
other	O
Restoratives	O
whatsoever	O
shall	O
do	O
in	O
many	O
Months	O
as	O
hath	O
been	O
sufficiently	O
experienc	O
'd	O
from	O
the	O
great	O
Quantities	O
thereof	O
sold	O
to	O
the	O
Nobility	O
and	O
Gentry	O
since	O
its	O
first	O
Publication	O
.	O
It	O
's	O
likewise	O
a	O
very	O
rich	O
Cordial	O
for	O
chearing	O
the	O
Heart	O
when	O
oppres	O
'd	O
with	O
Melancholy	O
and	O
Vapours	O
;	O
being	O
also	O
of	O
that	O
sovereign	O
Use	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
give	O
Ease	O
and	O
Relief	O
in	O
the	O
Cholick	O
,	O
violent	O
Pains	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
Coughs	O
and	O
Phtisicks	O
,	O
when	O
all	O
other	O
Medicines	O
have	O
failed	O
.	O
Neither	O
is	O
it	O
more	O
strange	O
than	O
true	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
by	O
taking	O
one	O
Bottle	O
,	O
voided	O
three	O
Ounces	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Gravel	O
,	O
which	O
may	O
be	O
seen	O
at	O
the	O
Place	O
of	O
Sale	O
.	O
This	O
Spirit	O
mix	O
'd	O
with	O
Punch	O
makes	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
agreeable	O
Liquours	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
;	O
and	O
to	O
take	O
off	O
the	O
Cruditles	O
of	O
a	O
cold	O
Phlegmatick	O
Stomach	O
,	O
oppressed	O
with	O
Wind	O
or	O
Water	O
,	O
no	O
one	O
Thing	O
can	O
be	O
more	O
effectual	O
.	O
To	O
create	O
an	O
Appetite	O
,	O
to	O
expel	O
nauseous	O
Humours	O
offending	O
the	O
Stomach	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
prevent	O
Vomitings	O
and	O
Reachings	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
better	O
Remedy	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
,	O
of	O
much	O
greater	O
Efficacy	O
than	O
the	O
Bitter	O
Draught	O
.	O
It	O
's	O
likewise	O
a	O
special	O
Antidote	O
against	O
any	O
Infection	O
of	O
the	O
Air	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
15	O
Drops	O
be	O
taken	O
going	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Spring-Water	O
,	O
never	O
faileth	O
to	O
procure	O
a	O
sound	O
Sleep	O
.	O
A	O
Gentleman	O
extremely	O
afflicted	O
with	O
the	O
Gout	O
,	O
by	O
taking	O
10	O
Drops	O
of	O
this	O
Volatile	O
Spirit	O
in	O
2	O
Glass	O
of	O
Spring-Water	O
,	O
Morning	O
,	O
Noon	O
and	O
Night	O
,	O
was	O
wonderfully	O
eased	O
of	O
his	O
Pains	O
and	O
Lameness	O
.	O
And	O
as	O
this	O
Volatile	O
Spirit	O
is	O
Chymically	O
extracted	O
from	O
the	O
purest	O
and	O
finest	O
Tea	O
that	O
can	O
be	O
had	O
,	O
so	O
is	O
it	O
likewise	O
a	O
certain	O
Remedy	O
in	O
all	O
the	O
abovementioned	O
Cases	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
&	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Bottle	O
.	O
Note	O
,	O
People	O
of	O
an	O
hot	O
and	O
feverish	O
Constitution	O
may	O
take	O
these	O
Drops	O
in	O
Barley	O
,	O
or	O
common	O
Spring-Water	O
.	O
Sold	O
now	O
only	O
at	O
Batson	O
's	O
Coffee	O
house	O
against	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
Cornhill	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
no	O
other	O
Place	O
.	O
Sealed	O
with	O
Black	O
Wax	O
,	O
having	O
a	O
double	O
Coat	O
of	O
Arms	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Two	O
Cinque-foils	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Bend	O
charged	O
with	O
three	O
Wheatsheaves	O
,	O
to	O
prevent	O
Counterfeits	O
.	O
As	O
Her	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Red	O
Ball	O
in	O
Queen-Street	O
,	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Three	O
Cranes	O
,	O
LIveth	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
,	O
the	O
Daughter	O
of	O
an	O
eminent	O
Physician	O
,	O
who	O
practis	O
'd	O
in	O
London	O
upwards	O
of	O
40	O
Years	O
.	O
She	O
hath	O
an	O
Ointment	O
call	O
'd	O
The	O
Royal	O
Ointment	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Gout	O
and	O
Rheumatick	O
Pains	O
,	O
giving	O
great	O
Ease	O
and	O
Comfort	O
to	O
both	O
Sexes	O
,	O
at	O
Home	O
or	O
Abroad	O
,	O
(	O
as	O
has	O
been	O
experienc	O
'd	O
by	O
many	O
that	O
have	O
carried	O
it	O
with'em	O
into	O
Foreign	O
Parts	O
,	O
therefore	O
of	O
excellent	O
Use	O
for	O
all	O
Travellers	O
)	O
and	O
compleats	O
the	O
Cure	O
;	O
asis	O
well	O
known	O
to	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
Nobility	O
and	O
Gentry	O
,	O
who	O
have	O
used	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
are	O
ready	O
to	O
testifie	O
the	O
Truth	O
of	O
its	O
wonderful	O
Success	O
.	O
She	O
hath	O
also	O
a	O
certain	O
and	O
infallible	O
Cure	O
for	O
the	O
Tooth-ach	O
,	O
without	O
Drawing	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
effectually	O
that	O
the	O
Pain	O
will	O
never	O
return	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
not	O
only	O
so	O
,	O
but	O
makes	O
the	O
Teeth	O
as	O
white	O
as	O
Ivory	O
,	O
fastening	O
those	O
that	O
are	O
loose	O
to	O
Admiration	O
.	O
She	O
likewise	O
alters	O
Red	O
or	O
Grey	O
Hair	O
,	O
making	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
delicate	O
light	O
or	O
dark	O
Brown	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
never	O
change	O
.	O
Her	O
Hours	O
are	O
from	O
8	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
till	O
12	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
2	O
to	O
6	O
.	O
Note	O
,	O
Removed	O
from	O
the	O
Cheshire-Cheese	O
in	O
Walbrook	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Good	O
of	O
the	O
Publick	O
.	O
WHereas	O
several	O
Gentlewomen	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
that	O
Sex	O
,	O
in	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
have	O
contracted	O
an	O
evil	O
Habit	O
of	O
Body	O
,	O
wherein	O
the	O
vicious	O
Humours	O
;	O
at	O
first	O
dispers	O
'd	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Whole	O
,	O
come	O
at	O
length	O
to	O
be	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
one	O
Part	O
or	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
times	O
,	O
for	O
Causes	O
too	O
long	O
to	O
be	O
here	O
mentioned	O
,	O
are	O
thrown	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Womb	O
,	O
occasioning	O
a	O
dangerous	O
Weakness	O
in	O
that	O
Part	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
neglected	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
turns	O
Cancerous	O
,	O
and	O
often	O
proves	O
Fatal	O
;	O
I	O
cure	O
the	O
Diabetes	O
when	O
gives	O
over	O
by	O
all	O
other	O
Persons	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
to	O
acquaint	O
all	O
such	O
as	O
may	O
have	O
occasion	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
speedy	O
Relief	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
had	O
from	O
an	O
Experienc	O
'd	O
Midwife	O
,	O
dwelling	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Arms	O
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Smith	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Exeter	O
Exchange	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
who	O
perform	O
'd	O
a	O
Cure	O
upon	O
a	O
Lady	O
at	O
the	O
Bath	O
,	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
given	O
over	O
by	O
the	O
Physicians	O
,	O
and	O
since	O
has	O
Cured	O
several	O
Gentlewomen	O
and	O
others	O
in	O
the	O
City	O
and	O
Suburbs	O
of	O
London	O
.	O
