TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
23d	O
,	O
24th	O
,	O
and	O
25th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
17	O
14/15	O
in	O
the	O
First	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
'S	O
Reign	O
,	O
BEfore	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HUMFREYS	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
and	O
Bart	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Powis	O
,	O
and	O
Duncan	B-pers
Dee	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
;	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
George	B-pers
Trim	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Hawford	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
Benjamin	B-pers
Nolton	I-pers
Noble	B-pers
Phelps	I-pers
George	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Clifton	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Constable	I-pers
John	B-pers
Grove	I-pers
Nathaniel	B-pers
May	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Thursfield	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
Adam	B-pers
White	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Collison	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Heather	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
Ebenezer	B-pers
Cawdron	I-pers
John	B-pers
Wibert	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Weeley	I-pers
William	B-pers
Smart	I-pers
John	B-pers
Prater	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Hull	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Beanmont	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Thomas	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Magdalen	I-place
Old	I-place
Fish	I-place
street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
3	O
Silver	O
Casters	O
,	O
4	O
Salvers	O
,	O
12	O
Spoons	O
,	O
2	O
Salts	O
,	O
and	O
12	O
Pair	O
of	O
Buckles	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Grammer	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Bound	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
sent	O
in	O
a	O
Box	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Warehouse	O
at	O
the	O
King	B-place
's	I-place
Head	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Old	I-place
Change	I-place
,	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Grammer	O
,	O
directed	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Lewis	O
at	O
Glacester	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Box	O
was	O
accordingly	O
sent	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
it	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
open	O
'd	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Lewis	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
in	O
it	O
but	O
a	O
Glass	O
Bottle	O
and	O
some	O
Hay	O
;	O
whereupon	O
be	O
sent	O
Word	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Grammer	O
,	O
who	O
making	O
Complaint	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Bound	O
the	O
Warehouse-keeper	O
,	O
he	O
look	O
'd	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Glass	O
broke	O
in	O
a	O
Window	O
of	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
which	O
look	O
'd	O
into	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Yard	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
to	O
search	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
some	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
after	O
a	O
while	O
confess	O
'd	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
rest	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Plate	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
put	O
in	O
a	O
Glass-Bottle	O
,	O
and	O
fasten	O
'd	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
at	O
his	O
Trial	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
intic	O
'd	O
to	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
Inn-keeper	O
's	O
Son	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
Witness	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
.	O
But	O
that	O
not	O
being	O
any	O
Extennation	O
of	O
his	O
Offence	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
so	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Christian	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Olave	I-place
Hartstreet	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ive	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
a	O
Table-Cloth	O
and	O
a	O
Napkin	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
for	O
Charity	O
employ	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
on	O
Errands	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
till	O
a	O
Guinea	O
being	O
lost	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
suspected	O
and	O
turn	O
'd	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
Year	O
afterwards	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
away	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
former	O
Suspicion	O
encreasing	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
had	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
both	O
the	O
Facts	O
,	O
but	O
deny	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
one	O
Dickenson	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Linnen	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
receiv	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Wide	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
speaking	O
seditious	O
Words	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
instant	O
,	O
by	O
saying	O
,	O
God	O
damn	O
King	O
George	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
no	O
Right	O
to	O
the	O
Crown	O
.	O
The	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
two	O
Watermen	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
drunk	O
into	O
an	O
Alehouse	B-place
at	I-place
Billingsgate	I-place
,	O
and	O
there	O
us	O
'd	O
the	O
Words	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
who	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
had	O
known	O
,	O
and	O
convers	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
any	O
Thing	O
against	O
the	O
Government	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
often	O
drank	O
King	O
George	O
's	O
Health	O
,	O
particularly	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
he	O
landed	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Words	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
being	O
so	O
positively	O
sworn	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
.	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Duncomb	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Gough	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Stead	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
instant	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
'em	O
to	O
an	O
Inn	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
drank	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
all	O
Night	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
4	O
Guineas	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
7	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Money	O
he	O
tax	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
denying	O
they	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
let	O
'em	O
go	O
;	O
but	O
afterwards	O
renewing	O
his	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
he	O
follow	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
Search	O
found	O
2	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
21	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Silver	O
.	O
Duncomb	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Guineas	O
to	O
lye	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
said	O
she	O
told	O
them	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
Share	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
not	O
well	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Dowlas	O
Shirt	O
,	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Head-Cloaths	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
seen	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
an	O
Alley	O
in	O
Aldersgate-street	B-place
,	O
and	O
after	O
a	O
while	O
come	O
out	O
with	O
something	O
in	O
her	O
Lap	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
stopt	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
the	O
Alley	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
Work	O
;	O
but	O
had	O
no	O
Proof	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
where	O
upon	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Hurrel	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
16	O
Yards	O
of	O
Stuff	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Bowdry	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
sworn	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
being	O
observ	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
loitring	O
about	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
Hurrel	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
put	O
up	O
his	O
Coat-sleeve	O
,	O
thrust	O
his	O
Arm	O
in	O
at	O
a	O
Hole	O
in	O
the	O
Glass	O
,	O
and	O
bring	O
out	O
something	O
;	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
acquainted	O
of	O
,	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
where	O
Hurrel	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
'em	O
.	O
This	O
making	O
the	O
Fact	O
plain	O
upon	O
Hurrel	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
against	O
Cook	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Muslin	O
Hood	O
and	O
Apron	O
,	O
two	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
belonging	O
to	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
Instant	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Door	O
being	O
left	O
open	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sneak	O
'd	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
down	O
.	O
With	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
selling	O
Oranges	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
a	O
Man	O
hir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
;	O
which	O
not	O
being	O
believ	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dionis	I-place
Back-church	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Wooden	O
Chest	O
,	O
and	O
163	O
Pound	O
of	O
Candles	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Tyrrell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
they	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
skulking	O
about	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
observing	O
them	O
a	O
while	O
,	O
saw	O
them	O
pull	O
the	O
Chest	O
by	O
degrees	O
off	O
the	O
Steps	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
it	O
about	O
10	O
or	O
12	O
Yards	O
;	O
whereupon	O
they	O
went	O
and	O
apprehended	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
escap	O
'd	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
nothing	O
material	O
to	O
offer	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
not	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
proving	O
they	O
pull	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
only	O
from	O
the	O
Steps	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Radley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Katherine	I-place
Cree	I-place
Church	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
live	O
Sheep	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Wade	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
Sheep	O
out	O
of	O
Greenwich	B-place
Marsh	I-place
;	O
and	O
another	O
Person	O
Depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Sarazon	B-place
's	I-place
Head	I-place
Inn	I-place
near	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
where	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
piece	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
suspected	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
honestly	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
stopt	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
Notice	O
to	O
the	O
Owner	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Sheep	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
brought	O
them	O
from	O
Greenwich	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
give	O
no	O
Account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripple-gate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Quilt	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Blankets	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cardinal	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
Instant	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Quilt	O
and	O
Blankets	O
were	O
stoln	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
House	O
at	O
Lambeth	B-place
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
running	O
away	O
from	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
was	O
suspected	O
and	O
taken	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
White	B-place
House	I-place
in	I-place
Fore-street	I-place
,	O
near	O
Moorfields	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
accordingly	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
nothing	O
material	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Isabel	B-pers
Sheers	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
Ludgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Purse	O
,	O
with	O
two	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Broad-piece	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
a	O
Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
came	O
both	O
out	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
they	O
passed	O
he	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
barbarously	O
beaten	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
suspected	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
by	O
some	O
Friends	O
of	O
hers	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
rude	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
refusing	O
,	O
he	O
thrust	O
the	O
Money	O
into	O
her	O
Bosom	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
her	O
Lodging	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
from	O
him	O
down	O
Black	O
Fryars	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
following	O
her	O
,	O
fell	O
down	O
twice	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
she	O
got	O
away	O
.	O
She	O
also	O
brought	O
Witness	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
up	O
another	O
Woman	O
upon	O
the	O
same	O
Account	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
Drink	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
several	O
Persons	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
,	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Tent	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Christopher	I-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Hughs	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
4	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
and	O
10	O
Plates	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Edward	O
Hughs	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
on	O
the	O
Night	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
Moses	B-pers
Whittle	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Accomplice	O
,	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
with	O
Tibbs	O
and	O
Savil	O
,	O
both	O
formerly	O
convicted	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
)	O
broke	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
Whittle	O
had	O
deny	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
Justice	O
Fuller	O
's	O
Clerk	O
to	O
justify	O
it	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Rachel	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
Christian	B-pers
Clarkson	I-pers
(	O
an	O
Infant	O
)	O
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Gold	O
Bob	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Evil-Gold	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
coming	O
from	O
School	O
,	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
been	O
seen	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
was	O
taken	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
and	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
owning	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Child	O
from	O
Gravel-lane	B-place
to	I-place
Shadwell-Church	I-place
.	O
It	O
was	O
also	O
prov	O
'd	O
where	O
she	O
sold	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
her	O
Trial	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
the	O
Child	O
gave	O
them	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
was	O
of	O
Opinion	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
Robbery	O
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Vincent	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Pound	O
of	O
Yarn	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Furnace	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
having	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
Linnen	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
besides	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
advis	O
'd	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
little	O
Ball	O
of	O
Worsted	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
positive	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Yarn	O
was	O
twisted	O
:	O
But	O
that	O
appearing	O
improbable	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
Proof	O
she	O
bought	O
it	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
July	O
before	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Priscilla	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Jane	B-pers
,	I-pers
Countess-Dowager	I-pers
of	I-pers
Bridgwater	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
Instant	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
outer	O
Door	O
being	O
open	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Lady	O
's	O
Woman	O
hearing	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
look	O
'd	O
out	O
and	O
saw	O
her	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
pursuit	O
,	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Candlesticks	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
so	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Bullock	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Tottenham	B-place
High	I-place
Cross	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Geese	O
and	O
a	O
Gander	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Bradford	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
she	O
lost	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
stopt	O
with	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
given	O
him	O
by	O
another	O
to	O
carry	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
William	I-pers
Bond	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Hatt	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
Instant	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
an	O
Iron	O
Pin	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
being	O
in	O
Bed	O
on	O
a	O
Ground	O
floor	O
,	O
she	O
heard	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Sash	O
thrust	O
up	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
wak	O
'd	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
who	O
rose	O
and	O
sate	O
by	O
the	O
Window	O
to	O
watch	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
long	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Sash	O
was	O
thrust	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Hand	O
put	O
in	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
catch	O
'd	O
hold	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
fast	O
till	O
,	O
Help	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Window	O
open	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
give	O
Notice	O
to	O
the	O
People	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Persons	O
appearing	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Frying-pan	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Aylworth	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
Pan	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
go	O
along	O
the	O
Street	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
follow	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
a	O
House	O
where	O
she	O
carry	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
no	O
Defence	O
at	O
her	O
Trial	O
,	O
whereupon	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Whitechapel	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Canes	O
,	O
and	O
30	O
Sticks	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Dring	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
That	O
during	O
the	O
hurry	O
at	O
the	O
late	O
dreadful	O
Fire	O
in	O
Tower	O
street	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
being	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
there	O
.	O
In	O
his	O
Defence	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
working	O
at	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
over	O
Tower	O
hill	O
,	O
a	O
Man	O
gave	O
them	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
;	O
but	O
having	O
no	O
Witness	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
believ	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Alexander	B-pers
Seymour	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
Rowland	B-pers
Pierce	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Hat	O
and	O
Peruke	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
going	O
along	O
Orange-street	B-place
,	O
he	O
felt	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
snatch	O
'd	O
off	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
them	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
no	O
Defence	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Court	O
being	O
of	O
Opinion	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
amount	O
to	O
robbing	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
33	O
Yards	O
of	O
Bombazeen	O
,	O
value	O
45	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Noble	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Oswin	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
go	O
stooping	O
along	O
in	O
the	O
New	B-place
Exchange	I-place
till	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
saw	O
him	O
reach	O
over	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
dropt	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
cries	O
News	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
then	O
going	O
for	O
the	O
Evening	O
Post	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
Man	O
coming	O
hastily	O
by	O
,	O
brush	O
'd	O
down	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Witness	O
being	O
positive	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
35	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Elias	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
Instant	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Man	O
whom	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
Husband	O
,	O
lodg	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
about	O
10	O
Nights	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
away	O
without	O
taking	O
leave	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
several	O
Goods	O
being	O
miss	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Gown	O
upon	O
her	O
Back	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Kimbal	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Copper	O
Stew	O
pan	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
from	O
Anthony	B-pers
Hepburn	I-pers
on	O
the	O
19th	O
Instant	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
on	O
an	O
Errand	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
miss	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
search	O
found	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
'em	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
pawn	O
'd	O
'em	O
for	O
another	O
Woman	O
;	O
but	O
had	O
no	O
Proof	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Parrot	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Reverend	O
Father	O
in	O
God	O
,	O
Charles	B-pers
,	I-pers
Lord	I-pers
Bishop	I-pers
of	I-pers
Norwich	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Diamond	O
of	O
Ear-Rings	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
l.	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
and	O
Chain	O
,	O
with	O
Plate	O
and	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
value	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
brought	O
from	O
Norwich	O
to	O
the	O
Bishop	B-place
's	I-place
House	I-place
in	I-place
King-street	I-place
,	O
which	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
and	O
they	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
Chance	O
,	O
and	O
Accomplice	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
kept	O
a	O
Geneva	O
Shop	O
over	O
against	O
the	O
Bishop	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
rich	O
Goods	O
brought	O
in	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
help	O
'd	O
to	O
unload	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
shew	O
him	O
how	O
they	O
might	O
get	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
take	O
them	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
go	O
accordingly	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
did	O
break	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
sold	O
to	O
one	O
White	O
in	O
Holborn	O
;	O
the	O
Rings	O
for	O
10	O
l.	O
and	O
the	O
Plate	O
for	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
per	O
Ounce	O
.	O
He	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
what	O
Chance	O
had	O
sworn	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
utterly	O
false	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
Proof	O
that	O
he	O
acknowledg	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samuel	B-pers
Culver	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Dupre	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Iron	O
Grates	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Barber	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
having	O
lost	O
the	O
Grates	O
from	O
his	O
Door	O
,	O
he	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
them	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
confess	O
'd	O
they	O
took	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
They	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
at	O
their	O
Trial	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
some	O
who	O
said	O
they	O
never	O
knew	O
them	O
Guilty	O
of	O
any	O
ill	O
Thing	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
Fact	O
being	O
so	O
plain	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Shadrach	B-pers
Guy	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Ralph	B-pers
Musgrave	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
and	O
Chain	O
,	O
value	O
35	O
l.	O
a	O
Pocket-book	O
,	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Pistols	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Cock	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Musgrave	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
such	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Chambers	O
in	O
Staples-Inn	B-place
;	O
and	O
his	O
Clerk	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Chambers	O
were	O
fast	O
at	O
8	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
11	O
were	O
found	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Musgrave	O
hereupon	O
sent	O
printed	O
Bills	O
abroad	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
going	O
to	O
pawn	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
the	O
Pistols	O
,	O
was	O
stopt	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
search	O
the	O
Pocket-	O
book	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
In	O
his	O
Defence	O
he	O
pretended	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Pistols	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
an	O
Oyster-woman	O
who	O
swore	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
blind	O
Story	O
relating	O
thereunto	O
;	O
which	O
not	O
availing	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Burglary	O
;	O
&	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Cock	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Dormer	I-pers
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
Side	O
of	O
his	O
Body	O
near	O
the	O
Pap	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
7	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
3	O
Witnesses	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
a	O
Field	O
by	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
they	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
push	O
at	O
each	O
other	O
a	O
pretty	O
while	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
part	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
go	O
to	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
reel	O
'd	O
backwards	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
against	O
some	O
Pales	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
Arms	O
and	O
Kiss	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
readily	O
surrender	O
'd	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
us	O
'd	O
him	O
fairly	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
yes	O
,	O
and	O
forgave	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
that	O
they	O
being	O
both	O
Drummers	O
,	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
demanded	O
a	O
share	O
of	O
some	O
Money	O
that	O
was	O
given	O
among	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
because	O
they	O
refus	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
swore	O
he	O
'd	O
have	O
the	O
Blood	O
of	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
also	O
declar	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
together	O
from	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
to	O
about	O
3	O
that	O
Day	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
being	O
very	O
quarrelsome	O
about	O
what	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
being	O
defrauded	O
of	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
left	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
homewards	O
along	O
Tyburn	B-place
Road	I-place
,	O
where	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
swearing	O
he	O
would	O
stab	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Heart	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
draw	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
thereupon	O
he	O
did	O
draw	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
received	O
the	O
Wound	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
who	O
swore	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
quarrelsome	O
Fellow	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
wounded	O
several	O
People	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
a	O
quite	O
contrary	O
Character	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Whitechapel	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cask	O
and	O
4	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Rum	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Marley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
having	O
lost	O
his	O
Rum	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Glass-house	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
inform	O
'd	O
ill	O
People	O
us	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
found	O
the	O
Cask	O
,	O
with	O
about	O
2	O
Quarts	O
of	O
the	O
Rum	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Custody	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
2	O
Men	O
brought	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Glass-house	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
some	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
leaving	O
him	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
it	O
;	O
which	O
not	O
being	O
thought	O
a	O
sufficient	O
Defence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Christian	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Linnen	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
Instant	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
to	O
wash	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
soon	O
after	O
miss	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
suspected	O
,	O
taken	O
up	O
by	O
a	O
Warrant	O
,	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
'em	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
accordingly	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
pawning	O
'em	O
at	O
her	O
Trial	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
with	O
an	O
Instant	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
to	O
supply	O
a	O
present	O
Necessity	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
restore	O
'em	O
again	O
.	O
This	O
being	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
as	O
frivolous	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hurd	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Paddington	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
7	O
Sheep	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Starkey	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
12th	O
Year	O
of	O
her	O
late	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
7	O
Sheep	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
could	O
find	O
who	O
stole	O
'em	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
19th	O
Instant	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
catch	O
'd	O
a	O
Man	O
carrying	O
off	O
part	O
of	O
two	O
Carcasses	O
;	O
who	O
being	O
brought	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
discover	O
'd	O
a	O
great	O
Number	O
of	O
Sheep-stealers	O
,	O
amongst	O
whom	O
were	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
against	O
whom	O
he	O
swore	O
the	O
Fact	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Downer	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
Instant	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
;	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
several	O
Watches	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
a	O
Watch-maker	O
by	O
Trade	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
lock	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
strong	O
Box	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
also	O
lock	O
'd	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Coffee-house	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
leaving	O
only	O
a	O
Servant	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
ironing	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchin	O
,	O
she	O
heard	O
a	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
whereupon	O
she	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
getting	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
stood	O
there	O
a	O
while	O
with	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
Pursuit	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
He	O
deny	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
ever	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
that	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
by	O
Mistake	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
run	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
walking	O
a	O
very	O
gentle	O
pace	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
immediately	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
nothing	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
also	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Robins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Burnet	I-pers
,	O
(	O
two	O
Boys	O
)	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
Callicoe	O
Gowns	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Diaper	O
Table	O
Cloth	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
hung	O
a	O
drying	O
in	O
the	O
Garden	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
seen	O
to	O
come	O
thence	O
thro	O
'	O
a	O
Hole	O
in	O
the	O
Pales	O
;	O
whereupon	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
with	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
'em	O
;	O
which	O
making	O
it	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Barns	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Milam	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Riding-hood	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
having	O
just	O
slept	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
her	O
taking	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
meet	O
Necessity	O
,	O
whereupon	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
wooden	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
Guineas	O
in	O
Gold	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Fromarty	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
Taylor	O
,	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
making	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
;	O
and	O
seeing	O
her	O
take	O
some	O
Thread	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
give	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
put	O
odd	O
things	O
in	O
:	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
refus	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
it	O
by	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
work	O
,	O
she	O
miss	O
'd	O
her	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
immediately	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
again	O
.	O
He	O
own	O
'd	O
at	O
his	O
Trial	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
but	O
knew	O
not	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
Gold	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
bringing	O
several	O
Persons	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Atsey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminister	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Linnen	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
perceiving	O
from	O
below	O
that	O
her	O
Chamber-door	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Trunk	O
broke	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
saw	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
dropt	O
the	O
Linnen	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Bag	O
.	O
She	O
deny	O
'd	O
she	O
was	O
ever	O
in	O
the	O
Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
some	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Precinct	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Katherines	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Fowling-pieces	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Nation	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
Instant	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
insufficient	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
being	O
Accessary	O
with	O
Rebekah	B-pers
Bottomly	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
convicted	O
last	O
Sessions	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Mug	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Prior	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
Lodgings	O
for	O
Bottomly	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
Notion	O
of	O
her	O
being	O
Colonel	O
Butler	O
's	O
Lady	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
frequently	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
she	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
present	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
when	O
she	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Lyner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
White	B-place
Chapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Perukes	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Hardings	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodging	O
at	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
hard	O
by	O
,	O
went	O
away	O
without	O
saying	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
thereupon	O
suspected	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
sold	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Parish	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Porringer	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Total	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
Brother	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
miss	O
'd	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
making	O
several	O
shuffling	O
Excuses	O
,	O
was	O
carry	O
'd	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Prison	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
several	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
;	O
but	O
his	O
own	O
Confession	O
prevail	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Jury	O
to	O
find	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Fadding	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Macfadding	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Frances	B-pers
Farmer	I-pers
(	O
an	O
Infant	O
)	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
her	O
of	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Gold	O
Ear-rings	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
Frock	O
and	O
Hood	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
Instant	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
found	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
led	O
astray	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Proof	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
doing	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
Word	O
;	O
which	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
satisfy	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cheshire-Cheese	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
Cheese	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shop	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Beadle	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Cheese	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
loose	O
Fellows	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
upon	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Eaton	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
another	O
young	O
Man	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
the	O
Cheese	O
to	O
carry	O
just	O
before	O
the	O
Beadle	O
met	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
not	O
being	O
belive	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Dooley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Acton	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Lambs	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bromley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
Day	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
12th	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
Queen	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
only	O
swore	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Lambs	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
fasten	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
by	O
an	O
Accomplice	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Hurd	O
and	O
Watkins	O
in	O
a	O
former	O
Tryal	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
exclaim	O
against	O
the	O
Witness	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Hammond	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Leg	O
of	O
Pork	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
instant	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Pork	O
being	O
stole	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shop	O
at	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
pursuing	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drop	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
nothing	O
material	O
to	O
offer	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Gill	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Wherry	O
Boat	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Sackley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
instant	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
having	O
lost	O
his	O
Boat	O
a	O
Night	O
and	O
a	O
Day	O
from	O
the	O
Old	B-place
Swan	I-place
,	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
at	O
Limekill-Dock	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
Boat	O
by	O
two	O
Men	O
,	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
it	O
till	O
High-water	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
come	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
Shilling	O
for	O
his	O
Pains	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
coming	O
before	O
,	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
stay	O
till	O
High	O
water	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
whether	O
they	O
would	O
come	O
or	O
no	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Case	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Millicent	B-pers
Downs	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchre	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Grizet	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Furbelow-Scarff	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Tayler	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
lodg	O
'd	O
a	O
Week	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
without	O
Warning	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
miss	O
'd	O
,	O
Search	O
was	O
made	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
confess	O
'd	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
alledg	O
'd	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
one	O
Sarah	B-pers
Heyden	I-pers
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
let	O
her	O
escape	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
Excuse	O
not	O
being	O
satisfactory	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susan	B-pers
Anderton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Stuff	O
Gowns	O
'	O
and	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Anderton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
very	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Gowns	O
taken	O
on	O
her	O
Back	O
,	O
whereupon	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Simons	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Lodging-Room	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Gratick	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Maye	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
a	O
Riding	O
Hood	O
,	O
a	O
Quilted	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
Silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
instant	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
out	O
,	O
her	O
Lodging	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Picklock-key	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
.	O
She	O
pretended	O
she	O
was	O
sent	O
by	O
another	O
so	O
carry	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
a	O
Woman	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
not	O
being	O
believ	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joanna	B-pers
Harpley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
and	O
Breeches	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
a	O
Pistole	O
,	O
and	O
40	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harpley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
coming	O
into	O
her	O
House	O
much	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
perswaded	O
him	O
to	O
lie	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
Bed	O
some	O
Time	O
,	O
her	O
Husband	O
came	O
and	O
jogg	O
'd	O
his	O
Head	O
to	O
wake	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
swearing	O
at	O
him	O
went	O
away	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
rise	O
all	O
his	O
Cloaths	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
His	O
Wife	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
instant	O
her	O
Husband	O
sent	O
for	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
found	O
him	O
fitting	O
in	O
Bed	O
with	O
a	O
Quilt	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
all	O
his	O
Cloths	O
being	O
gone	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
threatening	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
bid	O
her	O
not	O
make	O
such	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
she	O
'd	O
have	O
the	O
Goods	O
again	O
by	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
same	O
Purpose	O
was	O
sworn	O
by	O
another	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
with	O
a	O
Woman	O
who	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
drank	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
they	O
might	O
lodge	O
there	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
Woman	O
went	O
out	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
nor	O
knew	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
losing	O
the	O
Cloths	O
till	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
Noise	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Case	O
,	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Barnet	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Hackney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
Pigs	O
,	O
value	O
24	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
instant	O
.	O
The	O
Witness	O
was	O
one	O
Waple	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
bringing	O
a	O
Basket	O
of	O
fat	O
Pigs	O
to	O
Market	O
in	O
his	O
Cart	O
,	O
about	O
Stamford-hill	B-place
he	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
hankering	O
about	O
his	O
Cart	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
after	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
6	O
of	O
his	O
Pigs	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
back	O
again	O
in	O
Pursuit	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
getting	O
one	O
to	O
assist	O
him	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
stand	O
by	O
a	O
Stile	O
,	O
who	O
upon	O
their	O
Approach	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Pigs	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Basket	O
of	O
Black-Puddings	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
some	O
other	O
Cart	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
in	O
Waltham-stew	O
Parish	O
,	O
and	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
Waple	O
swore	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
being	O
full	O
Light	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
were	O
not	O
satisfy	O
'd	O
but	O
he	O
might	O
mistake	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecution	O
appear	O
'd	O
very	O
ridiculous	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Farringdon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
100	O
Weight	O
of	O
Hemp	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
200	O
Red	O
Herrings	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
instant	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
left	O
the	O
Hemp	O
with	O
one	O
Evans	O
to	O
sell	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
going	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
was	O
stopt	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
in	O
Expectation	O
of	O
Money	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
was	O
stopt	O
also	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
give	O
no	O
Account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
enquiry	O
the	O
Hemp	O
was	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
from	O
the	O
Bell-Inn	B-place
in	I-place
Warwick-lane	I-place
,	O
with	O
the	O
Herrings	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
when	O
taken	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
at	O
his	O
Trail	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gundy	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Treagoose	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Elliston	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
15	O
l.	O
of	O
Brass	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Hubbard	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Witness	O
swore	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
proving	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
one	O
Stoneham	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
caus	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
Prison	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Everton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Nathanael	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
having	O
lost	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
he	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
Justice	O
Ward	O
,	O
before	O
whom	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
at	O
her	O
Trial	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Lewis	B-pers
Amond	I-pers
de	I-pers
la	I-pers
Cour	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
speaking	O
dangerous	O
Words	O
against	O
his	O
Majesty	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
positively	O
sworn	O
by	O
one	O
Witness	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
utter	O
'd	O
himself	O
in	O
French	O
to	O
this	O
Purpose	O
,	O
King	O
George	O
has	O
not	O
any	O
just	O
Protection	O
to	O
the	O
Crowds	O
of	O
Great	O
Britain	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Pretender	O
has	O
a	O
lawful	O
Right	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
another	O
Witness	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
said	O
in	O
French	O
likewise	O
Words	O
importing	O
,	O
'T	O
is	O
Pity	O
the	O
Pretender	O
is	O
not	O
King	O
of	O
Great	O
Britain	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
fine	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Time	O
may	O
come	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
Crown	O
.	O
In	O
his	O
Defence	O
he	O
had	O
People	O
who	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Tavern	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Witnesses	O
with	O
other	O
Company	O
were	O
drinking	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
they	O
staid	O
till	O
6	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
very	O
friendly	O
,	O
only	O
much	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
till	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
bidding	O
them	O
call	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
spoke	O
Treason	O
.	O
One	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
their	O
Company	O
(	O
but	O
went	O
home	O
at	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
)	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
as	O
readily	O
as	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
drank	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Health	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
King	O
George	O
;	O
but	O
at	O
to	O
what	O
happen	O
'd	O
after	O
he	O
went	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
say	O
nothing	O
.	O
The	O
Words	O
were	O
very	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Misdemeanor	O
.	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	I-pers
(	I-pers
commonly	I-pers
known	I-pers
by	I-pers
the	I-pers
Name	I-pers
of	I-pers
Half	I-pers
hang	I-pers
'd	I-pers
Smith	I-pers
)	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Ware-house	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Longuit	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Partners	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
his	O
Trial	O
is	O
deferr	O
'd	O
till	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
over	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
,	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
3.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Parrot	I-pers
,	O
Shadrach	B-pers
Guy	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
21.	O
Christian	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hurrel	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Radley	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
Rachel	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
Priscilla	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hurd	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Barns	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Atsey	I-pers
,	O
C	O
-	O
A	O
-	O
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Parish	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Dooly	I-pers
,	O
Millicent	B-pers
Downs	I-pers
,	O
Susan	B-pers
Anderton	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Simons	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Farringdon	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gundy	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whip	O
'd	O
17.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Bullock	I-pers
,	O
Martha	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Moor	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Kimbal	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Culver	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Dupre	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Christian	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Robins	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Burnet	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Lyner	I-pers
,	O
Anthony	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Hammond	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Everton	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Wide	I-pers
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
at	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
fin	O
'd	O
a	O
Mark	O
,	O
lye	O
3	O
Months	O
in	O
Prison	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
Security	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
for	O
a	O
Year	O
.	O
Lewis	B-pers
Amond	I-pers
de	I-pers
la	I-pers
Cour	I-pers
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
at	O
Charing	O
Cross	O
,	O
fin	O
'd	O
a	O
Mark	O
,	O
lye	O
3	O
Months	O
in	O
Prison	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
Security	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
for	O
a	O
Year	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Good	O
of	O
the	O
Publick	O
.	O
Whereas	O
several	O
Gentlewomen	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
that	O
Sex	O
in	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
have	O
contracted	O
an	O
evil	O
Habit	O
of	O
Body	O
,	O
wherein	O
the	O
vicious	O
Humours	O
at	O
first	O
dispersed	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
come	O
at	O
length	O
to	O
be	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
one	O
Part	O
or	O
another	O
;	O
and	O
many	O
times	O
for	O
Causes	O
too	O
long	O
to	O
be	O
here	O
mentioned	O
,	O
are	O
thrown	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Womb	O
,	O
occasioning	O
a	O
dangerous	O
Weakness	O
in	O
that	O
Part	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
neglected	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
turns	O
cancerous	O
,	O
and	O
often	O
proves	O
fatal	O
.	O
I	O
the	O
Diabetes	O
,	O
when	O
given	O
over	O
by	O
all	O
other	O
Persons	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
to	O
acquaint	O
all	O
such	O
as	O
may	O
have	O
Occasion	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
speed	O
Relief	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
had	O
from	O
an	O
experienced	O
Midwife	O
,	O
dwelling	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms	O
,	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
near	O
Exeter	O
Exchange	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
who	O
perform	O
'd	O
a	O
Core	O
upon	O
a	O
Lady	O
at	O
the	O
Bath	O
,	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
given	O
over	O
by	O
Physicians	O
,	O
and	O
since	O
has	O
cured	O
several	O
Gentlewomen	O
and	O
others	O
in	O
the	O
City	O
and	O
Suburbs	O
of	O
London	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Cheshire	O
Cheese	O
in	O
Wallbrook	O
,	O
near	O
Stocks-market	O
.	O
LIveth	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
,	O
the	O
Daughter	O
of	O
an	O
eminent	O
Physician	O
,	O
who	O
practis	O
'd	O
in	O
London	O
for	O
upwards	O
of	O
40	O
Years	O
.	O
She	O
hath	O
a	O
never	O
failing	O
Ointment	O
that	O
cures	O
the	O
GOUT	O
,	O
altho	O
'	O
the	O
Parties	O
be	O
reduc	O
'd	O
to	O
their	O
Crutches	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Days	O
time	O
;	O
having	O
been	O
found	O
true	O
by	O
Experience	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
great	O
Ease	O
and	O
Comfort	O
of	O
many	O
.	O
It	O
also	O
cures	O
Rheumatick	O
Pains	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
also	O
a	O
certain	O
and	O
infallible	O
Cur	O
for	O
the	O
Toothach	O
,	O
without	O
Drawing	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
effectually	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Pain	O
will	O
never	O
return	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
not	O
only	O
so	O
,	O
but	O
makes	O
the	O
Teeth	O
as	O
white	O
as	O
Ivory	O
;	O
and	O
faslens	O
those	O
that	O
are	O
loose	O
toe	O
Admiration	O
.	O
Her	O
House	O
are	O
from	O
8	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
till	O
12	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
2	O
till	O
6	O
.	O
ALL	O
Melancholy	O
,	O
Hysterical	O
,	O
and	O
Hypochondriacal	O
Distempers	O
,	O
which	O
variously	O
affect	O
the	O
Mind	O
with	O
strange	O
Fears	O
,	O
and	O
dismal	O
Apprehensions	O
3	O
Faintings	O
and	O
Sinkings	O
of	O
the	O
Spirits	O
,	O
great	O
Hurries	O
,	O
Restlessness	O
,	O
and	O
Disquietment	O
,	O
(	O
little	O
understood	O
,	O
and	O
seldom	O
cur	O
'd	O
by	O
any	O
common	O
Means	O
.	O
)	O
Also	O
Pains	O
and	O
Giddiness	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
Risings	O
to	O
the	O
Throat	O
,	O
sick	O
Fits	O
,	O
Tremblings	O
,	O
Oppressions	O
of	O
the	O
Heart	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
other	O
Disorders	O
caus	O
'd	O
by	O
Vapours	O
,	O
are	O
successfully	O
cured	O
(	O
with	O
God	O
's	O
Blessing	O
)	O
by	O
a	O
Physician	O
well	O
experienced	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
more	O
than	O
20	O
Years	O
Practice	O
in	O
those	O
deplorable	O
Cases	O
;	O
who	O
also	O
cures	O
all	O
kind	O
of	O
Fits	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
strange	O
and	O
violent	O
,	O
if	O
curable	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
informs	O
on	O
sight	O
of	O
their	O
Water	O
.	O
Now	O
living	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
the	O
Shares	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
Chambers-Street	O
,	O
in	O
Goodmans-Fields	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Minories	O
;	O
where	O
those	O
that	O
have	O
Occasion	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
remote	O
,	O
may	O
direct	O
their	O
Letters	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
shall	O
be	O
speedily	O
answered	O
or	O
attended	O
on	O
if	O
desired	O
.	O
A	O
Friendly	O
and	O
Compassionate	O
Exhortation	O
to	O
Virtue	O
.	O
In	O
Five	O
short	O
Practical	O
Discourses	O
;	O
against	O
Prophane	O
Swearings	O
,	O
Downhouness	O
,	O
Gaming	O
,	O
Detraction	O
,	O
and	O
Immodesty	O
.	O
Wherein	O
the	O
Sinfulness	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
seriously	O
brought	O
home	O
to	O
every	O
Man	O
's	O
Consenuce	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Means	O
of	O
avoiding	O
'em	O
plainly	O
and	O
familiarly	O
set	O
forth	O
.	O
By	O
G.R.B.D	O
.	O
Price	O
Bound	O
6	O
d.	O
Youth	O
's	O
Introduction	O
to	O
Trade	O
.	O
An	O
Exercise	O
Book	O
,	O
chiefly	O
designed	O
for	O
the	O
Use	O
of	O
the	O
Writing	O
School	O
,	O
so	O
employ	O
Youth	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
vacant	O
Times	O
,	O
while	O
they	O
learn	O
to	O
Write	O
;	O
by	O
which	O
the	O
Young	O
Apprentice	O
may	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
apply	O
his	O
Writing	O
and	O
Arithmetick	O
to	O
Business	O
;	O
as	O
,	O
a	O
Merchant	O
,	O
Shop-keeper	O
,	O
or	O
other	O
Interior	O
Trades	O
.	O
First	O
Methodised	O
for	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
the	O
Author	O
's	O
Scholars	O
;	O
And	O
published	O
for	O
the	O
Use	O
of	O
such	O
as	O
much	O
Writing	O
and	O
Arithmetik	O
.	O
By	O
John	B-pers
Anon	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Fourth	O
Edition	O
,	O
Corrected	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
much	O
Enlarged	O
.	O
Just	O
Reprinted	O
,	O
The	O
New	O
A-la-moda	O
Secretary	O
,	O
Practical	O
Consisting	O
of	O
Variety	O
of	O
Hands	O
,	O
very	O
useful	O
for	O
Young	O
Beginners	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
same	O
Author	O
.	O
to	O
the	O
of	O
the	O
Common-Prayer-Book	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
People	O
attending	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Offered	O
to	O
the	O
Consideration	O
of	O
whole	O
who	O
for	O
promoting	O
Decency	O
in	O
the	O
Service	O
of	O
God	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
usage	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
Establish	O
'd	O
by	O
Law	O
.	O
With	O
a	O
Preface	O
of	O
Diana	O
Warship	O
in	O
General	O
.	O
By	O
T.	O
Soynor	O
,	O
Lay-man	O
.	O
The	O
Fourth	O
Edition	O
,	O
Corrected	O
.	O
The	O
Ingenious	O
and	O
Diverting	O
Letters	O
of	O
the	O
Lady	O
's	O
-	O
Travels	O
into	O
Spain	O
.	O
Describing	O
the	O
Devotions	O
,	O
Nunneries	O
,	O
Humour	O
,	O
Customs	O
,	O
Laws	O
Militia	O
,	O
Trade	O
,	O
Diet	O
,	O
and	O
Recreations	O
of	O
that	O
People	O
.	O
Intermixt	O
with	O
great	O
Variety	O
of	O
Modern	O
Adventures	O
,	O
and	O
surprising	O
Accidents	O
:	O
Being	O
the	O
truest	O
and	O
best	O
Remarks	O
extant	O
on	O
that	O
Court	O
and	O
Country	O
.	O
The	O
Seventh	O
Edition	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Addition	O
of	O
Letter	O
of	O
the	O
State	O
of	O
Spain	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
Year	O
1700	O
.	O
Never	O
before	O
in	O
English	O
.	O
In	O
Three	O
Parts	O
.	O
Tables	O
of	O
Simple	O
Interest	O
and	O
Discount	O
,	O
at	O
3	O
,	O
4	O
,	O
5	O
,	O
6	O
,	O
7	O
,	O
8	O
,	O
9	O
,	O
and	O
10	O
per	O
Cent	O
.	O
per	O
.	O
Ann	O
.	O
Also	O
Tables	O
of	O
Compound	O
Interest	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Rates	O
.	O
Whereby	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
present	O
Value	O
of	O
any	O
Sum	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
Annuity	O
,	O
or	O
other	O
yearly	O
Payment	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
for	O
any	O
Number	O
of	O
Years	O
,	O
not	O
exceeding	O
,	O
One	O
Hundred	O
,	O
is	O
readily	O
found	O
.	O
By	O
John	B-pers
Smart	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Town-Clerk's-Office	O
,	O
London	O
.	O
All	O
Printed	O
for	O
S.	O
Crouch	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Pope's-Head-Alley	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
CROUCH	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Pope's-head	O
Ally	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
;	O
And	O
Sold	O
by	O
J.	O
Baker	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Black	O
Boy	O
in	O
Pater-noster-row	O
.	O
Advertisements	O
are	O
taken	O
in	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Humfreys	I-pers
,	O
Printer	O
,	O
in	O
Bartholomew-Lane	O
,	O
behind	O
the	O
R.	O
Exchange	O
.	O
