TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
12th	O
,	O
13th	O
,	O
14th	O
,	O
and	O
15th	O
,	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
1715	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Second	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEfore	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HUMFREYS	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
and	O
Bart	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
Parker	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Tracy	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Bury	I-pers
,	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
;	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bridge	I-pers
Benjamin	B-pers
Gardiner	I-pers
John	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
George	B-pers
Lamb	I-pers
William	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
Mark	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
John	B-pers
Towers	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Garret	I-pers
Daniel	B-pers
Baily	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Leppidge	I-pers
William	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
Fenwick	B-pers
Lambert	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
Benjamin	B-pers
Jackman	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Orbell	I-pers
George	B-pers
Langton	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Tompkins	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Bateman	I-pers
John	B-pers
Millett	I-pers
John	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
John	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Anthony	B-pers
Goddard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
New-Fish-Street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hamper	O
containing	O
6	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Red	O
Wine	O
,	O
6	O
Quarts	O
of	O
Canary	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
Quarts	O
of	O
White	O
Wine	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Guy	I-pers
.	O
A	O
Beadle	O
swore	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
by	O
the	O
Hamper	O
with	O
Straws	O
in	O
his	O
Wigg	O
;	O
and	O
secur	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
A	O
Boy	O
swore	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
rest	O
the	O
Hamper	O
upon	O
a	O
Stall	O
;	O
and	O
Mr	O
.	O
Guy	O
swore	O
to	O
the	O
Wine	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
had	O
the	O
Hamper	O
.	O
The	O
jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Steel	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Elson	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Benson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Magnus	I-place
by	I-place
the	I-place
Bridge	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gallon	O
Pot	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Barrow	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
instant	O
.	O
An	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Pot	O
,	O
and	O
apprehended	O
him	O
;	O
who	O
then	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
nothing	O
else	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
;	O
and	O
was	O
therefore	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Fairclough	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Eastcheap	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
23	O
Yards	O
of	O
Masquerade	O
Rozette	O
S	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jacob	B-pers
Wyern	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
upon	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
another	O
Woman	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
for	O
a	O
Lining	O
to	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
occasion	O
'd	O
the	O
opening	O
of	O
several	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Goods	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Ridgeway	I-pers
came	O
in	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
want	O
a	O
Lining	O
for	O
a	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
and	O
appearing	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
Hurry	O
,	O
imployed	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
shew	O
him	O
Shaloon	O
for	O
that	O
purpose	O
and	O
whilst	O
the	O
Persons	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
were	O
so	O
busily	O
employ	O
'd	O
in	O
shewing	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Silk	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
between	O
her	O
Knees	O
.	O
In	O
her	O
Defence	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
Roll	O
of	O
Silk	O
fell	O
from	O
the	O
Counter	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
being	O
absurd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
contrary	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Wade	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
in	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
6	O
Yards	O
of	O
Silk	O
Ribbond	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Robert	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
An	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
want	O
some	O
Ribbond	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
being	O
shew	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
pleasing	O
,	O
while	O
they	O
was	O
looking	O
for	O
more	O
she	O
took	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
that	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
and	O
apprehended	O
,	O
she	O
brought	O
the	O
Goods	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
Box	O
again	O
privately	O
;	O
but	O
having	O
no	O
Opportunity	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
laid	O
it	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Counter	O
.	O
In	O
her	O
Defence	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
charg	O
'd	O
wrongfully	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Isaac	B-pers
Ragg	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Stanwell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
several	O
Yards	O
of	O
Checques	O
,	O
Dowlas	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Linen	O
and	O
Goods	O
from	O
the	O
said	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Stanwell	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
a	O
Witness	O
to	O
prove	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
drinking	O
Wine	O
at	O
a	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
till	O
Eleven	O
a	O
Clock	O
that	O
Night	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
lay	O
together	O
till	O
6	O
a	O
Clock	O
next	O
Morning	O
:	O
Upon	O
which	O
Account	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
failing	O
in	O
their	O
Proof	O
that	O
he	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
in	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
20	O
Yards	O
of	O
course	O
Muslin	O
,	O
value	O
24	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
An	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
coming	O
down	O
Cornhill	B-place
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
loitering	O
about	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
suspected	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
Rogues	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
them	O
run	O
on	O
a	O
sudden	O
cross	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
follow	O
'd	O
them	O
and	O
seiz	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
between	O
whom	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
was	O
dropt	O
the	O
Goods	O
above-mention	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
a	O
person	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
;	O
who	O
doing	O
him	O
but	O
little	O
Service	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Olave	I-place
Hartstreet	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
Case	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Rust	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Rust	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
,	O
she	O
observ	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
brush	O
close	O
by	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
after	O
miss	O
'd	O
her	O
Watch	O
Case	O
;	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
Suspecting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
charg	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
who	O
then	O
let	O
it	O
fall	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
to	O
the	O
fame	O
purpose	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
third	O
saw	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Hand	O
.	O
She	O
made	O
no	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Fell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Peter	I-place
's	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
21	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Tomkins	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Tomkins	O
swore	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
her	O
Stall	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
buying	O
a	O
Pennyworth	O
of	O
Pears	O
,	O
with	O
one	O
Hand	O
under	O
her	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
whilst	O
she	O
was	O
putting	O
them	O
into	O
her	O
Lap	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Hand	O
under	O
her	O
Apron	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
Pears	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
missing	O
her	O
Money	O
,	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
that	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
there	O
.	O
This	O
Evidence	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
another	O
's	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
Defence	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
own	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
just	O
receiv	O
'd	O
it	O
as	O
Wages	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Payne	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Olave	I-place
Hartstreet	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
180	O
l.	O
weight	O
of	O
Inkle	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Stafford	B-pers
Briscoe	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
Instant	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
very	O
fully	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
having	O
been	O
a	O
Robbery	O
about	O
George-yard	O
on	O
Tower-hill	O
just	O
before	O
;	O
the	O
Constable	O
there	O
kept	O
a	O
strict	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
3	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
coming	O
by	O
them	O
with	O
something	O
on	O
their	O
Heads	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
challeng	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
but	O
made	O
no	O
answer	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Watchman	O
Davis	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
see	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
Sack	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
must	O
have	O
:	O
the	O
Sack	O
,	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
d	O
-	O
d	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
threw	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
fame	O
time	O
calling	O
to	O
his	O
Companion	O
,	O
to	O
thrown	O
down	O
his	O
Sack	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
gone	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
he	O
'd	O
be	O
taken	O
;	O
as	O
himself	O
was	O
immediately	O
after	O
in	O
a	O
mighty	O
Sweat	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
swore	O
,	O
his	O
Master	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
the	O
Night	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
both	O
the	O
Sacks	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
sort	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
some	O
Persons	O
to	O
prove	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
that	O
Night	O
from	O
Gravesend	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
Land	O
till	O
between	O
3	O
and	O
4	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
having	O
an	O
indifferent	O
Reputation	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
too	O
busie	O
in	O
disswading	O
the	O
Evidence	O
from	O
appearing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
by	O
a	O
promise	O
of	O
5	O
Guineas	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
half	O
Guineas	O
,	O
1	O
Guinea	O
and	O
3	O
l.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
from	O
Ambrose	B-pers
Granger	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
very	O
presumptuous	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
positive	O
;	O
some	O
Persons	O
whom	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
giving	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
got	O
an	O
honest	O
Livelihood	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Barefoot	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White	I-place
Chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
an	O
Infant	O
,	O
by	O
drawing	O
the	O
off	O
Wheel	O
of	O
a	O
Dray	O
over	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
himself	O
sitting	O
on	O
the	O
Dray	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
he	O
languish	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
11th	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
some	O
Children	O
were	O
playing	O
together	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Child	O
George	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
was	O
stooping	O
to	O
take	O
some	O
Mulberry	O
Leaves	O
off	O
the	O
Ground	O
when	O
the	O
Dray	O
went	O
over	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
his	O
Skull	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
usually	O
very	O
careful	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Accident	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Man-slaughter	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Worsly	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Perjury	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Cause	O
between	O
Nath	B-pers
Simms	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Edw	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
tried	O
before	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
Parker	O
,	O
in	O
these	O
Words	O
;	O
Edw	O
.	O
Hunt	O
did	O
beat	O
Ann	B-pers
Simms	I-pers
so	O
,	O
that	O
Ann	O
Simms	O
was	O
carried	O
in	O
a	O
Doors	O
in	O
two	O
Minutes	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Ann	O
Simms	O
could	O
not	O
stand	O
in	O
7	O
Weeks	O
time	O
after	O
,	O
for	O
two	O
Days	O
,	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
a	O
new	O
born	O
Babe	O
.	O
Whereas	O
the	O
said	O
Ann	O
Simms	O
was	O
seen	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
very	O
frequently	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
ever	O
;	O
being	O
no	O
ways	O
Hurt	O
.	O
The	O
Council	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
brought	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
said	O
Trial	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Fast	O
,	O
and	O
most	O
of'em	O
agreed	O
in	O
the	O
Sense	O
of	O
the	O
Words	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
saw	O
Ann	O
Simms	O
very	O
frequently	O
after	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
by	O
her	O
Council	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
the	O
Words	O
she	O
swore	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Cause	O
were	O
,	O
That	O
Ann	O
Simms	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
her	O
being	O
beat	O
,	O
fell	O
into	O
a	O
Fit	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
them	O
so	O
often	O
after	O
,	O
that	O
in	O
7	O
Week	O
time	O
she	O
was	O
reduc	O
'd	O
so	O
low	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
stand	O
or	O
go	O
,	O
any	O
more	O
than	O
a	O
new	O
born	O
Babe	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Condition	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Colthurst	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
speaking	O
seditiously	O
,	O
maliciously	O
and	O
traitorously	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Person	O
,	O
his	O
Crown	O
,	O
and	O
Dignity	O
,	O
in	O
these	O
Words	O
;	O
If	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
with	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
(	O
meaning	O
the	O
King	O
of	O
Great	O
Britain	O
)	O
be	O
would	O
dash	O
his	O
Brains	O
out	O
against	O
the	O
Wall	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
if	O
they	O
should	O
beat	O
up	O
for	O
Voluntiers	O
for	O
King	O
GEORGE	O
,	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
the	O
Pretender	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
serve	O
the	O
Pretender	O
.	O
An	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
frequently	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
talk	O
'd	O
at	O
that	O
reasonable	O
Rate	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
once	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
mend	O
his	O
Language	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
himself	O
a	O
Mischief	O
;	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
durst	O
not	O
talk	O
so	O
before	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Face	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
desire	O
no	O
better	O
Sport	O
,	O
than	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
with	O
the	O
King	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
would	O
dash	O
his	O
Brains	O
out	O
against	O
the	O
Wall	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
,	O
That	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
beating	O
up	O
for	O
Voluntiers	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
the	O
Pretender	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
's	O
I	O
would	O
serve	O
the	O
Pretender	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
Witness	O
who	O
swore	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
desperate	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
once	O
had	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
murder	O
his	O
own	O
Wife	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
two	O
Persons	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
;	O
who	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
himself	O
,	O
did	O
no	O
Service	O
that	O
way	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Stephen	B-pers
Hutchinson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Cheat	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Margaret	B-pers
Yeoman	I-pers
,	O
did	O
contrive	O
and	O
send	O
a	O
Letter	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Bridget	B-pers
Hutchinson	I-pers
,	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
they	O
received	O
3	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Bridget	O
Hutchinson	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
appear	O
'd	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Glanister	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
4	O
Scarlet	O
Camblet	O
Curtains	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
and	O
abundance	O
of	O
other	O
rich	O
Goods	O
from	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	O
Shepherd	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Seal	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
directing	O
and	O
ordering	O
the	O
forging	O
a	O
counterfeit	O
Stamp	O
,	O
in	O
Imitation	O
of	O
the	O
King	B-pers
's	O
Stamp	O
upon	O
Cards	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
deprive	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Majesty	O
of	O
the	O
Duty	O
of	O
6	O
d.	O
per	O
Pack	O
,	O
by	O
Act	O
of	O
Parliament	O
so	O
made	O
and	O
provided	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
evident	O
,	O
Seal	O
went	O
to	O
one	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
imitate	O
such	O
a	O
Stamp	O
;	O
who	O
saying	O
he	O
could	O
,	O
Seal	O
gave	O
him	O
Directions	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
Seal	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
him	O
a	O
Crown	O
;	O
but	O
Street	O
thinking	O
it	O
too	O
much	O
,	O
contented	O
himself	O
with	O
3	O
s	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
counterfeit	O
Stamp	O
was	O
compar	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
true	O
one	O
;	O
and	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
exact	O
Imitation	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
he	O
ever	O
paid	O
Street	O
any	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
brought	O
several	O
Persons	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
;	O
but	O
a	O
Point	O
of	O
Law	O
arising	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
directed	O
the	O
Jury	O
to	O
bring	O
it	O
in	O
Special	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Mantle	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
;	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Dressing-box	O
value	O
4s	O
.	O
4	O
Linnen	O
Aprons	O
4s	O
.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Robert	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
.	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Sash	O
was	O
fore	O
'd	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Hand	O
was	O
seen	O
put	O
through	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
taking	O
hold	O
of	O
a	O
Napkin	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
a	O
Boy	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
fled	O
;	O
but	O
was	O
immediately	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Newell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
Furbelow	O
Scarf	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
1	O
Hood	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
unjust	O
Prosecution	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Fairborne	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Ralph	B-pers
Morton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
13th	O
Year	O
of	O
Queen	O
Anne	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Chip	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
5	O
l.	O
weight	O
of	O
dy	O
'd	O
Silk	O
,	O
5	O
l.	O
of	O
raw	O
Silk	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
great	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Day	O
time	O
,	O
no	O
Person	O
being	O
therein	O
.	O
Morton	O
swore	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
House	O
about	O
2	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
home	O
,	O
found	O
11	O
Locks	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
stole	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
,	O
one	O
Keene	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
two	O
more	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Harris	O
put	O
in	O
a	O
Picklock	O
Key	O
and	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
he	O
also	O
told	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
.	O
This	O
Evidence	O
describ	O
'd	O
all	O
the	O
Goods	O
that	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Information	O
;	O
and	O
swore	O
the	O
Fact	O
directly	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
who	O
for	O
his	O
Defence	O
exhibited	O
a	O
Petition	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
(	O
pretending	O
a	O
great	O
Impediment	O
in	O
his	O
Speech	O
)	O
Setting	O
forth	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
unfortunately	O
acquainted	O
with	O
this	O
latter	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
him	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
a	O
House-breaking	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
refused	O
it	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
said	O
Keene	O
swore	O
this	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
save	O
his	O
own	O
Life	O
:	O
But	O
sometime	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
forgot	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
a	O
clear	O
strong	O
Voice	O
quarsell	O
'd	O
with	O
this	O
Evidence	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
't	O
was	O
depos	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Mother	O
kept	O
a	O
very	O
ill	O
House	O
in	O
Houndsditch	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
Retreat	O
and	O
Receptacle	O
for	O
Pickpockets	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
loose	O
Persons	O
,	O
and	O
stolen	O
Goods	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Harld	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
half	O
a	O
Yard	O
of	O
Mantua	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Salt	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Moon	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Goods	O
above-mention	O
'd	O
;	O
which	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
when	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Daniel	B-pers
Blunt	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Snuff-Box	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Greenway	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
Greenway	O
swore	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
his	O
Snuff-box	O
to	O
oblige	O
his	O
Friend	O
with	O
a	O
Pinch	O
;	O
afterwards	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
standing	O
by	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
feeling	O
again	O
for	O
his	O
Box	O
,	O
miss	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
went	O
directly	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Coat	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
Ground	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
false	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Ewers	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
100	O
weight	O
of	O
Logwood	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Bowman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Rutter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
1	O
Muslin	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
4	O
Holland	O
Sleeves	O
,	O
2	O
Diaper	O
Napkins	O
,	O
a	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
15	O
s.	O
from	O
Edmund	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Thompson	O
swore	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
her	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
been	O
rob	O
'd	O
sometime	O
before	O
without	O
discovering	O
the	O
Thief	O
,	O
upon	O
this	O
Loss	O
she	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
knowing	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Child	O
at	O
Nurse	O
,	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
with	O
her	O
own	O
Clothes	O
,	O
they	O
lying	O
all	O
together	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
impossible	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
they	O
were	O
lock	O
'd	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Silver	O
Cups	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
2	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
some	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
Martin	B-pers
Innold	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
,	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
She	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
when	O
taken	O
;	O
which	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
;	O
and	O
making	O
no	O
Defence	O
at	O
her	O
Trial	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Muslin	O
Aprons	O
,	O
2	O
Holland	O
Aprons	O
,	O
2	O
Callico	O
Aprons	O
,	O
some	O
Sheets	O
,	O
Neckcloths	O
,	O
and	O
abundance	O
of	O
other	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
47	O
Shillings	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Burrows	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
27	O
Yards	O
of	O
Shalloon	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Yards	O
of	O
Serge	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jo	B-pers
.	I-pers
Boxman	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
boldly	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
got	O
upon	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
and	O
reach	O
'd	O
down	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
immediately	O
stop	O
'd	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
threw	O
down	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
He	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Peter	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Precinct	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Catherines	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Flock	O
Beds	O
and	O
Blankets	O
,	O
2	O
Coats	O
,	O
Wastcoats	O
,	O
and	O
1	O
Perriwig	O
,	O
from	O
James	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
apprehended	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Wigg	O
that	O
he	O
threw	O
down	O
a	O
Vault	O
,	O
was	O
sworn	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
,	O
a	O
Peruke	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
instant	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
home	O
with	O
a	O
Friend	O
,	O
about	O
10	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
his	O
Wigg	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
behind	O
him	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
his	O
friend	O
pursued	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
dropt	O
the	O
Wigg	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Bagnall	B-pers
Wallis	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
1	O
Silver	O
Skimmer	O
,	O
1	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Tongs	O
,	O
half	O
a	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Tea-Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
said	O
Bagnall	O
Wallis	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Day	O
time	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
evident	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Proof	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Dunstall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
16	O
Yards	O
of	O
Flannel	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Baily	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3	O
d	O
instant	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Baily	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
sitting	O
by	O
his	O
Bulk	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Flannel	O
move	O
;	O
and	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Flannel	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
very	O
positive	O
in	O
the	O
Man	O
;	O
who	O
making	O
but	O
a	O
trifling	O
Defence	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Britton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3	O
d.	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Britton	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
her	O
Shop	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
of	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
them	O
on	O
a	O
Bed	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
laid	O
a	O
Guinea	O
just	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
open	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
his	O
Bundle	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Guinea	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
apprehended	O
him	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
it	O
upon	O
him	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
a	O
good	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Nature	O
of	O
the	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Dennis	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Pigs	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Raymond	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
instant	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
driving	O
the	O
Pigs	O
towards	O
London	O
,	O
when	O
an	O
Evidence	O
met	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
the	O
Pigs	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
sworn	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
Callico	O
Gown	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
1	O
Petticoat	O
10	O
s.	O
1	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shooes	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Mably	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
Mrs	O
Mably	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
Hurry	O
did	O
not	O
suspect	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
by	O
and	O
by	O
her	O
Daughter	O
called	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Woman	O
was	O
come	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
with	O
her	O
Apron	O
full	O
of	O
Goods	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
she	O
pursu	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
her	O
Apron	O
.	O
She	O
only	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Stapleton	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Stevenson	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Merrick	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Marriot	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Gregory	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Coldwell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
instant	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
7	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
2	O
Damask	O
Table	O
clothes	O
,	O
12	O
Diaper	O
Table	O
clothes	O
,	O
12	O
Damask	O
Napkins	O
,	O
24	O
Diaper	O
Napkins	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
from	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
Coldwell	O
;	O
no	O
Person	O
being	O
therein	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Family	O
being	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
,	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
Street	O
Door	O
was	O
left	O
with	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
;	O
who	O
having	O
occasion	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
found	O
the	O
Door	O
but	O
single	O
lock	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Chip	O
under	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
going	O
up	O
2	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
found	O
a	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
gone	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
put	O
4	O
brave	O
stout	O
young	O
Men	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
arm	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Door	O
just	O
as	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Chip	O
under	O
it	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
,	O
the	O
young	O
Men	O
,	O
who	O
divided	O
themselves	O
;	O
two	O
into	O
the	O
Garret	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchin	O
,	O
heard	O
the	O
Lock	O
fly	O
back	O
as	O
readily	O
as	O
if	O
it	O
were	O
done	O
by	O
the	O
right	O
Key	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Persons	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
who	O
double	O
Lock	O
'd	O
and	O
bolted	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
;	O
and	O
immediately	O
after	O
,	O
those	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
heard	O
two	O
Pistols	O
go	O
off	O
,	O
who	O
then	O
struck	O
a	O
Light	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
Stapleton	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
two	O
Friends	O
who	O
were	O
above	O
,	O
coming	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Rogues	O
being	O
first	O
,	O
they	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Dining	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
shut	O
the	O
Door	O
upon	O
themselves	O
,	O
thrusting	O
their	O
Backs	O
against	O
it	O
,	O
to	O
keep	O
it	O
close	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
threatened	O
by	O
an	O
Evidence	O
he	O
would	O
fire	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
open	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
Stapleton	O
taken	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
others	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
escap	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
2	O
young	O
Men	O
who	O
were	O
above	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
heard	O
the	O
Door	O
unlock	O
'd	O
,	O
thought	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
their	O
own	O
Companions	O
,	O
but	O
were	O
soon	O
better	O
inform	O
'd	O
,	O
by	O
hearing	O
a	O
Man	O
with	O
a	O
hoarse	O
Voice	O
(	O
like	O
Merrick	O
's	O
)	O
say	O
,	O
If	O
we	O
find	O
any	O
Body	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
we	O
'll	O
shoot	O
'em	O
,	O
who	O
coming	O
up	O
the	O
Garret-Stairs	O
,	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
whereupon	O
they	O
turn	O
'd	O
their	O
Lanthorn	O
dark	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
By	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
wo	O
n't	O
fire	O
now	O
,	O
we	O
will	O
:	O
Upon	O
which	O
they	O
fir	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
missing	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
who	O
immediately	O
ran	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
they	O
pursued	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
their	O
Companions	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Merrick	O
,	O
nor	O
King	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
;	O
but	O
Stapleton	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Katherine	B-pers
Vincent	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Ink	O
Stand	O
,	O
and	O
Sandish	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Christiern	B-pers
Hartemburgh	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
was	O
very	O
weak	O
and	O
uncertain	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
calling	O
some	O
Persons	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Stiff	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Calico	O
Quilt	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
Queen	O
.	O
One	O
Keene	O
made	O
himself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
describ	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
that	O
were	O
stole	O
in	O
his	O
Information	O
;	O
he	O
depos	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
with	O
a	O
Pick-lock	O
Key	O
.	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Stiff	O
swore	O
she	O
was	O
rob	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
He	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
but	O
had	O
no	O
Body	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Sull	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
a	O
Velvet	O
Scarf	O
,	O
some	O
Shirts	O
,	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
Timothy	B-pers
Merriman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Merriman	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
the	O
Fact	O
positively	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
who	O
brought	O
some	O
Persons	O
that	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
;	O
therefore	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Turvy	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
5	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
1	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Grindall	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
Grindall	O
swore	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
by	O
him	O
to	O
mend	O
his	O
Stair-Case	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
lost	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
apprehended	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Spoons	O
,	O
but	O
denied	O
taking	O
the	O
Cup	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
also	O
prov	O
'd	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
pawn	O
the	O
Spoons	O
.	O
He	O
made	O
a	O
poor	O
Defence	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Blunt	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Bunner	I-pers
,	O
Rachael	B-pers
Peters	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Vanderbuss	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Peters	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Blunt	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
he	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Goslin	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
16	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Necklace	O
,	O
a	O
Coral	O
,	O
abundance	O
of	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
15	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	O
Goslin	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Kestern	I-pers
;	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
Women	O
as	O
Accessaries	O
in	O
receiving	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
Mrs	O
Goslin	O
swore	O
,	O
her	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
stole	O
.	O
The	O
Maid	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
Cellar-Window	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
strange	O
Knife	O
upon	O
the	O
Stairs	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
notorious	O
Offender	O
,	O
Mrs	O
Goslin	O
had	O
a	O
Warrant	O
to	O
search	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Abundance	O
of	O
her	O
Goods	O
there	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Fellow	O
of	O
the	O
Knife	O
that	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Board	O
that	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Cellar-Window	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
also	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
James	O
Blunt	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
did	O
the	O
Robbery	O
himself	O
:	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
very	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
Sarah	O
Peters	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
Blunt	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Rachael	B-pers
Peters	I-pers
was	O
her	O
Mother	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
upon	O
his	O
Trial	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
they	O
were	O
stole	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Man	O
guilty	O
but	O
acquitted	O
the	O
two	O
Women	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Hycroft	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stoke-Newington	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
7	O
Holland	O
Aprons	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
2	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
some	O
Caps	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
Instant	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Maid	O
was	O
washing	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
the	O
Goods	O
for	O
Convenience	O
by	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
and	O
by	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Parish	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
steal	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
Instant	O
.	O
Mr.	O
White	O
depos	O
'd	O
the	O
Night	O
after	O
the	O
first	O
Robbery	O
,	O
his	O
Man	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
Thieves	O
were	O
come	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
untiling	O
his	O
Wash-house	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Servant	O
having	O
a	O
Spit	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
secur	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
that	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
discharge	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
miss	O
'd	O
Fire	O
;	O
this	O
occasion	O
'd	O
searching	O
his	O
Pockets	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
found	O
a	O
Flint	O
and	O
Steel	O
,	O
some	O
Gunpowder	O
,	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Candle	O
,	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
such	O
as	O
Glaziers	O
use	O
to	O
take	O
out	O
Pannels	O
of	O
Glass	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Cap	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
that	O
were	O
stole	O
from	O
the	O
Wash-house	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
escap	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
Indictment	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
being	O
no	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
;	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
18	O
China	O
Dishes	O
,	O
6	O
China	O
Cups	O
,	O
2	O
Silver	O
Salts	O
,	O
8	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
said	O
Peter	O
Barker	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
very	O
plain	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
gone	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
suspected	O
,	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
found	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
at	O
one	O
Walker	O
's	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Directions	O
,	O
who	O
then	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
his	O
Trial	O
,	O
denied	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Dublois	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
and	O
selling	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
President	B-pers
and	I-pers
Fellows	I-pers
of	I-pers
Magdalen	I-pers
College	I-pers
in	I-pers
Oxford	I-pers
,	O
and	O
as	O
an	O
Accessary	O
into	O
doing	O
with	O
one	O
Richard	B-pers
Groom	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
convicted	O
at	O
the	O
last	O
Assizes	O
at	O
Oxford	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
fame	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
as	O
an	O
Accessary	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Gloom	O
,	O
in	O
receiving	O
and	O
selling	O
4	O
Silver	O
Cups	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Warden	B-pers
and	I-pers
Fellows	I-pers
of	I-pers
Merton	I-pers
College	I-pers
in	I-pers
Oxford	I-pers
.	O
But	O
the	O
Proof	O
not	O
being	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Kanton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
taking	O
to	O
Wife	O
Mary	B-pers
Lawton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
his	O
first	O
Wife	O
Dorothy	O
being	O
then	O
alive	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
Dorothy	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
but	O
denied	O
the	O
other	O
Marriage	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
not	O
prov	O
'd	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
therefore	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Carpenter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Yards	O
of	O
stitch	O
'd	O
quilted	O
Callico	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Adam	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
Instant	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
beg	O
'd	O
Leave	O
to	O
lodge	O
a	O
Night	O
or	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
and	O
took	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
quite	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
after	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
seen	O
selling	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Cloth	O
that	O
the	O
Callico	O
was	O
in	O
,	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
.	O
In	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
she	O
laid	O
it	O
upon	O
some	O
others	O
who	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
well	O
acquainted	O
with	O
some	O
Offenders	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
not	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
she	O
stole	O
the	O
Callico	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Deal	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
Callico	O
Manteau	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
1	O
Shirt	O
,	O
1	O
Porringer	O
,	O
and	O
1	O
Spoon	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Lodging	O
Room	O
of	O
Phillip	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
.	O
-	O
Fountaine	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Ellis	O
swore	O
she	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
other	O
Evidences	O
made	O
it	O
plain	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stole	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Millicent	B-pers
Downes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
1	O
stuff	O
Manteau	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
1	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Law	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Mrs.	O
Law	O
's	O
Nurse	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
sometime	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
met	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
and	O
secur	O
'd	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
own	O
'd	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
:	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Cock	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
)	O
of	O
Harrow	B-place
on	I-place
the	I-place
Hill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
8	O
Yards	O
of	O
Lutestring	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Sawcer	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
Queen	O
.	O
No	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Grace	B-pers
Prior	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
11	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Silver	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Lewis	B-pers
Clifton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
Clifton	O
swore	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Dish	O
of	O
Coffee	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
who	O
kept	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
sate	O
down	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
drink	O
any	O
Brandy	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
consented	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
3	O
Quarterns	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
for	O
'em	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
drank	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
fell	O
asleep	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
;	O
but	O
in	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
's	O
time	O
she	O
wak	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
more	O
Brandy	O
,	O
but	O
feeling	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
all	O
his	O
Silver	O
,	O
about	O
21	O
s.	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Guineas	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Fobb	O
:	O
Upon	O
this	O
he	O
told	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
she	O
had	O
rob	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
denied	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
down	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
make	O
him	O
easy	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Maid	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
follow	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
very	O
near	O
sighted	O
,	O
he	O
lost	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
never	O
been	O
there	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
he	O
was	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
be	O
sure	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
took	O
away	O
his	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
thereupon	O
going	O
close	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
he	O
look	O
'd	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
about	O
a	O
Minute	O
before	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
Person	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
deny	O
'd	O
his	O
drinking	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
it	O
very	O
drunk	O
with	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
private	O
Room	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
not	O
having	O
any	O
Mind	O
to	O
oblige	O
him	O
,	O
turn	O
'd	O
him	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
pickt	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Her	O
Maid	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Constable	O
swore	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
was	O
of	O
no	O
ill	O
Repute	O
as	O
he	O
knew	O
of	O
;	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
committing	O
a	O
Rape	O
upon	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Burt	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
Ann	O
Burt	O
swore	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
making	O
an	O
Afternoon	O
's	O
Holiday	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
young	O
Women	O
that	O
work	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
at	O
a	O
Throwsters	O
's	O
and	O
having	O
been	O
at	O
Stepney	O
,	O
about	O
10	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
she	O
left	O
her	O
Company	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
inclin	O
'd	O
to	O
stay	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
she	O
durst	O
not	O
do	O
)	O
and	O
came	O
homewards	O
alone	O
;	O
but	O
was	O
met	O
in	O
the	O
Way	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
put	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
into	O
her	O
Mouth	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
her	O
in	O
his	O
Arms	O
to	O
a	O
Field	O
,	O
distant	O
from	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
and	O
forc	O
'd	O
her	O
Body	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
he	O
beat	O
her	O
and	O
bruised	O
her	O
for	O
crying	O
and	O
struggling	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
's	O
time	O
lay	O
with	O
her	O
again	O
,	O
in	O
both	O
which	O
Actions	O
he	O
did	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
carnal	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
her	O
Body	O
by	O
Force	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
hid	O
her	O
self	O
(	O
as	O
she	O
thought	O
)	O
under	O
a	O
Bush	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
got	O
home	O
.	O
She	O
depos	O
'd	O
farther	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
his	O
Knife	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
her	O
Butcher	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
yield	O
,	O
or	O
if	O
ever	O
she	O
told	O
her	O
Mother	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
He	O
was	O
at	O
his	O
Father	O
's	O
that	O
Evening	O
,	O
from	O
5	O
a	O
Clock	O
till	O
12	O
,	O
about	O
remarkable	O
business	O
and	O
brought	O
several	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
who	O
agreed	O
in	O
their	O
Evidence	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Shute	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
an	O
Assault	O
on	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Abbot	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
37	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Banister	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Henry	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Enfield	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
an	O
Assault	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
High-way	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
Boy	O
)	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Marmaduke	B-pers
Soul	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
an	O
Assault	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
High-way	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Tutty	I-pers
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
him	O
of	O
a	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
1	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
1	O
Whip	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Pound	O
of	O
Coffee	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
Hunt	O
was	O
riding	O
in	O
the	O
Road	O
toward	O
Enfield	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bottom	O
of	O
Stamford-Hill	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
Hartford	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
them	O
ride	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
a	O
led	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
would	O
make	O
him	O
drink	O
;	O
he	O
consenting	O
to	O
this	O
,	O
White	O
got	O
upon	O
the	O
Gelding	O
,	O
and	O
Banister	O
rode	O
behind	O
the	O
Boy	O
;	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
this	O
Evidence	O
discover	O
'd	O
Tutty	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
all	O
rode	O
together	O
,	O
till	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
a	O
Place	O
between	B-place
Ponder	I-place
's	I-place
End	I-place
and	I-place
Green-street	I-place
,	O
where	O
White	O
rode	O
before	O
Tutty	O
,	O
and	O
turning	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
bid	O
him	O
stand	O
;	O
and	O
with	O
a	O
Pistol	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
demanded	O
his	O
Money	O
and	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
away	O
with	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Things	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
off	O
the	O
Bridle	O
from	O
the	O
Horse	O
that	O
the	O
Boy	O
rode	O
on	O
,	O
cut	O
his	O
Girts	O
,	O
and	O
turn	O
'd	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
they	O
rode	O
away	O
.	O
A	O
little	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
the	O
Horse	O
White	O
rode	O
on	O
threw	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Higler	O
coming	O
on	O
the	O
Road	O
help	O
'd	O
him	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
much	O
hurt	O
by	O
his	O
Fall	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
talking	O
together	O
,	O
Tutty	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Higler	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
two	O
Men	O
upon	O
Grey	O
Geldings	O
,	O
White	O
standing	O
by	O
him	O
;	O
who	O
immediately	O
after	O
that	O
rode	O
away	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Higler	O
and	O
Tutty	O
pursu	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
soon	O
quitted	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
to	O
a	O
Field	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
He	O
confes	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
Information	O
where	O
they	O
might	O
find	O
Banister	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Evidence	O
made	O
Enquiry	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
meeting	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
contriv	O
'd	O
a	O
Letter	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
Sister	O
,	O
who	O
presently	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
her	O
Brother	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
follow	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
at	O
a	O
distance	O
,	O
they	O
taking	O
it	O
by	O
Turns	O
to	O
go	O
foremost	O
,	O
to	O
prevent	O
Discovery	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
she	O
turn	O
'd	O
short	O
,	O
andd	O
met	O
her	O
Landlord	O
,	O
who	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
what	O
Business	O
,	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
that	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
Town	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
a	O
Letter	O
was	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
for	O
her	O
Brother	O
Banister	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
believed	O
she	O
might	O
find	O
him	O
by	O
and	O
by	O
at	O
a	O
certain	O
Gaming-house	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
parted	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Companion	O
went	O
immediately	O
to	O
the	O
Gaming-house	O
she	O
spoke	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
his	O
Voice	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
at	O
last	O
they	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
secur	O
'd	O
him	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jefferies	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Purse	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
17	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
instant	O
.	O
Wood	O
swore	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
calling	O
for	O
a	O
Mug	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
sate	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
drinking	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sate	O
down	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
on	O
that	O
Side	O
where	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
missing	O
it	O
immediately	O
he	O
pursued	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Purse	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
People	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
shut	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
prevented	O
his	O
taking	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
:	O
upon	O
this	O
he	O
threatened	O
to	O
indict	O
them	O
for	O
a	O
Rescue	O
;	O
to	O
prevent	O
which	O
they	O
discover	O
'd	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
liv	O
'd	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
thereupon	O
apprehended	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Busby	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
)	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
perswading	O
John	B-pers
Busby	I-pers
to	O
cheat	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stainford	I-pers
,	O
of	O
some	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
;	O
which	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
for	O
an	O
Indictment	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
,	O
late	O
of	O
Boston	B-place
in	I-place
New	I-place
England	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Hanvy	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Club	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
he	O
died	O
.	O
No	O
Person	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
over	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
,	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
14.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Goddard	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Fairclough	I-pers
,	O
T	O
-	O
E	O
-	O
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Payne	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Fairborne	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Blunt	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Stapleton	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Stevenson	O
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Blunt	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Bonner	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Banister	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jefferies	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
15.	O
Henry	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Fell	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Barefoot	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Harld	I-pers
,	O
Anne	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
Anne	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Dunstoll	I-pers
,	O
Dennis	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Turvy	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Dubluis	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Deal	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whip	O
'd	O
,	O
6.	O
Robert	B-pers
Steel	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Elson	O
,	O
alias	O
Benson	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Wade	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Ewers	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Rutter	I-pers
,	O
Millicent	B-pers
Downes	I-pers
,	O
Williams	O
Mantle	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Coletburst	I-pers
,	O
fin	O
'd	O
20	O
Marks	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
imprison	O
'd	O
one	O
Year	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
give	O
Security	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
for	O
three	O
Years	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Hutchinson	I-pers
,	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
at	O
the	O
West	O
End	O
of	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Seal	I-pers
's	O
Verdict	O
being	O
Special	O
,	O
his	O
Sentence	O
is	O
deferr	O
'd	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Fairclongh	I-pers
,	O
T	O
-	O
E	O
-	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jefferies	I-pers
,	O
pleaded	O
their	O
Bellies	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
being	O
impanell	O
'd	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
found	O
Quick	O
with	O
Child	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
MR.	O
Vicker	O
's	O
the	O
Clergy-man	O
,	O
who	O
hath	O
cured	O
several	O
People	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Evil	O
,	O
Liveth	O
in	O
Sherbourne	O
Lane	O
near	O
Lambard-Street	O
.	O
The	O
Volatile	O
Spirit	O
of	O
BOHEE-TEA	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
of	O
this	O
Kind	O
that	O
ever	O
was	O
made	O
in	O
England	O
,	O
which	O
hath	O
been	O
found	O
the	O
most	O
absolute	O
case	O
for	O
Consumptions	O
,	O
inward	O
Wastings	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
Decays	O
of	O
Nature	O
whatsoever	O
,	O
incident	O
to	O
Mankind	O
:	O
Being	O
infinitely	O
more	O
Balsamick	O
,	O
healing	O
to	O
the	O
Lungs	O
,	O
and	O
fattening	O
the	O
whole	O
Constitution	O
,	O
than	O
the	O
common	O
Infusion	O
of	O
the	O
Leaf	O
in	O
Water	O
;	O
in	O
so	O
much	O
that	O
15	O
or	O
20	O
Drops	O
taken	O
twice	O
a	O
Day	O
in	O
Ale	O
,	O
Wine	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
Dish	O
of	O
Bohee-Tea	O
,	O
sweeten	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
finest	O
Loaf-Sugar	O
,	O
shall	O
do	O
more	O
Service	O
to	O
weak	O
Consumptive	O
People	O
in	O
one	O
Week	O
,	O
than	O
all	O
other	O
Restoratives	O
whatsoever	O
,	O
shall	O
do	O
in	O
many	O
Months	O
,	O
as	O
hath	O
been	O
sufficiently	O
experienc	O
'd	O
from	O
the	O
great	O
Quantities	O
thereof	O
sold	O
to	O
the	O
Nobility	O
and	O
Gentry	O
since	O
its	O
first	O
Publication	O
.	O
It	O
's	O
likewise	O
's	O
a	O
very	O
rich	O
Cordial	O
for	O
chearing	O
the	O
Heart	O
when	O
oppress	O
'd	O
with	O
Melancholy	O
and	O
Vapours	O
;	O
being	O
also	O
of	O
that	O
sovereign	O
Use	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
give	O
Ease	O
and	O
Relief	O
in	O
the	O
Cholick	O
,	O
violent	O
Pains	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
Coughs	O
and	O
Phtisicks	O
,	O
when	O
all	O
other	O
Medicines	O
have	O
failed	O
.	O
Neither	O
is	O
it	O
more	O
strange	O
than	O
true	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
by	O
taking	O
one	O
Bottle	O
,	O
voided	O
three	O
Ounces	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Gravel	O
,	O
which	O
may	O
be	O
seen	O
at	O
the	O
Place	O
of	O
Sale	O
.	O
This	O
Spirit	O
mix	O
'd	O
with	O
Punch	O
makes	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
agreeable	O
Liquors	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
;	O
and	O
takes	O
of	O
the	O
Crudities	O
of	O
a	O
cold	O
Phlegmatick	O
Stomach	O
,	O
oppressed	O
with	O
Wind	O
or	O
Water	O
,	O
no	O
one	O
Thing	O
can	O
be	O
more	O
effectual	O
.	O
To	O
create	O
an	O
Appetite	O
,	O
to	O
expel	O
nauseous	O
Humours	O
offending	O
the	O
Stomach	O
and	O
to	O
prevent	O
Vomitings	O
and	O
Reachings	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
better	O
Remedy	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
,	O
of	O
much	O
greater	O
Efficacy	O
than	O
the	O
bitter	O
Draught	O
.	O
It	O
's	O
likewise	O
a	O
special	O
Antidote	O
against	O
any	O
Infection	O
of	O
the	O
Air	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
15	O
Drops	O
be	O
taken	O
going	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Spring-Water	O
,	O
never	O
faileth	O
to	O
procure	O
a	O
sound	O
Sleep	O
.	O
A	O
Gentleman	O
extremely	O
afflicted	O
with	O
the	O
Gout	O
,	O
by	O
taking	O
10	O
Drops	O
of	O
this	O
Volatile	O
Spirit	O
in	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Spring-Water	O
.	O
Morning	O
,	O
Noon	O
,	O
and	O
Night	O
,	O
was	O
wonderfully	O
eased	O
of	O
his	O
Pains	O
and	O
Lameness	O
.	O
And	O
as	O
this	O
Volatile	O
Spirit	O
is	O
chymically	O
extracted	O
from	O
the	O
purest	O
and	O
finest	O
Tea	O
that	O
can	O
be	O
had	O
,	O
so	O
is	O
it	O
likewise	O
a	O
certain	O
Remedy	O
in	O
all	O
the	O
above	O
mention	O
'd	O
Cases	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Bottle	O
.	O
Note	O
,	O
People	O
of	O
an	O
hot	O
and	O
feverish	O
Constitution	O
may	O
take	O
these	O
Drops	O
in	O
Barley	O
,	O
or	O
common	O
Spring-Water	O
.	O
Sold	O
now	O
only	O
at	O
Batson	O
's	O
Coffee-house	O
against	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
Cornhill	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
no	O
other	O
Place	O
.	O
Sealed	O
with	O
Black	O
Wax	O
,	O
having	O
a	O
double	O
Coat	O
of	O
Arms	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Two	O
Cinquefoils	O
and	O
a	O
Bend	O
charged	O
with	O
three	O
Wheatsheaves	O
,	O
to	O
prevent	O
Counterfeits	O
.	O
At	O
Her	O
House	O
at	O
the	O
Red	O
Ball	O
in	O
Queen-street	O
,	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Three	O
Cranes	O
,	O
LIveth	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
,	O
the	O
Daughter	O
of	O
an	O
eminent	O
Physician	O
,	O
who	O
practis	O
'd	O
in	O
London	O
upwards	O
of	O
40	O
Years	O
.	O
She	O
hath	O
an	O
Ointment	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Royal	O
Ointment	O
for	O
the	O
Gout	O
,	O
and	O
Rheumatick	O
Pains	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
great	O
Ease	O
and	O
Comfort	O
to	O
both	O
Sexes	O
,	O
at	O
Home	O
and	O
Abroad	O
as	O
hath	O
been	O
experience	O
'd	O
by	O
many	O
who	O
have	O
carry	O
'd	O
it	O
with	O
them	O
into	O
foreign	O
Parts	O
;	O
and	O
is	O
therefore	O
of	O
excellent	O
Use	O
for	O
all	O
Travellers	O
.	O
Thus	O
is	O
the	O
Cure	O
compleated	O
;	O
as	O
it	O
well	O
known	O
to	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
Nobility	O
and	O
Gentry	O
,	O
who	O
have	O
experienc	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
are	O
ready	O
to	O
testify	O
the	O
Truth	O
of	O
its	O
wonderful	O
Success	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
also	O
a	O
certain	O
and	O
Infallible	O
Cure	O
for	O
the	O
Tooth-ach	O
,	O
without	O
Drawing	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
effectually	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Pain	O
will	O
never	O
return	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
not	O
only	O
so	O
,	O
but	O
makes	O
the	O
Teeth	O
as	O
white	O
as	O
Ivory	O
;	O
and	O
fastens	O
those	O
that	O
are	O
loose	O
to	O
Admiration	O
.	O
She	O
changes	O
Red	O
or	O
Gray	O
Hair	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
time	O
,	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
distinguish	O
'd	O
from	O
a	O
natural	O
Complexion	O
.	O
Note	O
,	O
Remov	O
'd	O
from	O
the	O
Cheshire	O
Cheese	O
in	O
Wall-brook	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Good	O
of	O
the	O
Publick	O
.	O
WHereas	O
several	O
Gentlewomen	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
that	O
Sex	O
in	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
have	O
contracted	O
an	O
evil	O
Habit	O
of	O
Body	O
,	O
wherein	O
the	O
vicious	O
Humours	O
,	O
at	O
first	O
dispersed	O
through	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
come	O
at	O
length	O
to	O
be	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
one	O
Part	O
or	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
times	O
(	O
for	O
Causes	O
too	O
long	O
to	O
be	O
here	O
mentioned	O
)	O
are	O
thrown	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Womb	O
,	O
occasioning	O
a	O
dangerous	O
Weakness	O
in	O
that	O
Part	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
neglected	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
turns	O
cancerous	O
,	O
and	O
often	O
proves	O
fatal	O
.	O
I	O
cure	O
the	O
Diabetes	O
when	O
given	O
over	O
by	O
all	O
other	O
Persons	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
to	O
acquaint	O
all	O
such	O
as	O
may	O
have	O
occasions	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
speedy	O
Relief	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
had	O
from	O
an	O
experienced	O
Midwife	O
,	O
dwelling	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Queens	O
Arms	O
,	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
near	O
Exeter	O
Charge	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
who	O
perform	O
'd	O
a	O
Cure	O
upon	O
a	O
Lady	O
at	O
the	O
Bath	O
,	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
given	O
over	O
by	O
Physicians	O
;	O
and	O
since	O
has	O
cured	O
several	O
Gentlewomen	O
and	O
others	O
in	O
the	O
City	O
and	O
Suburbs	O
of	O
London	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Povey	I-pers
,	O
Remov	O
'd	O
from	O
Hatton-Garden	O
near	O
Exeter	O
Exchanges	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
London	O
,	O
Operator	O
for	O
the	O
Teeth	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
the	O
Honour	O
to	O
clean	O
her	O
Late	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Teeth	O
,	O
He	O
sells	O
a	O
pleasant	O
Dentrifice	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
King	O
Charles	O
the	O
Second	O
constantly	O
used	O
,	O
it	O
makes	O
the	O
Teeth	O
as	O
white	O
as	O
Ivory	O
,	O
and	O
preserves	O
them	O
from	O
Decaying	O
:	O
Destroying	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
.	O
He	O
hath	O
a	O
Cephalick	O
which	O
certainly	O
cures	O
the	O
Tooth-Ach	O
in	O
2	O
Minutes	O
Time	O
;	O
if	O
the	O
Teeth	O
are	O
rotten	O
,	O
or	O
uneven	O
,	O
and	O
full	O
of	O
Holes	O
,	O
or	O
black	O
Specks	O
,	O
he	O
will	O
make	O
them	O
smooth	O
,	O
even	O
sound	O
and	O
white	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
no	O
Person	O
shall	O
distinguish	O
where	O
the	O
defect	O
had	O
been	O
:	O
He	O
Sets	O
in	O
Artificial	O
Teeth	O
so	O
easy	O
,	O
neat	O
and	O
firm	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
need	O
not	O
be	O
removed	O
for	O
some	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
may	O
eat	O
with	O
them	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
with	O
their	O
former	O
,	O
and	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
distinguished	O
from	O
their	O
Natural	O
ones	O
:	O
He	O
Sells	O
a	O
pleasant	O
Water	O
that	O
takes	O
all	O
Pains	O
and	O
Imposthumes	O
,	O
or	O
Swellings	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Gums	O
,	O
and	O
fastens	O
loose	O
Teeth	O
,	O
which	O
several	O
Persons	O
of	O
Quality	O
know	O
all	O
this	O
to	O
be	O
true	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
several	O
Pretenders	O
that	O
put	O
out	O
a	O
Powder	O
for	O
whitening	O
the	O
Teeth	O
,	O
and	O
curing	O
the	O
Tooth-ach	O
and	O
Scurvey	O
in	O
the	O
Gums	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
advise	O
all	O
Persons	O
to	O
beware	O
of	O
:	O
For	O
they	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
from	O
whence	O
any	O
of	O
those	O
Distempers	O
proceeds	O
.	O
But	O
thank	O
God	O
I	O
do	O
.	O
BOOKS	O
printed	O
for	O
Andrew	O
Bell	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Cross	O
Keys	O
and	O
Bible	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
.	O
The	O
History	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
Remarkable	O
Trials	O
in	O
Great	O
Britain	O
and	O
Ireland	O
in	O
Capital	O
Cases	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Heresy	O
,	O
Treason	O
,	O
Incest	O
,	O
Adultery	O
,	O
Rapes	O
,	O
Sodomy	O
,	O
Perjury	O
,	O
Murder	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
faithfully	O
extracted	O
from	O
Records	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
authentick	O
Authorities	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
Manuscript	O
as	O
printed	O
.	O
Price	O
6	O
s.	O
Where	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
the	O
present	O
State	O
of	O
Great	O
Britain	O
and	O
Ireland	O
.	O
In	O
Three	O
Parts	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
the	O
present	O
State	O
of	O
King	O
George	O
's	O
Dominions	O
in	O
Germany	O
.	O
Containing	O
an	O
exact	O
Description	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
new	O
Map	O
of	O
them	O
all	O
.	O
The	O
Third	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
6	O
s.	O
The	O
Life	O
and	O
Posthumous	O
Works	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
famous	O
Arthur	O
Manwaring	O
,	O
Esq	O
,	O
pr	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
The	O
History	O
of	O
the	O
Wars	O
of	O
the	O
present	O
King	O
of	O
Sweden	O
,	O
pr	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
The	O
Third	O
Edition	O
of	O
Memoirs	O
of	O
the	O
Affairs	O
of	O
Scotland	O
;	O
in	O
which	O
is	O
the	O
whole	O
Secret	O
of	O
the	O
Pretender	O
's	O
Invasion	O
&	O
c.	O
pr.5	O
s.	O
Fourteen	O
Sermons	O
on	O
several	O
Occasions	O
by	O
his	O
Grace	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Daws	I-pers
,	O
Lord	O
Archbishop	O
of	O
York	O
.	O
pr	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
A	O
Collection	O
of	O
the	O
best	O
Odes	O
and	O
Imitations	O
of	O
Horace	O
.	O
pr	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
The	O
Life	O
of	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Marlborough	O
and	O
Prince	O
Eugene	O
;	O
with	O
both	O
their	O
Effigies	O
,	O
pr	O
.	O
4.	O
s.	O
The	O
Arabian	O
Nights	O
Entertainments	O
,	O
consisting	O
of	O
1001	O
Stories	O
.	O
In	O
Eight	O
Vols	O
.	O
pr	O
.	O
11	O
s.	O
The	O
diverting	O
Works	O
of	O
the	O
Countes	O
D'Anois	O
,	O
Author	O
of	O
the	O
Ladies	O
Travels	O
into	O
Spain	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
the	O
Tales	O
of	O
the	O
Fairies	O
.	O
With	O
several	O
new	O
Cuts	O
.	O
pr	O
.	O
6	O
s.	O
The	O
Art	O
of	O
Memory	O
.	O
pr	O
.	O
1.	O
s.	O
The	O
History	O
of	O
Genesis	O
.	O
pr	O
.	O
1.	O
s.	O
The	O
Rules	O
of	O
the	O
Waterside	O
;	O
Or	O
,	O
General	O
Practice	O
of	O
the	O
Customs	O
.	O
Price	O
stitch	O
'd	O
2	O
s.	O
Bound	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d	O
.	O
