TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
'S	O
commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTRY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
11th,12th	O
,	O
and	O
13th	O
,	O
of	O
April,1716	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Second	O
year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEfore	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
CHARLES	B-pers
PEERS	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Thomas	O
Lord	O
Parker	O
,	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
of	O
the	O
King's-Bench	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Bary	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Tracy	O
,	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
;	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
,	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Hilliard	I-pers
William	B-pers
Norris	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Jacobs	I-pers
William	B-pers
Sherborne	I-pers
John	B-pers
Willmott	I-pers
William	B-pers
Marsland	I-pers
Paul	B-pers
Knewstub	I-pers
Jesoph	B-pers
Grimstead	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Dawell	I-pers
William	B-pers
Bigsby	I-pers
Samnel	B-pers
Bangbton	I-pers
Christopher	B-pers
Fincbivedd	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
Jury	O
.	O
Giles	B-pers
Riddle	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Stroud	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Bavand	I-pers
Jereiny	B-pers
Levin	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Prior	I-pers
Wiliam	B-pers
Clements	I-pers
John	B-pers
Prater	I-pers
James	B-pers
Rigby	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
Lowrence	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
How	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Hanson	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tarikard	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Moor	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
with	O
another	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Moor	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Tankard	O
of	O
Beer	O
(	O
Smith	O
having	O
been	O
there	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
.	O
)	O
which	O
was	O
accordingly	O
brought	O
them	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Daughter	O
:	O
Then	O
Smith	O
,	O
whose	O
Part	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
make	O
himself	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
Landlord	O
to	O
prevent	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
several	O
intimate	O
Questions	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
measur	O
'd	O
out	O
many	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Oysters	O
for	O
him	O
(	O
having	O
inform	O
'd	O
himself	O
before	O
that	O
that	O
was	O
his	O
Business	O
)	O
and	O
came	O
purely	O
out	O
of	O
Love	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
:	O
But	O
Mr.	O
Meer	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
under	O
some	O
Concern	O
for	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
not	O
being	O
so	O
easily	O
deceiv	O
'd	O
,	O
kept	O
an	O
Eye	O
upon	O
his	O
new	O
Acquaintance	O
,	O
and	O
observ	O
'd	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
go	O
often	O
out	O
,	O
under	O
as	O
many	O
Pretences	O
:	O
At	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Scheme	O
being	O
settled	O
,	O
Hanson	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Daughter	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Way	O
to	O
old	O
Bedlam	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
directed	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
immediately	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
spoke	O
aloud	O
to	O
his	O
Confederates	O
,	O
Sue	O
's	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
wo	O
n't	O
come	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
alway	O
,	O
another	O
Person	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
'	O
em	O
in	O
Plate	O
Buttons	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
replied	O
,	O
Then	O
I	O
'll	O
fetch	O
her	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
stepping	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
held	O
it	O
open	O
till	O
smith	O
made	O
a	O
clear	O
Passage	O
with	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
now	O
near	O
Night	O
;	O
however	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
pursu	O
'd	O
and	O
taken	O
,	O
being	O
much	O
soil	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Beer	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
carried	O
it	O
under	O
his	O
Coat	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
very	O
plain	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Hanson	O
was	O
principally	O
assisting	O
and	O
abetting	O
in	O
the	O
Felony	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Stevenson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
Bassishaw	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
and	O
Wastcoat,1	O
pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Stockings,5	O
Shirts	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
value	O
4.l	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Cloth	O
,	O
Coat	O
and	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
value	O
3.l	O
.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Knapp	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
An	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
going	O
under	O
a	O
Gateway	O
in	O
Aldermanbury	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
of	O
Goods	O
,	O
seemingly	O
unresolv	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
under	O
a	O
vicious	O
Confusion	O
,	O
which	O
occasion	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
suspect	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
Rogue	O
,	O
who	O
thereupon	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
other	O
Persons	O
,	O
watch	O
'd	O
and	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
into	O
Forestreet	O
,	O
and	O
thence	O
into	O
an	O
Alley	O
by	O
Moorfields	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
his	O
.	O
Goods	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
Way	O
he	O
dropt	O
a	O
Shirt	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
was	O
very	O
near	O
satting	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
S.W	O
.	O
stood	O
for	O
,	O
he	O
replied	O
Samuel	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
a	O
HorseJocky	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
did	O
upon	O
his	O
Trial	O
but	O
could	O
give	O
no	O
Account	O
of	O
him	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
plain	O
Fact	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
seeing	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
change	O
'd	O
Clothes	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
leaving	O
his	O
own	O
fifty	O
Rags	O
in	O
their	O
Room	O
which	O
illegal	O
and	O
criminal	O
Exchange	O
being	O
a	O
plain	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
giving	O
no	O
Account	O
of	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Birch	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
with	O
Intention	O
to	O
steal	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
An	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
That	O
going	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
between	O
3	O
and	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Mourning	O
,	O
he	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Boy	O
very	O
industrious	O
in	O
breaking	O
it	O
open	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
stopd	O
,	O
and	O
remain	O
'd	O
unperceiv	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
by	O
breaking	O
the	O
Pallisadoes	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
out	O
a	O
Pam	O
of	O
Glass	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
rais	O
'd	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
it	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
made	O
his	O
Escape	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
but	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
his	O
Trial	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
insignificant	O
under	O
such	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
1	O
Silver	O
Hilted	O
Sword	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Kelley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
Instant	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
fix	O
the	O
Felony	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
Wherefore	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Matthew	I-place
in	I-place
Friday-Street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Nathanael	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
an	O
Evidence	O
who	O
thin	O
Iron	O
,	O
that	O
had	O
a	O
Hook	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
,	O
drawing	O
out	O
Stockings	O
over	O
the	O
Stall	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
immediately	O
convey	O
'd	O
to	O
a	O
Confederate	O
;	O
who	O
thereupon	O
occasion	O
'd	O
his	O
being	O
apprehended	O
with	O
the	O
Iron	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
plainly	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
accordingly	O
found	O
so	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Gile	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
49	O
s.6	O
d.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Monies	O
of	O
William	B-pers
State	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
with	O
State	O
,	O
and	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
of	O
9	O
d.	O
which	O
he	O
discovering	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
return	O
'd	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
gone	O
;	O
but	O
sometime	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
injur	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
not	O
own	O
the	O
whole	O
Sum	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bartholomew	I-place
the	I-place
Great	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Bond	O
depos	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
follow	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Long-lane	B-place
,	O
and	O
going	O
with	O
her	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
,	O
She	O
discover	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Ring	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
exchanging	O
a	O
Brass	O
one	O
for	O
it	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
agreed	O
to	O
the	O
Exchange	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
Constable	O
swore	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
do	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
apprehended	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
4	O
oz	O
.	O
of	O
Silver	O
Wire	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shed	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
,	O
with	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Goodale	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Upon	O
Trial	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Boy	O
had	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
one	O
Faith	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
when	O
apprehended	O
;	O
but	O
now	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
from	O
Goodale	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
Orders	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Harris	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
found	O
the	O
Boy	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Whitt	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
1	O
Horse	O
Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.1	O
Rowler	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Stable	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Lovell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
Instant	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
an	O
Evidence	O
who	O
perceived	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
a	O
Court	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
suspecting	O
her	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
packing	O
them	O
up	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
Stable	O
but	O
Half	O
an	O
Hour	O
before	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Goods	O
there	O
,	O
leaving	O
them	O
under	O
Lock	O
with	O
the	O
Key	O
in	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Lovell	O
swore	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
his	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
much	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
believe	O
herself	O
Guilty	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
her	O
Case	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Woolnoth	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
1	O
Letter-Case	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hansom	I-pers
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hanson	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
Post	O
Office	O
,	O
he	O
felt	O
something	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
searching	O
,	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket-Book	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
;	O
who	O
immediately	O
replied	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
he	O
'd	O
give	O
it	O
him	O
and	O
accordingly	O
did	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
the	O
Post	O
Office	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
Pocekt-Book	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
look	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
and	O
found	O
he	O
had	O
and	O
so	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
again	O
;	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
it	O
came	O
there	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Frances	B-pers
Duckhouse	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
Outwich	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
Camblet	O
Ridinghood	O
,	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
s.1	O
Linnen	O
Sheet,4	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
Aprons	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Kent	O
depos	O
'd	O
they	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
s	O
Servant	O
-Maid	O
,	O
and	O
believ	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
Person	O
;	O
but	O
one	O
Day	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
was	O
lame	O
,	O
and	O
out	O
of	O
Place	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
lie	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
till	O
she	O
was	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
provided	O
her	O
self	O
with	O
another	O
Place	O
of	O
Service	O
;	O
this	O
Request	O
being	O
granted	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
long	O
before	O
the	O
Cripple	O
danc	O
'd	O
off	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
sent	O
her	O
;	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
denied	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Nicholls	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Helen	I-place
within	I-place
Bishopgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
She	O
with	O
one	O
Frances	B-pers
Hickman	I-pers
,	O
who	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
,	O
did	O
privately	O
steal	O
35	O
Ivory	O
Combs	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.11	O
Horn	O
Combs	O
value	O
9	O
d.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Astly	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
the	O
Shop	O
asking	O
for	O
a	O
Dadriff	O
Comb	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
;	O
and	O
occasion	O
'd	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
trouble	O
in	O
opening	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
gave	O
her	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
convey	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
into	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
found	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
David	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Christ	B-place
Church	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
79	O
Yards	O
of	O
Silk	O
and	O
Worsted	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Pattin	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23rd	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
and	O
Martha	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
107	O
Guineas	O
,	O
9	O
s	O
and	O
9	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Moneys	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Rhodes	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Rhodes	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
having	O
and	O
extraordinary	O
Opinion	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Lewis	O
's	O
Honesty	O
,	O
she	O
having	O
an	O
occasion	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
,	O
left	O
a	O
little	O
Trunk	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Goods	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
hollow	O
Sword-Blade-Company	O
's	O
Bond	O
,	O
believing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
safest	O
in	O
her	O
Possesion	O
but	O
upon	O
her	O
Return	O
Mrs.Lewis	O
met	O
,	O
her	O
with	O
a	O
Dream	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
had	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
she	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
that	O
her	O
little	O
Daughters	O
,	O
her	O
Maid	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Person	O
,	O
had	O
taken	O
out	O
the	O
Bottom	O
of	O
the	O
Trunk	O
,	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
her	O
of	O
her	O
Money	O
and	O
Things	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
bid	O
her	O
fetch	O
it	O
down	O
as	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
away	O
before	O
it	O
was	O
opened	O
.	O
There	O
Mrs.	O
Rhodes	O
search	O
'd	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
not	O
finding	O
the	O
Bond	O
neither	O
,	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
sent	O
away	O
to	O
stop	O
the	O
Payment	O
;	O
but	O
Mrs.	O
Lawin	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
find	O
that	O
,	O
may	O
be	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
her	O
look	O
again	O
for	O
it	O
:	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
there	O
.	O
These	O
were	O
at	O
least	O
strong	O
Presumptions	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
;	O
who	O
on	O
their	O
Part	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
clear	O
themselves	O
by	O
Insinuating	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
That	O
Mrs.	O
Rhodes	O
was	O
much	O
inclined	O
to	O
Gaming	O
and	O
Extravagance	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
some	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
in	O
Evidence	O
,	O
which	O
upon	O
,	O
hearing	O
no	O
ways	O
answered	O
their	O
Expection	O
,	O
but	O
rather	O
shwed	O
,	O
the	O
Guilt	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
cleared	O
,	O
the	O
Reputation	O
of	O
the	O
Gentlewoman	O
they	O
accused	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
proceeded	O
to	O
relate	O
some	O
Circumstances	O
of	O
a	O
Jealousy	O
and	O
Dispute	O
between	O
Mrs.	O
Rhodes	O
and	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
to	O
as	O
Little	O
Purpose	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
submitted	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
;	O
whether	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
Guilty	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
would	O
not	O
in	O
some	O
measure	O
have	O
shew	O
itself	O
and	O
by	O
some	O
means	O
or	O
other	O
been	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
;	O
whereas	O
there	O
appears	O
an	O
Alteration	O
in	O
their	O
Condition	O
nor	O
Reputation	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
well	O
maintained	O
by	O
some	O
Persons	O
they	O
called	O
for	O
that	O
Purpose	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
prov	O
'd	O
that	O
either	O
Mr.Lewis	O
did	O
take	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Trunk	O
,	O
or	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
who	O
denied	O
she	O
told	O
Mrs.	O
Rhodes	O
of	O
her	O
dreaming	O
of	O
any	O
Money	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
she	O
said	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
before	O
Justice	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
only	O
a	O
Posibbility	O
(	O
as	O
the	O
Jury	O
concerv	O
'd	O
)	O
that	O
the	O
Money	O
might	O
by	O
some	O
unknown	O
Circumstance	O
on	O
Accident	O
be	O
either	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Trunk	O
while	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Possession	O
without	O
their	O
Knowledge	O
or	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
without	O
the	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
or	O
before	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Robertson	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
in	O
receiving	O
120	O
yards	O
of	O
white	O
Durance	O
value	O
5	O
l.72	O
Yards	O
of	O
Striped	O
allimanco	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Stallon	I-pers
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
The	O
act	O
was	O
fully	O
made	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
being	O
therewith	O
satisfied	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Richburn	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
speaking	O
very	O
scandalous	O
,	O
false	O
,	O
seditious	O
,	O
and	O
traitorous	O
Words	O
of	O
his	O
most	O
Sacred	O
Majesty	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Court	O
having	O
Information	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Drink	O
when	O
he	O
said	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
generally	O
subjects	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
state	O
of	O
a	O
Madman	O
;	O
and	O
no	O
Body	O
being	O
in	O
Court	O
as	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Emmery	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Katherine	I-place
ed	O
Church	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
one	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ring	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
only	O
denied	O
against	O
a	O
plain	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
therefore	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
and	O
were	O
Severally	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictments	O
they	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Clare	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Woolnoth	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
I	O
Silk	O
Scarf	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Lucan	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Ashley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
But	O
no	O
Prosetutor	O
appearing	O
to	O
make	O
Good	O
the	O
Indicment	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Goddard	I-pers
,	O
Sen	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Goddard	I-pers
,	O
Jun	O
.	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
52	O
lb	O
Wt	O
.	O
of	O
double-refined	O
Loaf-Sugar	O
;	O
value	O
43	O
s.	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bagnall	I-pers
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
both	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
Upon	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Father	O
pretended	O
he	O
bought	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
brought	O
none	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
his	O
Story	O
seem	O
likely	O
.	O
The	O
Son	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
his	O
Father	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
carrying	O
them	O
by	O
his	O
Order	O
when	O
taken	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
acquitted	O
but	O
his	O
Father	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
an	O
Assault	O
and	O
Robbery	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
,	O
value	O
35	O
s.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
aforesaid	O
for	O
an	O
Assault	O
and	O
Robbery	O
on	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Huggins	I-pers
,	O
Sen	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Cane	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
indicted	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
and	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
for	O
assaulting	O
and	O
robbing	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Huggins	I-pers
Jun	O
.	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
and	O
Case	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
Steel	O
Seal	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
very	O
Full	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
three	O
Prosecutors	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
Fleetstreet	B-place
about	O
8	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Huggins	O
Jun	O
being	O
foremost	O
with	O
a	O
Link	O
in	O
one	O
Hand	O
and	O
a	O
Cane	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
one	O
Hutton	O
who	O
was	O
convicted	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
snatch	O
'd	O
at	O
his	O
Cane	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
disappointed	O
before	O
they	O
had	O
gone	O
many	O
Yards	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
more	O
attack	O
'd	O
them	O
all	O
and	O
he	O
with	O
a	O
short	O
Knife	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
stabb	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Huggings	O
Jun	O
in	O
the	O
Thigh	O
who	O
soon	O
after	O
received	O
long	O
Gashes	O
down	O
his	O
Black	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Cheek	O
was	O
cut	O
from	O
his	O
Mouth	O
to	O
his	O
Ear	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
two	O
receiv	O
'd	O
some	O
Wounds	O
and	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
abovementioned	O
in	O
the	O
Scuffle	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
no	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
all	O
three	O
Indictments	O
Edward	O
Spencer	O
was	O
a	O
fourth	O
time	O
indicted	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
in	O
the	O
Country	O
of	O
Midlesex	O
for	O
assaulting	O
and	O
robbing	O
Robert	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
value	O
6	O
l	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
Evidence	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
thrust	O
Adams	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
broke	O
his	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Wigg	O
Which	O
he	O
was	O
carrying	O
to	O
the	O
Barber	O
's	O
but	O
being	O
persued	O
he	O
dropt	O
it	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
However	O
this	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Assault	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
ws	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
Giles	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Necks	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.2	O
Holland	O
Sleeves	O
2	O
s	O
2	O
Linnen	O
Caps	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Value	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Ridge	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
10	O
Yards	O
of	O
Persian	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
who	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
acquitted	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
.	O
Isabella	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
and	O
Katherine	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Holland	O
Frocks	O
,	O
value	O
1.s.6	O
d.2	O
Holland	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
from	O
Giles	B-pers
Walton	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Katherine	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
confes	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Katherine	O
desired	O
the	O
Court	O
to	O
acquit	O
her	O
Sister	O
,	O
who	O
she	O
was	O
sure	O
was	O
very	O
innocent	O
;	O
an	O
as	O
to	O
what	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
herself	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
frighten	O
'd	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
No	O
Pawn-broker	O
appeared	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
however	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Nature	O
of	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
acquitted	O
her	O
Sister	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ralph	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Parker	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Durance	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
1	O
Velvet	O
Cap	O
1	O
Sagathee	O
Wastcoat	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Peter	O
Durance	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Durance	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
having	O
been	O
to	O
visit	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
back	O
she	O
found	O
her	O
House	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
abovemention	O
'd	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Sack	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
brought	O
there	O
for	O
that	O
Purpose	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
stopp	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
no	O
satisfactory	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchures	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
Holland	O
Sheets	O
value	O
20	O
s.1	O
Flaxen	O
Sheet,3	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
Diaper	O
Table-Cloth,6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Tath	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Mourning	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
time	O
she	O
was	O
apprehended	O
by	O
a	O
watchman	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
knocking	O
at	O
a	O
Brandy	O
Shop	O
Door	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
made	O
no	O
Defence	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Matth.ew	B-pers
Cattings	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
1	O
Holland	O
Sheet,5	O
Aprons,10	O
Silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Baily	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
jury	O
upon	O
due	O
Consideration	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
160	O
Guineas	O
1	O
Half	O
Guineas	O
and	O
1	O
Broad	O
piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Batchelor	I-pers
upon	O
the	O
7th	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
the	O
Oppurtunity	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Batchelor	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
's	O
being	O
abroad	O
,	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
before	O
they	O
came	O
home	O
who	O
making	O
the	O
Discovery	O
,	O
made	O
Enquiries	O
of	O
all	O
sides	O
,	O
by	O
Land	O
and	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
found	O
her	O
on	O
Board	O
a	O
Ship	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
all	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
On	O
her	O
Trial	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
led	O
away	O
;	O
which	O
doing	O
her	O
but	O
little	O
Service	O
after	O
was	O
retaken	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Dicrey	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Maguier	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
Side	O
of	O
his	O
Belly	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Navel	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Breadth	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
and	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
8	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
All	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
agreed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
very	O
ill	O
Behaviour	O
when	O
in	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
much	O
dispos	O
'd	O
to	O
quarrel	O
;	O
but	O
gave	O
the	O
quite	O
contrary	O
Character	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Those	O
who	O
were	O
Evidence	O
to	O
the	O
Fact	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
were	O
drinking	O
Wine	O
at	O
a	O
Tavern	O
,	O
where	O
appear	O
'd	O
no	O
Signs	O
of	O
a	O
pre	O
mediated	O
Malice	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
follow	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
coming	O
to	O
a	O
Place	O
were	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Descent	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Collar	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
several	O
Paces	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
'D	O
-	O
n	O
je	O
draw	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
I	O
'll	O
stick	O
you	O
,	O
his	O
own	O
Sword	O
being	O
naked	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
he	O
immediately	O
push	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
wounded	O
him	O
(	O
as	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
sware	O
)	O
in	O
the	O
Lungs	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
but	O
getting	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
retreated	O
to	O
the	O
Wall	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
making	O
another	O
Pass	O
,	O
thrust	O
himself	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Sword	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
drew	O
just	O
before	O
for	O
his	O
own	O
Defence	O
:	O
General	O
Tatton	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Honourable	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
appear	O
'd	O
in	O
Behalf	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
it	O
in	O
Se	O
Defendendo	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
some	O
Shirts	O
and	O
other	O
Linnen	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Blare	I-pers
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Opinion	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
to	O
Brass	O
Hilted	O
Swords,2	O
small	O
Swords	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Hangers	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
Kemp	O
depos	O
'd	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Night	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
above	O
named	O
were	O
then	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
nor	O
no	O
other	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
could	O
prove	O
he	O
stole	O
them	O
;	O
On	O
his	O
Part	O
were	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
who	O
swore	O
they	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
buy	O
part	O
of	O
'em	O
and	O
pay	O
for	O
'em	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
believ	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Man	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
Credit	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
at	I-place
Islington	I-place
;	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
brown	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mr.	O
M	O
-	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
s,6	O
d	O
,	O
in	O
Money	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Burton	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
going	O
from	B-place
London	I-place
to	I-place
Hornsey	I-place
,	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
met	O
on	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
by	O
two	O
Men	O
on	O
Horseback	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
on	O
Foot	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
away	O
his	O
Horse	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
rode	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
But	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
he	O
committed	O
another	O
Robbery	O
upon	O
Mr.	O
M	O
-	O
's	O
Horse	O
,	O
which	O
alarming	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
pursued	O
and	O
being	O
hard	O
put	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
quitted	O
the	O
Horse	O
and	O
his	O
,	O
great	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
jump	O
'd	O
over	O
a	O
Hedge	O
into	O
a	O
Field	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
a	O
loaded	O
Pistol	O
lay	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
Money	O
was	O
found	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
l.5	O
s	O
.2	O
d.	O
Halfpedny	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
some	O
in	O
every	O
Pocket	O
:	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
dented	O
the	O
Horse	O
and	O
the	O
Great	O
Coat	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Field	O
to	O
sleep	O
.	O
After	O
she	O
was	O
secur	O
'd	O
an	O
Advertisement	O
was	O
publish	O
'd	O
describing	O
the	O
Man	O
and	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
M	O
-	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Three	O
pidgeans	O
at	O
Bradford	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Horse	O
was	O
left	O
,	O
and	O
ducover	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
own	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
only	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Perwold	I-pers
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Hillingdon	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
24	O
Yards	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Camblet	O
,	O
value	O
26	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
on	O
the	O
1	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
Mr.	O
Scott	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
pair	O
Stockings	O
,	O
bought	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
when	O
presently	O
a	O
Man	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
hit	O
or	O
2	O
s	O
6	O
d	O
for	O
.	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
;	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Scott	O
having	O
son	O
and	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
ou	O
to	O
pursue	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
hinder	O
'd	O
by	O
this	O
Man	O
,	O
whic	O
oblig	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
force	O
his	O
Way	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
presently	O
aou	O
ter	O
his	O
Wife	O
took	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
under	O
her	O
Arm	O
In	O
her	O
Defence	O
:	O
the	O
said	O
a	O
Woman	O
gave	O
them	O
he	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Atterbury	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Precinct	B-place
of	I-place
Norton	I-place
Fal	I-place
gate	I-place
,	O
Butcher	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Rape	O
on	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Frances	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Virgin	O
of	O
the	O
Age	O
of	O
18	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
Frances	O
Adams	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
her	O
Mistress	O
and	O
Fellow-Servants	O
being	O
out	O
at	O
Market	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Night	O
aforesaid	O
about	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bit	O
of	O
her	O
put	O
the	O
Child	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
coming	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
he	O
spread	O
a	O
Great	O
Coat	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
'd	O
cut	O
her	O
to	O
pieces	O
it	O
she	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
le	O
him	O
lie	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
stop	O
'd	O
her	O
Mouth	O
,	O
and	O
forc	O
'd	O
her	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
spent	O
herself	O
an	O
Hour	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
wite	O
'd	O
,	O
struggling	O
.	O
That	O
about	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
after	O
this	O
she	O
told	O
her	O
Brother	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
not	O
daring	O
to	O
acquaint	O
her	O
Misstress	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
left	O
her	O
Master	O
should	O
be	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
A	O
Midwife	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
search	O
'd	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Frances	O
Adams	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
injur	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
Man	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
all	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
and	O
two	O
of	O
his	O
Servants	O
to	O
disprove	O
it	O
the	O
Substance	O
of	O
whole	O
Evidence	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Neighbour	O
were	O
at	O
Cards	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
But	O
till	O
late	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Prentice	O
fetch	O
'd	O
them	O
some	O
Drinks	O
that	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
Work	O
,	O
then	O
to	O
Supper	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
to	O
Bed	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Servant	O
coming	O
home	O
found	O
only	O
they	O
Maid	O
up	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Midwife	O
on	O
their	O
Side	O
swore	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
discover	O
any	O
Signs	O
of	O
Violence	O
upon	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Body	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Ruster	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
12	O
Sheets,3	O
Kettles	O
a	O
Sauce	O
pan,1	O
Pail	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
of	O
little	O
Value	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
Edward	B-pers
Fastnidge	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
,	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
in	O
Buckinghamshire	B-place
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Sheets	O
upon	O
him	O
in	O
Middlesex	O
;	O
who	O
saying	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hyman	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Kettles	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Booty	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Brass	O
,	O
Candlesticks,34	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
some	O
Napkins	O
,	O
Tablecloths	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1	O
st	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
A	O
Watchman	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
3	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
of	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
his	O
Mother	O
's	O
in	O
Piccadilly	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
ask	O
'd	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
those	O
Goods	O
,	O
he	O
replied	O
from	O
Esquire	O
Dyers	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
not	O
being	O
the	O
Way	O
to	O
Piccadilly	O
from	O
Elquire	O
Dyers	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
Mr	O
.	O
Booty	O
's	O
Door	O
being	O
found	O
open	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
up	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
found	O
he	O
was	O
rob	O
'd	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
A.	O
Constable	O
swore	O
he	O
search	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
Pistol	O
charg	O
'd	O
and	O
prisn	O
'd	O
,3	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Ring	O
in	O
his	O
Pockets	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Booty	O
's	O
Maid	O
swore	O
to	O
the	O
Ring	O
.	O
He	O
made	O
no	O
Defence	O
only	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Briscow	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Precinct	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Katherines	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
Silk	O
Scarf	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
to	O
1	O
Gane	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
,	O
s.	O
and	O
1	O
Callicoe	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
30l	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jacob	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
and	O
was	O
apprehended	O
by	O
the	O
Man	O
be	O
sold	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
,	O
but	O
denied	O
,	O
it	O
upon	O
his	O
,	O
That	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Waybank	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Hampstead	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
4	O
Holland	O
Aprons	O
,	O
Shirts	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Linnen	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Slimwood	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
Instant	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
those	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
;	O
but	O
Roberts	O
said	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
hir	O
'd	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
Second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Francis	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
and	O
Parish	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Francis	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Daughter	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
their	O
House	O
under	O
Pretence	O
of	O
taking	O
a	O
Lodging	O
for	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
if	O
a	O
Man	O
and	O
a	O
Boy	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
by	O
their	O
Door	O
(	O
the	O
two	O
other	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
Indictment	O
)	O
and	O
kept	O
them	O
in	O
Chat	O
and	O
Action	O
till	O
he	O
found	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Spoon	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
miss	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
back	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
me	O
Starch	O
which	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
but	O
then	O
she	O
was	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
she	O
was	O
charg	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Spoon	O
;	O
and	O
another	O
Evidence	O
saw	O
her	O
slide	O
thro	O
'	O
her	O
Fingers	O
upon	O
a	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
.	O
This	O
ocasion	O
'd	O
them	O
all	O
to	O
be	O
apprehended	O
,	O
herself	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
two	O
Servants	O
that	O
carried	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
liv	O
'd	O
by	O
buying	O
id	O
felling	O
of	O
Old	O
Clothes	O
,	O
Starch	O
,	O
and	O
such	O
sort	O
of	O
Goods	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
full	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Finch	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hollier	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
1	O
Gallon	O
of	O
Rum	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.1	O
Cane,2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hollier	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
plain	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
accordingly	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Barret	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Cloth	O
Coats	O
,	O
one	O
Cloth	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
one	O
Dowlas	O
Shirt	O
,	O
from	O
James	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
Ball	O
depos	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
his	O
Wife	O
was	O
abroad	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
lame	O
,	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
quite	O
away	O
the	O
prisoner	O
denied	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
because	O
it	O
was	O
an	O
ill	O
House	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
Wife	O
which	O
took	O
,	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Country	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Weather	O
Sheep	O
,	O
Value	O
25	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sheoble	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Weather	O
Sheep	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Proof	O
was	O
very	O
deficient	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Newall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
Occupation	O
>	O
poulterer	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Rape	O
on	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Morning	O
when	O
her	O
Mistress	O
was	O
,	O
gone	O
out	O
to	O
her	O
whilst	O
she	O
was	O
after	O
and	O
paid	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
her	O
body	O
,	O
which	O
surprising	O
Behaviour	O
obliged	O
turn	O
upon	O
her	O
Belly	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
do	O
it	O
one	O
Way	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
do	O
it	O
t'other	O
;	O
which	O
,	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
quite	O
tir	O
'd	O
with	O
struggling	O
,	O
her	O
Breasts	O
being	O
bit	O
and	O
her	O
Body	O
much	O
abus	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
at	O
last	O
accomplish	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
spite	O
of	O
all	O
her	O
Rage	O
and	O
assion	O
,	O
turn	O
'd	O
her	O
about	O
and	O
satisfied	O
himself	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
that	O
Place	O
where	O
Nature	O
most	O
excuses	O
it	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
her	O
Mistress	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
her	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
who	O
being	O
justly	O
enraged	O
at	O
so	O
monstrous	O
and	O
detestable	O
an	O
Action	O
,	O
advis	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
take	O
out	O
a	O
Warrant	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
Evidences	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Morris	O
told	O
them	O
of	O
it	O
immediately	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
whole	O
Story	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
several	O
Persons	O
to	O
prove	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Noise	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
whether	O
they	O
were	O
asleep	O
or	O
no	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
;	O
these	O
lodg	O
'd	O
or	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
one	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
she	O
heard	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
say	O
,	O
If	O
her	O
Master	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
five	O
Guineas	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
prosecute	O
.	O
Another	O
depos	O
'd	O
she	O
heard	O
her	O
say	O
,	O
Her	O
Master	O
had	O
enter	O
'd	O
her	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
she	O
was	O
awak	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
found	O
herself	O
in	O
an	O
uncleanly	O
Circumstance	O
:	O
This	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
she	O
kept	O
a	O
young	O
Man	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Hours	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
.	O
A	O
Midwife	O
depos	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
she	O
were	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
how	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
injured	O
;	O
which	O
at	O
last	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
no	O
Marks	O
of	O
Violence	O
nor	O
Pregnancy	O
.	O
And	O
some	O
others	O
gave	O
Evidence	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
appear	O
a	O
Malicious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
occasion	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Wife	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
took	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
into	O
their	O
Consideration	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
their	O
Verdict	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
,	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death,13	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hanson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Stevenson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
T	O
-	O
E	O
-	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Ralph	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
alias	O
Parker	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
T	O
-	O
D	O
-	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pyman	I-pers
alias	O
Kettles	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
alias	O
Finch	O
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Chester	I-pers
,	O
who	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
to	O
three	O
Indictments	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
was	O
called	O
down	O
to	O
his	O
former	O
Sentence	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand,4	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
David	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Goddard	I-pers
,	O
Sen.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt,13	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Unitt	I-pers
,	O
M	O
-	O
J	O
-	O
,	O
Frances	B-pers
Duckhouse	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Nicholls	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
Giles	I-pers
,	O
Katharine	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Cattings	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Mecomb	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Briscow	I-pers
,	O
Ralph	B-pers
Emmery	I-pers
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Robertson	I-pers
fin	O
'd	O
20	O
Marks	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
pleaded	O
her	O
,	O
Belly	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
being	O
impanell	O
'd	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Quick	O
with	O
Child	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
Lately	O
Published	O
,	O
ARichmetick	O
made	O
Easie	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
New	O
Method	O
now	O
taught	O
and	O
practis	O
'd	O
in	O
London	O
.	O
Wherein	O
the	O
Rules	O
of	O
that	O
necessary	O
Art	O
are	O
briefly	O
explain	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
illustrated	O
with	O
such	O
familiar	O
Examples	O
,	O
as	O
may	O
suit	O
the	O
meanest	O
Capacity	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
desire	O
to	O
learn	O
it	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
a	O
succinct	O
Treatise	O
of	O
Decimal	O
Fractions	O
,	O
with	O
compleat	O
Tables	O
,	O
Rules	O
,	O
and	O
Examples	O
demonstrating	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
like	O
not	O
extant	O
in	O
any	O
other	O
Treatise	O
of	O
this	O
Nature	O
.	O
By	O
John	B-pers
Copeland	I-pers
,	O
Writing	O
Master	O
.	O
The	O
2d	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
st	O
The	O
London	O
new	O
Method	O
and	O
Art	O
of	O
Teaching	O
Children	O
to	O
Spell	O
and	O
Read	O
;	O
so	O
as	O
they	O
may	O
,	O
without	O
the	O
Help	O
of	O
any	O
other	O
Books	O
,	O
read	O
the	O
Bible	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
Twelve	O
Months	O
.	O
Note	O
,	O
This	O
Way	O
of	O
Teaching	O
is	O
approved	O
by	O
most	O
School-Masters	O
as	O
the	O
best	O
.	O
Price	O
Bound	O
6	O
d.	O
with	O
great	O
Allowance	O
to	O
those	O
who	O
sell	O
or	O
give	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
Both	O
printed	O
for	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
Edmund	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
and	O
Crown	O
in	O
Lombard-strees	O
,	O
near	O
Stocks-Market	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Good	O
of	O
the	O
Publish	O
.	O
WHereas	O
several	O
Gentlewomen	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
that	O
Sex	O
,	O
in	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
have	O
contracted	O
an	O
evil	O
Habit	O
of	O
Body	O
,	O
wherein	O
the	O
vicious	O
Humours	O
,	O
at	O
first	O
dispers	O
'd	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Whole	O
,	O
come	O
at	O
length	O
to	O
be	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
one	O
Part	O
or	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
times	O
,	O
for	O
Canses	O
too	O
long	O
to	O
be	O
here	O
mentioned	O
,	O
are	O
thrown	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Womb	O
,	O
occasioning	O
a	O
dangerous	O
Weakness	O
in	O
that	O
Part	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
neglected	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
turns	O
Cancerous	O
,	O
and	O
often	O
proves	O
Fatal	O
.	O
I	O
cure	O
the	O
Diabetes	O
when	O
given	O
over	O
by	O
all	O
other	O
Persons	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
to	O
acquaint	O
all	O
such	O
as	O
may	O
have	O
occasion	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
speedy	O
Relief	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
had	O
from	O
an	O
Experienc	O
'd	O
Midwife	O
,	O
dwelling	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Queens	O
Arms	O
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Smith	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
near	O
charge	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
;	O
who	O
perform	O
'd	O
a	O
Care	O
upon	O
a	O
Lady	O
at	O
the	O
Bath	O
,	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
given	O
over	O
by	O
the	O
Physicians	O
,	O
and	O
since	O
has	O
Cured	O
several	O
Gentlewomen	O
and	O
others	O
in	O
the	O
City	O
and	O
Suburbs	O
of	O
London	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
put	O
my	O
self	O
in	O
Publick	O
Print	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
satisfy	O
the	O
Afflicted	O
where	O
they	O
may	O
have	O
speedy	O
Relief	O
after	O
they	O
are	O
given	O
over	O
by	O
all	O
other	O
Persons	O
.	O
A	O
Water	O
that	O
perfectly	O
cures	O
the	O
Itch	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
Itching	O
Humour	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
,	O
without	O
necessity	O
of	O
Purging	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
dangerous	O
life	O
of	O
Mercury	O
;	O
as	O
will	O
be	O
attested	O
by	O
several	O
Persons	O
of	O
sufficient	O
Credit	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.6	O
d.	O
the	O
Bottle	O
,	O
Prepar	O
'd	O
by	O
A	O
.	O
Downing	O
,	O
Chyn	O
at	O
the	O
Golden	O
Ball	O
and	O
Crown	O
in	O
d-Alley	O
,	O
without	O
Bid	O
.	O
Where	O
also	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
,	O
A	O
curious	O
Preparation	O
for	O
Teeth	O
and	O
Gums	O
which	O
fastens	O
loose	O
Teeth	O
,	O
cures	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
in	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
preve	O
their	O
rotting	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
And	O
a	O
Remedy	O
for	O
the	O
Tooth-A	O
the	O
most	O
general	O
for	O
giving	O
effectual	O
Ease	O
of	O
any	O
yet	O
know	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
Likewise	O
the	O
true	O
Essential	O
Spirits	O
of	O
Scurvy-g	O
Purging	O
and	O
Plain	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
the	O
Spirits	O
of	O
Ground-Ivy	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
Bottle	O
.	O
DAVID	B-pers
POVET	I-pers
,	O
removed	O
from	O
Hatton	O
Garden	O
to	O
Exeter-Exchange	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
London	O
,	O
Opera	O
for	O
the	O
Teeth	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
the	O
Honour	O
to	O
clean	O
her	O
late	O
jesty	O
's	O
Teeth	O
;	O
he	O
sells	O
a	O
pleasant	O
Dentrifice	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
that	O
King	O
Charles	B-pers
II	I-pers
.	O
constantly	O
used	O
:	O
It	O
makes	O
the	O
Teeth	O
as	O
white	O
as	O
Ivory	O
,	O
and	O
preserves	O
them	O
from	O
decaying	O
,	O
destroying	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
.	O
He	O
hath	O
a	O
Cephalick	O
which	O
certain	O
cures	O
the	O
Tooth-Ach	O
in	O
a	O
Minute	O
's	O
Time	O
,	O
beyond	O
any	O
son	O
in	O
England	O
.	O
If	O
the	O
Teeth	O
are	O
rotten	O
,	O
or	O
uneven	O
,	O
full	O
of	O
Holes	O
or	O
black	O
Specks	O
,	O
he	O
will	O
make	O
them	O
smo	O
even	O
,	O
sound	O
,	O
and	O
white	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
no	O
Person	O
shall	O
difting	O
where	O
the	O
Defect	O
has	O
been	O
.	O
He	O
sets	O
in	O
Artificial	O
Teeth	O
easie	O
,	O
neat	O
,	O
and	O
firm	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
need	O
not	O
be	O
removed	O
seven	O
Years	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
may	O
eat	O
with	O
them	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
their	O
former	O
,	O
and	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
distinguished	O
from	O
their	O
ones	O
.	O
He	O
sells	O
a	O
pleasant	O
Water	O
,	O
that	O
prevents	O
any	O
tenness	O
from	O
seizing	O
the	O
Teeth	O
,	O
takes	O
all	O
Pains	O
and	O
positivenes	O
,	O
Cankers	O
or	O
Swellings	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Gams	O
,	O
and	O
loose	O
Teeth	O
,	O
which	O
several	O
Persons	O
of	O
Quality	O
and	O
know	O
to	O
be	O
true	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
sold	O
all	O
that	O
is	O
printed	O
here	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
Kings	O
,	O
Queens	O
,	O
Princes	O
,	O
Nobility	O
and	O
Ge	O
in	O
England	O
,	O
since	O
King	O
Charles	O
II	O
dy	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
to	O
give	O
Notice	O
,	O
THAT	O
at	O
the	O
Glass	O
Lane	O
High-Court	O
in	O
still	O
lives	O
the	O
only	O
nal	O
and	O
Daughter	O
to	O
Dr	O
.	O
The	O
Kilcns	O
,	O
a	O
Collegiate	O
cian	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Sword	O
Physician	O
in	O
Ordinary	O
to	O
K	O
Charles	O
II	O
.	O
who	O
with	O
his	O
Famous	O
Pills	O
and	O
Drink	O
cures	O
Ulcers	O
,	O
Sores	O
,	O
Scurfs	O
,	O
Scurvies	O
,	O
Leprosies	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
Scor	O
Humours	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Venereal	O
Disease	O
,	O
be	O
it	O
never	O
so	O
bad	O
,	O
all	O
times	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
,	O
without	O
Confinement	O
or	O
the	O
use	O
Mercury	O
,	O
which	O
destroys	O
many	O
by	O
raising	O
the	O
Malig	O
the	O
Head	O
.	O
She	O
hath	O
cured	O
Hundreds	O
that	O
have	O
been	O
by	O
others	O
.	O
The	O
Drink	O
is	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
Quart	O
,	O
the	O
Pills	O
1	O
s.2	O
l.	O
with	O
Directions	O
.	O
They	O
cleanse	O
the	O
Body	O
and	O
Blood	O
of	O
Impurities	O
,	O
which	O
cause	O
Dropfies	O
,	O
Gouts	O
,	O
Scurvies	O
,	O
and	O
Gravel	O
,	O
Giddiness	O
and	O
Palns	O
in	O
the	O
Head	O
and	O
other	O
She	O
given	O
her	O
Advice	O
to	O
all	O
that	O
write	O
or	O
come	O
to	O
her	O
and	O
can	O
cure	O
any	O
that	O
send	O
their	O
Grief	O
and	O
Age	O
,	O
soeing	O
them	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
PHILLIPS	O
;	O
by	O
M.	O
Jenour	O
against	O
St.	O
Sepalchres	O
Back	O
Gate	O
in	O
Gilt	O
Spar	O
St	O
near	O
Newgate	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
Sold	O
by	O
J.	O
Roberts	O
near	O
the	O
Oxford-Arms	O
in	O
Warwick	O
Lane	O
.	O
17th	O
Where	O
Advertisements	O
are	O
taken	O
in	O
(	O
Price	O
2	O
d	O
.	O
)	O
