TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
,	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
5th,6th,7th,8th	O
,	O
and	O
10th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
November,1716	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Third	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
1	O
Dec.1716	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
JAMES	B-pers
BATEMAN	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
and	O
Bart	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
King	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Eyres	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
Names	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
William	B-pers
Brandson	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Dicks	I-pers
Abraham	B-pers
Pottifer	I-pers
Hellers	B-pers
Thursbury	I-pers
John	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
Jacob	B-pers
Hilliard	I-pers
John	B-pers
West	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Burridge	I-pers
John	B-pers
Tailor	I-pers
William	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
William	B-pers
Tailor	I-pers
Christopher	B-pers
Clayton	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cliff	I-pers
Abraham	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Chase	I-pers
John	B-pers
Pashly	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Billing	I-pers
Daniel	B-pers
Croker	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
John	B-pers
Cash	I-pers
Alexander	B-pers
Kilgore	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Stiff	I-pers
John	B-pers
Marley	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followth	O
:	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hardy	I-pers
one	O
Mug	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
October	O
1715	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
,	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
Master	O
's	O
House	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Acquaintance	O
of	O
hers	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
some	O
Person	O
(	O
as	O
she	O
said	O
)	O
of	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
recommending	O
her	O
is	O
a	O
her	O
self	O
to	O
be	O
Cook	O
go	O
to	O
but	O
be	O
answer	O
'd	O
she	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Ne	O
he	O
mightily	O
pretty	O
House	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Maid	O
,	O
how	O
two	O
such	O
Instances	O
,	O
found	O
in	O
London	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
;	O
offering	O
her	O
Master	O
with	O
her	O
in	O
that	O
;	O
found	O
her	O
very	O
busy	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
her	O
to	O
come	O
looking	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
Several	O
Persons	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
she	O
to	O
take	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
'd	O
the	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
silver	O
Mug	O
of	O
depos	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
seeing	O
Apartments	O
for	O
some	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Cashes	I-pers
Family	O
;	O
she	O
approved	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
appointed	O
a	O
time	O
when	O
the	O
Persons	O
themselves	O
should	O
come	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
she	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Mug	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
swearing	O
positively	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hartly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Tottenham	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
Steers	O
,	O
value	O
51.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Cawthorn	I-pers
of	O
Ely	B-place
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Snipp	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
employ	O
'd	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Cawthorn	O
to	O
endeavour	O
to	O
find	O
his	O
Beasts	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
them	O
at	O
Tottenham	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
the	O
Beasts	O
were	O
deliver	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
by	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Drake	I-pers
in	O
Yorkshire	O
,	O
to	O
sell	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
:	O
but	O
that	O
appearing	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
improbable	O
Story	O
,	O
they	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
Second	O
time	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bay	O
Colt	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
of	O
Ely	B-place
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
October	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
Francis	O
Harrison	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Horse	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Grounds	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
Mr.	O
Cawthorn	O
lost	O
his	O
Steers	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Stomp	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
knowing	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Harrison	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Custody	O
of	O
one	O
Carter	O
at	O
the	O
Green	O
Man	O
at	O
Carter	O
who	O
had	O
set	O
him	O
there	O
?	O
and	O
Carter	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Will	O
.	O
Hartly	O
;	O
he	O
thereupon	O
gave	O
notice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Harrison	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
and	O
owned	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
deliver	O
'd	O
any	O
Horse	O
to	O
Carter	O
:	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
plainness	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
bought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
also	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Salts	O
,	O
val.15	O
s.4	O
Silver	O
Tasters	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
1	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
val.20	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Box	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
9	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
val.5	O
l.	O
and	O
4	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
M	I-pers
..	I-pers
ser	I-pers
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
her	O
Servant	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
aforesaid	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Box	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
before	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Abney	I-pers
,	O
and	O
had	O
dispos	O
'd	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
several	O
Persons	O
;	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
gave	O
Evidence	O
thereof	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Johnston	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Boxford	I-pers
,5	O
silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
40s	O
.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Salt	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
Taster	O
,	O
value	O
3s	O
.	O
6	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	O
Boxford	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
Eliz	O
Boxford	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
living	O
in	O
an	O
Apartment	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
,	O
had	O
often	O
seen	O
where	O
she	O
laid	O
the	O
said	O
plate	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Boxford	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
at	O
his	O
going	O
out	O
to	O
Work	O
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
being	O
abroad	O
likewise	O
,	O
he	O
lock	O
'd	O
his	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
his	O
return	O
found	O
it	O
so	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
things	O
missing	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
apprehend	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
hid	O
in	O
the	O
Cieling	O
,	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
one	O
Partridge	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Boxford	I-pers
,	O
jun	O
.	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
while	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
offered	O
to	O
help	O
her	O
to	O
her	O
Wedding-Ring	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
Crown	O
.	O
All	O
which	O
she	O
denied	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Vintner	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
one	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
51.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
Brooks	O
;	O
and	O
likewise	O
one	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
and	O
Seal	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
l.	O
from	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Th	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
from	O
Hampton-Court	B-place
to	I-place
R	I-place
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
robb	O
'd	O
by	O
3	O
Highway-men	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dark	O
of	O
the	O
Evening	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
deposed	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
thereupon	O
advertised	O
her	O
Watch	O
and	O
Chain	O
,	O
offering	O
a	O
Reward	O
of	O
15	O
l.	O
upon	O
which	O
her	O
Watch	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
the	O
Silver	O
one	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
her	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Holder	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Holder	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
drinking	O
in	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
one	O
Trippuck	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pull	O
'd	O
the	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
desiring	O
to	O
have	O
some	O
Money	O
borrowed	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
won	O
it	O
at	O
a	O
Gaming	O
Table	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Holder	O
thinking	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
true	O
,	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
borrow	O
'd	O
10	O
l.	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
after	O
,	O
Trippuck	O
met	O
Holder	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
borrow	O
some	O
Money	O
upon	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
seeming	O
unwilling	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
Trippuck	O
used	O
some	O
menacing	O
Language	O
;	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
worse	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
afterwards	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Watches	O
being	O
advertis	O
'd	O
,	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
.	O
The	O
Watches	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
swear	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Persons	O
who	O
robb	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
received	O
the	O
Watch	O
of	O
Trippuck	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
not	O
positive	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
taking	O
them	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
New	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Bromley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Chiswick	B-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
County	I-place
of	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
2	O
Linnen	O
Cloths	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
that	O
he	O
going	O
through	O
his	O
Ground	O
,	O
espy	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
immediately	O
ran	O
into	O
an	O
Out-house	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
some	O
Cloths	O
in	O
a	O
tub	O
where	O
they	O
used	O
to	O
lie	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
one	O
Cloth	O
and	O
a	O
Sack	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
poor	O
necessitous	O
Creature	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
Catherines	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
together	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Erasmus	I-pers
(	O
not	O
taken	O
)	O
for	O
stealing	O
12	O
pieces	O
of	O
Lignum-Vitae	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Roop	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
put	O
397	O
sticks	O
of	O
Lignum	O
Vitae	O
on	O
board	O
of	O
a	O
Lighter	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
shipped	O
off	O
for	O
Holland	O
,	O
committing	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Care	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Eskin	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Watchman	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Eskin	I-pers
deposed	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
down	O
with	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
falling	O
asleep	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
at	O
taking	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Lighter	O
there	O
were	O
12	O
sticks	O
wanting	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Cox	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
several	O
times	O
lost	O
Coats	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
Bell	B-place
Wharf	I-place
seeing	O
a	O
Boat	O
run	O
ashore	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
up	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
in	O
it	O
the	O
Lignum-Vitae	O
in	O
the	O
Stern	O
,	O
cover	O
'd	O
with	O
a	O
Rag	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
piece	O
flung	O
on	O
Shore	O
.	O
Upon	O
his	O
coming	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
ran	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Boat	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
call	O
him	O
to	O
Breakfast	O
.	O
He	O
follow	O
'd	O
them	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
who	O
pleaded	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
That	O
going	O
to	O
Work	O
,	O
his	O
Boat	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
the	O
Water	O
with	O
the	O
Wood	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
brought	O
it	O
over	O
to	O
this	O
side	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
the	O
Owner	O
.	O
But	O
this	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
but	O
a	O
Pretence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
an	O
Assault	O
and	O
Robbery	O
committed	O
upon	O
Margaret	B-pers
Harwood	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Pocket	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
a	O
Tortoise-shell	O
Snuff-box	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
Knife	O
and	O
Fork	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s	O
:	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
val.1	O
s.6	O
d.	O
and	O
4	O
Shillings	O
in	O
foreign	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
along	O
Walbrook	B-place
about	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
two	O
others	O
dogg	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
struck	O
her	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
his	O
hand	O
upon	O
her	O
while	O
another	O
of	O
them	O
pulled	O
her	O
pocket	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
they	O
all	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
made	O
their	O
escape	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
some	O
cry	O
out	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
stop	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
very	O
positive	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Woolistone	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
Shop	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Ring	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
show	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
liking	O
it	O
,	O
bid	O
him	O
weigh	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
presending	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
Weights	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
might	O
be	O
cheated	O
,	O
laid	O
a	O
Brass	O
Ring	O
into	O
the	O
Draw	O
instead	O
of	O
the	O
Gold	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
:	O
The	O
Goldsmith	O
immediately	O
perceiving	O
it	O
,	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Ring	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Brass	O
Ring	O
as	O
a	O
Pattern	O
to	O
by	O
a	O
Gold	O
one	O
by	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
a	O
Pretence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
of	O
London	O
,	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
9	O
Ells	O
of	O
Sleazy	O
Holland	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bower	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hains	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
being	O
employ	O
'd	O
to	O
carry	O
a	O
Pack	O
and	O
Case	O
of	O
Goods	O
from	O
the	O
Four	O
Swans	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
,	O
to	O
Mr	O
Bower	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Hellens	I-place
,	O
he	O
stepping	O
for	O
a	O
Porter	O
to	O
help	O
him	O
unload	O
them	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
Cart	O
,	O
and	O
suspecting	O
him	O
,	O
looked	O
upon	O
the	O
Pack	O
,	O
saw	O
it	O
cut	O
,	O
and	O
seized	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
charging	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
his	O
bosom	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
supposing	O
it	O
to	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
Pack	O
in	O
the	O
Cart	O
,	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
deliver	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Carman	O
.	O
But	O
this	O
pretence	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Withers	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anne	I-place
Undershaft	I-place
in	I-place
Limestreets	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
9	O
Cloth	O
Mourning-Cloaks	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Boulthy	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
Lodging	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
loft	O
his	O
Cloaks	O
about	O
8	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Counter	O
,	O
in	O
such	O
manner	O
that	O
he	O
thought	O
no	O
person	O
but	O
one	O
who	O
was	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
house	O
could	O
steal	O
them	O
,	O
was	O
informed	O
by	O
a	O
friend	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
his	O
Lodger	O
was	O
a	O
person	O
of	O
an	O
ill	O
Character	O
,	O
he	O
therefore	O
apprehended	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
prove	O
them	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
bringing	O
some	O
Persons	O
to	O
swear	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
elsewhere	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
the	O
Cloaks	O
were	O
stole	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Bartholmew	B-pers
Nicholson	I-pers
of	O
London	O
,	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
,	O
value	O
50s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
one	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Stamp	I-pers
,	O
from	O
Usher	B-pers
Bull	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Boy	O
.	O
Usher	O
Bull	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Lombard	B-place
street	I-place
with	O
a	O
Box	O
and	O
Wig	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
into	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
some	O
people	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
the	O
Wig	O
to	O
another	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
the	O
Wig	O
was	O
not	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Boy	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Bithiah	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Gardiner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
3	O
Dozen	O
skeins	O
of	O
Thread	O
,	O
Silk	O
,	O
and	O
Thread	O
Laces	O
,	O
a	O
Swanskin	O
Petticoat	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Welsted	I-pers
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
depos	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
her	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
married	O
person	O
,	O
gave	O
her	O
Warning	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
inquiry	O
found	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
sold	O
to	O
a	O
Chandler	O
Woman	O
,	O
who	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Mother	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Mother	O
deposed	O
,	O
her	O
Danghter	O
brought	O
the	O
things	O
home	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
given	O
her	O
by	O
a	O
Servant	O
Maid	O
that	O
liv	O
'd	O
there	O
before	O
she	O
came	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Father	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
came	O
a	O
Porter	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
his	O
Daughter	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Servant	O
before	O
mentioned	O
,	O
to	O
inform	O
her	O
that	O
Search	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Welsted	O
after	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
that	O
Servant	O
.	O
Several	O
Persons	O
appear	O
'd	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Pauls	I-place
Shadwel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
steal-	O
from	O
on	O
Shipboard	O
40	O
Yards	O
of	O
Camlet	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
and	O
85	O
Yards	O
of	O
Farendine	O
,	O
value	O
81.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Anthony	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Merry	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Master	O
of	O
the	O
Ship	O
depos	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
desiring	O
to	O
be	O
entertain	O
'd	O
as	O
a	O
Sailor	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
him	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
.	O
The	O
Mate	O
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
left	O
him	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
Sunday	O
in	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
Ship	O
and	O
Good	O
;	O
but	O
on	O
Monday	O
Morning	O
he	O
going	O
on	O
board	O
,	O
found	O
no	O
body	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Packs	O
cut	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
gone	O
;	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
him	O
till	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
him	O
by	O
chance	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
time	O
be	O
had	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
on	O
made	O
of	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Farendine	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
matter	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hurd	I-pers
and	I-pers
Anne	I-pers
his	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
and	O
Anne	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwel	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Weather	O
Sheep	O
,	O
value	O
31.	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Gadsby	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Lambeth	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Sheep	O
being	O
stolen	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Newteners-lane	O
to	O
search	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
at	O
a	O
boyling	O
Cook	O
's	O
3	O
Pelts	O
with	O
the	O
Heads	O
and	O
Feet	O
cut	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Wooll	O
pulled	O
off	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
Mutton	O
hanging	O
behind	O
a	O
Bed	O
.	O
The	O
Person	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Meat	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Going	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
8	O
Stone	O
of	O
Fat	O
,	O
Bags	O
of	O
Wool	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
nature	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
a	O
Sheep	O
stealing	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
for	O
being	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
disposing	O
of	O
the	O
Carcasses	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
his	O
Share	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
been	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
therefore	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
guilty	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
Wife	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Sheep	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
value	O
3l	O
.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wildey	I-pers
:	O
But	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Quinby	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cabinet	O
,	O
value	O
6l	O
.	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
22	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
Nov	O
.	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
Edmund	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
,	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lived	O
in	O
two	O
several	O
Tenements	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
lock	O
'd	O
his	O
Door	O
,	O
leaving	O
the	O
Things	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
;	O
that	O
upon	O
his	O
return	O
he	O
found	O
indeed	O
his	O
Door	O
lock	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
opening	O
it	O
found	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
wherein	O
these	O
Things	O
were	O
,	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Things	O
gone	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
getting	O
a	O
Search-warrant	O
,	O
searched	O
her	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
which	O
he	O
called	O
a	O
Cabinet	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
only	O
a	O
square	O
Pastboard	O
Box	O
)	O
with	O
his	O
Writings	O
upon	O
her	O
Bed	O
's	O
Tester	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
And	O
as	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Box	O
down	O
from	O
the	O
Tester	O
himself	O
,	O
is	O
being	O
but	O
a	O
small	O
one	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
suggested	O
it	O
might	O
possibly	O
be	O
conveyed	O
thither	O
by	O
himself	O
,	O
especially	O
since	O
she	O
frequently	O
left	O
her	O
Room	O
open	O
.	O
And	O
there	O
had	O
lately	O
been	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
betwixt	O
them	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
carried	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
for	O
beating	O
her	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
heard	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
up	O
with	O
the	O
Old	O
Bitch	O
,	O
She	O
brought	O
so	O
many	O
of	O
her	O
Neighbours	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
having	O
known	O
her	O
for	O
20	O
or	O
30	O
Years	O
,	O
gave	O
her	O
so	O
fair	O
a	O
Character	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
carried	O
in	O
it	O
a	O
flagrant	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
being	O
malicious	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
John	B-pers
Mooney	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Dane	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Jacob	B-pers
Pattison	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
Sept	O
.	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Day-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
1	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.1	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.1	O
silver	O
Box	O
,	O
val.40	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
l	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Truss	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
committed	O
the	O
Robbery	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
double	O
Casements	O
to	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
open	O
,	O
Moony	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Window	O
and	O
handed	O
the	O
Goods	O
ont	O
to	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
they	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
the	O
Evidence	O
in	O
their	O
Lives	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
but	O
John	B-pers
Truss	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Moony	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Dane	I-pers
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
Hours	O
of	O
7	O
and	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
12	O
Shirts	O
and	O
Shifts	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
val.20	O
s	O
and	O
3	O
Pillowbiers	O
,	O
val.3	O
s	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Window	O
was	O
shut	O
.	O
John	O
Truss	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
he	O
committed	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
that	O
Moony	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
and	O
handed	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
Dane	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
sold	O
to	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Price	I-pers
in	O
Turnbowl-street	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Lewis	B-pers
Goldsborough	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Goldsborough	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
(	O
Father	O
and	O
Son	O
)	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
28	O
Bolts	O
of	O
Willow	O
Osier-rod	O
,	O
val.17	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Merriack	I-pers
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Person	O
that	O
found	O
them	O
swore	O
the	O
Rods	O
to	O
be	O
John	O
Merriack	O
's	O
and	O
Jeremiah	O
Howel	O
depos	O
'd	O
they	O
both	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Weeten	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Weeten	I-pers
,	O
his	O
Father	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Serge	O
Breeches	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
Brass	O
Cock	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
val.3	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
his	O
Father	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
broke	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
notorious	O
Offender	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Father	O
swore	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
the	O
like	O
twenty	O
times	O
:	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
tenderly	O
considering	O
the	O
Case	O
,	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Charlsworth	I-pers
,	O
between	O
the	O
Hours	O
of	O
12	O
and	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
,	O
Muslin	O
Head-cloths	O
,	O
value	O
3l	O
.	O
16	O
Silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
Thread	O
,	O
Tape	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Shop	O
was	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
gone	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Day	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
himself	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
William	O
A	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
and	O
one	O
called	O
Will	O
the	O
Sailor	O
,	O
broke	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Fields	O
and	O
shared	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
6d	O
.	O
for	O
his	O
Part	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
ever	O
known	O
or	O
seen	O
John	O
Day	O
in	O
his	O
Life	O
:	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
Companions	O
,	O
He	O
called	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
Ann	B-pers
Brickheaver	I-pers
,	O
who	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
the	O
Night	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
done	O
by	O
9	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
rise	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
till	O
7	O
.	O
And	O
being	O
asked	O
how	O
she	O
knew	O
?	O
she	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
lay	O
with	O
his	O
Mother	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
bed	O
at	O
the	O
feet	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
Sister	O
that	O
swore	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
Proof	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
depending	O
upon	O
the	O
single	O
Evidence	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Day	I-pers
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Wallgrave	B-pers
Freer	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Night-gown	O
,	O
a	O
Holland	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Burridge	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
cou	O
'd	O
not	O
swear	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
the	O
Persons	O
who	O
robbed	O
her	O
:	O
they	O
were	O
apprehended	O
by	O
the	O
Information	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Young	I-pers
an	O
Accomplice	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
though	O
he	O
informed	O
against	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Names	O
,	O
these	O
were	O
not	O
the	O
Persons	O
.	O
So	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Sewet	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
2	O
Brass	O
Stew	O
pans	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Keilin	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Weilder	I-pers
,	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
Nov.	O
last	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Lawn	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
going	O
along	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Shop	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
that	O
he	O
shop	O
'd	O
him	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
back	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
again	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
drop	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
But	O
tho	O
'	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Bridget	B-pers
Birk	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
Seal	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Chain	O
,	O
val.2	O
s.3	O
Moidores	O
,	O
val.4	O
l.	O
and	O
9	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Rotherham	I-pers
,	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
Nov	O
,	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
's	O
Girl	O
she	O
employ	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
wash	O
a	O
Room	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
that	O
opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Things	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Waterman	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
hat	O
she	O
going	O
in	O
his	O
Boat	O
to	O
Brentford	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
seeing	O
her	O
have	O
so	O
much	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Watch-string	O
hang	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Bosom	O
,	O
he	O
suspected	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
come	O
honestly	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
therefore	O
stopp	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
notice	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Nodes	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
an	O
Assault	O
and	O
Robbery	O
upon	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Persons	O
of	O
Grace	B-pers
Stacy	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Carleton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
taking	O
from	O
them	O
2	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
a	O
Crown-piece	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
more	O
in	O
small	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutors	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
Noon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
rode	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Whetstone	O
Coach	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Finchly	B-place
Common	I-place
,	O
having	O
a	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
black	O
Crape	O
over	O
one	O
side	O
of	O
his	O
Face	O
;	O
and	O
presenting	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
demanded	O
their	O
Money	O
and	O
Rings	O
,	O
which	O
not	O
coming	O
off	O
easily	O
,	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
them	O
off	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
rased	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
's	O
Finger	O
in	O
pulling	O
them	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
rode	O
off	O
,	O
but	O
notice	O
being	O
immediately	O
given	O
at	O
Finchly	O
,	O
several	O
Persons	O
pursu	O
'd	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
Evidences	O
that	O
were	O
positive	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Matter	O
being	O
so	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
an	O
Assault	O
and	O
Robbery	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
committed	O
on	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Sheldon	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
Novemb	O
.	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
41	O
and	O
40	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
on	O
Finchly	B-place
Common	I-place
upon	O
a	O
Sorrel	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
deliver	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
alias	O
Nodes	O
turn	O
'd	O
about	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
Whetstone	O
Coach	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
rode	O
away	O
together	O
;	O
but	O
were	O
so	O
closely	O
pursued	O
by	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
obliged	O
to	O
take	O
into	O
a	O
Wood	O
,	O
and	O
Hudson	O
alias	O
Butler	O
,	O
being	O
unhors	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
Bough	O
of	O
a	O
Tree	O
,	O
was	O
tsken	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
positive	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
therefore	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
David	B-pers
Blair	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Katharine	B-pers
Morecock	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
her	O
1	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
val.10	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
l	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
having	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
Carrier	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
in	O
Radcliff	B-place
Highway	I-place
,	O
and	O
offered	O
her	O
his	O
Hand	O
to	O
help	O
her	O
over	O
a	O
Kennel	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
refused	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
offering	O
to	O
carry	O
her	O
Bundle	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
refused	O
likewise	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
her	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
Bundle	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
by	O
the	O
Information	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Day	I-pers
.	O
She	O
was	O
positive	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
her	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bentley	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Potter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Callico	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
81.	O
a	O
Callico	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
a	O
Laced	O
Head	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
l.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Laced	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
val	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
25	O
l.	O
the	O
3d	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Bridget	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
she	O
bought	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
them	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
act	O
as	O
a	O
Chairwoman	O
in	O
the	O
Family	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Swan	O
with	O
Two	O
Necks	O
in	O
Lad	O
lane	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
be	O
carried	O
to	O
a	O
Lady	O
:	O
But	O
3	O
Weeks	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
advice	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
never	O
received	O
the	O
Things	O
.	O
The	O
Carrier	O
and	O
Book-keeper	O
deposed	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
they	O
never	O
received	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
deliver	O
'd	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
Inn	O
to	O
one	O
who	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
Carrier	O
.	O
She	O
being	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
no	O
ill	O
Character	O
,	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
probable	O
she	O
might	O
be	O
bit	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
by	O
some	O
Sharper	O
;	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
B-	B-pers
P-	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Indian	O
Carpets	O
,	O
val	O
6l	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Work-house	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Wren	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
along	O
with	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Draper	O
,	O
to	O
have	O
some	O
Callico	O
glaz	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
she	O
missed	O
the	O
Carpets	O
,	O
and	O
sending	O
her	O
Apprentice	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
back	O
.	O
The	O
Apprentice	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Carpets	O
up	O
within	O
some	O
Pallisadoes	O
near	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
supposing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
thrown	O
there	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Linnen	O
Draper	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
(	O
being	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
Credit	O
)	O
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
perceive	O
her	O
either	O
have	O
or	O
throw	O
any	O
thing	O
away	O
.	O
And	O
she	O
brought	O
so	O
many	O
Persons	O
of	O
Worth	O
and	O
unexceptionable	O
Credit	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
so	O
extraordinary	O
a	O
Character	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Dobson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Ann	B-pers
Downs	I-pers
upon	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Pocket	O
value	O
2	O
s	O
a	O
Holland	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
val.1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
her	O
Pocket	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Pocket	O
was	O
not	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Waterman	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Hungerford	O
ford	O
Stairs	O
:	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
of	O
London	O
,	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Mary	B-pers
Rutherford	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Tickin	O
Pocket	O
,	O
val.4	O
d.	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
val.18	O
d.	O
a	O
Cambrick	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
val.1	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Goves	O
,	O
val	O
1s	O
,	O
a	O
Muslim	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
Street	O
about	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
an	O
Accomplice	O
of	O
his	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Companion	O
pulled	O
her	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
her	O
Pocket	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
dark	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
possible	O
for	O
the	O
Evidence	O
to	O
the	O
mistaken	O
;	O
thereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Draw	I-pers
of	O
London	O
,	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
Martha	B-pers
Peacock	I-pers
a	O
Linnen	O
Pocket	O
,	O
val.2	O
s.1	O
Holland	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
val.1	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
White	O
Gloves	O
,	O
val	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Scissars	O
and	O
3	O
Keys	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
behind	O
her	O
,	O
thrust	O
his	O
Hand	O
up	O
her	O
Riding-hood	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
her	O
Pocket	O
of	O
;	O
that	O
upon	O
her	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
followed	O
and	O
knocked	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Pocket	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Augustine	B-pers
Lincoln	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Woolnoth	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
an	O
Assault	O
and	O
Murder	O
committed	O
on	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Fibbot	I-pers
the	O
25th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
inside	O
of	O
the	O
Thigh	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Breadth	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Manslaughter	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Beans	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
himself	O
were	O
all	O
Fellow-	O
Servants	O
at	O
the	O
Swan	B-place
Tavern	I-place
in	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
;	O
that	O
himself	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
both	O
been	O
cleaning	O
of	O
Knives	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
having	O
had	O
some	O
Oysters	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
pitching	O
the	O
Shells	O
into	O
a	O
Hole	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Deceased	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
bid	O
him	O
forbear	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
not	O
doing	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
foot	O
upon	O
the	O
Hole	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pitched	O
some	O
Oyster-shells	O
on	O
his	O
Foot	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Deceased	O
threw	O
the	O
Oyster	O
Measure	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
who	O
immediately	O
threw	O
it	O
back	O
at	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
who	O
taking	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
clapp	O
'd	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
who	O
enraged	O
thereat	O
,	O
ran	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
and	O
kicked	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
retiring	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
the	O
Knife	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
stuck	O
in	O
his	O
Thigh	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Wound	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
The	O
Surgeon	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
immediately	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
bled	O
such	O
a	O
vast	O
quantity	O
of	O
Blood	O
in	O
so	O
little	O
time	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
feared	O
the	O
Wound	O
might	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
Crucal	O
Artery	O
,	O
which	O
among	O
Surgeons	O
is	O
generally	O
looked	O
upon	O
to	O
be	O
mortal	O
;	O
but	O
however	O
he	O
bound	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
stopp	O
'd	O
the	O
Effusion	O
,	O
and	O
acquainted	O
Dr.	O
Blundel	O
with	O
what	O
he	O
apprehened	O
;	O
and	O
opening	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
was	O
confirmed	O
in	O
his	O
Opinion	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
the	O
Deceased	O
died	O
of	O
that	O
Wound	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Gay	O
(	O
the	O
Master	O
)	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
lived	O
very	O
friendly	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Quarrel	O
nor	O
Animosity	O
between	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
like	O
was	O
said	O
by	O
others	O
in	O
the	O
Family	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
afterwards	O
several	O
times	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
freely	O
forgave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
verily	O
believed	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Intent	O
at	O
all	O
to	O
kill	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
only	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Peel	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
an	O
Assault	O
committed	O
on	O
the	O
Bodies	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Pettit	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jucy	I-pers
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutors	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
Curiosity	O
to	O
the	O
Nonjuring	O
Meeting	O
in	O
Scroops-Court	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
hearing	O
them	O
pray	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
without	O
mentioning	O
any	O
Name	O
,	O
they	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
King	O
George	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
the	O
Royal	O
Family	O
,	O
without	O
mentioning	O
any	O
particular	O
Persons	O
,	O
they	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
their	O
Royal	O
Highnesses	O
,	O
Prince	O
and	O
Princess	O
of	O
Wales	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
upon	O
this	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
clapp	O
'd	O
his	O
Hand	O
upon	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
thrust	O
down	O
stairs	O
;	O
but	O
going	O
up	O
again	O
with	O
more	O
Company	O
,	O
apprehended	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
indeed	O
at	O
the	O
Nonjuring	O
Meeting	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
out	O
of	O
Curiosity	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
hurly	O
burly	O
among	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
rose	O
up	O
hastily	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
his	O
Sword	O
some	O
way	O
intangled	O
by	O
a	O
Seat	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
clap	O
his	O
Hand	O
upon	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
draw	O
it	O
against	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
.	O
He	O
brought	O
several	O
Persons	O
to	O
testifie	O
he	O
was	O
no	O
way	O
disaffected	O
to	O
his	O
Majesty	O
King	O
George	O
and	O
Government	O
,	O
but	O
on	O
the	O
contrary	O
a	O
hearty	O
Well-wisher	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
often	O
drank	O
King	O
George	O
's	O
Health	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
loyal	O
Healths	O
in	O
their	O
Company	O
,	O
with	O
all	O
the	O
Heartiness	O
imaginable	O
.	O
And	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Evidences	O
said	O
,	O
had	O
he	O
not	O
been	O
well	O
assured	O
of	O
his	O
good	O
Affection	O
towards	O
his	O
present	O
Majesty	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
Brother	O
,	O
he	O
wou	O
'd	O
not	O
have	O
said	O
one	O
Word	O
in	O
his	O
behalf	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
is	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Mistake	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecuter	O
,	O
they	O
not	O
knowing	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
his	O
clapping	O
his	O
Hand	O
upon	O
his	O
Sword	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Martin	B-pers
Purcel	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
a	O
Silver	O
Canister	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
William	B-pers
Carlisle	I-pers
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
out	O
a	O
thieving	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lifted	O
up	O
the	O
Sash	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
out	O
the	O
Canister	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
him	O
afterwards	O
a	O
Guinea	O
for	O
his	O
Share	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
Evidence	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Thief	O
from	O
his	O
Cradle	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Benjamin	B-pers
How	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
and	O
Susanna	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
of	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Major	O
John	B-pers
Sinclare	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
a	O
silver	O
Monteth	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
a	O
silver	O
Tea-kettle	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
l.	O
a	O
silver	O
Salver	O
,	O
val.50	O
s	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
50	O
l.	O
with	O
Writings	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
a	O
few	O
Doors	O
off	O
,	O
about	O
7	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
to	O
fetch	O
some	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
locked	O
the	O
Street-Door	O
after	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
the	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Street-Door	O
,	O
the	O
Parlour-Door	O
,	O
and	O
Closet-door	O
all	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
gone	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
some	O
small	O
time	O
after	O
a	O
Person	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
Major	O
's	O
Door	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
opening	O
the	O
Door	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Writings	O
lying	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
soon	O
after	O
there	O
came	O
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
the	O
Major	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
hurt	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
inform	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
should	O
find	O
the	O
Persons	O
that	O
robbed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
Major	O
's	O
Promise	O
,	O
gave	O
Directions	O
for	O
apprehending	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
were	O
apprehended,2	O
spoons	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
Susan	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
that	O
suited	O
with	O
10	O
that	O
were	O
left	O
of	O
a	O
Dozen	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Major	O
's	O
Servant	O
was	O
very	O
positive	O
were	O
her	O
Matter	O
's	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
being	O
not	O
mark	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pretenting	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
left	O
her	O
by	O
an	O
Aunt	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Soldier	O
who	O
inform	O
'd	O
against	O
them	O
absconding	O
;	O
the	O
Proof	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
Roger	B-pers
Wisdale	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Ware-house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
thence	O
4	O
dozen	O
of	O
Hats	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
on	O
Feb.12.1713	O
.	O
Abel	B-pers
Downs	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
himself	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Christofer	O
Margon	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
walk	O
'd	O
in	O
Covent-Garden	B-place
Church-porch	O
,	O
and	O
dodg	O
'd	O
the	O
Watch	O
till	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
their	O
Stands	O
,	O
then	O
went	O
and	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Shutters	O
,	O
and	O
himself	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
handed	O
the	O
Hats	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
who	O
carried	O
them	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
one	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Salmon	I-pers
alias	O
Iverson	O
for	O
24	O
s.	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
6	O
s.	O
for	O
his	O
share	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
depending	O
only	O
on	O
Downs	O
's	O
Evidence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Ware-house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
3	O
dozen	O
of	O
Hats	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
sufficient	O
Proof	O
being	O
given	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Reed	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Reeves	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
5	O
Hats	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
Edmund	B-pers
Juby	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Day-time	O
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
Octob	O
,	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
with	O
the	O
Hats	O
,	O
by	O
one	O
passing	O
by	O
;	O
who	O
,	O
suspecting	O
him	O
,	O
stopp	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Owner	O
's	O
house	O
with	O
the	O
Hats	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Hats	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Shoplifting	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henrietta	B-pers
Brady	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
Girl	O
)	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
from	O
Joseph	B-pers
Stiles	I-pers
:	O
the	O
owned	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
3	O
s.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Banister	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Burnet	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
James	O
Burnet	O
of	O
Fulham	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Manly	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
60	O
Shifts	O
and	O
Shirt,6	O
Callico	O
Gowns	O
and	O
Petticoats	O
and	O
other	O
Linnen	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Washer-woman	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
the	O
found	O
her	O
House	O
broken	O
open	O
about	O
5	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
missing	O
;	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
search	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	O
,	O
saw	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
hang	O
up	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
by	O
the	O
Buyer	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Shifts	O
upon	O
her	O
back	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Things	O
were	O
given	O
her	O
by	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
some	O
Evidences	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
not	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
be	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
very	O
ill	O
Husband	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
now	O
gone	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
probable	O
,	O
therefore	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Addison	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
set	O
with	O
an	O
Emerald	O
and	O
2	O
Diamonds	O
,	O
value	O
39	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Pugh	I-pers
the	O
28th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Proof	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Ring	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
that	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
extorted	O
the	O
Confession	O
from	O
her	O
by	O
Threats	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
but	O
young	O
,	O
and	O
newly	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
.	O
Several	O
Persons	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
;	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Elton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linnen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
Holland	O
Apron	O
,	O
val	O
1	O
s.6	O
d	O
and	O
two	O
Pictures	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Judge	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
stolen	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
Pictures	O
,	O
but	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Looking-glass	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Dressing-box	O
,	O
val.5	O
s.	O
a	O
Carpet	O
,	O
val.5	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Dale	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
Nov	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
some	O
small	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
them	O
gradually	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
Chandler's-shop	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
sent	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
Relation	O
's	O
where	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
.	O
And	O
thought	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
other	O
Evidences	O
swore	O
that	O
some	O
Pictures	O
and	O
a	O
Looking-glass	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
were	O
the	O
Furniture	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Room	O
for	O
some	O
years	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
insisted	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
had	O
had	O
them	O
for	O
4	O
Years	O
last	O
past	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
again	O
indicted	O
for	O
marrying	O
a	O
Second	O
Husband	O
,	O
her	O
First	O
Husband	O
being	O
alive	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
the	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samuel	B-pers
Bendrick	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.4	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
val.2	O
s.6	O
d.	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3rd	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
washing	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Coach	O
,	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
go	O
from	O
the	O
Door	O
with	O
some	O
Things	O
,	O
ran	O
up	O
into	O
his	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
missing	O
them	O
,	O
follow	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Porter	O
and	O
a	O
Man	O
gave	O
him	O
Six-pence	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Wiseman	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Wooton	I-pers
of	O
London	O
,	O
Spinster	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
or	O
Robert	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
him	O
1	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
in	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
and	O
drink	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
refusing	O
,	O
she	O
thrust	O
her	O
Hand	O
into	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
push	O
'd	O
her	O
away	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
immediately	O
felt	O
after	O
his	O
Pocket	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
turn	O
'd	O
in	O
side	O
out	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
presently	O
apprehended	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
being	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
of	O
London	O
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
with	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Tod	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
were	O
,	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
1	O
Silver	O
Tea-spoon	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bartholomew	I-place
the	I-place
Great	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bed-Quilt	O
,	O
val.20	O
s.	O
1	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Squire	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Willy	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
le	I-place
Grand	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Brass	O
Kettles	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.12	O
Ells	O
of	O
Linnen	O
Cloth	O
,	O
val.36	O
s.	O
and	O
30	O
Books	O
,	O
val.15	O
.	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Royroft	I-pers
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
the	O
fact	O
in	O
part	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
2	O
Muslin	O
Aprons	O
,	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
Gloves	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
d	O
in	O
Copper	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
Mary	B-pers
Rutherford	I-pers
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depon	O
'd	O
that	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
a	O
Companion	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
and	O
push	O
'd	O
her	O
down	O
;	O
and	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
upon	O
her	O
knees	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
her	O
Pocket	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Indiciment	O
being	O
laid	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
,	O
when	O
it	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
for	O
an	O
Assault	O
and	O
Robbery	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Indictment	O
brought	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Edge	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Old-Fish-Street	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
full	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
,	I-place
John	I-place
's	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Shop-books	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.6d	O
.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Compting-house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
as	O
Principal	O
;	O
and	O
Dinah	B-pers
Pearse	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Bently	I-pers
;	O
Dinah	B-pers
Pearse	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
;	O
and	O
Hannah	B-pers
Pearse	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
as	O
Accessaries	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
;	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Salver	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
val.10	O
l.	O
2	O
Silver	O
Mugs	O
,	O
val.5	O
l.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Coffee-pot	O
,	O
val.9	O
l.12	O
Silver	O
Plates	O
,	O
value	O
28	O
l.14	O
Forks	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
Value	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Molt	I-pers
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
3	O
other	O
Prisoners	O
above-mention	O
'd	O
did	O
receive	O
these	O
Goods	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
lived	O
with	O
him	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
getting	O
the	O
Keys	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
before	O
the	O
Family	O
was	O
a	O
,	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
washing	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
went	O
of	O
with	O
the	O
Plate	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
:	O
but	O
there	O
wanting	O
Proof	O
sufficient	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
three	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Caleb	B-pers
Lockwood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Maybank	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
December	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
desiring	O
him	O
to	O
help	O
him	O
to	O
King	O
Charles	O
's	O
Farthings	O
and	O
Halfpences	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
Abroad	O
where	O
they	O
would	O
go	O
for	O
double	O
the	O
Value	O
;	O
and	O
therefore	O
giving	O
him	O
Five	O
Farthings	O
for	O
a	O
Penny	O
,	O
afterwards	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
K.	O
Charles	O
's	O
Shillings	O
;	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
picking	O
them	O
out	O
,	O
catch	O
'd	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
:	O
but	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Barns	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Porridge-Pot	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tailor	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
Pot	O
was	O
stolen	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
back	O
Kitchen	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Pot	O
in	O
a	O
Basket	O
of	O
Rags	O
(	O
she	O
going	O
about	O
a	O
Ragging	O
)	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
Woman	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Penny	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
only	O
a	O
Pretence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Monday	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Chafingdish	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Jekil	I-pers
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
pretended	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
for	O
14	O
d.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
an	O
Iron	O
Jack	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mr	B-pers
Woodfield	I-pers
,	O
from	O
the	O
Stall	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Sweatman	I-pers
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
draw	O
it	O
gradually	O
off	O
from	O
the	O
Stall	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
Bag	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
off	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
apprehended	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
70	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Walter	B-pers
Kennedy	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
an	O
Assault	O
and	O
Robbery	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.6	O
d	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
not	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolphs	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
stealing	O
three	O
Stuff-Gowns	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.2	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
val.3	O
l.	O
a	O
Coral	O
,	O
val.5	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
8	O
Pounds	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Matth.ew	B-pers
Ransford	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
her	O
Master	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Marshalsea	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Mistress	O
in	O
New	O
Prison	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
her	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
hastening	O
her	O
to	O
some	O
Necessaries	O
to	O
her	O
Mistress	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
her	O
return	O
she	O
found	O
her	O
room	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Good	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gone	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
she	O
had	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
hers	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
bought	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
her	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
kept	O
an	O
ill	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
seduced	O
her	O
to	O
ply	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
that	O
she	O
has	O
sold	O
her	O
to	O
appear	O
in	O
her	O
Cullies	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
to	O
plain	O
the	O
Woman	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
Character	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
sufficient	O
to	O
justify	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
therefore	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Raven	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
one	O
Brass	O
Porridge	O
Pot	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Poils	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Pot	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
a	O
Woman	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
2	O
Pence	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
in	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Whitlock	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
4	O
Stuff	O
Curtains	O
and	O
Vallence	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Fleet	I-pers
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
the	O
Maid	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
draw	O
it	O
,	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Barter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Spade	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Tailor	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
at	O
a	O
Pawnbroker	O
's	O
pawn	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Name	O
;	O
he	O
having	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Spectacles	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
1	O
Shilling	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
she	O
picked	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
herself	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Whiting	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	B-pers
Robert	I-pers
Malory	I-pers
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
7	O
pair	O
of	O
Yarn	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
at	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Walsers	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
near	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
breaks	O
the	O
Sash	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
stockings	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
getting	O
Assistance	O
,	O
apprehended	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
stockings	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
.	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
but	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Strickland	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Slater	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Gruby	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
7	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
servant	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
fetch	O
some	O
Necessaries	O
,	O
locking	O
the	O
Door	O
after	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
coming	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Parlour	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
enquire	O
for	O
an	O
Acquaintance	O
.	O
He	O
having	O
stollen	O
nothing	O
,	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Horn	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Wiseman	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Homeby	I-pers
(	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
45s	O
.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Turbot	I-pers
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
November	O
left	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Horn	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
to	O
offer	O
a	O
shilling	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Two	O
penny	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
the	O
Tankard	O
.	O
Horn	O
pleaded	O
be	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
Wiseman	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
consent	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
Homeby	O
carried	O
away	O
the	O
Tankard	O
:	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
Homeby	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
Horn	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
Wiseman	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Knap	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Pewter	O
plates	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Coster	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
:	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
some	O
Women	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
pretence	O
of	O
helping	O
a	O
Woman	O
to	O
a	O
Nurse	O
child	O
;	O
and	O
calling	O
for	O
Cloth	O
and	O
Plates	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
eat	O
something	O
,	O
takes	O
the	O
Plates	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Cooks	O
to	O
fetch	O
Meat	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
positive	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
therefore	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Manly	I-pers
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
to	O
plainly	O
proved	O
on	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Cotterel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
felony	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Day-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
20	O
Velvet	O
Caps	O
,	O
val.5	O
l	O
40	O
silk	O
Caps	O
,	O
val.40	O
s.	O
9	O
Feather	O
Muffs	O
,	O
val.30	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
11	O
l.	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
she	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
did	O
observe	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lurking	O
about	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
She	O
had	O
Information	O
given	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
with	O
a	O
Search-Warrant	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Caps	O
in	O
her	O
Room	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
wife	O
and	O
Servant	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
she	O
lent	O
10	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
Caps	O
to	O
one	O
Ralph	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
that	O
was	O
since	O
hanged	O
;	O
but	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
stealing	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
brought	O
a	O
Person	O
to	O
confirm	O
what	O
she	O
said	O
;	O
thereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
as	O
an	O
Accessary	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Hutchins	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Carlisle	I-pers
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
Edward	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
and	O
sealing	O
thence	O
30	O
Perriwings	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
l.	O
29	O
Rasors	O
,	O
val	O
20s	O
.	O
a	O
Looking-glass	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
William	O
Carlisle	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
one	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
deos	O
'd	O
that	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
committed	O
the	O
Robbery	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
about	O
4	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
telling	O
her	O
what	O
they	O
bad	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
bought	O
of	O
them	O
18	O
Perriwings	O
and	O
9	O
Rasors	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
as	O
Accessary	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Steel	I-pers
of	O
London	O
,	O
Labourer	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Portmanteau	O
,	O
with	O
Linnen	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
from	O
off	O
a	O
Horse	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lemire	I-pers
,	O
the	O
12th	O
October	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Proof	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
be	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hutchins	I-pers
of	O
London	O
,	O
Labourer	O
,	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
30	O
Perriwigs	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
l.	O
29	O
Razors	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Carlisle	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
others	O
committed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Thread-Satin	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Wren	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
plain	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Carol	I-pers
of	O
London	O
,	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Calico	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
2	O
Aprons	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Day-time	O
.	O
The	O
fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Pool	I-pers
of	O
London	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cask	O
val.2	O
s.	O
and	O
12	O
Gallons	O
of	O
pickled	O
Cucumbers	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
,	O
the	O
19	O
h	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Carol	I-pers
of	O
London	O
,	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Tobacco-Box	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d	O
,	O
the	O
19	O
h	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
having	O
taken	O
George	B-pers
Pool	I-pers
abovemention	O
'd	O
,	O
with	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Confederate	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
escaped	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
the	O
Assurance	O
to	O
come	O
into	O
his	O
Shop	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
parlying	O
with	O
George	B-pers
Pool	I-pers
,	O
and	O
pick	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
positive	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ralph	B-pers
Harwood	I-pers
of	O
London	O
,	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Day	I-pers
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
indeed	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
plainly	O
appearing	O
how	O
he	O
got	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
nothing	O
being	O
stollen	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Northage	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
60	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Coals	O
,	O
val.2	O
l.10	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Coxson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
Two	O
Evidences	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
porters	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
hired	O
them	O
to	O
carry	O
Coals	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
Peoples	O
Houses	O
,	O
he	O
saying	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
own	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
filling	O
them	O
by	O
Guess	O
without	O
Measuring	O
them	O
,	O
gave	O
them	O
cause	O
to	O
Inspect	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
they	O
made	O
Enquiry	O
who	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
notice	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Butolph	I-place
's	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Dimity	O
Pocket	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Thimble	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
from	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Spooler	I-pers
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
fact	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
clearly	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Esther	B-pers
Partridge	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
Gold	O
Rings,2	O
Silver	O
Salts	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
from	O
Mary	B-pers
Boxford	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
sufficiently	O
proved	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Sewet	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Stew-Pans	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Propriety	O
of	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Keilin	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Wilder	I-pers
,	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
the	O
Denial	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
So	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Holms	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Woollen	O
Shroud	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
(	O
N.B	O
.	O
No	O
Notice	O
taken	O
of	O
the	O
Corps	O
)	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
altering	O
Pursers	O
Accounts	O
:	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
other	O
stealing	O
a	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
and	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
69	O
l.	O
to	O
which	O
indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Isaac	B-pers
Dalton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
printing	O
and	O
publishing	O
a	O
scandalous	O
Libel	O
,	O
entit'led	O
,	O
The	O
Shift	O
Shifted	O
.	O
The	O
fact	O
being	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Peter	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
printing	O
a	O
scandalous	O
Libel	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Shift	O
Shifted	O
:	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
only	O
employ	O
'd	O
as	O
a	O
Press-Man	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Daborn	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
printing	O
the	O
Shift	O
Shifted	O
:	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
imposed	O
upon	O
,	O
being	O
told	O
by	O
the	O
Persons	O
that	O
brought	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Dying	O
Speeches	O
of	O
Paul	O
and	O
Hall	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
printing	O
and	O
publishing	O
The	O
Shift	O
Shifted	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
fact	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Flint	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
printing	O
and	O
publishing	O
The	O
Shift	O
Shifted	O
.	O
The	O
fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Laugham	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
publishing	O
a	O
scandalous	O
Libel	O
,	O
intitled	O
A	O
Poem	O
upon	O
the	O
Sight	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Picture	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Dormer	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
publishing	O
The	O
Shift	O
Shifted	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Child	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
forging	O
a	O
Counterfeit	O
Note	O
for	O
8	O
l.	O
under	O
the	O
Hand	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hails	I-pers
;	O
But	O
the	O
Fact	O
wanting	O
Proof	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
forging	O
a	O
Receipt	O
for	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
receiving	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Exchequer	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Account	O
of	O
an	O
Annuity	O
to	O
Sarah	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Fultis	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Langsdale	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Heathcot	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
.	O
for	O
forging	O
and	O
publishing	O
a	O
false	O
Bill	O
of	O
Sale	O
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
Wages	O
of	O
Archibald	B-pers
Hammon	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
the	O
ship	O
Anglesea	O
Which	O
being	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Lilly	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
in	O
forging	O
and	O
publishing	O
false	O
powers	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
receive	O
the	O
Wages	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Ship	O
Weymouth	O
;	O
of	O
which	O
indictment	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Ambrose	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
in	O
publishing	O
a	O
false	O
will	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
receive	O
the	O
Wages	O
of	O
Humphry	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Ship	O
York	O
;	O
of	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
in	O
publishing	O
a	O
false	O
letter	O
of	O
Attorney	O
for	O
the	O
receiving	O
the	O
Wages	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Treby	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Ship	O
Success	O
;	O
of	O
which	O
indictment	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Christian	B-pers
Vickars	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
publishing	O
a	O
false	O
power	O
to	O
receive	O
the	O
Wages	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Lambeth	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Ship	O
Anglesea	O
;	O
of	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	I-pers
commonly	I-pers
call	I-pers
'd	I-pers
Half	I-pers
Hang	I-pers
'd	I-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Opinions	O
of	O
the	O
Judges	O
upon	O
the	O
special	O
Verdict	O
on	O
the	O
Indictment	O
brought	O
against	O
him	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Longate	I-pers
,	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
brought	O
against	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Fact	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
dead	O
.	O
(	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
said	O
)	O
no	O
body	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
had	O
the	O
unmerited	O
good	O
Fortune	O
to	O
be	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bigs	I-pers
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
informed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Judges	O
had	O
considered	O
his	O
Case	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
of	O
Opinion	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
erasing	O
or	O
taking	O
the	O
Indorsment	O
of	O
90	O
l.	O
off	O
from	O
a	O
Bank-Note	O
,	O
was	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
within	O
the	O
meaning	O
of	O
the	O
Act	O
of	O
Parliament	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
therefore	O
he	O
must	O
receive	O
sentence	O
accordingly	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Francia	I-pers
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Attorney-General	O
producing	O
in	O
Court	O
two	O
Affidavits	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Horatio	B-pers
Walpole	I-pers
,	O
a	O
material	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
was	O
detain	O
'd	O
in	O
Holland	O
by	O
Indisposition	O
,	O
his	O
Tryal	O
was	O
deferr'dd	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
follows	O
.	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death,20	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
,	O
S	O
-	O
J	O
-	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Big	I-pers
,	O
Deborah	O
Aldridge	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Knowles	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hartley	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Gabe	O
,	O
alias	O
Hawkins	O
;	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Chompson	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Nodes	O
;	O
James	B-pers
Handson	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Busler	O
;	O
Arhur	O
Rogers	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Reed	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
R	O
;	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hard	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Davis	O
,	O
David	B-pers
Blair	I-pers
,	O
Amm	O
Thomson	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Moomy	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Dane	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Slater	O
,	O
alias	O
Sturt	O
;	O
Mary	B-pers
Abbot	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ousin	I-pers
,	O
were	O
called	O
down	O
to	O
their	O
former	O
Sentence	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand,13	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Wiseman	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Northage	I-pers
,	O
B	O
-	O
H	O
-	O
,	O
alias	O
M	O
-	O
;	O
Angustin	B-pers
Blinkborn	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hatchins	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
catterel	O
;	O
Sarah	B-pers
Johnston	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
,	O
David	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
Caleb	B-pers
Lockwood	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Munday	I-pers
,	O
Bridget	B-pers
Birk	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Holms	I-pers
bailed	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt,25	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Johnsan	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Wily	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Knap	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Jame	B-pers
Wifeman	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dyon	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Steel	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Carol	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Pool	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Barns	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Whiting	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Raven	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Corol	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Whitlook	I-pers
Elizabeth	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Lewis	B-pers
Goldsburongh	I-pers
,	O
Tho.Goldsborough	B-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Stanton	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Sewet	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Elton	I-pers
.	O
W	O
-	O
G	O
-	O
fin	O
'd	O
50	O
l.	O
and	O
1	O
year	O
's	O
imprisonment	O
.	O
Iassc	O
Dalton	O
,	O
fin	O
'd	O
20	O
Marks	O
,	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
,	O
and	O
1	O
year	O
's	O
imprisonment	O
after	O
the	O
expiration	O
of	O
his	O
consinement	O
upon	O
the	O
last	O
Sentence	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Yares	I-pers
,	O
fin	O
'd	O
20	O
Marks	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Drmer	I-pers
,	O
fin	O
'd	O
5	O
Marks	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Flint	I-pers
,	O
fin	O
'd	O
20	O
Marks	O
and	O
6	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
Dirst	O
by	O
Longhoan	O
,	O
fin	O
'd	O
5	O
Marks	O
and	O
6	O
Months	O
imprisonment	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
fin	O
'd	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
3	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Fnicis	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Longdale	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Heathess	I-pers
Ann	B-pers
Lilly	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Ambrose	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Christian	B-pers
Vikars	I-pers
,	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
Monts	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
The	O
Women	O
pleaded	O
their	O
Bellies	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
being	O
impannell	O
'd	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Knowls	I-pers
Elizabeth	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Onwin	I-pers
,	O
were	O
found	O
with	O
quick	O
Child	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Sessions	O
to	O
begin	O
on	O
Friday	O
Jan,11.171617	O
.	O
God	O
Save	O
King	O
GEORGE	O
.	O
Sir	O
JAMES	O
BATEMAN	O
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
and	O
Bart	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
.	O
AN	O
Indictment	O
was	O
preferred	O
.	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
June	O
1715	O
,	O
against	O
John	B-pers
Bigg	I-pers
;	O
which	O
set	O
forth	O
That	O
one	O
Joshua	O
Odams	O
,	O
being	O
intrusted	O
by	O
the	O
Governor	O
and	O
Company	O
of	O
the	O
Bank	O
of	O
England	O
to	O
sign	O
Notes	O
on	O
their	O
Behalf	O
for	O
Payment	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
did	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
February	O
1714	O
,	O
make	O
a	O
Bank-Note	O
,	O
whereby	O
he	O
promised	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Governor	O
and	O
Company	O
,	O
to	O
pay	O
to	O
Mr.	O
James	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
or	O
Bearer	O
,	O
upon	O
Demand,100	O
l.	O
The	O
Indictment	O
further	O
set	O
forth	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Month	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
90	O
l.	O
was	O
paid	O
by	O
the	O
Bank	O
in	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Note	O
;	O
and	O
thereupon	O
an	O
Indorsement	O
was	O
made	O
thereon	O
,	O
purporting	O
,	O
that	O
Ninety	O
Pounds	O
were	O
paid	O
22d	O
Feb.1714	O
.	O
The	O
Indictment	O
further	O
set	O
forth	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Bigg	I-pers
feloniously	O
ERASED	O
the	O
said	O
Indorsement	O
,	O
contrary	O
to	O
the	O
Form	O
of	O
the	O
Stature	O
made	O
in	O
this	O
behalf	O
Another	O
Indictment	O
was	O
preferr	O
'd	O
against	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
Bigg	O
.	O
and	O
the	O
same	O
was	O
for	O
ALTERING	O
the	O
Indorsement	O
on	O
the	O
Bank-Bill	O
abovemention	O
'd	O
.	O
To	O
these	O
Indictments	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
:	O
And	O
after	O
a	O
long	O
and	O
full	O
Evidence	O
on	O
the	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
specially	O
these	O
Facts	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
That	O
Joshua	B-pers
Odams	I-pers
made	O
such	O
Bank-Note	O
for	O
Payment	O
of	O
such	O
Sum	O
of	O
100	O
l.	O
as	O
abovemention	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
February	O
1714	O
.	O
90	O
l.	O
was	O
paid	O
in	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Note	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
upon	O
such	O
Payment	O
,	O
cross	O
the	O
writing	O
thereof	O
,	O
were	O
written	O
these	O
words	O
and	O
Figures	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
22	O
Feb.1714	O
.	O
Paid	O
Ninety	O
Pounds	O
.	O
Which	O
Words	O
and	O
Figures	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
totally	O
Expunge	O
and	O
take	O
out	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Whole	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
doubted	O
whether	O
in	O
Point	O
of	O
Law	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
by	O
expunging	O
the	O
Words	O
and	O
Figures	O
written	O
upon	O
the	O
Face	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Note	O
,	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
or	O
,	O
in	O
other	O
Words	O
,	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
Altering	O
or	O
Erasing	O
an	O
Indorsement	O
of	O
a	O
Bank-Note	O
,	O
within	O
the	O
Meaning	O
of	O
the	O
Statute	O
.	O
The	O
Judges	O
,	O
upon	O
this	O
Occasion	O
,	O
being	O
assembled	O
at	O
Serjeants-Inn-Hall	O
in	O
Fleetstreet	O
,	O
were	O
attended	O
by	O
Council	O
on	O
both	O
Sides	O
;	O
where	O
the	O
Point	O
of	O
Law	O
was	O
solemnly	O
argued	O
:	O
And	O
after	O
consideration	O
thereof	O
,	O
the	O
judges	O
were	O
of	O
Opinion	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
within	O
the	O
Meaning	O
of	O
the	O
statute	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
this	O
sessions	O
Judgement	O
of	O
Death	O
was	O
pronounced	O
against	O
him	O
accordingly	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENT	O
'S	O
DAVID	B-pers
POVEY	I-pers
,	O
removed	O
from	O
Hatton	O
Garden	O
near	O
Exctar-Exchange	O
in	O
the	O
strand	O
,	O
London	O
,	O
Operator	O
for	O
the	O
Teeth	O
;	O
who	O
had	O
the	O
Honour	O
to	O
clean	O
her	O
late	O
Majety	O
's	O
Teeth	O
.	O
He	O
sells	O
that	O
pleasant	O
Dentrifice	O
King	O
Charles	B-pers
II	I-pers
.	O
corconstantly	O
used	O
:	O
It	O
makes	O
the	O
Teeth	O
as	O
white	O
as	O
Ivory	O
,	O
preserves	O
them	O
from	O
decaying	O
,	O
destroying	O
the	O
scurry	O
.	O
He	O
hath	O
a	O
Gephalick	O
which	O
certainly	O
cures	O
the	O
Tooth-Ach	O
in	O
a	O
Minute	O
's	O
Time	O
,	O
beyond	O
any	O
person	O
in	O
England	O
.	O
If	O
the	O
Teeth	O
be	O
rotten	O
,	O
or	O
uneven	O
,	O
and	O
full	O
of	O
Holes	O
or	O
black	O
Specks	O
,	O
he	O
will	O
make	O
them	O
smooth	O
,	O
even	O
,	O
sound	O
,	O
and	O
white	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
no	O
person	O
shall	O
distinguish	O
where	O
the	O
Defect	O
has	O
been	O
,	O
He	O
sets	O
in	O
Artificial	O
teeth	O
so	O
even	O
,	O
neat	O
,	O
and	O
firm	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
need	O
not	O
be	O
removed	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
may	O
eat	O
with	O
them	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
with	O
their	O
former	O
,	O
and	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
distinguish	O
'd	O
from	O
their	O
natural	O
ones	O
.	O
He	O
sells	O
a	O
pleasant	O
Water	O
,	O
that	O
presents	O
any	O
Rottenoess	O
from	O
seizing	O
the	O
Teeth	O
,	O
and	O
takes	O
all	O
Paints	O
and	O
Impo	O
,	O
Cankers	O
or	O
Swellings	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Gums	O
,	O
and	O
fastens	O
loose	O
teeth	O
,	O
which	O
