TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
22d	O
,	O
23d	O
,	O
24th	O
,	O
and	O
25th	O
,	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
17	O
15/16	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Second	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
'S	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEfore	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
CHARLES	B-pers
PEERS	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Powis	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Dormer	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Montague	O
,	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
;	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Merttins	I-pers
John	B-pers
Applebee	I-pers
John	B-pers
Staples	I-pers
Adams	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
William	B-pers
Staples	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Cope	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Hawford	I-pers
Hugh	B-pers
Wackworth	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Soamast	I-pers
John	B-pers
Spinest	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Cliffton	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Bruce	B-pers
Randall	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Lord	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
William	B-pers
Diston	I-pers
Ebonezer	B-pers
Cawdron	I-pers
John	B-pers
Marley	I-pers
Guy	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Kingsman	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Stiff	I-pers
William	B-pers
Giles	I-pers
Edward	O
Perciuall	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Ramsden	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Lawrence	I-place
Jewry	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
50	O
Pound	O
weight	O
of	O
white	O
and	O
colour	O
'd	O
Thread	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Bonner	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sparrow	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
Felony	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
coming	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lauson	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Faulstone	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
,	I-place
Sepulchres	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Bryan	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
1	O
Camblet	O
Coat	O
,	O
1	O
Stuff	O
G	O
.....	O
n	O
Sute	O
of	O
Headcloaths	O
,	O
3	O
Yards	O
of	O
Drugget	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
Instant	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
depos	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
that	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
;	O
And	O
two	O
Watchmen	O
swore	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Goods	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
Companion	O
who	O
shot	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Cheek	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
his	O
Escape	O
;	O
but	O
threw	O
down	O
his	O
Bundle	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
also	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
applied	O
himself	O
chiefly	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
to	O
clear	O
himself	O
of	O
the	O
Wigg	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
his	O
by	O
exchange	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
its	O
being	O
stole	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
Goods	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
hir	O
'd	O
to	O
carry	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepuchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
Porridge-pot	O
,	O
1	O
Riding-hood	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Sheets	O
,	O
the	O
whole	O
Value	O
20	O
s.	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Governour	B-pers
and	I-pers
one	I-pers
of	I-pers
the	I-pers
Matrons	I-pers
of	I-pers
St.	I-pers
Thomas	I-pers
's	I-pers
Hospital	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
fact	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
recover	O
'd	O
from	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
(	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
apprehended	O
)	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
;	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Laurence	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
New	I-place
Fish-street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
2	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Fustian	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bullock	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
clear	O
enough	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
stole	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
some	O
Doubt	O
concerning	O
the	O
Nature	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Speed	I-pers
(	O
a	O
Boy	O
)	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mildred	I-place
in	I-place
Breadstreet	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
80	O
Pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Bacon	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s	O
,	O
3	O
Legs	O
of	O
Mutton	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Burn	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plain	O
enough	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Age	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Harrell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Linnen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
1	O
Table-Cloth	O
,	O
and	O
1	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Reason	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
some	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hutton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
la	I-place
Bow	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
1	O
Silver	O
hilted	O
Sword	O
,	O
value	O
52	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Capt	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
Instant	O
.	O
Capt	O
.	O
Cox	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
late	O
Queen	O
's	O
Birth-day	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
being	O
out	O
with	O
his	O
Company	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
upon	O
Duty	O
at	O
Bow	B-place
Church	I-place
,	O
about	O
Six	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
alone	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
two	O
other	O
Persons	O
came	O
by	O
him	O
and	O
jostled	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
thrust	O
him	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Wall	O
;	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
held	O
down	O
his	O
Hands	O
,	O
stood	O
Face	O
to	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
drew	O
away	O
his	O
Swords	O
which	O
he	O
immediately	O
shifted	O
to	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
off	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
was	O
a	O
Witness	O
to	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
inform	O
'd	O
the	O
Captain	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
who	O
,	O
being	O
at	O
Liberty	O
,	O
and	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Surprize	O
,	O
pursu	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
him	O
under	O
a	O
Guard	O
and	O
afterwards	O
sent	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
The	O
Proof	O
was	O
very	O
satisfactory	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
Second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
for	O
an	O
Assault	O
and	O
Robbery	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
,	O
value	O
35	O
s	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
Time	O
indicted	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
for	O
assaulting	O
and	O
robbing	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Huggins	I-pers
,	I-pers
sen	I-pers
.	I-pers
,	O
sen.	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
,	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Cane	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
fourth	O
Time	O
indicted	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
and	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
for	O
assaulting	O
and	O
robbing	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Huggins	I-pers
,	I-pers
Jun	I-pers
.	I-pers
,	O
Jun	O
.	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
and	O
Case	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
Steel	O
Seal	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
's	O
Evidence	O
and	O
that	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
Huggin	O
's	O
was	O
much	O
the	O
same	O
in	O
relating	O
the	O
Circumstances	O
of	O
the	O
Facts	O
by	O
which	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
three	O
Prosecutors	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
Fleetstreet	B-place
about	O
8	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
;	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Huggins	O
,	O
jun	O
being	O
forerr	O
oft	O
about	O
Fleet-Bridge	B-place
,	O
with	O
a	O
Link	O
in	O
one	O
Hand	O
and	O
a	O
Cane	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Cane	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
foil	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Scuffle	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
gone	O
many	O
Yards	O
before	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
attack	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
more	O
of	O
his	O
Gang	O
,	O
who	O
us	O
'd	O
them	O
barbarously	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
Mr.	O
Huggins	O
the	O
younger	O
from	O
his	O
Mouth	O
to	O
his	O
Ear	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
also	O
very	O
much	O
wounded	O
,	O
twice	O
down	O
his	O
Back	O
stobb	O
'd	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Thight	O
and	O
at	O
lay	O
know	O
'd	O
high	O
down	O
.	O
The	O
others	O
also	O
receive	O
'd	O
some	O
slight	O
Cuts	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Blows	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Fray	O
they	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
abovemention	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
principal	O
Man	O
amongst	O
'em	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
was	O
very	O
genteel	O
,	O
now	O
dress	O
'd	O
like	O
a	O
Soldier	O
:	O
All	O
the	O
rest	O
escap	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
very	O
well	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
all	O
three	O
indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Frances	B-pers
Tate	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Oxbury	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
in	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
40	O
Yards	O
of	O
Dimity	O
,	O
value	O
38	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23rd	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
Oxbury	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
Tate	O
denied	O
she	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
's	O
Intention	O
,	O
and	O
nothing	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
,	O
acquitted	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
Oxbury	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
several	O
Yards	O
of	O
Muslin	O
and	O
Cambrick	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Tyler	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Wakefield	I-pers
on	O
the	O
2d	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
very	O
full	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
some	O
Confederates	O
were	O
loitering	O
about	O
a	O
Board	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
Fleetstreet	B-place
,	O
for	O
Passengers	O
to	O
get	O
over	O
.	O
That	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Martin	O
having	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
a	O
Bandbox	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
thrust	O
her	O
up	O
against	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
broke	O
a	O
Corner	O
of	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
above	O
mention	O
'd	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
immediately	O
convey	O
'd	O
to	O
his	O
Confederates	O
,	O
'who	O
were	O
not	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Davd	B-pers
Cooke	I-pers
and	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
,	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Katharine	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
4	O
Perukes	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
30oz	O
.	O
of	O
Human	O
Hair	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
1	O
Looking-Glass	O
,	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
Razors	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Burrows	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
both	O
old	O
Offenders	O
in	O
this	O
Kind	O
:	O
And	O
one	O
Marshall	O
,	O
who	O
made	O
himself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
swore	O
he	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
with	O
them	O
in	O
this	O
Pact	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
a	O
particular	O
account	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
whom	O
they	O
sold	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
recover	O
'd	O
.	O
They	O
made	O
no	O
Defence	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Frances	B-pers
Wetheridge	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
persuading	O
,	O
encouraging	O
,	O
and	O
employing	O
one	O
Ann	B-pers
Grant	I-pers
to	O
personate	O
the	O
Widow	B-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Murray	I-pers
,	O
and	O
to	O
receive	O
10	O
1	O
.	O
9	O
s.	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
Queen	O
's	O
Bounty-Money	O
for	O
Widows	O
,	O
whose	O
Husbands	O
were	O
slain	O
in	O
the	O
Service	O
of	O
the	O
Crown	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
forging	O
a	O
Warrant	O
to	O
that	O
Purpose	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
publishing	O
a	O
false	O
power	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Bradbury	I-pers
by	O
which	O
she	O
received	O
21	O
l.	O
which	O
was	O
due	O
by	O
a	O
legal	O
Certificate	O
to	O
the	O
Assigns	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Henry	B-pers
Bradbury	I-pers
,	O
lately	O
blown	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Edgar	O
Man	O
of	O
War	O
.	O
Which	O
Fact	O
being	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
a	O
second	O
,	O
Wife	O
,	O
his	O
first	O
being	O
then	O
alive	O
.	O
The	O
Proof	O
being	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Christopher	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Simplon	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Boy	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Westler	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
Jan	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Doubt	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Guilty	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
having	O
by	O
some	O
Means	O
spirited	O
away	O
a	O
Boy	O
who	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
Wigg	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Band-box	O
as	O
Simpson	O
was	O
going	O
over	O
a	O
Board	O
,	O
and	O
who	O
was	O
the	O
Principal	O
Evidence	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
were	O
oblig	O
'd	O
to	O
acquit	O
him	O
.	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Ayliffe	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Fast	O
was	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Hopman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
in	I-place
Black-fryars	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
1	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
Movement	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
1	O
Guinea	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
and	O
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Hopman	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Blackfryars	B-place
to	O
drink	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
staid	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
time	O
Hopman	O
strugling	O
to	O
kiss	O
him	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
Movement	O
,	O
and	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pockets	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
A.	O
J.	O
sold	O
the	O
Watch	O
to	O
one	O
Turbitt	B-pers
.	O
But	O
Turbitt	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
in	O
Drink	O
when	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
Ludgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Casbery	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
18	O
Perriwigs	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Casbery	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
Casbery	O
swore	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
afore-said	O
Goods	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
search	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
there	O
;	O
but	O
going	O
to	O
one	O
Smith	O
's	O
,	O
found	O
some	O
of	O
Wiggs	O
,	O
and	O
Smith	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
from	O
Walker	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
Smith	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
she	O
saw	O
her	O
Master	O
pay	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
dawn	O
'd	O
some	O
Goods	O
to	O
make	O
up	O
the	O
Money	O
(	O
3l	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
)	O
.	O
This	O
Girl	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
to	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
Wiggs	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
shew	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
Evidence	O
who	O
swore	O
he	O
found	O
these	O
two	O
Wiggs	O
at	O
Smith	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
vouch	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
Face	O
;	O
which	O
the	O
other	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
denied	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
once	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
admittted	O
to	O
Bail	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
withdrawn	O
his	O
Recognizances	O
;	O
but	O
was	O
now	O
reprehended	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
Crime	O
he	O
was	O
no	O
ways	O
Guilty	O
of	O
.	O
He	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
considerable	O
Persons	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
an	O
extraordinary	O
Character	O
;	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Smith	O
himself	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
the	O
Deficiency	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
in	O
proving	O
the	O
Burglary	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Beam	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Boyce	I-pers
and	O
David	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Olave	I-place
Jewry	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
1	O
Perriwig	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
Instant	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
Old	O
Jewry	O
with	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
having	O
a	O
Link	O
in	O
one	O
Hand	O
,	O
Stephens	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
snatch	O
'd	O
his	O
Link	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
Boyce	O
took	O
away	O
his	O
Wigg	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
got	O
away	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
pursu	O
'd	O
were	O
both	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
some	O
Persons	O
who	O
gave	O
'em	O
fair	O
Characters	O
;	O
but	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
believ	O
'd	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
only	O
a	O
quarrelsom	O
Humour	O
;	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
,	O
brought	O
them	O
both	O
in	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Katharine	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Poplin	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
value	O
20s	O
.	O
18	O
Linnen	O
Aprons	O
,	O
18	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
Hugh	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
Jan	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
This	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
trifling	O
and	O
insidious	O
Prosecution	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Katharine	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Hill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
2	O
Checque	O
Linnen	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Gore	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
Jan	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
fact	O
was	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Value	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
single	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cannington	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
1	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
1	O
Perriwig	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
1	O
Shirt	O
2	O
s.	O
with	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
falling	O
in	O
fixing	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dunbar	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
Cloth	O
Cloak	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Beversham	B-pers
Rivers	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
Instant	O
.	O
Two	O
Witnesses	O
swore	O
they	O
caught	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Cloak	O
upon	O
his	O
Shoulders	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
:	O
However	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
plain	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
not	O
carried	O
it	O
off	O
the	O
Premisses	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
,	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
.....	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Obadiah	B-pers
Lemon	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Oby	I-pers
Lemons	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
30	O
Yards	O
of	O
Drugget	O
,	O
Value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
Instant	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Pritchard	O
's	O
boy	O
was	O
order	O
'd	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Goods	O
to	O
a	O
customer	O
to	O
due	O
which	O
tir	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
he	O
rested	O
the	O
Bundle	O
upon	O
a	O
Staff	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
pretending	O
to	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
next	O
House	O
)	O
look	O
'd	O
through	O
the	O
Keyhole	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Boy	O
if	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Maid	O
bring	O
in	O
two	O
bottles	O
of	O
Wine	O
's	O
and	O
the	O
Boy	O
replying	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms	O
Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
her	O
make	O
hastle	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
Penny	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Boy	O
refus	O
'd	O
it	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
not	O
knowing	O
where	O
to	O
leave	O
his	O
Goods	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
leave	O
his	O
Goods	O
any	O
where	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
Care	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
gave	O
hid	O
ny	O
and	O
a	O
Brass	O
Ring	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Boy	O
believing	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
one	O
,	O
accepted	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
of	O
the	O
Birrand	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
no	O
and	O
on	O
his	O
Return	O
no	O
Goods	O
:	O
But	O
an	O
Evidence	O
who	O
observ	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
stopt	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Bundle	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
before	O
he	O
had	O
gone	O
far	O
,	O
who	O
appear	O
'd	O
in	O
great	O
Surprize	O
and	O
Confusion	O
.	O
He	O
made	O
a	O
very	O
weak	O
Defence	O
;	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
28	O
Yards	O
of	O
Shalloon	O
,	O
Value	O
11	O
s.	O
2	O
Yards	O
of	O
Broad	O
Cloath	O
,	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Towsegg	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
An	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
His	O
Master	O
was	O
a	O
Dyer	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sent	O
by	O
him	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Towsegg	O
's	O
for	O
the	O
Goods	O
aforesaid	O
to	O
dye	O
;	O
but	O
pitching	O
his	O
Burthen	O
to	O
his	O
Way	O
home	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sitting	O
at	O
a	O
Door	O
,	O
who	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Ticket-Porter	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
Great	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Castle	O
Tavern	O
and	O
enquire	O
for	O
one	O
Captain	O
Williams	B-pers
,	O
and	O
tell	O
him	O
,	O
Mr	O
.	O
Lemon	O
defir	O
'd	O
his	O
Company	O
at	O
Supper	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
Care	O
of	O
his	O
Burthen	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
doing	O
accordingly	O
,	O
found	O
upon	O
his	O
Return	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
both	O
his	O
Goods	O
and	O
his	O
Wages	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
apprehended	O
for	O
the	O
Fact	O
abovemention	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
:	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
other	O
Evidence	O
to	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Prince	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
2	O
Paper	O
Shop	O
Books	O
,	O
Value	O
10	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Tobias	B-pers
Maynard	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
proved	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Nature	O
of	O
some	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Somerset	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
8	O
Bushels	O
of	O
White	O
Corn	O
,	O
Value	O
(	O
with	O
the	O
two	O
Sacks	O
)	O
33	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Beaton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
Jan	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Man	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
last	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
1	O
Sack	O
of	O
Brown	O
Malt	O
,	O
Value	O
13	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Beaton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
Instant	O
.	O
This	O
Fact	O
was	O
also	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
drawn	O
in	O
by	O
Williams	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Nathanael	B-pers
Bridgeman	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Skelton	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
publishing	O
a	O
forg	O
'd	O
Indenture	O
to	O
defraud	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Forster	I-pers
of	O
41	O
l.	O
due	O
to	O
him	O
from	O
the	O
Government	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Service	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Madley	I-pers
,	O
his	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
on	O
Board	O
the	O
Ruby	O
Man	O
of	O
War	O
.	O
This	O
Fact	O
was	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
;	O
who	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Beadle	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Christ	B-place
Church	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
Value	O
20	O
s.	O
1	O
Pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
55	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hills	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Fellow-	O
Servant	O
at	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Arms	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Newgate-street	O
:	O
That	O
having	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
he	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
Search	O
found	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Shirts	O
upon	O
his	O
Back	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Parish	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
Value	O
15s	O
.	O
and	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Susan	B-pers
Cypress	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Constable	O
had	O
the	O
Rings	O
;	O
but	O
neither	O
the	O
Constable	O
nor	O
a	O
Confession	O
appearing	O
in	O
Evidence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
of	O
this	O
Indictement	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
Silver	O
Salver	O
,	O
Value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Spurs	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
New	I-place
Fish-street	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
him	O
an	O
Injury	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
make	O
him	O
amends	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
most	O
of	O
them	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Directions	O
;	O
but	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
spake	O
very	O
favourably	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Wade	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Vedast	I-place
,	O
alias	O
Foster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
11	O
Yards	O
of	O
Taffety-Ribbon	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
proved	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Value	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Bartwick	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Vedast	I-place
,	O
alias	O
Foster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
10	O
Yards	O
of	O
Ferreting	O
,	O
one	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Laces	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
of	O
16	O
s	O
;	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
Half-penny-worth	O
of	O
Thread	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servants	O
having	O
a	O
Suspicion	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Shop-lifter	O
,	O
observed	O
her	O
Actions	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
search	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
same	O
put	O
into	O
a	O
Place	O
in	O
her	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
made	O
only	O
for	O
such	O
Purpose	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Woman	O
:	O
but	O
that	O
sometimes	O
she	O
was	O
crazy	O
,	O
and	O
behav	O
'd	O
herself	O
like	O
a	O
Mad	O
Woman	O
:	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Cad	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Peter	I-place
in	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
dead	O
Lamb	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Child	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
Instant	O
.	O
This	O
Indictment	O
was	O
well	O
prov	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Lamb	O
taken	O
upon	O
him	O
:	O
however	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
young	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Frances	B-pers
Pirchell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
11	O
Sheets	O
,	O
12	O
Huckaback	O
Table-Cloths	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Shirt	O
,	O
value	O
35	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Gardener	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
Instant	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Leech	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
Value	O
7	O
s.	O
8	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
12	O
s	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brownrigg	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Camblet	O
Ridinghood	O
,	O
Value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
Parish	O
.	O
Both	O
Facts	O
were	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
confess	O
'd	O
them	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
of	O
Peace	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Confession	O
not	O
being	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
saying	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
took	O
it	O
into	O
Consideration	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Hurrel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
James	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
him	O
of	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
Perriwig	O
,	O
and	O
Coat	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
8	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Substance	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
Wright	O
coming	O
over	O
Bunhill-Fields	B-place
,	O
was	O
set	O
upon	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
about	O
10	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
not	O
far	O
from	O
the	O
Snow-House	O
;	O
and	O
some	O
Gentlemen	O
going	O
along	O
by	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
a	O
Voice	O
say	O
,	O
Tie	O
him	O
,	O
shoot	O
him	O
,	O
cried	O
out	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
sled	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
pursued	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
Scott	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
sworn	O
to	O
,	O
the	O
Snow	O
giving	O
a	O
great	O
Light	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
carried	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
Hurrel	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
order	O
'd	O
to	O
draw	O
up	O
his	O
Confession	O
in	O
Form	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
be	O
sign	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
chang	O
'd	O
his	O
Mind	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
know	O
nor	O
own	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
acquitted	O
both	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Bullock	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
Stepney	I-place
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Breeman	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
101	O
Yards	O
of	O
Callimanco	O
Stuff	O
,	O
1	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
50	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Breeman	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
having	O
married	O
a	O
Widow	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
her	O
Daughter	O
into	O
his	O
Family	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
having	O
been	O
acquainted	O
(	O
as	O
he	O
has	O
since	O
discover	O
'd	O
)	O
with	O
a	O
Gang	O
of	O
Thieves	O
and	O
Rogues	O
;	O
left	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
them	O
Company	O
and	O
being	O
reduc	O
'd	O
to	O
great	O
Poverty	O
(	O
the	O
ordinary	O
Fate	O
of	O
such	O
dissolute	O
Persons	O
)	O
she	O
acquainted	O
them	O
how	O
they	O
might	O
rob	O
her	O
honest	O
Father-in-Law	O
;	O
accordingly	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Night	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
Bullock	O
and	O
Hurrell	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
House	O
together	O
for	O
that	O
Purpose	O
,	O
Hurrell	O
having	O
a	O
dark	O
Lanthorn	O
and	O
a	O
Bed-Screw	O
,	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
leaving	O
the	O
Lanthorn	O
and	O
Screw	O
behind	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
honest	O
Man	O
ruin	O
'd	O
;	O
his	O
miserable	O
Daughter-in-Law	O
,	O
finding	O
her	O
self	O
deceiv	O
'd	O
and	O
disappointed	O
in	O
her	O
Companions	O
,	O
made	O
herself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
fix	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
Hurrell	O
,	O
beside	O
the	O
Circumstance	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
Confession	O
,	O
which	O
however	O
could	O
not	O
affect	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
.	O
They	O
all	O
denied	O
it	O
at	O
their	O
Tryal	O
;	O
and	O
Hurrell	O
brought	O
an	O
Evidence	O
who	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
Breeman	O
's	O
Daughter	O
was	O
in	O
Bed	O
all	O
that	O
Night	O
with	O
a	O
Young	O
Man	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
that	O
she	O
lay	O
in	O
with	O
two	O
others	O
;	O
That	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
Beds	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
three	O
Prisoners	O
lay	O
in	O
them	O
,	O
from	O
8	O
a	O
Clock	O
that	O
Night	O
till	O
10	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
taking	O
the	O
Matter	O
into	O
their	O
Consideration	O
,	O
brought	O
Hurrell	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
and	O
acquitted	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
.	O
Melchior	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
marrying	O
a	O
second	O
Wife	O
,	O
his	O
first	O
being	O
then	O
alive	O
.	O
Both	O
Marriages	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
Boy	O
)	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Hillinghall	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Crosier	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Day-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Deal-Box	O
,	O
with	O
about	O
4	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
Instant	O
in	O
the	O
Day-time	O
.	O
The	O
Felony	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Burglary	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
;	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
,	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Hannah	B-pers
Ratford	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Leathern	O
Trunk	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
it	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
little	O
Value	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
confese	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
which	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
and	O
proved	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
appearing	O
very	O
penitent	O
and	O
dejected	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hutchins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
in	I-place
White-chapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
14	O
Yards	O
of	O
Stuff	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
some	O
Yards	O
of	O
Tape	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
d.	O
and	O
some	O
Rows	O
of	O
Pins	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Susan	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
being	O
of	O
little	O
value	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
Burglary	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Tomlins	I-pers
;	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
38	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
;	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Richardson	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
just	O
before	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
a	O
young	O
lady	O
that	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
believed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
followed	O
her	O
in	O
for-it	O
;	O
but	O
missing	O
of	O
her	O
End	O
there	O
,	O
took	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
pick	O
her	O
Pocket	O
;	O
her	O
Money	O
being	O
gone	O
,	O
she	O
secured	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Pocket	O
to	O
the	O
exact	O
Quantity	O
she	O
had	O
named	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
own	O
Money	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
forty	O
People	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
apprehended	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
being	O
denied	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
by	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
Second	O
time	O
indicted	O
with	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Fell	I-pers
not	O
taken	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
9	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Tibby	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
Jan	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Tibby	O
's	O
and	O
cheapned	O
a	O
Leg	O
of	O
Mutton	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
not	O
pleasing	O
,	O
they	O
fix	O
'd	O
upon	O
a	O
leg	O
with	O
the	O
Loyn	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
to	O
be	O
separated	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
Tomlins	O
went	O
in	O
;	O
and	O
whilst	O
Mrs.	O
Tibby	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
in	O
cutting	O
off	O
the	O
loyn	O
,	O
pick	O
'd	O
her	O
pocket	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
Mutton	O
no	O
longer	O
pleasing	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
:	O
but	O
Mrs.	O
Tibby	O
presently	O
missing	O
her	O
Money	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
them	O
back	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
which	O
would	O
serve	O
their	O
purpose	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
charg	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
the	O
Money	O
she	O
lost	O
was	O
a	O
half	O
Crown	O
,	O
3	O
Shillings	O
,	O
3	O
plain	O
Sixpences	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
rest	O
crooked	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
made	O
her	O
pull	O
out	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
just	O
the	O
Sum	O
she	O
mention	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Frances	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Griffith	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Day-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
1	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
,	O
and	O
1	O
Damask	O
Night-Gown	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Esq	B-pers
;	I-pers
Venner	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
instant	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Proof	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Felony	O
being	O
evident	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
that	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
;	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
3	O
pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Gloves	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Best	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
Jan	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
for	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Black	O
Silk	O
Gloves	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
liking	O
the	O
first	O
(	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Custom	O
of	O
such	O
Persons	O
)	O
others	O
were	O
shown	O
her	O
;	O
in	O
which	O
time	O
she	O
had	O
put	O
up	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
was	O
very	O
difficult	O
,	O
and	O
nothing	O
could	O
please	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
But	O
being	O
call	O
'd	O
back	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
begg	O
'd	O
for	O
Mercy	O
.	O
In	O
her	O
Defence	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
long	O
'd	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
not	O
why	O
else	O
she	O
did	O
it	O
,	O
not	O
having	O
any	O
occasion	O
as	O
she	O
knew	O
of	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Roger	B-pers
Mort	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
a	O
Copper	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
Reverend	O
Mr.	B-pers
Langley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
Jan	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Langley	O
depos	O
'd	O
his	O
House	O
in	O
Surrey	B-place
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
stole	O
away	O
.	O
That	O
afterwards	O
the	O
Copper	O
being	O
stopped	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Fuller	O
's	O
and	O
he	O
informed	O
of	O
it	O
by	O
a	O
Publick	O
Advertisement	O
,	O
be	O
sent	O
the	O
Dimensions	O
of	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
in	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Fuller	O
,	O
which	O
exactly	O
agreeing	O
with	O
the	O
sald	O
Copper	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Fuller	O
returned	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
suited	O
every	O
way	O
with	O
the	O
Brick-work	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
:	O
Hereupon	O
the	O
Receiver	O
produced	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
However	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
not	O
fairly	O
fixed	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
brought	O
some	O
Persons	O
that	O
swore	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
that	O
Night	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
other	O
Respects	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Addison	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Allison	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anne	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
Jan	O
last	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intention	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
proved	O
.	O
Some	O
locks	O
were	O
broke	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
taken	O
in	O
a	O
Stable	O
adjoining	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Dark-lanthorn	O
and	O
other	O
suspcious	O
Things	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
nothing	O
offered	O
on	O
the	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sufficient	O
to	O
clear	O
his	O
Innocence	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Judith	B-pers
Bunny	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Camblet	O
Ridinghood	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
10	O
Yards	O
of	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
Jan	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
confessed	O
,	O
she	O
stole	O
the	O
ridinghood	O
before	O
a	O
justice	O
;	O
which	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
and	O
proved	O
in	O
Court	O
;	O
but	O
denied	O
it	O
upon	O
her	O
Trial	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mathew	B-pers
Chester	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Cheshire	I-pers
;	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Hendon	B-place
;	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bay	O
Mare	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Oakley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
Second	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Parish	O
,	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Edward	B-pers
More	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
him	O
of	O
a	O
Gelding	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
,	O
Bart	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Edward	B-pers
More	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
Sept	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
likewise	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
Third	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Hendon	O
,	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Richard	B-pers
Upton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
Robbing	O
him	O
of	O
8	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
8	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Richard	B-pers
Upton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
Sept	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
also	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
to	O
this	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
David	B-pers
Long	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Enfield	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
the	O
Reverend	O
Mr.	O
Charles	B-pers
Sybbald	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
him	O
of	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
and	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Charles	O
Sybbald	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.Sybbald	O
depos	O
'd	O
That	O
going	O
over	O
Enfield-Chase	B-place
in	O
his	O
Chariot	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
met	O
upon	O
the	O
Road	O
by	O
three	O
Highway-Men	O
;	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
disguis	O
'd	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
pipe	O
in	O
his	O
mouth	O
bare-fac	O
'd	O
,	O
who	O
stood	O
by	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Pistol	O
cock	O
'd	O
whilst	O
the	O
rest	O
robbed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
the	O
Seats	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Sybbald	O
's	O
Man	O
.	O
Sometime	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
a	O
Robbery	O
committed	O
in	O
Surrey	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
received	O
a	O
Wound	O
that	O
had	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
proved	O
Mortal	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
deserted	O
by	O
his	O
two	O
Comrades	O
(	O
Cheshire	O
and	O
Long	O
)	O
he	O
became	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
save	O
his	O
Soul	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
some	O
Amends	O
to	O
his	O
Country	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
himself	O
expressed	O
it	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
so	O
effectually	O
in	O
charging	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Fact	O
he	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
make	O
no	O
Defence	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Symonds	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
14	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Baldwin	I-pers
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
Jan	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
stopped	O
in	O
selling	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
Mr.Beldwin	O
having	O
before	O
published	O
an	O
Advertisement	O
of	O
his	O
Loss	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
give	O
an	O
Account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
was	O
apprehended	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
learnt	O
his	O
Story	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
upon	O
his	O
Trial	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
great	O
Pains	O
to	O
prove	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Spoons	O
of	O
a	O
Dutchman	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Way	O
to	O
London	O
from	O
Bristol	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
not	O
call	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
under	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
40	O
s	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Sparrow	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Sparrow	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstans	I-place
at	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
12	O
Yards	O
of	O
blue	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
1	O
Suit	O
of	O
Headcloths	O
,	O
several	O
Yards	O
of	O
Lace	O
,	O
a	O
Mocon	O
Stone	O
set	O
in	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
Martha	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
Jan	O
.last	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Hudson	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
having	O
lost	O
the	O
goods	O
abovementioned	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
informed	O
her	O
.	O
Acquaintance	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
Time	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
came	O
to	O
a	O
Friend	O
of	O
hers	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
up	O
who	O
thereupon	O
inform	O
'd	O
her	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
whole	O
House	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
it	O
that	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Man	O
jumped	O
out	O
at	O
Window	O
,	O
however	O
he	O
was	O
pursued	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
said	O
Macok	O
Stone	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
women	O
had	O
the	O
Headcloths	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
also	O
found	O
a	O
Chiffel	O
coloured	O
with	O
Brickdust	O
,	O
a	O
Gimlet	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Dark	O
lanthorn	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
the	O
Man	O
saying	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
whose	O
Bussiness	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
buy	O
and	O
sell	O
about	O
Streets	O
,	O
as	O
her	O
self	O
used	O
to	O
do	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
upon	O
the	O
Whole	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Woman	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Dobbinson	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
1	O
Holland	O
Sheet	O
,	O
1	O
Drugget	O
Coat	O
and	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Isaac	O
Dobbinson	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Dobbinsom	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
between	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
o	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
shut	O
the	O
Door	O
after	O
coming	O
back	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
House	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
her	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
D-	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
my	O
Mother	O
and	O
kept	O
on	O
talking	O
so	O
her	O
at	O
that	O
till	O
the	O
rest	O
got	O
away	O
;	O
as	O
he	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
Scaple	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
forc	O
'd	O
into	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
dark	O
lanthorn	O
was	O
left	O
upon	O
the	O
Table	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Favell	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminister	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
Value	O
11	O
s	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Imber	B-pers
Soloron	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
Jan	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
A	O
Servant	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Soloron	O
's	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Tankard	O
being	O
lost	O
,	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
stopp	O
's	O
d	O
the	O
Lid	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
they	O
miss	O
'd	O
and	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
Feb	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
toss	O
'd	O
into	O
their	O
Balcony	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Goldsmith	O
who	O
had	O
stopt	O
the	O
Lid	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
to	O
match	O
exactly	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
give	O
no	O
Account	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
Lid	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samuel	B-pers
Field	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Maria	B-pers
James	I-pers
(	O
a	O
Man	O
)	O
were	O
all	O
indicted	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Marribone	B-place
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
5	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
s.	O
10	O
Pewter	O
plates	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
Pint	O
Pots	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Alexander	O
Bond	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
Instant	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
not	O
being	O
satisfactory	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Hayes	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
Stepney	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
.	I-pers
Triquerne	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
Feb	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
43	O
Pound	O
Weight	O
of	O
TinValue	O
100	O
l	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
fact	O
which	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
the	O
Court	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Thorpe	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Onion	I-pers
John	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
Elizabeth	B-pers
Payne	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Cotterell	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Scott	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Askit	I-pers
and	O
Christine	B-pers
Styles	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
the	O
Men	O
as	O
Principals	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Juby	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
120	O
Hats	O
,	O
Value	O
50	O
l.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Women	O
as	O
Accessories	O
in	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
One	O
Marshal	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
made	O
himself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
that	O
Hunter	O
,	O
Onton	O
,	O
and	O
Wilkinson	O
,	O
were	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Payne	O
bought	O
several	O
of	O
them	O
for	O
1s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
a	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
stole	O
them	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
circumstances	O
to	O
.which	O
but	O
weakly	O
affected	O
Ascit	O
and	O
Styles	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
acquitted	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
all	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
indictment	O
Thomas	O
Hunter	O
alias	O
Thorpe	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Payne	O
alias	O
Cotterell	O
,	O
alias	O
Scott	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Askit	O
and	O
Christine	O
Stylesof	O
St.	O
Paul	O
Shadwell	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bayly	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
thence	O
of	O
80	O
Yards	O
of	O
Checque	O
Linnen	O
,	O
Value	O
8	O
l.	O
22	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
5	O
l.	O
several	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
Drawers	O
,	O
Shirts	O
,	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Muslin	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Linnen	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
Jan	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
Hunter	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
his	O
back	O
;	O
and	O
Marshal	O
swore	O
he	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Payne	O
bought	O
the	O
stockings	O
for	O
and	O
was	O
privy	O
to	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
Given	O
the	O
whole	O
evidence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
Hunter	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Burglary	O
,	O
Payne	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
.	O
[	O
Hunter	O
,	O
Onion	O
,	O
Wilkinson	O
:	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Payne	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Dickman	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Peter	I-place
le	I-place
Chaine	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
12	O
Yards	O
of	O
Callico	O
,	O
Value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Mayning	I-pers
on	O
the	O
10th	O
Instant	O
.	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
with	O
country	O
man	O
were	O
they	O
sold	O
things	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
then	O
her	O
peticoats	O
She	O
made	O
no	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4s	O
.	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Chambers	O
of	O
Lewis	B-pers
Monnocks	I-pers
,	O
16th	O
Instant	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
2	O
Scarlet	O
Curtains	O
Value	O
12s	O
.	O
8	O
Cushions	O
,	O
a	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
and	O
other	O
rich	O
Goods	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Susan	B-pers
Hates	I-pers
alias	O
K	O
........	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
some	O
Yards	O
of	O
Scarlet	O
and	O
Green	O
Cloth	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
by	O
William	B-pers
Sassell	I-pers
who	O
has	O
since	O
been	O
convicted	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Lack	I-pers
.	O
Which	O
Felony	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Giles	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
140	O
Pound	O
,	O
weight	O
of	O
Hemp	O
,	O
Value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
Jan.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
made	O
no	O
Defence	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Heard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
him	O
of	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
and	O
3	O
Guineas	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
Instant	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
failing	O
in	O
fixing	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Jacob	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
Value	O
12	O
s.	O
1	O
Muslin	O
Apron	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
said	O
Jacob	O
Lane	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
Jan.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Felony	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Burglary	O
dubious	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Chance	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
19	O
China	O
Cups	O
,	O
4	O
Silver	O
Sawcers	O
,	O
7	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Peter	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Possession	O
which	O
could	O
give	O
no	O
credible	O
Account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
;	O
and	O
Evans	O
,	O
who	O
has	O
already	O
been	O
convicted	O
for	O
this	O
same	O
Fact	O
having	O
declar	O
'd	O
having	O
declar	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Weedon	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
Mary	I-place
,	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
4	O
Bushels	O
of	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
Jan	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Barn	O
at	O
St	O
....	O
green	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
crept	O
under	O
the	O
Door	O
He	O
made	O
no	O
Defence	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
,	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
40	O
Pound	O
Weight	O
of	O
Sugars	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Heysham	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
Instant	O
,	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
enough	O
to	O
convict	O
him	O
,	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Buckstan	I-pers
and	O
Katharine	B-pers
Buckstan	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
9	O
Guineas	O
and	O
14	O
Shillings	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Cane	I-pers
.	O
But	O
Cane	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
Dimity	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
2	O
Holland	O
Aprons	O
3	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sleeves	O
1s	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
Jan	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
Which	O
Felony	O
being	O
proved	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
Second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
,	O
stealing	O
1	O
Drugget	O
,	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
21	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
June	O
Last	O
.	O
Which	O
being	O
very	O
evident	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
also	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Paul	B-pers
Lawler	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
1	O
Snuff-box	O
,	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
belonging	O
to	O
John	B-pers
....	I-pers
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
and	O
10d	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
1	O
Flaxen	O
Sheet	O
,	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Ruggs	O
,	O
15	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Shorlove	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
unclear	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
surprized	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
but	O
little	O
value	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
Jane	B-pers
Cartey	I-pers
and	O
Martha	B-pers
Jewell	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
privately	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
on	O
the	O
Instant	O
Shop	O
,	O
asking	O
for	O
a	O
Quilted	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
till	O
Carey	O
had	O
convey	O
'd	O
the	O
Gown	O
into	O
her	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
purpose	O
,	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Constance	B-pers
Dun	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
belonging	O
to	O
John	B-pers
London	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
Jan	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Poleson	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
in	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
1	O
Horse	O
Body	O
Cloth	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Saddle-Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Whiskins	I-pers
on	O
the	O
14th	O
instant	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
having	O
some	O
Consideration	O
for	O
the	O
Value	O
brought	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
only	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Farmer	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
No	O
body	O
appearing	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Forest	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
Anne	B-pers
Aaron	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Alice	B-pers
Joyner	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
publishing	O
a	O
false	O
power	O
or	O
forg	O
'd	O
Letter	O
of	O
Attorney	O
,	O
for	O
42	O
l.	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
Cole	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
rest	O
were	O
found	O
so	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bowley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Cheating	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stainsmore	I-pers
who	O
not	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
in	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assisting	O
in	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
together	O
with	O
Matthew	O
Fleming	O
,	O
and	O
John	O
Frost	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
Jan.	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appears	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
Two	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
having	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
in	O
their	O
Company	O
,	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
Drink	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
refused	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
Brandy	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
drank	O
two	O
Quar	O
which	O
,	O
with	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
before	O
made	O
her	O
dead	O
Drunk	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
laid	O
her	O
all	O
along	O
by	O
the	O
fire	O
and	O
left	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
never	O
recover	O
'd	O
.	O
A	O
Surgeon	O
swore	O
that	O
having	O
searched	O
her	O
.	O
He	O
found	O
no	O
Injury	O
done	O
to	O
her	O
Body	O
,	O
and	O
verily	O
believed	O
she	O
suffocated	O
herself	O
with	O
Spirits	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
Lewis	B-pers
Dubrell	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Precinct	B-place
of	I-place
the	I-place
Old	I-place
Artillery	I-place
Ground	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
Silks	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
30	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Monk	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
a	O
Frenchman	O
,	O
and	O
pretending	O
not	O
to	O
have	O
our	O
Language	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Razor	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
Holland	O
Smock	O
,	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Hood	O
,	O
value	O
about	O
5s	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
Jan	O
.	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
Service	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgement	O
,	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
19.	O
Samuel	B-pers
David	I-pers
cooke	O
Last	O
Sessions	O
throwing	O
himself	O
to	O
prevent	O
such	O
things	O
of	O
iron	O
over	O
that	O
place	O
that	O
nothing	O
can	O
be	O
person	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
John	O
Lawrence	O
Mills	O
To	O
be	O
Whip	O
'd	O
50	O
.	O
Gills	O
Willis	O
Lewis	O
Frances	O
and	O
to	O
have	O
Six	O
Nathniel	O
Elizabeth	O
Quick	O
with	O
child	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
THE	O
London	O
Method	O
and	O
Art	O
of	O
Childern	O
Read	O
and	O
perfectly	O
along	O
them	O
know	O
the	O
Sounds	O
of	O
Dipthonges	O
then	O
Letter	O
all	O
the	O
Rules	O
of	O
Spelling	O
which	O
are	O
several	O
Chapters	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
are	O
added	O
Chapters	O
to	O
learn	O
it	O
the	O
marks	O
,	O
the	O
Numeral	O
letters	O
and	O
Figures	O
and	O
Abbrivations	O
;	O
So	O
as	O
the	O
child	O
may	O
immidiately	O
pass	O
from	O
Learning	O
this	O
books	O
to	O
the	O
Rule	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
any	O
other	O
Book	O
.	O
This	O
Way	O
of	O
teaching	O
is	O
approval	O
by	O
most	O
school	O
as	O
the	O
Best	O
Price	O
Bound	O
with	O
great	O
who	O
fail	O
or	O
give	O
them	O
to	O
School	O
.	O
Arithmetic	O
made	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
new	O
method	O
now	O
tought	O
in	O
London	O
where	O
in	O
the	O
Rules	O
are	O
of	O
that	O
necessary	O
Art	O
capacity	O
if	O
they	O
desig	O
tables	O
rules	O
,	O
and	O
Examples	O
the	O
like	O
extends	O
Master	O
Writing	O
Short-Hand	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
the	O
the	O
Law	O
Thirty	O
Copper	O
Plates	O
.	O
Mathes	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
of	O
the	O
Publish	O
Where	O
others	O
of	O
that	O
in	O
Kingdom	O
the	O
Whole	O
,	O
I	O
cured	O
the	O
Decease	O
This	O
is	O
to	O
that	O
a	O
speedy	O
relief	O
and	O
Suburbs	O
of	O
London	O
A	O
vetal	O
Persons	O
of	O
sufficient	O
Credit	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
,	O
6d	O
.	O
the	O
Bettle	O
.	O
and	O
there	O
rotting	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Remedy	O
for	O
the	O
At	O
,	O
Spirits	O
of	O
ground	O
.	O
at	O
