TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
C	O
I	O
T	O
Y	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
,	O
On	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
17th	O
,	O
18th	O
,	O
and	O
19th	O
,	O
of	O
May	O
1716	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Second	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
CHARLES	B-pers
PEERS	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
King	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Eyres	O
,	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
;	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Country	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
were	O
as	O
followith	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Bernardiston	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Badwell	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Brackstone	I-pers
Smith	B-pers
Duckwell	I-pers
John	B-pers
Stanley	I-pers
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Upsall	I-pers
John	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
George	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
John	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
Robert	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hinton	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Beckington	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Partridge	I-pers
William	B-pers
Attly	I-pers
John	B-pers
Charlewood	I-pers
John	B-pers
Curtis	I-pers
Abraham	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
John	B-pers
Hern	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Bowman	I-pers
Aaron	B-pers
Gibbs	I-pers
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
an	O
Assault	O
on	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Abigail	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
and	O
for	O
robbing	O
her	O
of	O
a	O
Dimity	O
Pocket	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.1	O
Pair	O
of	O
Gloves,6	O
d.1	O
Key,2	O
d.	O
and	O
1.s	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
Instant	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
passing	O
thro	O
'	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Miles	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
Anne	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Alice	B-pers
Beemont	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
an	O
Assault	O
on	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
3	O
s.	O
But	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
not	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
's	O
Satisfaction	O
,	O
who	O
thereupon	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
1	O
Suit	O
of	O
lac	O
'd	O
Head-cloths	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
40	O
Yard	O
of	O
Thread-laces	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Mildred	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Mildred	O
Saunders	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
going	O
along	O
Shooe-lane	B-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Boy	O
met	O
her	O
and	O
dodg	O
'd	O
her	O
;	O
That	O
they	O
held	O
down	O
her	O
Hands	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
into	O
her	O
Band	O
box	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
abovementioned	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
both	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Headcloths	O
in	O
his	O
Bosom	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
seen	O
to	O
drop	O
the	O
Lace	O
.	O
This	O
Evidence	O
was	O
corroborated	O
by	O
another	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Floyd	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Callicoe	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
1	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
10s	O
.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
from	O
Seth	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Service	O
when	O
she	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
away	O
immediately	O
after	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
missing	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
fetch	O
'd	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
Chamber	O
at	O
an	O
Inn	O
from	O
whence	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
next	O
Morning	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
given	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
,	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Niece	O
for	O
an	O
adequate	O
Consideration	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
Master	O
brought	O
upon	O
her	O
this	O
Disgrace	O
and	O
Trouble	O
for	O
not	O
complying	O
with	O
his	O
unlawful	O
Desires	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
prove	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
nor	O
having	O
any	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Abbott	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Deal-Box	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
and	O
in	O
it	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
238	O
l.	O
in	O
Gold	O
and	O
Silver	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Monies	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Tappenden	I-pers
and	O
others	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
made	O
herself	O
acquainted	O
with	O
a	O
Servant	O
Maid	O
of	O
Mrs.Leonard	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
liv	O
'd	O
at	O
the	B-place
Kentish-Hoy	I-place
in	I-place
Thames-street	I-place
,	O
where	O
the	O
Goods	O
aforesaid	O
were	O
lodg	O
'd	O
;	O
one	O
Day	O
,	O
after	O
Mr.	O
Leonard	O
was	O
burnt	O
out	O
,	O
she	O
chanc	O
'd	O
to	O
meet	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
pleas	O
'd	O
she	O
might	O
live	O
with	O
her	O
as	O
accordingly	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
which	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
several	O
Opportunities	O
to	O
importune	O
her	O
to	O
rob	O
her	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
corrupt	O
her	O
every	O
way	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
resisted	O
a	O
long	O
while	O
,	O
till	O
at	O
last	O
,	O
when	O
her	O
Master	O
was	O
re-establish	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
again	O
;	O
at	O
which	O
time	O
she	O
was	O
prevail	O
'd	O
on	O
to	O
discover	O
the	O
Nature	O
of	O
his	O
Business	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
his	O
Effects	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
who	O
,	O
having	O
fix	O
'd	O
upon	O
her	O
Project	O
,	O
came	O
one	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
Liberty	O
to	O
lodge	O
there	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
come	O
from	O
on	O
Board	O
a	O
Hoy	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
be	O
unprovided	O
with	O
such	O
Conveniency	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
persuaded	O
Mrs.	O
Leonard	O
to	O
Agree	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
lie	O
with	O
her	O
Daughter	O
,	O
she	O
looking	O
like	O
a	O
clean	O
honest	O
Woman	O
;	O
to	O
requite	O
which	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
after	O
she	O
sent	O
a	O
Box	O
home	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
every	O
way	O
exactly	O
suited	O
to	O
receive	O
that	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
wherein	O
was	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
,	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
pretending	O
to	O
pay	O
honourably	O
for	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
had	O
,	O
sent	O
away	O
the	O
Box	O
(	O
which	O
but	O
pass	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
which	O
she	O
brought	O
in	O
)	O
to	O
a	O
Coach	O
which	O
she	O
took	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Maid	O
herself	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Evidences	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hillier	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.1	O
Silver	O
Chain	O
2	O
s.6	O
d.	O
1	O
Silver	O
Seal	O
1s	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bill	I-pers
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
Mr.	O
Bill	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
Fob	O
Pocket	O
being	O
torn	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
Watch	O
into	O
his	O
Wastcoat	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
along	O
Ludgate-hill	B-place
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
some	O
Questions	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
agree	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
she	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
heard	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
pawn	O
'd	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
it	O
was	O
trac	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
who	O
denied	O
she	O
ever	O
had	O
or	O
saw	O
it	O
and	O
the	O
Pawnbroker	O
not	O
appearing	O
to	O
fix	O
it	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Purdue	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
(	O
with	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Fry	I-pers
,	O
not	O
taken	O
)	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Alice	B-pers
Brigg	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Day-time	O
,	O
no	O
Person	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
a	O
Shift	O
,	O
some	O
Aprons,1	O
Silk	O
Hood	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Langworth	I-pers
,	O
Mrs.	O
Langworth	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
lock	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
her	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
on	O
her	O
Return	O
found	O
it	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
aforesaid	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Trunk	O
.	O
Another	O
depos	O
'd	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
Mob	O
about	O
her	O
for	O
offering	O
to	O
sell	O
a	O
good	O
Hat	O
for	O
a	O
Shilling	O
,	O
which	O
occasion	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
suspected	O
for	O
a	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
be	O
apprehended	O
.	O
Upon	O
her	O
Trial	O
she	O
made	O
a	O
very	O
poor	O
Defence	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
satisfie	O
the	O
Court	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
Goods	O
honestly	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Rhodes	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Linnen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
2	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
2	O
Shifts	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Matth.ias	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
Instant	O
:	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Hankerson	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
Queenhithe	I-place
;	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Lisle	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
12	O
Guineas	O
and	O
3	O
Half	O
Broad	O
Piece	O
,	O
1	O
Broad	O
Piece	O
,	O
1	O
Moydor	O
,	O
25	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
2	O
Portuguese	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Silver	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
2	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
5l	O
.	O
40	O
Bathmetal	O
Buttons	O
6s	O
.	O
3	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
8s	O
.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
from	O
the	O
said	O
Richard	O
Lisle	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
Second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
44	O
Gallons	O
of	O
value	O
of	O
Gallons	O
Brandy	O
,	O
value	O
20s	O
.	O
20	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Colourd	O
Water,8	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Cinnamon	O
Water	O
,	O
8	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Dr.	O
Stephensts	O
Water	O
,	O
8	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Surfeit	O
Water	O
,	O
130	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Vinegar	O
,	O
120	O
gallons	O
of	O
Wormwood	O
;	O
112	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Angelica	O
Water	O
;	O
and	O
12	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Lyme-juice	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Richard	O
Lisle	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
April	O
Mr.	O
Lisle	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
his	O
Servant	O
and	O
much	O
in	O
his	O
Favour	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
trusted	O
him	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
the	O
Management	O
of	O
his	O
Business	O
but	O
missing	O
at	O
Times	O
Quantities	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
grew	O
jealous	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
paid	O
him	O
his	O
Wages	O
,	O
and	O
discharg	O
'd	O
him	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
beg	O
'd	O
earnestly	O
that	O
his	O
Trunk	O
might	O
be	O
left	O
till	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Conveniency	O
to	O
fetch	O
it	O
away	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
consented	O
;	O
but	O
about	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
a	O
Watchman	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
up	O
;	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
this	O
Cellar	O
Window	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
Compting-house	O
and	O
found	O
some	O
Money	O
gone	O
;	O
but	O
observing	O
a	O
Till	O
shut	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
most	O
Money	O
which	O
was	O
always	O
used	O
in	O
the	O
Way	O
of	O
this	O
Trade	O
,	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
Well	O
,	O
the	O
Thief	O
is	O
very	O
civil	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
not	O
taken	O
all	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
his	O
Surprize	O
upon	O
opening	O
it	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
100	O
l.	O
Bag	O
with	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictement	O
,	O
gon	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
his	O
Trunk	O
,	O
took	O
an	O
Occasion	O
to	O
slink	O
into	O
a	O
Cellar	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
lay	O
till	O
the	O
Family	O
was	O
a	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
committed	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
(	O
being	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
that	O
rob	O
'd	O
him	O
)	O
he	O
cross	O
'd	O
the	O
Water	O
to	O
Southwark	O
where	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
Shop	O
,	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
him	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
found	O
him	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
Water	O
at	O
a	O
By-pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
agreed	O
to	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
would	O
not	O
own	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
he	O
was	O
charg	O
'd	O
with	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
intreated	O
to	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
kindest	O
Manner	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
he	O
was	O
charg	O
'd	O
with	O
a	O
Constable	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
drop	O
something	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Constable	O
took	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Lisle	O
't	O
was	O
some	O
Buttons	O
and	O
a	O
Buckle	O
;	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Lisle	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
they	O
were	O
Bathmetal	O
Buttons	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Buckle	O
was	O
Silver	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
:	O
Then	O
he	O
was	O
search	O
'd	O
and	O
the	O
Bag	O
aforesaid	O
with	O
55	O
l	O
6	O
s.6	O
d.	O
the	O
Top	O
of	O
a	O
Tea	O
Canister	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
,	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
all	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
several	O
others	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
Spirits	O
and	O
Liquors	O
,	O
one	O
Maun	O
who	O
dealt	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Lisle	O
depos	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
Consideration	O
of	O
a	O
Watch	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
for	O
him	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stole	O
them	O
,	O
being	O
then	O
in	O
Credit	O
with	O
his	O
Master	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
more	O
in	O
Consideration	O
of	O
a	O
Clock	O
which	O
he	O
bespoke	O
of	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
Use	O
of	O
his	O
House	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
in	O
Southwark	O
.	O
The	O
rest	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Shop	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Porter	O
Swore	O
he	O
carried	O
them	O
there	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Lisle	O
's	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Order	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
brought	O
a	O
Person	O
who	O
swore	O
she	O
saw	O
him	O
borrow	O
50	O
l.	O
of	O
one	O
Rowland	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
,	O
and	O
remember	O
'd	O
some	O
Talk	O
about	O
a	O
4	O
s	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
Piece	O
,	O
a	O
half	O
Moydore	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
odd	O
Pieces	O
which	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
name	O
nor	O
distinguish	O
.	O
He	O
denied	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
Buckles	O
or	O
Buttons	O
of	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
and	O
as	O
:	O
for	O
the	O
Liquors	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
paid	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
to	O
Cash	O
;	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Lisle	O
denied	O
,	O
and	O
proved	O
the	O
contrary	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Roger	B-pers
Hewit	I-pers
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Sparkes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
.	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
and	O
Breeches,1	O
Callicoe	O
,	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Serjeant	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Serjeant	O
swore	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Hewit	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Morning	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Rumford	O
Market	O
,	O
took	O
his	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
but	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
after	O
he	O
met	O
him	O
in	O
Old	O
Gravel-Lane	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
Clothes	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
lent	O
him	O
the	O
Clothes	O
once	O
before	O
,	O
upon	O
Condition	O
to	O
pay	O
him	O
9	O
s.	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
them	O
any	O
Injury	O
and	O
having	O
occasion	O
for	O
'em	O
to	O
go	O
on	O
board	O
Ship	O
;	O
he	O
thought	O
he	O
might	O
take	O
'em	O
upon	O
the	O
same	O
foot	O
without	O
Offence	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
detain	O
'd	O
on	O
Board	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Way	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Woman	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
both	O
.	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
5	O
Yards	O
of	O
Thread	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Rivers	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
,	O
was	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
her	O
Age	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Peter	I-place
's	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
12	O
pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
on	O
the	O
18th	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
Guilty	O
and	O
was	O
accordingly	O
found	O
so	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
in	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
;	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
Rugg	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.1	O
Blanket,1	O
s.2	O
Sheets,2	O
s.	O
and	O
an	O
Apron,6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Peters	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Which	O
Fact	O
was	O
also	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Attly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
in	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Day-time	O
,	O
(	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
George	B-pers
Wale	I-pers
,	O
not	O
taken	O
)	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
2	O
China	O
Gowns	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.1	O
Silk	O
Petticoat,16	O
s.1	O
Cloth	O
Petticoat,20	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
from	O
the	O
said	O
Richard	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
very	O
mean	O
and	O
of	O
indifferent	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
tho	O
'	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
)	O
made	O
a	O
notable	O
Defence	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Corny	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Pattons	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Cloth	O
Coats	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.1	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
and	O
Chain,4	O
l.	O
a	O
Seal,1	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
belonging	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Willinghurst	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Barnes	O
depos	O
'd	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
some	O
at	O
Pawn	O
Brokers	O
,	O
who	O
produc	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
that	O
cries	O
Old	O
Clothes	O
about	O
Streets	O
,	O
in	O
Pepper-Alley	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Persons	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Man	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Abel	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
Ludgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
1	O
Cambrick	O
Neck-cloth	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Pycott	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
This	O
Prosecution	O
appearing	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
to	O
be	O
trifling	O
and	O
litigious	O
,	O
they	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pauls	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
1	O
Silver	O
and	O
Mother-of-Pearl	O
Snuff-box	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Salt	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
Instant	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pick	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Salt	O
's	O
Pocket	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Play-house	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
afterwards	O
dropt	O
the	O
Box	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
but	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Martha	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
some	O
Sheets	O
and	O
other	O
Linnen	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
40s	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
fully-prov	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Martha	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
at	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Hously	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Day-time	O
,	O
no	O
Person	O
being	O
,	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
1	O
Poplin	O
Mantua	B-pers
Gown	I-pers
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
another	O
Petticoat	O
value	O
8	O
s.1	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
15	O
s.1	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
1	O
s.6	O
d.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Richard	O
Hously	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Hously	O
swore	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
aforesaid	O
;	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
that	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
her	O
House	O
was	O
shut	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
had	O
them	O
swore	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
9	O
s.	O
Who	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
Woman	O
to	O
sell	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
nor	O
bring	O
any	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gee	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
at	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
Instant	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
a	O
plain	O
Case	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Daws	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anne	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	B-pers
Willoughby	I-pers
of	O
Brook	O
.	O
A	O
Coachman	O
depos	O
'd	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
steal	O
the	O
Coat	O
off	O
the	O
Coach-box	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
pursued	O
he	O
drop	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
which	O
Evidence	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
another	O
's	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Rachel	B-pers
Allison	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
Instant	O
.	O
Lloyd	O
swore	O
he	O
was	O
stop	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
him	O
gone	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
drink	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
refus	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
heard	O
the	O
clinking	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
searching	O
his	O
Pockets	O
,	O
found	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
5	O
s.	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
who	O
coming	O
up	O
,	O
search	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
Pocket-piece	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
crooked	O
Shilling	O
remarkably	O
bent	O
,	O
pass	O
thro	O
'	O
her	O
Hands	O
to	O
a	O
Confederate	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Colter	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Gardiner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Holland	O
Sheets	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
le	I-pers
Teict	I-pers
,	O
1	O
Holland	O
Sheet,6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Tomkins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
1	O
chequer	O
'd	O
Holland	O
Apron	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joan	B-pers
Frost	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2	O
d	O
Instant	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Frost	O
had	O
put	O
a	O
Quantity	O
,	O
of	O
wet	O
Linnen	O
into	O
a	O
Tray	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
be	O
Hung	O
up	O
to	O
dry	O
;	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
accordingly	O
so	O
hung	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Lines	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
for	O
all	O
,	O
the	O
rest	O
remain	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Tray	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
soon	O
after	O
stole	O
and	O
the	O
three	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
were	O
discover	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
Dickenson	O
threw	O
over	O
a	O
Wall	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
all	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White-chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
Pair	O
of	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.1	O
Pound	O
of	O
Raw	O
Silk,2	O
Bibles	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
from	O
Nathanael	B-pers
Lamb	I-pers
on	O
the	O
15th	O
Instant	O
.	O
It	O
seems	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
;	O
That	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
afterwards	O
caught	O
selling	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
his	O
Master	O
lent	O
him	O
the	O
Books	O
to	O
read	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
credited	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
him	O
of	O
3	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
Instant	O
.	O
Adams	O
depos	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
the	B-place
Broomfield	I-place
near	I-place
Rosemary-branch	I-place
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
a	O
Pig	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
No	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
Wilson	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Throat	O
(	O
he	O
being	O
an	O
old	O
Man	O
)	O
and	O
threw	O
him	O
down	O
saying	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
is	O
You	O
have	O
stole	O
it	O
from	O
yonder	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
his	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
it	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
for	O
some	O
Boys	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
washing	O
themselves	O
thereabouts	O
,	O
would	O
have	O
murder	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Boys	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
hearing	O
,	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
with	O
some	O
others	O
and	O
heard	O
Wilson	O
say	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Hold	O
him	O
,	O
Sarah	O
till	O
I	O
go	O
and	O
call	O
my	O
Husband	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
his	O
Rings	O
were	O
put	O
under	O
his	O
Door	O
a	O
little-time	O
after	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
(	O
especially	O
Wilson	O
)	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
represent	O
it	O
a	O
Malicious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
the	O
Effect	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Adam	O
's	O
peevish	O
morose	O
Temper	O
,	O
and	O
related	O
some	O
Circumstances	O
to	O
confirm	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
them	O
both	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
at	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Benning	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Day-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
then	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
Cloth	O
Breeches	O
value	O
10s	O
;	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Mantle	O
4s	O
.	O
2	O
Yards	O
of	O
Child	O
's	O
Stuff	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
Goods	O
of	O
said	O
Joseph	O
Benning	O
,	O
no	O
Person	O
being	O
therein	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
Second	O
time	O
indicted	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
's	I-place
Bromley	I-place
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
4	O
Dowlas	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
2	O
Dowlas	O
Shift	O
2	O
s.	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary-Long	B-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16	O
th	O
Instant	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
swore	O
to	O
the	O
first	O
Indictment	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
been	O
hiding	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Field	O
,	O
but	O
finding	O
himself	O
discover	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
however	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
to	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
left	O
fast	O
lock	O
'd	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
second	O
,	O
a	O
Girl	O
swore	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
's	O
to	O
light	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
back	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
all	O
together	O
in	O
the	O
Bundle	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
hid	O
,	O
who	O
only	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
Rag	O
Fair	O
;	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
nor	O
produce	O
any	O
Persons	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
1	O
Quilted	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Proof	O
was	O
full	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Dikes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
4l	O
.	O
1	O
Cloth	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
30	O
s.	O
1	O
Cloth	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
15	O
s	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
George	B-pers
Somerset	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Jordan	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
Second	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
and	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.1	O
Silver	O
Tea	O
Pot	O
,	O
9l	O
.	O
2	O
Silver	O
Pint	O
Pots	O
,	O
7	O
l.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Jordan	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Facts	O
were	O
both	O
proved	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
some	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
brought	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Single	O
Felony	O
of	O
each	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Perdy	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.Clement	B-place
,	I-place
Danes	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
,	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
1	O
Holland	O
Neck	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Dighton	I-pers
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
the	O
Fact	O
and	O
a	O
Dark	O
lanthorn	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
suspicious	O
Things	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Arnold	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
Bart	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
an	O
Iron	O
Chest	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
a	O
Diamond	O
Necklace	O
100l	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Sir	O
Richard	O
Reynolds	O
Bart	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
which	O
most	O
affected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
only	O
saw	O
him	O
help	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
Chest	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Hathaway	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
Edward	B-pers
Hathaway	I-pers
(	O
Since	O
fled	O
from	O
Justice	O
)	O
did	O
kill	O
and	O
Murder	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
by	O
giving	O
him	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Pen-knife	O
near	O
the	O
left	O
Pap	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
he	O
lanuguish	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
April	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
,	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
Richard	B-pers
Hathaway	I-pers
was	O
aiding	O
and	O
assisting	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
upon	O
an	O
Inquisition	O
before	O
the	O
Coroner	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
murder	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Edward	O
Hathaway	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
Provocation	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Briggs	O
his	O
Friend	O
was	O
also	O
much	O
abus	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
agreed	O
on	O
both	O
Sides	O
that	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Main	O
's	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
Collier	O
depos	O
'd	O
who	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
it	O
)	O
that	O
one	O
Day	O
he	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
reprimand	O
the	O
said	O
Edward	O
Hathaway	O
very	O
severely	O
for	O
his	O
insupportable	O
Insolence	O
and	O
Profaneness	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
threatened	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
his	O
Life	O
;	O
and	O
beliv	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
being	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
was	O
mistaken	O
for	O
himself	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
receiv	O
'd	O
the	O
Stab	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
Edward	O
Hathaway	O
.	O
Damn	O
ye	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
ye	O
want	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
it	O
had	O
the	O
Face	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
mad	O
rash	O
Action	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
premeditated	O
against	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
who	O
was	O
very	O
active	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
side	O
as	O
his	O
Brother	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Circumstances	O
in	O
the	O
Eye	O
of	O
the	O
Law	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Trimble	I-pers
jun	O
.	O
Gent	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bone	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Moses	B-pers
Pierce	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Rapier	O
near	O
the	O
right	O
Pap	O
;	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
Same	O
Murder	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Decease	O
'd	O
was	O
Journey-man	O
Carpenter	O
,	O
and	O
believing	O
himself	O
to	O
have	O
atain	O
'd	O
Some	O
Skill	O
in	O
Small	O
Sword	O
,	O
would	O
always	O
wear	O
one	O
,	O
or	O
have	O
one	O
by	O
him	O
;	O
which	O
made	O
his	O
Behaviour	O
founded	O
upon	O
that	O
Conceit	O
,	O
unsupportable	O
.	O
Sometime	O
before	O
this	O
unfortunate	O
Action	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
being	O
in	O
Company	O
,	O
they	O
differ	O
'd	O
about	O
the	O
Manner	O
and	O
Posture	O
of	O
holding	O
the	O
Sword	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
took	O
Root	O
in	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
him	O
restless	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Day	O
on	O
which	O
the	O
Action	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
heard	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
answer	O
'd	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
You	O
say	O
(	O
said	O
he	O
)	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
Skill	O
in	O
Small	O
Sword	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
ready	O
to	O
answer	O
you	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
fight	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
beat	O
you	O
.	O
Name	O
your	O
Ground	O
then	O
,	O
said	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
The	O
Road	O
said	O
the	O
Deceased	O
and	O
away	O
they	O
both	O
went	O
:	O
Before	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
came	O
up	O
the	O
fatal	O
Wound	O
was	O
given	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
holding	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Sword	O
very	O
thirsty	O
and	O
desirous	O
of	O
a	O
Dram	O
of	O
Brandy	O
;	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
fight	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
his	O
Blood	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
after	O
fell	O
down	O
dead	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
brought	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
Fan	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
s.	O
Silk	O
Hood,10	O
s.	O
2	O
Gold	O
Rings,30	O
s.	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
Walter	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
charg	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
no	O
material	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
he	O
lodg	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
two	O
Years	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
Time	O
she	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
:	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
found	O
a	O
Fan	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
upon	O
his	O
Bed	O
's	O
Tester	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
was	O
sometime	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
away	O
,	O
In	O
a	O
Word	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
very	O
trifling	O
and	O
weak	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
greatest	O
Incitement	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
was	O
from	O
a	O
modern	O
Piece	O
of	O
Conjuration	O
,	O
by	O
putting	O
a	O
Key	O
upon	O
the	O
18th	O
,	O
19th	O
,	O
20th	O
,	O
and	O
21st	O
Verses	O
of	O
the	O
50th	O
Psalm	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
naming	O
,	O
the	O
Persons	O
suspected	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
done	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Jones	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
the	O
Key	O
(	O
as	O
they	O
said	O
)	O
turn	O
'd	O
round	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Name	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
down	O
;	O
this	O
confirm	O
'd	O
her	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
charged	O
others	O
with	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
;	O
)	O
and	O
was	O
accounted	O
a	O
Woman	O
of	O
Strange	O
Notions	O
and	O
Caprice	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
several	O
reputable	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Judith	B-pers
,	I-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White-chappel	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
3	O
Guineas	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
That	O
having	O
receiv	O
'd	O
some	O
Money	O
in	O
Broad	O
street	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
Brandy	B-place
Shop	I-place
in	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
Stairs	O
which	O
he	O
consented	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
Bed	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
drank	O
part	O
of	O
5	O
Pints	O
of	O
Punch	O
,	O
in	O
about	O
two	O
Hours	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
6d	O
.	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
lie	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
at	O
that	O
Price	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
swore	O
this	O
Robbery	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Giles	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Middle	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Gough	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
1	O
Feather	O
Bolster	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
1	O
Callicoe	O
Quilt	O
,	O
5s	O
.	O
and	O
4	O
Callimancoe	O
Curtains	O
,	O
value	O
20s	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
them	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
their	O
Confederates	O
,	O
whose	O
Evidence	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
others	O
;	O
except	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
lifting	O
up	O
the	O
Sash	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
(	O
together	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
)	O
1	O
Weather	O
;	O
value	O
27	O
s.	O
2	O
Ewe	O
20s	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
1	O
Weather	O
value	O
14s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Prior	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
Instant	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Proof	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
who	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Tyre	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
;	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Weather	O
Sheep	O
value.30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wendy	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
20	O
Yards	O
of	O
Velvet	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
6	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cloth	O
,	O
4o	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
John	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
where	O
the	O
Lining	O
of	O
a	O
Coach	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
single	O
a	O
Felony	O
under	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
40s	O
.	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Macgrah	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
Value	O
10	O
s	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Manning	I-pers
;	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
Instant	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Manning	O
depos	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
drink	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
but	O
has	O
left	O
it	O
some	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
came	O
to	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Spoon	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
d.	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Drawer	O
;	O
and	O
absconded	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
but	O
in	O
Waggery	O
to	O
vex	O
the	O
Maid	O
.	O
Then	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Gillingham	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
,	O
feloniously	O
,	O
stealing	O
2	O
Carbines	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.2	O
pair	O
of	O
Pistols	O
;	O
value	O
40	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
my	O
Lord	O
James	B-pers
Cavendish	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
the	O
Pistols	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Cart	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
of	O
the	O
Horse	O
Guards	O
depos	O
'd	O
he	O
bought	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
Half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
.	O
The	O
Gunsmith	O
's	O
Mark	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Lord	O
's	O
Crest	O
,	O
were	O
erased	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
at	O
his	O
Shop	O
for	O
9	O
s.	O
and	O
his	O
Daughter	O
and	O
Servants	O
made	O
Oath	O
they	O
saw	O
him	O
pay	O
the	O
Money	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Thurland	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
were	O
arraigned	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Knapp	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
him	O
of	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
arraigned	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
William	O
White	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Knapp	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
her	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Bullet	O
in	O
the	O
left	O
Cheek	O
near	O
the	O
Eye	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
instantly	O
died	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
for	O
aiding	O
and	O
assisting	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
Also	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
William	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Thurland	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
were	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
arraign	O
'd	O
for	O
an	O
Assault	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Gough	I-pers
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
him	O
of	O
a	O
Brown	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
one	O
Fustian	O
Frock,5	O
s.2	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buttons,1	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Russell	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
White	I-pers
;	O
were	O
arraign	O
'd	O
for	O
breaking	O
(	O
with	O
Timothy	B-pers
Dunn	I-pers
not	O
taken	O
)	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Barkley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
,	O
thence	O
4	O
Gold	O
Rings,2	O
Stuff	O
Coats,6	O
Handkerchiefs,1	O
Sattin	O
Gown	O
,	O
1	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
4	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
Several	O
sorts	O
of	O
other	O
rich	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
and	O
Deborah	B-pers
Stent	I-pers
as	O
Accessory	O
to	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
in	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
To	O
all	O
which	O
Arraignments	O
,	O
White	O
and	O
Thurland	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
plead	O
,	O
but	O
stood	O
obstinately	O
without	O
speaking	O
or	O
holding	O
up	O
their	O
Hands	O
;	O
upon	O
Which	O
the	O
Court	O
read	O
the	O
Law	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
by	O
virtue	O
of	O
which	O
their	O
two	O
Thumbs	O
were	O
tied	O
together	O
with	O
Whipcord	O
,	O
and	O
drawn	O
by	O
the	O
whole	O
Force	O
of	O
two	O
Men	O
,	O
each	O
above	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
which	O
having	O
no	O
Effect	O
upon	O
their	O
,	O
contumacious	O
Humour	O
,	O
Sentence	O
was	O
pass	O
'd	O
upon	O
on	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
press	O
'd	O
to	O
Death	O
according	O
to	O
Law	O
but	O
when	O
they	O
saw	O
Death	O
so	O
near	O
and	O
terrible	O
they	O
relax	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
pleaded	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
to	O
each	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
challeng	O
'd	O
all	O
the	O
old	O
Jury	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
new	O
one	O
being	O
sworn	O
,	O
the	O
Jurors	O
Names	O
were	O
,	O
as	O
followeth	O
John	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Oakly	I-pers
William	B-pers
Gunstone	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Prior	I-pers
Jeremy	B-pers
Lewin	I-pers
John	B-pers
Toward	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Winch	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Barnet	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Winkle	I-pers
William	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
Benjamin	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
.	O
Then	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
indicted	O
as	O
above	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
being	O
called	O
to	O
the	O
first	O
and	O
second	O
indictments	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
who	O
had	O
made	O
his	O
Mother	O
a	O
Visit	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
before	O
,	O
among	O
other	O
things	O
in	O
Conversation	O
,	O
was	O
pleas	O
'd	O
to	O
express	O
himself	O
very	O
well	O
satisfied	O
with	O
the	O
Diversion	O
he	O
met	O
with	O
at	O
Sadler	O
's	O
Wells	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
,	O
was	O
very	O
desirous	O
to	O
see	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Evening	O
which	O
prov	O
'd	O
so	O
fatal	O
they	O
both	O
went	O
there	O
together	O
and	O
perceiving	O
his	O
Mother	O
inclin	O
'd	O
to	O
stay	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
them	O
if	O
they	O
could	O
provide	O
him	O
a	O
Link	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Mother	O
staid	O
till	O
10	O
a	O
Clock	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
lighted	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
her	O
without	O
meeting	O
any	O
Accident	O
till	O
they	O
came	O
within	O
40	O
Yards	O
of	O
the	O
Houses	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
first	O
met	O
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
who	O
prov	O
'd	O
2	O
very	O
honest	O
Fellow	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
an	O
Instant	O
of	O
Time	O
his	O
Link	O
was	O
blown	O
out	O
,	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wigg	O
taken	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
himself	O
beat	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Ground	O
;	O
which	O
made	O
his	O
Mother	O
scream	O
out	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
fir	O
'd	O
a	O
Pistol	O
close	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
he	O
heard	O
his	O
Mother	O
say	O
,	O
Lord	O
,	O
help	O
me	O
,	O
help	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Rogues	O
fled	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
went	O
immediately	O
to	O
the	O
Houses	O
for	O
Help	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Soldier	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Assistance	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
a	O
Light	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
his	O
Mother	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
dead	O
.	O
This	O
Evidence	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
it	O
concern	O
'd	O
the	O
Action	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
Isaac	B-pers
Ragg	I-pers
(	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Gang	O
)	O
and	O
the	O
Soldier	O
,	O
but	O
Ragg	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
they	O
(	O
himself	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
)	O
came	O
back	O
to	O
drink	O
together	O
,	O
they	O
all	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
their	O
Pistols	O
,	O
having	O
each	O
a	O
Brace	O
to	O
examine	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
discharg	O
'd	O
and	O
they	O
found	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
White	O
had	O
discharg	O
'd	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Reason	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
to	O
frighten	O
the	O
Woman	O
and	O
make	O
her	O
hold	O
,	O
her	O
Tongue	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
immediately	O
,	O
Who	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
shot	O
the	O
Woman	O
to	O
another	O
;	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
intend	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
sir	O
'd	O
to	O
frighten	O
her	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
done	O
by	O
Grass-Inn	B-place
Garden-Wall	I-place
.	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
others	O
who	O
saw	O
Mrs.	O
Knapp	O
lie	O
dead	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
Prisoners	O
Thurland	O
and	O
Chapman	O
were	O
sworn	O
by	O
Ragg	O
to	O
be	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Murder	O
and	O
Robbery	O
,	O
which	O
neither	O
of	O
them	O
could	O
deny	O
upon	O
Trial	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
all	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
sworn	O
to	O
the	O
Indictment	O
of	O
the	O
Assault	O
and	O
Robbery	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Gough	O
,	O
committed	O
by	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Prisoners	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Gough	O
depos	O
'd	O
they	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
between	B-place
Holloway	I-place
and	I-place
the	I-place
Half	I-place
Way-House	I-place
,	O
took	O
away	O
his	O
Horse	O
and	O
all	O
his	O
Cloths	O
.	O
That	O
Thurland	O
took	O
his	O
Breeches	O
off	O
;	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
bound	O
and	O
thrown	O
into	O
a	O
Field	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
comfort	O
him	O
but	O
Promises	O
of	O
more	O
Company	O
;	O
Which	O
was	O
also	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
Isaac	O
Ragg	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
,	O
That	O
White	O
and	O
Chapman	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
(	O
Timothy	O
Dunn	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
)	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
were	O
concern	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
all	O
Guilty	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Then	O
came	O
on	O
the	O
Trial	O
of	O
Russel	O
,	O
White	O
and	O
Stent	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Burglary	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Barkley	O
and	O
receiving	O
the	O
stol'n	O
Goods	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Barkley	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
stole	O
;	O
and	O
Ragg	O
swore	O
he	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
it	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
Timothy	B-pers
Dunn	I-pers
,	O
That	O
they	O
watch	O
'd	O
Mrs.	O
Burkley	O
's	O
going	O
out	O
with	O
some	O
Linnen	O
.	O
(	O
as	O
she	O
used	O
to	O
do	O
about	O
that	O
Time	O
)	O
to	O
a	O
Member	O
of	O
Parliament	O
,	O
and	O
forc	O
'd	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
That	O
two	O
said	O
(	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
)	O
they	O
sold	O
to	O
Stent	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
had	O
done	O
others	O
several	O
times	O
before	O
,	O
using	O
the	O
Expression	O
which	O
they	O
had	O
stole	O
for	O
Her	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Chissel	O
and	O
a	O
Bayonet	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
;	O
which	O
Bayonet	O
Mrs.	O
Barkley	O
was	O
inform	O
'd	O
by	O
some	O
Mark	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
First	O
Regiment	O
of	O
Foot	O
Guards	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
and	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
a	O
Serjeant	O
,	O
she	O
discover	O
'd	O
Russel	O
,	O
who	O
discover	O
'd	O
Stent	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
,	O
House	O
being	O
Search	O
'd	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
there	O
.	O
Stent	O
denied	O
she	O
knew	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
,	O
the	O
rest	O
said	O
nothing	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
all	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
White	O
,	O
Thurland	O
,	O
Chapman	O
,	O
Russell	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Stent	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Priscilla	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
,	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
Reverend	O
John	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
D.D	O
.	O
and	O
Stealing	O
thence	O
a	O
Hat,7	O
Wiggs	O
,	O
1	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
Cassocks	O
,	O
value	O
8l	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
Day-time	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
very	O
clear	O
and	O
strong	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Muntsy	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
11s	O
.	O
1	O
Silver	O
Necklace	O
,	O
3	O
s.1	O
Silver	O
Locket	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
57	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wilks	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wilks	O
depos	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
his	O
Servants	O
and	O
worked	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
having	O
been	O
the	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
in	O
Spital	O
Fields	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
Home	O
,	O
found	O
his	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
were	O
all	O
gone	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
being	O
taken	O
about	O
3	O
Weeks	O
after	O
they	O
confes	O
'd	O
Fact	O
,	O
which	O
William	O
subscrib	O
'd	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
refus	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
However	O
upon	O
Trial	O
Muntsy	O
would	O
have	O
taken	O
it	O
all	O
upon	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
other	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
stolen	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
brought	O
them	O
both	O
in	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Kating	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Griffin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Perish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
11	O
Sheets,4	O
Diaper	O
Towels	O
,	O
9	O
Flaxen	O
Table-cloths	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
Diana	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
13th	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
Queen	O
:	O
But	O
no	O
body	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
,	O
being	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
5	O
.	O
Pistols	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
Mr.	O
Cross	O
depos	O
'd	O
his	O
Shop	O
was	O
shut	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
with	O
him	O
Men	O
being	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
coming	O
Home	O
,	O
found	O
his	O
Lock	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
gone	O
.	O
That	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Pistols	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
when	O
taken	O
.	O
(	O
These	O
Pistols	O
were	O
divided	O
amongst	O
that	O
Gang	O
that	O
murder	O
'd	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
)	O
However	O
,	O
the	O
Burglary	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
plain	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Traverse	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
an	O
Ewe	O
Sheep	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
A	O
Watchman	O
swore	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Sheep	O
on	O
his	O
Back	O
at	O
One	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
and	O
stopp	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
who	O
afterwards	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
stole	O
it	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
discover	O
'd	O
who	O
were	O
his	O
Confederates	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
,	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death,10	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Abbott	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hankerson	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Thurland	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Russell	I-pers
,	O
Priscilla	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand,21	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Floyd	I-pers
,	O
Martha	B-pers
Purdue	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Rhodes	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
Martha	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
Martha	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gee	I-pers
,	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Daws	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
James	O
,	O
Robinson	O
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Dikes	I-pers
,	O
Arnold	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Hathway	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Trimble	I-pers
,	O
Williams	B-pers
Giles	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Middle	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
Deborah	B-pers
Stent	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Muntsy	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt,8	O
,	O
R	O
-	O
M	O
-	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
Rachel	B-pers
Allison	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Colter	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Gardiner	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Perdy	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Macgrah	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Traverse	I-pers
.	O
Mary	O
Abbott	O
and	O
Priscilla	O
Spencer	O
pleaded	O
their	O
Bellies	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
being	O
impanell	O
'd	O
,	O
Mary	O
Abbott	O
was	O
found	O
quick	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
not	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
Lately	O
Publish	O
'd	O
The	O
London	O
new	O
Method	O
and	O
Art	O
of	O
Teaching	O
Children	O
to	O
spell	O
and	O
Read	O
;	O
so	O
as	O
they	O
may	O
,	O
without	O
the	O
Help	O
of	O
any	O
other	O
books	O
,	O
read	O
the	O
Bible	O
In	O
less	O
than	O
Twelve	O
Months	O
Note	O
,	O
This	O
Way	O
of	O
Teaching	O
approved	O
by	O
Most	O
School-Masters	O
as	O
the	O
best	O
.	O
Price	O
Bound	O
6d	O
.	O
with	O
great	O
allowanced	O
to	O
those	O
who	O
sell	O
or	O
give	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
Arithmetic	O
made	O
easie	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
New	O
Method	O
now	O
taught	O
ans	O
practis	O
'd	O
in	O
London	O
.	O
Wherein	O
the	O
Rules	O
of	O
that	O
necessary	O
Art	O
are	O
briefly	O
explain	O
'd	O
and	O
illustrated	O
with	O
such	O
Examples	O
,	O
as	O
may	O
suit	O
the	O
meanest	O
Capacity	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
desire	O
to	O
learn	O
it	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
a	O
succinct	O
Treatise	O
of	O
decimal	O
Fractions	O
,	O
with	O
compleat	O
Tables	O
,	O
Rules	O
and	O
Examples	O
demonstrating	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
like	O
not	O
extant	O
in	O
any	O
other	O
Treatise	O
of	O
this	O
Nature	O
.	O
By	O
John	O
Copelayd	O
,	O
Writing-Master	O
.	O
The	O
2d	O
Edition	O
,	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
The	O
Pen	O
's	O
Dexterity	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Ingenious	O
and	O
useful	O
Art	O
of	O
writing	O
Short-Hand	O
.	O
Containing	O
Twenty	O
Copper	O
Plates	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
letters	O
,	O
Characters	O
and	O
Contractions	O
used	O
therein	O
.	O
With	O
Rules	O
and	O
Directions	O
explaining	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
the	O
meanest	O
Capacity	O
.	O
By	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Rich	I-pers
.	O
Pr.1	O
s.	O
Maximum	O
in	O
Minimo	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Jer	O
.	O
Rich	O
's	O
Pen	O
's	O
Dexterity	O
compleated	O
,	O
Being	O
the	O
planest	O
and	O
easiest	O
Method	O
of	O
Writing	O
Short-Hand	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
are	O
added	O
.	O
The	O
Terms	O
of	O
the	O
Law	O
complear	O
in	O
Characters	O
at	O
length	O
,	O
Never	O
done	O
till	O
now	O
.	O
By	O
Samuel	B-pers
Botley	I-pers
.	O
The	O
whole	O
curiously	O
engrav	O
'd	O
on	O
Thirty	O
Copper	O
Plates	O
.	O
Pr.1	O
s.6	O
d.	O
All	O
Four	O
printed	O
for	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
Edmund	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
and	O
Crown	O
in	O
Lombard-Street	O
,	O
near	O
Stocks-Market	O
.	O
BOOKS	O
printed	O
for	O
Andrew	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Cross	O
Keys	O
and	O
Bible	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
.	O
THE	O
Second	O
Volume	O
of	O
the	O
History	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
Remarkable	O
Tryals	O
in	O
Great	O
Britain	O
and	O
Ireland	O
in	O
Capital	O
Cases	O
;	O
in	O
which	O
is	O
the	O
Tryal	O
of	O
Sir	O
Walter	O
Rileigh	O
,	O
the	O
Earl	O
of	O
Somerset	O
and	O
his	O
Lady	O
,	O
K.	O
Charl	O
's	O
the	O
First	O
,	O
Ec	O
.	O
Price	O
6	O
s.	O
Where	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
the	O
First	O
Volume	O
,	O
pr.6	O
s.	O
The	O
diverting	O
Works	O
of	O
the	O
Counters	O
of	O
D'Anois	O
,	O
Author	O
of	O
the	O
Ladies	O
Travels	O
into	O
Spain	O
:	O
Containing,1st	O
,	O
The	O
Memoirs	O
of	O
her	O
Own	O
Life	O
;	O
2dly	O
,	O
All	O
her	O
Spanish	O
Novels	O
and	O
Histories	O
;	O
3dly	O
,	O
Her	O
Letters	O
;	O
4thly	O
,	O
The	O
Tales	O
of	O
the	O
Fairies	O
:	O
In	O
three	O
Parts	O
,	O
illustrated	O
with	O
Cuts	O
.	O
pr.6	O
s.	O
Fourteen	O
Sermons	O
by	O
his	O
Grace	O
Sir	O
William	O
Daws	O
,	O
Lord	O
Archbishop	O
of	O
York	O
.	O
pr.1	O
s.6	O
d.	O
stitch	O
'd	O
2	O
s.	O
bound	O
.	O
Prayers	O
and	O
Meditations	O
Before	O
,	O
At	O
,	O
and	O
After	O
the	O
Sacrament	O
,	O
by	O
Mons	O
.	O
Drellingcourt	O
,	O
Author	O
of	O
the	O
Christian	O
's	O
Consolation	O
against	O
the	O
Fear	O
of	O
Death	O
.	O
pr.6	O
d.	O
stich	O
'd	O
9	O
d.	O
bound	O
.	O
The	O
Rules	O
of	O
the	O
Water-side	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
general	O
Practice	O
of	O
the	O
Customs	O
,	O
pr.2	O
s.	O
The	O
Arabian	O
Nights	O
Entertainments	O
;	O
consisting	O
of	O
1001	O
Stories	O
told	O
by	O
the	O
Sultaness	O
of	O
the	O
Indies	O
to	O
divert	O
the	O
Sultan	O
from	O
the	O
Execution	O
of	O
a	O
bloody	O
Vow	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
,	O
to	O
marry	O
a	O
Lady	O
every	O
Day	O
;	O
and	O
have	O
her	O
cut	O
off	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
in	O
8	O
Volumes	O
pr.11	O
s.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
against	O
the	O
Rebels	O
in	O
the	O
West	O
,	O
for	O
taking	O
Arms	O
under	O
the	O
D.	O
of	O
Monmouth	O
;	O
tried	O
before	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
Jefferies	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
with	O
a	O
compleat	O
List	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Persons	O
that	O
suffer	O
'd	O
.	O
pr.1	O
s.	O
A	O
General	O
History	O
of	O
Dreams	O
and	O
Visions	O
,	O
in	O
two	O
Parts	O
pr.2	O
s.6	O
d.	O
The	O
History	O
of	O
Genesis	O
;	O
containing	O
the	O
Lives	O
of	O
the	O
Patriarchs	O
;	O
with	O
40	O
Cuts	O
.	O
pr.1	O
s.	O
The	O
Art	O
of	O
Memory	O
,	O
a	O
Treatise	O
very	O
proper	O
for	O
those	O
that	O
are	O
to	O
speak	O
in	O
Publick	O
,	O
pr.1	O
s.	O
DAVID	O
POVEY	O
,	O
removed	O
from	O
Hatton	O
Garden	O
near	O
to	O
Exeter-Exchange	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
London	O
,	O
Operator	O
for	O
the	O
Teeth	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
the	O
Honour	O
to	O
clean	O
her	O
late	O
,	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Teeth	O
;	O
he	O
sells	O
a	O
pleasant	O
Dentrifice	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
King	O
Charles	O
II	O
constantly	O
used	O
.	O
It	O
makes	O
the	O
Teeth	O
as	O
white	O
as	O
Ivory	O
,	O
and	O
preserves	O
them	O
from	O
decaying	O
,	O
destroying	O
the	O
Scarvy	O
.	O
He	O
hath	O
a	O
Cephalick	O
which	O
certainly	O
cures	O
the	O
Tooth-Art	O
in	O
a	O
Minute	O
's	O
Time	O
,	O
beyond	O
any	O
person	O
in	O
England	O
.	O
If	O
the	O
Teeth	O
are	O
rotten	O
,	O
or	O
uneven	O
,	O
and	O
full	O
of	O
Holes	O
or	O
black	O
Specks	O
,	O
he	O
will	O
make	O
them	O
smooth	O
even	O
sound	O
,	O
and	O
white	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
no	O
Person	O
shall	O
distinguish	O
where	O
the	O
Defect	O
has	O
been	O
.	O
He	O
sets	O
in	O
Artificial	O
Teeth	O
so	O
easie	O
,	O
near	O
,	O
and	O
firm	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
need	O
not	O
be	O
removed	O
for	O
seven	O
Years	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
may	O
eat	O
with	O
them	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
with	O
their	O
former	O
,	O
and	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
distinguished	O
from	O
their	O
natural	O
ones	O
.	O
He	O
sells	O
a	O
pleasant	O
Water	O
,	O
that	O
prevents	O
any	O
Rottenness	O
from	O
seizing	O
the	O
Teeth	O
,	O
takes	O
all	O
Pains	O
and	O
Imposthumes	O
,	O
Cankers	O
or	O
Swellings	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Gums	O
,	O
and	O
fastens	O
loose	O
Teeth	O
,	O
which	O
several	O
Persons	O
of	O
Quality	O
and	O
others	O
know	O
to	O
be	O
true	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
sold	O
all	O
that	O
is	O
printed	O
here	O
to	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
Kings	O
,	O
Queens	O
,	O
Princes	O
,	O
Nobility	O
and	O
Gentry	O
in	O
England	O
,	O
since	O
King	O
Charles	O
II	O
.	O
dy	O
'd	O
and	O
before	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Good	O
of	O
the	O
Publick	O
.	O
WHereas	O
several	O
Gentlewomen	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
that	O
Sex	O
in	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
have	O
contracted	O
an	O
evil	O
Habit	O
of	O
Body	O
,	O
wherein	O
the	O
vicious	O
Humours	O
at	O
first	O
dispers	O
'd	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Whole	O
,	O
come	O
at	O
length	O
to	O
be	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
one	O
Part	O
or	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
times	O
,	O
for	O
Causes	O
too	O
long	O
to	O
be	O
here	O
mentioned	O
are	O
thrown	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Womb	O
,	O
occasioning	O
a	O
dangerous	O
.	O
Weakness	O
in	O
one	O
Part	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
neglected	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
turns	O
Cancerous	O
,	O
and	O
often	O
proves	O
Fatal	O
.	O
I	O
cure	O
the	O
Diabetes	O
when	O
given	O
over	O
by	O
all	O
other	O
Persons	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
to	O
acquaint	O
all	O
may	O
have	O
occasion	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Speedy	O
Relief	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
had	O
from	O
an	O
Experienc	O
'd	O
Midwife	O
,	O
dwelling	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Arms	O
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Smith	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
near	O
Exeter	O
Exchange	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
who	O
perform	O
'd	O
a	O
Cure	O
upon	O
a	O
Lady	O
at	O
the	O
Bath	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
given	O
over	O
by	O
the	O
Physicians	O
,	O
and	O
since	O
has	O
Cured	O
several	O
Gentlewomen	O
and	O
others	O
in	O
the	O
City	O
and	O
Suburbs	O
of	O
London	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
put	O
my	O
self	O
in	O
Publick	O
Print	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
satisfy	O
the	O
Afflicted	O
where	O
they	O
may	O
,	O
have	O
speedy	O
Relief	O
after	O
they	O
are	O
given	O
over	O
by	O
all	O
other	O
Persons	O
.	O
