TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
,	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
and	O
Thursday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
10th	O
and	O
11th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October,1716	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Third	O
Tear	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEfore	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
CHARLES	B-pers
PEERS	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
Parker	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Tracy	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
Names	O
were	O
as	O
followith	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
:	O
John	B-pers
Hazel	I-pers
Ebeneazer	B-pers
Ebbetson	I-pers
Jeremy	B-pers
Pierce	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Raper	I-pers
Simon	B-pers
Mayo	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Fielder	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Leppidge	I-pers
William	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
John	B-pers
Shanks	I-pers
James	B-pers
Man	I-pers
Joshita	B-pers
Fearry	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Giles	B-pers
Riddle	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bavand	I-pers
John	B-pers
Curtis	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Tomkins	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
William	B-pers
Giles	I-pers
Lawrence	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
William	B-pers
Clements	I-pers
James	B-pers
Kirby	I-pers
John	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
John	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
upon	O
the	O
Statute	O
made	O
the	O
First	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
present	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
for	O
Felony	O
,	O
for	O
unlawfully	O
,	O
riotously	O
and	O
tumultuously	O
assembling	O
upon	O
the	O
24th	O
Day	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Love	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bean	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Pruchase	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Price	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
(	O
who	O
were	O
all	O
since	O
Convicted	O
and	O
Executed	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Fact	O
,	O
)	O
and	O
with	O
diverse	O
other	O
Persons	O
to	O
the	O
Number	O
of	O
One	O
Hundred	O
and	O
upward	O
,	O
in	O
disturbance	O
of	O
the	O
the	O
Publick	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
feloniouslly	O
beginning	O
to	O
pull	O
down	O
and	O
to	O
demolish	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Read	I-pers
,	O
contrary	O
to	O
the	O
Form	O
of	O
the	O
Statute	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
John	B-pers
Boyle	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
lodged	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Read	O
's	O
Mug-house	O
for	O
some	O
Time	O
past	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
asked	O
to	O
give	O
account	O
what	O
their	O
Demeanor	O
usually	O
was	O
when	O
the	O
Company	O
which	O
used	O
the	O
House	O
met	O
together	O
,	O
he	O
answered	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
never	O
knew	O
the	O
Society	O
give	O
any	O
Provocation	O
or	O
Affront	O
to	O
any	O
Person	O
,	O
except	O
that	O
once	O
they	O
turned	O
a	O
Man	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
for	O
hissing	O
at	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Marlborough	O
's	O
Health	O
:	O
And	O
being	O
asked	O
,	O
whether	O
they	O
ever	O
drank	O
Confusion	O
to	O
any	O
Persons	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
any	O
Sort	O
or	O
Order	O
of	O
Men	O
;	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
That	O
he	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Confusion	O
drank	O
but	O
once	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
since	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
they	O
drank	O
Confusion	O
to	O
the	O
Ottoman	O
Attempts	O
against	O
Prince	O
Eugene	O
and	O
the	O
Empire	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
that	O
Effect	O
.	O
He	O
further	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Friday-Night	O
before	O
the	O
Day	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
a	O
Mob	O
gathered	O
about	O
the	O
Mug-house	O
,	O
whereupon	O
some	O
Gentlemen	O
sent	O
to	O
a	O
Mug-house	O
in	O
Tavistock-Street	O
to	O
some	O
of	O
their	O
Friends	O
,	O
who	O
immediately	O
came	O
and	O
disperst	O
the	O
Mob	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
no	O
Harm	O
was	O
done	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
only	O
a	O
few	O
Panes	O
of	O
Grass	O
were	O
broke	O
.	O
That	O
upon	O
Monday	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
a	O
Mob	O
began	O
to	O
gather	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
when	O
the	O
Society	O
was	O
assembled	O
;	O
that	O
one	O
Overs	O
,	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
with	O
some	O
Watchmen	O
,	O
and	O
drew	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Rink	O
before	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Mob	O
began	O
to	O
increase	O
very	O
fast	O
,	O
and	O
hiss	O
'd	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
as	O
they	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
out	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Witness	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
them	O
what	O
they	O
hiss	O
'd	O
at	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
threw	O
Stones	O
at	O
him	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
Windows	O
.	O
That	O
some	O
Time	O
after	O
one	O
Johnson	O
,	O
another	O
Constable	O
,	O
came	O
with	O
more	O
Watchmen	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
endeavour	O
to	O
disperse	O
the	O
Mob	O
,	O
but	O
encouraged	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
continued	O
to	O
throw	O
Stones	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
whilst	O
the	O
Constables	O
stood	O
by	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Coffee-Room	O
,	O
a	O
Stone	O
was	O
thrown	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Street	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
which	O
hit	O
him	O
upon	O
the	O
Leg	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
Constables	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
wondred	O
they	O
would	O
suffer	O
Stones	O
to	O
be	O
thrown	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
by	O
the	O
Mob	O
when	O
they	O
had	O
Power	O
enough	O
to	O
disperse	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
People	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
threw	O
the	O
Stones	O
from	O
above	O
and	O
broke	O
their	O
own	O
Windows	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
impossible	O
for	O
them	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Window	O
shutters	O
above	O
were	O
fast	O
shut	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
no	O
Stone	O
could	O
be	O
thrown	O
out	O
.	O
That	O
Mrs.	O
Read	O
offer	O
'd	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
a	O
Quart	O
of	O
strong	O
Ale	O
to	O
drink	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Health	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Constables	O
would	O
not	O
suffer	O
them	O
.	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Hucks	O
offered	O
them	O
a	O
Crown	O
to	O
drink	O
the	O
Kings	O
's	O
Health	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Constables	O
refused	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
given	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
made	O
him	O
return	O
it	O
.	O
That	O
all	O
this	O
while	O
the	O
Mob	O
continued	O
throwing	O
Stones	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
Windows	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
was	O
scarce	O
a	O
whole	O
Pane	O
left	O
below	O
Stairs	O
;	O
whereupon	O
one	O
Badcock	O
,	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
read	O
the	O
Proclamation	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Mob	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
hiss	O
'd	O
at	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
very	O
soon	O
after	O
the	O
Proclamation	O
was	O
read	O
the	O
Constables	O
and	O
Watchmen	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Mob	O
went	O
away	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
:	O
And	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
made	O
the	O
Mob	O
go	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Constables	O
and	O
Watch	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
stay	O
after	O
the	O
Constables	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
more	O
afraid	O
of	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
than	O
of	O
the	O
Constables	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
about	O
Six	O
a	O
Clock	O
the	O
mob	O
began	O
to	O
gather	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
Stones	O
at	O
the	O
Windows	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
persuade	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
quiet	O
and	O
to	O
do	O
no	O
more	O
Mischief	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
received	O
two	O
Blows	O
on	O
his	O
Head	O
by	O
Stones	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
great	O
Swelling	O
in	O
his	O
Forehead	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
cut	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
him	O
bleed	O
very	O
much	O
.	O
That	O
thereupon	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
brought	O
out	O
a	O
Stick	O
and	O
drove	O
them	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
,	O
but	O
struck	O
no	O
body	O
but	O
the	O
Man	O
who	O
hit	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Stone	O
.	O
That	O
afterwards	O
the	O
Mob	O
encreasing	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
Number	O
being	O
come	O
from	O
Fleetstreet	B-place
arm	O
'd	O
with	O
Sticks	O
,	O
the	O
Witness	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Read	O
and	O
a	O
Grenadier	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
drove	O
the	O
Mob	O
to	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
over	O
power	O
'd	O
they	O
were	O
forced	O
to	O
retire	O
again	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Mob	O
advanced	O
in	O
great	O
Numbers	O
,	O
with	O
Daniel	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
at	O
their	O
Head	O
,	O
crying	O
Down	O
with	O
the	O
Mug-house	O
.	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Read	O
and	O
the	O
Grenadier	O
presented	O
their	O
Pieces	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Minutes	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
them	O
stand	O
off	O
and	O
have	O
a	O
care	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
pressing	O
on	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Read	O
and	O
the	O
Grenadier	O
fir	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
Vaughan	O
fell	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Mob	O
coming	O
on	O
still	O
with	O
great	O
Fury	O
,	O
the	O
Witness	O
and	O
another	O
Man	O
consulted	O
together	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Barricade	O
upon	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
Means	O
the	O
upper	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
preserved	O
till	O
such	O
time	O
as	O
the	O
Mob	O
were	O
disperst	O
by	O
the	O
Guards	O
:	O
But	O
that	O
below	O
Stairs	O
the	O
Windows	O
and	O
sashes	O
were	O
all	O
broke	O
to	O
pieces	O
,	O
the	O
Bar	O
and	O
the	O
Cupboard	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Post	O
to	O
which	O
the	O
Coffee-Mill	O
was	O
fixt	O
,	O
were	O
broke	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
the	O
Benches	O
and	O
Wainscoat	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
look	O
'd	O
just	O
like	O
a	O
House	O
that	O
was	O
pulling	O
down	O
;	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
broke	O
to	O
pieces	O
and	O
destroy	O
'd	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Arrowsmith	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Mug-house	O
upon	O
Monday	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
;	O
That	O
about	O
8	O
or	O
9	O
'	O
a-Clock	O
the	O
Mob	O
insulted	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
as	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
out	O
,	O
hisshing	O
and	O
throwing	O
Stones	O
at	O
them	O
.	O
That	O
a	O
Constable	O
and	O
some	O
Watchmen	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
another	O
Constable	O
and	O
Watchman	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
fir	O
'd	O
rathet	O
to	O
encrease	O
the	O
Mob	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
bid	O
the	O
Mob	O
be	O
quiet	O
and	O
go	O
away	O
,	O
or	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
worse	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Constable	O
took	O
their	O
part	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
Windows	O
were	O
broke	O
by	O
the	O
People	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
the	O
Witness	O
go	O
away	O
from	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
House	O
ought	O
to	O
be	O
pull	O
'd	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
the	O
Mob	O
gathered	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
Dirt	O
and	O
Stones	O
at	O
the	O
Windows	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
two	O
Brickbats	O
and	O
broke	O
the	O
Windows	O
with	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
bid	O
her	O
be	O
gone	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
threw	O
another	O
,	O
crying	O
out	O
High	O
Church	O
and	O
Ormond	O
,	O
Damn	O
all	O
the	O
Hanoverians	O
,	O
Down	O
with	O
the	O
Presbyterians	O
.	O
That	O
thereupon	O
he	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
bringing	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
but	O
one	O
Delander	O
a	O
Watchmaker	O
made	O
several	O
Strokes	O
at	O
the	O
Witness	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
by	O
some	O
among	O
the	O
Mob	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
was	O
rescu	O
'd	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
getting	O
up	O
again	O
pursued	O
Delander	O
towards	O
the	O
Water-side	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Mug-house	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Mob	O
increasing	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
told	O
his	O
Name	O
and	O
where	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
,	O
was	O
let	O
go	O
.	O
That	O
afterwards	O
the	O
Witness	O
,	O
Mr.Read	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
,	O
drove	O
the	O
Mob	O
back	O
to	O
Fleet-street	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
over	O
powered	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
forced	O
to	O
retreat	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Mob	O
prest	O
upon-them	O
crying	O
out	O
High	O
Church	O
and	O
Ormond	O
,	O
Down	O
with	O
the	O
Mug-house	O
.	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Freebody	O
a	O
Constable	O
read	O
the	O
Proclamation	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
serving	O
only	O
to	O
enrage	O
the	O
Mob	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Read	O
and	O
the	O
Witness	O
fired	O
their	O
Pieces	O
,	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
bid	O
them	O
stand	O
off	O
and	O
have	O
a	O
care	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
then	O
retired	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
defended	O
it	O
till	O
some	O
People	O
had	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
Windows	O
and	O
thrust	O
the	O
Witness	O
into	O
the	O
Street	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
,	O
they	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
drag	O
'd	O
him	O
along	O
the	O
Chanel	O
,	O
and	O
beat	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Women	O
struck	O
him	O
over	O
the	O
Head	O
with	O
their	O
Pattens	O
till	O
they	O
cut	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Skull	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
murdered	O
but	O
by	O
the	O
Assistance	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Cheesbrook	O
the	O
Clerk	O
of	O
the	O
Artillery	O
Company	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Castle	O
Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
his	O
Wounds	O
drest	O
.	O
That	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
the	O
two	O
Constables	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
seized	O
him	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
another	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
the	O
satisfaction	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
Hang	O
'd	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
told	O
them	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
satisfaction	O
to	O
know	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
Hang	O
'd	O
that	O
Day	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Read	O
's	O
House	O
again	O
that	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Windows	O
broke	O
and	O
the	O
inside	O
pull	O
'd	O
to	O
pieces	O
.	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Read	O
's	O
House	O
on	O
Monday	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
like	O
Account	O
as	O
the	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
of	O
the	O
Proceedings	O
that	O
Night	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
staid	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
all	O
Night	O
,	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Read	O
's	O
desire	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Defence	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
:	O
That	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
the	O
Mob	O
gathered	O
again	O
about	O
Seven	O
or	O
Eight	O
a	O
Clock	O
.	O
That	O
a	O
Woman	O
came	O
by	O
,	O
Crying	O
,	O
Damn	O
all	O
the	O
Presbyterians	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
the	O
Windows	O
with	O
Brick-bats	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
Grenadier	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
,	O
Delander	O
rescued	O
her	O
from	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
imediately	O
made	O
off	O
towards	O
the	O
Waterside	O
:	O
That	O
the	O
Witness	O
and	O
the	O
Grenadier	O
pursuing	O
him	O
seized	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
begg	O
'd	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
exposed	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
his	O
utter	O
Ruin	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Mug-House	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
kept	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
was	O
let	O
go	O
:	O
That	O
the	O
Mob	O
growing	O
very	O
strong	O
the	O
Proclamation	O
was	O
read	O
by	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
People	O
in	O
the	O
Mug-House	O
,	O
huzza	O
'd	O
,	O
King	O
George	O
for	O
ever	O
;	O
But	O
the	O
Mob	O
advanced	O
,	O
crying	O
,	O
High-church	O
and	O
Ormond	O
,	O
No	O
King	O
George	O
,	O
No	O
Hanoverians	O
;	O
Down	O
with	O
the	O
Mug-House	O
,	O
throwing	O
Stones	O
and	O
Sticks	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
breaking	O
the	O
Windows	O
to	O
pieces	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
heard	O
Vaughan	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
afterwards	O
killed	O
)	O
cry	O
fall	O
on	O
brave	O
Boys	O
,	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Ormond	O
is	O
landed	O
in	O
the	O
West	O
,	O
with	O
20000	O
.	O
Men	O
,	O
others	O
said	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Berwick	O
and	O
others	O
the	O
Lord	O
Tinmouth	O
:	O
That	O
after	O
Mr.	O
Read	O
had	O
fired	O
,	O
the	O
Witness	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
Barricade	O
,	O
which	O
probably	O
prevented	O
their	O
being	O
all	O
killed	O
;	O
that	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
up	O
Stairs	O
;	O
he	O
heard	O
great	O
clattering	O
and	O
breaking	O
of	O
the	O
Wainscot	O
and	O
Goods	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
a	O
Black	O
Patch	O
upon	O
his	O
Nose	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
Five	O
or	O
Six	O
Minutes	O
,	O
very	O
busy	O
,	O
breaking	O
the	O
Sashes	O
and	O
Frames	O
of	O
the	O
Windows	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
an	O
instrument	O
like	O
a	O
Butcher	O
's	O
Cleaver	O
with	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
cutting	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Side	O
Posts	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
joined	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
in	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Cries	O
.	O
Mr.	O
James	B-pers
Harbottle	I-pers
Deposed	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
that	O
Morning	O
at	O
Holbourn-Bridge	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
Mob	O
passing	O
along	O
with	O
Sticks	O
upon	O
their	O
Shoulders	O
who	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
pull	O
down	O
the	O
Mug-House	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
he	O
follow	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Sticks	O
delivered	O
to	O
them	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Nichols	O
's	O
a	O
Soapboilers	O
,	O
by	B-place
Holbourn-Bridge	I-place
;	I-place
That	I-place
from	I-place
thence	I-place
they	I-place
went	I-place
down	I-place
Shoe-Lane	I-place
,	O
and	O
at	O
a	O
Brasier	O
's	O
in	O
Shoe-Lane	O
,	O
more	O
Sticks	O
were	O
delivered	O
them	O
.	O
That	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
an	O
Alley	O
by	O
Adam	O
's	O
the	O
Cook	O
's	O
in	O
Shoe-Lane	O
,	O
they	O
distributed	O
the	O
Sticks	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
heard	O
them	O
say	O
,	O
come	O
Boys	O
,	O
here	O
are	O
Sticks	O
enough	O
:	O
That	O
thereupon	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Mug-House	O
,	O
and	O
acquainted	O
them	O
with	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Proclamation	O
was	O
read	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
prest	O
forwards	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
afterwards	O
beat	O
back	O
again	O
by	O
the	O
Grenadier	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
growing	O
stronger	O
beat	O
back	O
the	O
Grenadier	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
others	O
who	O
were	O
in	O
defence	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
throwing	O
Stones	O
and	O
Sticks	O
in	O
great	O
numbers	O
at	O
them	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Robins	O
depos	O
'd	O
That	O
on	O
Monday	O
Night	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
great	O
Crowd	O
of	O
People	O
at	O
the	O
Mug-house	O
Door	O
,	O
who	O
hiss	O
'd	O
at	O
and	O
abused	O
every	O
Body	O
that	O
went	O
in	O
or	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Mug-house	O
,	O
but	O
knew	O
no	O
body	O
there	O
;	O
however	O
he	O
durst	O
not	O
venture	O
out	O
immediately	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
the	O
Stones	O
that	O
were	O
flung	O
by	O
the	O
Mob	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
having	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
,	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Castle	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Fleetstreet	O
.	O
That	O
about	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
he	O
went	O
again	O
to	O
the	O
Mug-house	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
brought	O
a	O
Blunderbuss	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
People	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
prodigious	O
Mob	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
Shoe-lane	O
.	O
That	O
a	O
great	O
Mob	O
appeared	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Witness	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
the	O
Square	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
there	O
till	O
the	O
Piece	O
went	O
off	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Windows	O
of	O
the	O
Mug-house	O
broke	O
to	O
Pieces	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Mob	O
threw	O
Ropes	O
over	O
the	O
Sign-Irons	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
with	O
such	O
Violence	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
pull	O
down	O
the	O
Sign	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
the	O
Front	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
would	O
come	O
down	O
and	O
do	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Mischief	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Sticks	O
deliver	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Mob	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Druggist	O
's	O
House	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Salisbury	O
Court	O
in	O
Fleetstreet	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
he	O
saw	O
several	O
single	O
Sticks	O
delivered	O
to	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
Window	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Michael	B-pers
Burrel	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
Monday	O
Night	O
he	O
going	O
by	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
Salisbury-Court	O
in	O
Fleetstreet	O
,	O
saw	O
a	O
great	O
Mob	O
in	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
told	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
pull	O
down	O
the	O
Mug-house	O
;	O
and	O
going	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
two	O
Constables	O
and	O
several	O
Watchmen	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
before	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
who	O
encouraged	O
the	O
Mob	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
they	O
were	O
able	O
to	O
have	O
dispers	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
Mind	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
That	O
Stones	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
Baskets	O
to	O
the	O
Mob	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
Pound	O
Weight	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
down	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
Constables	O
and	O
Watchmen	O
who	O
suffered	O
the	O
Mob	O
to	O
throw	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
That	O
when	O
the	O
Constables	O
and	O
Watchmen	O
went	O
off	O
the	O
Mob	O
presently	O
after	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
apprehending	O
(	O
as	O
he	O
believed	O
)	O
more	O
Danger	O
from	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
whom	O
they	O
had	O
abused	O
,	O
than	O
from	O
the	O
Constables	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
he	O
went	O
there	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
great	O
Mob	O
breaking	O
the	O
Windows	O
and	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
to	O
pieces	O
;	O
and	O
heard	O
them	O
say	O
,	O
Just	O
thus	O
will	O
we	O
pull	O
King	O
George	O
from	O
his	O
Crown	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
none	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Rich	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
mention	O
'd	O
many	O
of	O
the	O
Particulars	O
of	O
the	O
Riot	O
,	O
both	O
on	O
Monday	O
Night	O
and	O
Tuesday	O
Morning	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
with	O
the	O
former	O
Witnesses	O
.	O
That	O
after	O
the	O
Mob	O
had	O
beat	O
the	O
Grenadier	O
and	O
the	O
others	O
with	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Mug	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
bring	O
out	O
two	O
Bottles	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
over	O
against	O
the	O
Swan	O
Ale	O
house	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
and	O
several	O
others	O
drank	O
the	O
Pretender	O
's	O
Health	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
King	O
James	O
the	O
Third	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
answered	O
with	O
Huzza	O
's	O
by	O
the	O
People	O
at	O
the	O
Swan	O
Windows	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Carleton	O
Smith	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
by	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
to	O
Salisbury-Court	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
Morning	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
doing	O
there	O
.	O
That	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Crowd	O
so	O
great	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
in	O
Fleetstreet	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
went	O
thro	O
'	O
St	O
.	O
Brides	O
Passage	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
two	O
Parties	O
engaging	O
and	O
Daniel	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
deceased	O
at	O
the	O
Head	O
of	O
the	O
Mob	O
.	O
That	O
as	O
the	O
Witness	O
was	O
getting	O
into	O
the	O
said	O
St	O
.	O
Brides	O
Passage	O
to	O
save	O
himself	O
,	O
Vaughan	O
was	O
shot	O
;	O
and	O
fell	O
just	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
presently	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
great	O
Noise	O
,	O
and	O
rashing	O
of	O
Boards	O
breaking	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
And	O
then	O
he	O
thought	O
high	O
time	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
inform	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
what	O
was	O
doing	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
that	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
committed	O
by	O
his	O
Lordship	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
then	O
a	O
Patch	O
upon	O
his	O
Nose	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Badcock	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
being	O
informed	O
on	O
Monday	O
Night	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Design	O
to	O
pull	O
down	O
the	O
Mug-house	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
desired	O
to	O
go	O
thither	O
to	O
keep	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
accordingly	O
did	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
great	O
Mob	O
about	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Constable	O
and	O
some	O
Watchmen	O
before	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Mob	O
stung	O
Stones	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
keep	O
the	O
Peace	O
and	O
to	O
disperse	O
the	O
Mob	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
answered	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Disturbance	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
made	O
by	O
the	O
People	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Hour	O
(	O
10	O
a	O
Clock	O
)	O
was	O
not	O
come	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Mob	O
continuing	O
to	O
throw	O
Stones	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Johnson	O
(	O
another	O
Constable	O
)	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
20	O
Watchmen	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Witness	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
wondred	O
he	O
would	O
suffer	O
the	O
People	O
to	O
throw	O
Stones	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
insult	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
acquainting	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
himself	O
was	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
offering	O
to	O
assist	O
him	O
in	O
dispersing	O
the	O
Mob	O
.	O
But	O
Johnson	O
answer	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
(	O
the	O
Witness	O
)	O
was	O
no	O
Constable	O
of	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
nor	O
of	O
that	O
Ward	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
no	O
Stones	O
thrown	O
but	O
what	O
were	O
thrown	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
impossible	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Shutters	O
were	O
fast	O
shut	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
nothing	O
could	O
be	O
thrown	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Windows	O
.	O
And	O
then	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Witness	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
pulled	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
That	O
afterwards	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
often	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Stair-head	O
to	O
hearken	O
whether	O
the	O
Noise	O
encreased	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
And	O
after	O
some	O
time	O
finding	O
it	O
very	O
great	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
ventured	O
into	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
read	O
the	O
Proclamation	O
;	O
and	O
during	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
reading	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Mob	O
threw	O
Stones	O
and	O
Dirt	O
so	O
thick	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
turn	O
his	O
Back	O
to	O
them	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
receiving	O
Mischief	O
from	O
them	O
.	O
That	O
presently	O
after	O
reading	O
the	O
Proclamation	O
,	O
the	O
Constables	O
,	O
and	O
Watchmen	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Mob	O
went	O
away	O
almost	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gott	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
there	O
;	O
That	O
he	O
took	O
particular	O
Notice	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
black	O
square	O
Patch	O
upon	O
his	O
Nose	O
;	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
Stick	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
he	O
broke	O
the	O
Glass	O
and	O
Sashes	O
or	O
Frames	O
of	O
the	O
Windows	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
active	O
and	O
violent	O
in	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
That	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
Report	O
that	O
the	O
Guards	O
were	O
coming	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
off	O
towards	O
Water-lane	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
proving	O
false	O
,	O
he	O
returned	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
to	O
work	O
again	O
with	O
the	O
same	O
Fury	O
as	O
before	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bone	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
Stick	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
very	O
active	O
among	O
the	O
Mob	O
,	O
and	O
breaking	O
the	O
Goods	O
that	O
were	O
thrown	O
into	O
the	O
Street	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Newell	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
among	O
the	O
Mob	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
Morning	O
;	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
black	O
Patch	O
upon	O
his	O
Nose	O
;	O
That	O
after	O
the	O
Proclamation	O
was	O
read	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
advance	O
towards	O
the	O
Mug-house	O
with	O
a	O
Stick	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
afterwards	O
chopping	O
the	O
Frame	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
with	O
something	O
like	O
a	O
Butcher	O
's	O
Cleaver	O
.	O
That	O
during	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
Mob	O
,	O
the	O
general	O
Cry	O
among	O
them	O
was	O
,	O
High	O
Church	O
and	O
Ormond	O
,	O
No	O
Hannoverians	O
,	O
No	O
King	O
George	O
,	O
Down	O
with	O
the	O
Mug-house	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
join	O
with	O
the	O
Mob	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
coming	O
through	O
the	O
Court	O
accidentally	O
in	O
his	O
Way	O
from	O
Dinner	O
out	O
of	O
Shoe-Lane	O
to	O
his	O
Place	O
of	O
Work	O
;	O
and	O
denied	O
his	O
being	O
in	O
Read	O
's	O
House	O
:	O
Then	O
he	O
called	O
abundance	O
of	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
all	O
heard	O
,	O
The	O
First	O
swore	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
Blow	O
on	O
the	O
Face	O
which	O
occasioned	O
the	O
Patch	O
.	O
The	O
Second	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
put	O
the	O
Patch	O
upon	O
his	O
Nose	O
.	O
The	O
Third	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
dined	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
in	O
Shoe-Lane	O
with	O
the	O
Patch	O
upon	O
his	O
Nose	O
;	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
about	O
One	O
a-Clock	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
gave	O
an	O
Account	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
some	O
from	O
his	O
Birth	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
then	O
behav	O
'd	O
himself	O
well	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
gave	O
any	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Character	O
for	O
Three	O
or	O
Four	O
Years	O
past	O
.	O
But	O
nothing	O
of	O
all	O
this	O
Evidence	O
serving	O
to	O
clear	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
but	O
rather	O
to	O
confirm	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Beaver	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Eldridge	I-pers
,	O
Hester	B-pers
Stibbs	I-pers
,	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Hornsby	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Anne	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Riot	O
,	O
in	O
assembling	O
themselves	O
with	O
diverse	O
other	O
Persons	O
in	O
a	O
Riotous	O
Manner	O
under	O
a	O
Pretence	O
of	O
celebrating	O
in	O
a	O
publick	O
and	O
insulting	O
Manner	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bean	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Malefactor	O
convicted	O
last	O
Sessions	O
for	O
Felony	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
the	O
First	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
and	O
executed	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
open	O
Contempt	O
of	O
the	O
Government	O
and	O
the	O
Laws	O
of	O
the	O
Land	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Carleton	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Friday	O
before	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
having	O
Information	O
that	O
a	O
Procession	O
was	O
intended	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
the	O
next	O
Sunday	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
Number	O
of	O
Persons	O
who	O
were	O
to	O
be	O
drest	O
with	O
White	O
Hoods	O
and	O
Favours	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
walk	O
in	O
that	O
Manner	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
principal	O
Streets	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
his	O
Lordship	O
gave	O
him	O
Orders	O
to	O
enquire	O
diligently	O
into	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
endeavour	O
to	O
find	O
out	O
where	O
they	O
who	O
compos	O
'd	O
it	O
were	O
assembled	O
;	O
and	O
about	O
Nine	O
a	O
Clock	O
that	O
Morning	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
great	O
Crowd	O
of	O
People	O
(	O
near	O
a	O
Thousand	O
)	O
in	O
Salisbury	B-place
Court	I-place
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
he	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
acquaint	O
the	O
Train	O
'd	O
Bands	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
posted	O
at	O
Bridewell	O
;	O
thereupon	O
they	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Multitude	O
and	O
bid	O
them	O
disperse	O
;	O
which	O
signifying	O
but	O
little	O
,	O
they	O
drove	O
them	O
away	O
by	O
Force	O
.	O
That	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
Search	O
of	O
them	O
again	O
,	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
imagined	O
they	O
were	O
;	O
and	O
about	O
Three	O
a	O
Clock	O
saw	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
Concourse	O
of	O
People	O
at	O
the	O
farther	O
End	O
of	O
Water-lane	B-place
;	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
proper	O
to	O
go	O
too	O
near	O
them	O
,	O
being	O
alone	O
,	O
lest	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
discover	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
inform	O
'd	O
himself	O
of	O
their	O
Motions	O
by	O
another	O
Observer	O
:	O
Then	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Captain	O
of	O
the	O
Train	O
'd	O
Bands	O
,	O
who	O
sent	O
a	O
Detachment	O
to	O
disperse	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
to	O
Black	B-place
Fryars	I-place
;	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
follow	O
'd	O
them	O
and	O
saw	O
them	O
upon	O
the	O
Water	O
in	O
two	O
Boats	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
that	O
in	O
which	O
were	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
had	O
put	O
off	O
some	O
Time	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
away	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
Train	O
'd	O
Bands	O
level	O
their	O
Pieces	O
to	O
make	O
that	O
Boat	O
bring	O
to	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
fit	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
.	O
That	O
Beaver	O
jump	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Boat	O
into	O
the	O
Water	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
Escape	O
;	O
but	O
was	O
retaken	O
.	O
The	O
Men	O
had	O
White	O
Gloves	O
and	O
Favours	O
;	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Women	O
White	O
Favours	O
,	O
White	O
Sarsenet-Hoods	O
,	O
and	O
White	O
Gloves	O
;	O
others	O
had	O
no	O
Favours	O
.	O
That	O
all	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
then	O
carried	O
before	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
upon	O
Examination	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
Church	O
.	O
Mr.	O
John	O
Hill	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
with	O
the	O
Captain	O
of	O
the	O
Train	O
'd	O
Bands	O
that	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
came	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
Multitude	O
of	O
People	O
in	O
a	O
Procession	O
in	O
Water-Lane	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
a	O
Detachment	O
was	O
order	O
'd	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
to	O
observe	O
their	O
Motions	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
them	O
take	O
a	O
Boat	O
at	O
Black-Fryars-Stairs	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
for	O
them	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
other	O
being	O
ready	O
,	O
he	O
hastned	O
to	O
the	O
Officer	O
of	O
the	O
Train	O
'd	O
Bands	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
overtake	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
before	O
they	O
could	O
get	O
off	O
,	O
who	O
therefore	O
march	O
'd	O
with	O
all	O
Expedition	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
just	O
as	O
they	O
had	O
put	O
off	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
jumpt	O
into	O
the	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Boat-rope	O
and	O
haul	O
'd	O
it	O
ashore	O
.	O
That	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
others	O
with	O
them	O
dress	O
'd	O
after	O
the	O
same	O
Manner	O
who	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
discharg	O
'd	O
,	O
it	O
appearing	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
at	O
Bean	O
's	O
Funeral	O
with	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
but	O
were	O
invited	O
and	O
allur	O
'd	O
into	O
this	O
Procession	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
Lieutenant	O
Blackwell	B-pers
swore	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
he	O
march	O
'd	O
under	O
Captain	O
Kelson	B-pers
in	O
the	O
Train	O
'd	O
Bands	O
;	O
who	O
having	O
Notice	O
of	O
the	O
Design	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Procession	O
,	O
as	O
had	O
been	O
mention	O
'd	O
,	O
commanded	O
him	O
to	O
march	O
with	O
the	O
greatest	O
Expedition	O
,	O
and	O
overtake	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
coming	O
to	O
Water-Lane	O
,	O
he	O
receiv	O
'd	O
Information	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Mob	O
.	O
who	O
hiss	O
'd	O
at	O
,	O
and	O
shov	O
'd	O
his	O
Men	O
,	O
hollowing	O
for	O
Joy	O
of	O
their	O
Escape	O
,	O
and	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
They	O
are	O
gone	O
,	O
They	O
are	O
gone	O
.	O
But	O
Mr.	O
Hill	O
bringing	O
him	O
Advice	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
still	O
come	O
up	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
before	O
another	O
Boat	O
could	O
be	O
ready	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
off	O
,	O
he	O
pursu	O
'd	O
his	O
March	O
to	O
Black-Fryars-Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
They	O
all	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
excuse	O
themselves	O
to	O
him	O
by	O
saying	O
,	O
We	O
have	O
done	O
no	O
Harm	O
;	O
Ca	O
n't	O
we	O
go	O
where	O
we	O
will	O
with	O
our	O
own	O
Favours	O
,	O
and	O
such	O
like	O
.	O
He	O
further	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
receiv	O
'd	O
Information	O
that	O
the	O
Procession	O
was	O
to	O
consist	O
of	O
2	O
or	O
300	O
People	O
dress	O
'd	O
like	O
these	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
to	O
St.	O
Septebres	O
Church	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
a	O
Turn	O
round	O
by	O
all	O
the	O
Mug-houses	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
to	O
St	O
.	O
Brides	O
Church	O
yard	O
where	O
Bean	O
was	O
buried	O
,	O
to	O
commemorate	O
him	O
:	O
which	O
being	O
a	O
most	O
infamous	O
Contrivance	O
to	O
disturb	O
the	O
Peace	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Government	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
open	O
Defiance	O
of	O
the	O
Laws	O
of	O
the	O
Land	O
,	O
he	O
thought	O
it	O
his	O
Duty	O
to	O
give	O
Notice	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
;	O
for	O
which	O
Service	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Leaders	O
of	O
the	O
Party	O
had	O
since	O
arrested	O
him	O
in	O
an	O
Action	O
of	O
50	O
l.	O
Captain	O
Kelson	B-pers
swore	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
Lieutenant	O
Blackwell	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
informed	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Procession	O
a	O
Day	O
or	O
2	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
his	O
turn	O
to	O
march	O
that	O
Day	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
together	O
to	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
's	O
,	O
to	O
acquaint	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
and	O
receive	O
his	O
Orders	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
his	O
Lordship	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
to	O
his	O
Major	O
for	O
Orders	O
to	O
raise	O
his	O
company	O
by	O
7	O
a	O
Clock	O
that	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
,	O
those	O
he	O
already	O
had	O
being	O
to	O
meet	O
at	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
accordingly	O
did	O
and	O
was	O
upon	O
Guard	O
with	O
his	O
Company	O
by	O
9	O
;	O
and	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
2	O
Constables	O
(	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
Johnson	O
,	O
who	O
encourag	O
'd	O
the	O
Riot	O
at	O
the	O
Mug	O
house	O
in	O
Salisbury-Court	O
)	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
why	O
he	O
suffer	O
'd	O
such	O
a	O
Mob	O
in	O
the	O
Streets	O
,	O
having	O
a	O
Power	O
and	O
Instructions	O
sufficient	O
to	O
disperse	O
them	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
order	O
'd	O
a	O
Detachment	O
to	O
asist	O
the	O
Constables	O
in	O
the	O
Performance	O
of	O
their	O
Office	O
(	O
according	O
to	O
his	O
Lordshi'ps	O
Directions	O
)	O
and	O
afterwards	O
another	O
with	O
his	O
Lieutenant	O
to	O
pursue	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Robinson	B-pers
Swore	I-pers
,	O
That	O
being	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
desired	O
by	O
Lieutenant	O
Blackwell	O
the	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
before	O
,	O
to	O
accompany	O
him	O
to	O
Salisbury-Court	O
that	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
Detachment	O
to	O
Black-Friars	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
charg	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
Manner	O
before	O
depos	O
'd	O
;	O
who	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
done	O
no	O
Harm	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
chosen	O
the	O
By-Ways	O
to	O
prevent	O
giving	O
Offence	O
.	O
He	O
also	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
Hundreds	O
of	O
People	O
through	O
which	O
they	O
pass	O
'd	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
very	O
rude	O
,	O
violent	O
,	O
and	O
tumultuous	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
Men	O
,	O
Beaver	O
and	O
Eldridge	O
,	O
said	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
intimately	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
late	O
Bean	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
invited	O
to	O
his	O
Burial	O
by	O
his	O
Mother	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
they	O
agreed	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
also	O
invited	O
,	O
to	O
Church	O
in	O
their	O
Favours	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Funeral	O
Ornaments	O
,	O
as	O
was	O
usual	O
in	O
such	O
Cases	O
;	O
and	O
neither	O
thought	O
nor	O
intended	O
to	O
give	O
Offence	O
;	O
and	O
humbly	O
hop	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Court	O
would	O
consider	O
their	O
Youth	O
and	O
inexperience	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
punish	O
that	O
for	O
a	O
Crime	O
which	O
was	O
never	O
intended	O
by	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
they	O
all	O
said	O
too	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
invited	O
to	O
the	O
Burial	O
,	O
and	O
Stibbs	O
said	O
she	O
made	O
an	O
Excuse	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
Aunt	O
,	O
to	O
her	O
Master	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
Lane	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
Bean	O
's	O
Fellow	O
Servant	O
;	O
and	O
Hornsby	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
liv	O
'd	O
once	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Court	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
And	O
that	O
they	O
furnish	O
'd	O
themselves	O
with	O
what	O
Ornaments	O
they	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
they	O
had	O
committed	O
no	O
Offence	O
,	O
nor	O
done	O
any	O
thing	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
usual	O
.	O
And	O
all	O
of	O
them	O
own	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
what	O
they	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
was	O
in	O
Respect	O
to	O
Bean	O
's	O
Memory	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Men	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
but	O
Seven	O
or	O
Eight	O
Couple	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
Swore	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
Twenty	O
or	O
Thirty	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
replied	O
,	O
the	O
rest	O
did	O
not	O
belong	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
he	O
know	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
thought	O
they	O
might	O
belong	O
to	O
another	O
Funeral	O
,	O
which	O
happen	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
Evening	O
in	O
St	O
.	O
Brides	O
Church-Yard	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Lord	O
Parker	O
summ	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
Evidence	O
;	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
Considering	O
,	O
brought	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Haines	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
several	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Linnen	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
different	O
Persons	O
;	O
but	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
appearing	O
to	O
prosecute	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
6	O
Muslin	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Muslin	O
Aprons	O
7	O
s.7	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Hyon	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3rd	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
being	O
produc	O
'd	O
to	O
support	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Broome	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
Huckaback	O
Table-cloth	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Holford	I-pers
,	O
and	O
1	O
Holland	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Frances	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
Instant	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Goods	O
abovemention	O
'd	O
were	O
hanging	O
upon	O
a	O
Line	O
on	O
the	O
Leads	O
to	O
dry	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
accidentally	O
miss	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
not	O
having	O
Time	O
to	O
make	O
off	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
left	O
the	O
Table-cloth	O
wrapt	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Sleeve	O
of	O
the	O
Shift	O
upon	O
the	O
Leads	O
,	O
and	O
jumpt	O
into	O
a	O
Garden	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
almost	O
kill	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Fall	O
.	O
He	O
,	O
in	O
Defence	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
with	O
a	O
Ship-mate	O
,	O
who	O
,	O
being	O
fuddled	O
,	O
threw	O
his	O
Hat	O
upon	O
the	O
Leads	O
,	O
which	O
put	O
him	O
upon	O
the	O
Necessity	O
of	O
climbing	O
up	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
too	O
heavy	O
in	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Linnen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
down	O
his	O
stairs	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
;	O
and	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
knew	O
that	O
Woman	O
had	O
no	O
Business	O
in	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
being	O
surprized	O
,	O
he	O
let	O
her	O
pass	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
out	O
;	O
but	O
going	O
up	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
no	O
Sheets	O
upon	O
his	O
Bed	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
and	O
a	O
Friend	O
followed	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
overtook	O
her	O
with	O
them	O
in	O
her	O
Apron	O
;	O
which	O
his	O
Wife	O
swore	O
to	O
be	O
theirs	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Closet	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Chamber	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
truck	O
'd	O
Earthen-Ware	O
for	O
them	O
with	O
a	O
Woman	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
but	O
cou	O
'd	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Dorril	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Muslin	O
Headcloths	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Blackborough	I-pers
's	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Blackborough	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
went	O
a	O
way	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
but	O
was	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
in	O
Southwark	O
Fair	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
first	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
appeared	O
heartily	O
sorry	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Downing	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Downer	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
Ludgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sword	O
with	O
a	O
Tortoise-shell	O
Handle	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Constable	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
Instant	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Constable	O
depos	O
'd	O
nothing	O
material	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Sword	O
;	O
but	O
another	O
Witness	O
swore	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
it	O
from	O
his	O
side	O
.	O
A	O
Constable	O
also	O
made	O
Oath	O
he	O
overheard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
making	O
Offers	O
of	O
Satisfaction	O
to	O
that	O
Witness	O
not	O
to	O
appear	O
in	O
his	O
Evidence	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
other	O
Circumstances	O
prov	O
'd	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Friends	O
tampering	O
with	O
,	O
threating	O
and	O
frightening	O
the	O
said	O
Witness	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
Honesty	O
and	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
to	O
no	O
Effect	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
several	O
Things	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
to	O
take	O
off	O
the	O
Force	O
of	O
the	O
Proof	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
solliciting	O
Creatures	O
to	O
vouch	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
no	O
Purpose	O
;	O
neither	O
he	O
nor	O
they	O
having	O
any	O
Reputation	O
to	O
support	O
what	O
they	O
said	O
against	O
the	O
sound	O
evidence	O
which	O
oppos	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Edge	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Alhallows	B-place
the	I-place
Great	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Folio	O
Common-Prayer-Book	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
Instant	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Charles	B-pers
Motte	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
Book	O
on	O
the	O
Evening	O
aforesaid	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
but	O
observing	O
the	O
Parish	O
Characters	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
believing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
the	O
Maid	O
for	O
a	O
Porter	O
,	O
and	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
Church-Warden	O
who	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Book	O
's	O
being	O
owned	O
,	O
was	O
secured	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Sexton	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
appeard	O
clear	O
so	O
far	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
proof	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
stealing	O
it	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
upon	O
a	O
Bulk	O
;	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
willing	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
the	O
Porter	O
;	O
but	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Letters	O
on	O
the	O
Book	O
,	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Chance	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
at	I-place
,	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Pomeroy	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
1	O
Silk-Gown	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.2	O
Silk	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
11	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
;	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Parish	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Boyce	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
1	O
Silver	O
Coffee-pot	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.12	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
6	O
l.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Stibbs	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
also	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
to	O
this	O
Indictment	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
indicted	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Parish	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Eliz	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
3	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
35	O
Plates	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
5	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
39	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
's	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
:	O
But	O
pleading	O
not	O
Guilty	O
to	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
himself	O
upon	O
his	O
Trial	O
,	O
one	O
Shepherd	O
appeared	O
to	O
fix	O
it	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
was	O
concerned	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
related	O
all	O
the	O
Circumstances	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
concerned	O
in	O
several	O
Facts	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
in	O
this	O
,	O
which	O
not	O
being	O
credited	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Greenland	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Jacob	B-pers
Goddard	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
a	O
Cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
1	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
1	O
Stuff	O
Petticoat	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
from	O
the	O
said	O
Jacob	O
Goddard	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Goddard	O
swore	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Goods	O
abovemention	O
'd	O
stolen	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Burglars	O
,	O
till	O
Abel	B-pers
Downes	I-pers
made	O
his	O
information	O
.	O
Then	O
Downes	O
stood	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
to	O
thieve	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Benjamin-street	B-place
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lived	O
,	O
he	O
broke	O
open	O
a	O
Shutter	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
go	O
in	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
did	O
half	O
Way	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Room	O
being	O
dark	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
no	O
farther	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
feeling	O
about	O
,	O
he	O
bundled	O
up	O
every	O
thing	O
he	O
could	O
find	O
loose	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
seeing	O
a	O
Woman	O
go	O
into	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
,	O
and	O
believing	O
they	O
were	O
discover	O
'd	O
,	O
cried	O
Tomme	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Watch-Word	O
;	O
which	O
put	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
Fright	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
hid	O
himself	O
in	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
like	O
an	O
Owl	O
(	O
as	O
he	O
exprest	O
it	O
)	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
got	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
escaped	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
he	O
ever	O
was	O
concerned	O
with	O
the	O
Evidence	O
in	O
Facts	O
of	O
this	O
Kind	O
,	O
but	O
owned	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
play	O
the	O
Rogue	O
late	O
at	O
Night	O
in	O
the	O
Streets	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
only	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Trapp	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
intending	O
to	O
steal	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
Upon	O
Evidence	O
it	O
appeared	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
Burglary	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Slaughter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Caesar	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
intending	O
to	O
steal	O
his	O
Goods	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
Instant	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Proof	O
not	O
being	O
full	O
enough	O
to	O
satisfie	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
they	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Solomon	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
Brown	O
Gelding	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
l.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Grounds	O
of	O
Mark	B-pers
Bilby	I-pers
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
proving	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
a	O
good	O
Reputation	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
11	O
Yards	O
of	O
Satin	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
considerable	O
Value	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Long	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Long	O
swore	O
she	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
And	O
one	O
Mills	O
swore	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
he	O
committed	O
the	O
Fact	O
with	O
one	O
Robert	O
Evans	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
convicted	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
sold	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
Deborah	B-pers
Stent	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Humfrey	B-pers
Clements	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anne	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Susan	B-pers
Hepburne	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
24	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
4	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
25	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
from	O
the	O
said	O
Susan	O
Hepburne	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Mills	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
of	O
the	O
Gang	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
and	O
Frances	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
at	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
50	O
lb	O
.	O
Wt	O
.	O
of	O
Feathers	O
,	O
value	O
22	O
s.	O
1	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Pillow-bear	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Matthew	B-pers
Hilliard	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
Lodgers	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
;	O
but	O
Frances	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
took	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
Sister	O
might	O
be	O
acquitted	O
;	O
as	O
she	O
accordingly	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
herself	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coral	O
set	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mark	B-pers
Anthony	I-pers
Nay	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
under	O
Pretence	O
of	O
sending	O
two	O
of	O
her	O
Children	O
to	O
his	O
School	O
to	O
learn	O
French	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Rowland	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Chelsea	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Silver	O
Salvers,1	O
Silver	O
Ladle	O
,	O
18	O
Spoons	O
,	O
1	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
60	O
odd	O
Pounds	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Thicksara	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
the	O
Side-board	O
Table	O
as	O
his	O
Mistress	O
was	O
abroad	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Fellow-Servant	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
his	O
Mother	O
was	O
very	O
ill	O
at	O
Darby	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
ask	O
leave	O
to	O
go	O
,	O
lest	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
refus	O
'd	O
;	O
which	O
Excuse	O
was	O
of	O
no	O
Service	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
a	O
great	O
Quantity	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
;	O
and	O
an	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
he	O
bought	O
some	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
which	O
Madam	O
Thicksara	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
hers	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Langdon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Book	O
of	O
Accounts	O
,	O
val.10	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
our	O
Sovereign	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
short	O
Allowance	O
Office	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Book	O
,	O
intending	O
to	O
defraud	O
some	O
Sailors	O
of	O
Their	O
Wages	O
,	O
which	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
book	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
had	O
not	O
yet	O
receiv	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
by	O
making	O
false	O
Powers	O
in	O
their	O
Names	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Beaufort	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Compton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Hounslow	B-place
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bay	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Curtis	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
sworn	O
positively	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Gibbs	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Fulham	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
Cock	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
30	O
Pullets	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
Suspicion	O
;	O
and	O
not	O
giving	O
a	O
good	O
Account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
prosecuted	O
.	O
Upon	O
Trial	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Persons	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
nor	O
none	O
to	O
prove	O
he	O
came	O
honestly	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Howell	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Eling	B-place
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
6	O
Geese	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
16	O
Ducks	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
Instant	O
.	O
An	O
Evidence	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
hid	O
in	O
his	O
Grounds	O
,	O
and	O
watching	O
to	O
see	O
who	O
came	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
directly	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
with	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
discover	O
'd	O
grumbled	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
this	O
Witness	O
shew	O
'd	O
himself	O
with	O
his	O
Firelock	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
Help	O
and	O
secured	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Woman	O
got	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
came	O
there	O
by	O
Direction	O
in	O
his	O
Way	O
to	O
South	O
Acton	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
believing	O
him	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Crawford	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pocket	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
and	O
14	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
Instant	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
thinking	O
the	O
Proof	O
sufficient	O
,	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
Woollen	O
Apron	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Farthings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
being	O
Satisfied	O
with	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dustan	I-place
at	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
10	O
Guineas	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
Followeth	O
:	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death,17	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Downing	I-pers
alias	O
Downer	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Chance	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Humfrey	B-pers
Clements	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Rowland	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Beaufort	I-pers
alias	O
Compton	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand,3	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Greenland	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt,6	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Dorril	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Broome	I-pers
,	O
Frances	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Langsdale	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Gibbs	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Howell	I-pers
Then	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
fine	O
James	B-pers
Beaver	I-pers
,	O
Hester	B-pers
Stibbs	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Eldridge	I-pers
,	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Hornsby	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Anne	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
,20	O
Marks	O
each	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
The	O
most	O
excellent	O
BALSAMICK	O
WATER	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
greatest	O
Preservative	O
of	O
Health	O
in	O
Nature	O
,	O
that	O
in	O
50	O
Years	O
Study	O
of	O
Physick	O
I	O
could	O
find	O
out	O
,	O
needs	O
not	O
much	O
to	O
be	O
said	O
in	O
its	O
Commendation	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
will	O
recommend	O
it	O
self	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
other	O
Interest	O
in	O
making	O
of	O
it	O
Publick	O
,	O
but	O
for	O
the	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
my	O
Friends	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
general	O
Good	O
of	O
Mankind	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
may	O
not	O
die	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
(	O
like	O
the	O
English	O
Quack	O
)	O
say	O
that	O
it	O
cures	O
all	O
Distempers	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
infallibly	O
keeps	O
the	O
Body	O
in	O
good	O
Health	O
,	O
and	O
defends	O
it	O
from	O
all	O
infectious	O
Airs	O
and	O
distempers	O
,	O
by	O
taking	O
3	O
spoonfuls	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
half	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
warm	O
Ale	O
,	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
White	O
Wine	O
,	O
Tea	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
other	O
Liquid	O
.	O
It	O
may	O
be	O
taken	O
by	O
all	O
Persons	O
,	O
of	O
what	O
Age	O
or	O
Sex	O
soever	O
,	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
Day	O
,	O
without	O
Confinement	O
or	O
Hinderance	O
of	O
Business	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
printed	O
Directions	O
given	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
It	O
prevents	O
Consumptions	O
,	O
and	O
cures	O
them	O
if	O
not	O
too	O
far	O
gone	O
;	O
it	O
relieves	O
the	O
Tissick	O
and	O
Shortness	O
of	O
Breath	O
;	O
cures	O
Ulcers	O
in	O
the	O
Lungs	O
,	O
or	O
in	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Body	O
;	O
it	O
opens	O
all	O
Obstructions	O
,	O
and	O
infallibly	O
destroys	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
Worms	O
in	O
Young	O
or	O
Old	O
.	O
It	O
cures	O
the	O
Yellow	O
and	O
Black	O
Jaundice	O
,	O
Leprosy	O
,	O
Itch	O
,	O
and	O
Scald	O
Heads	O
.	O
It	O
certainly	O
eradicates	O
that	O
reigning	O
Distemper	O
the	O
Scurvey	O
;	O
chears	O
the	O
Spirits	O
,	O
strengthens	O
the	O
Stomach	O
,	O
and	O
creates	O
a	O
good	O
Appetite	O
.	O
I	O
recommend	O
it	O
to	O
all	O
Child-bearing	O
Women	O
,	O
it	O
preserving	O
the	O
Infant	O
from	O
those	O
Infirmities	O
that	O
Children	O
are	O
generally	O
afflicted	O
with	O
,	O
purifies	O
the	O
whole	O
Mass	O
of	O
Blood	O
,	O
renders	O
the	O
Skin	O
beautiful	O
and	O
clear	O
,	O
and	O
causes	O
easy	O
Delivery	O
.	O
Likewise	O
I	O
recommend	O
it	O
to	O
Sea-faring	O
Men	O
that	O
Trade	O
to	O
the	O
East	O
or	O
West	O
Indies	O
,	O
or	O
those	O
Countries	O
where	O
Fevers	O
or	O
the	O
Plague	O
are	O
infectious	O
.	O
When	O
all	O
other	O
Remedies	O
fail	O
,	O
this	O
excellent	O
Balsamick	O
Water	O
drives	O
out	O
the	O
small	O
Pox	O
or	O
Measles	O
,	O
and	O
keeps	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
Stomach	O
or	O
Throat	O
,	O
preventing	O
that	O
Soreness	O
which	O
generally	O
accompanies	O
,	O
and	O
often	O
proves	O
fatal	O
to	O
that	O
Distemper	O
;	O
and	O
also	O
prevents	O
the	O
Small	O
Pox	O
or	O
any	O
other	O
infectious	O
Distemper	O
,	O
from	O
spreading	O
in	O
a	O
Family	O
.	O
It	O
's	O
excellent	O
for	O
Gentlemen	O
after	O
hard	O
Drinking	O
,	O
far	O
exceeding	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
it	O
discharges	O
the	O
Body	O
from	O
the	O
Impurity	O
of	O
bad	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
cleanses	O
it	O
from	O
all	O
Scorbutick	O
Sports	O
,	O
Scabs	O
,	O
or	O
Boyls	O
,	O
by	O
bathing	O
outwardly	O
;	O
and	O
cures	O
all	O
Old	O
Sores	O
and	O
Green	O
Wounds	O
,	O
by	O
washing	O
the	O
Place	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
sore	O
Mouths	O
caused	O
by	O
inward	O
Heat	O
or	O
Canker	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
also	O
excellent	O
for	O
all	O
Persons	O
that	O
drink	O
the	O
Waters	O
,	O
causing	O
them	O
to	O
pass	O
and	O
evacuate	O
whatever	O
Humours	O
offend	O
the	O
Body	O
.	O
This	O
excellent	O
Balsamick	O
Water	O
is	O
put	O
up	O
in	O
half	O
Pint	O
Bottles	O
,	O
at	O
2	O
s.6	O
d.	O
each	O
Bottle	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
at	O
large	O
for	O
the	O
Taking	O
and	O
Use	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
close	O
stopp	O
'd	O
retains	O
its	O
Virtue	O
in	O
all	O
Climates	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
older	O
it	O
grows	O
,	O
the	O
better	O
it	O
is	O
:	O
It	O
generally	O
gives	O
one	O
Stool	O
,	O
and	O
works	O
off	O
by	O
Urine	O
.	O
This	O
excellent	O
Balsamick	O
Water	O
is	O
made	O
by	O
none	O
but	O
my	O
self	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
to	O
prevent	O
Counterfeits	O
,	O
is	O
fold	O
only	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Parker	O
's	O
Books-seller	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
and	O
Crown	O
in	O
Lombard	O
Street	O
,	O
near	O
Stocks-Market	O
,	O
sealed	O
with	O
a	O
Lion	O
and	O
Dagger	O
.	O
Perform	O
'd	O
by	O
HENDRICK	O
VANDOR	O
We	O
Thomas	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Griffiths	I-pers
,	O
who	O
keep	O
the	O
great	O
o	O
'd	O
publick	O
News-shop	O
over	O
against	O
the	O
Blue	O
posts	O
and	O
Rummer	O
Eating-house	O
at	O
Charing-Cross	O
,	O
do	O
hereby	O
testify	O
,	O
that	O
by	O
only	O
putting	O
about	O
our	O
Child	O
's	O
Neck	O
at	O
three	O
Months	O
old	O
,	O
the	O
celebrated	O
Necklace	O
recommended	O
by	O
Dr.	O
Chamberlen	O
for	O
Childrens	O
Teeth	O
,	O
it	O
has	O
now	O
cut	O
most	O
of	O
its	O
Teeth	O
,	O
being	O
near	O
a	O
Year	O
old	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
has	O
had	O
any	O
Fever	O
,	O
Convulsions	O
,	O
Pains	O
,	O
or	O
such	O
usual	O
Illness	O
and	O
Uneasiness	O
,	O
which	O
commonly	O
attend	O
Children	O
in	O
breeding	O
and	O
cutting	O
their	O
Teeth	O
;	O
but	O
has	O
all	O
this	O
Time	O
(	O
notwithstanding	O
it	O
has	O
bred	O
and	O
cut	O
so	O
many	O
Teeth	O
)	O
so	O
thriv	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
all	O
along	O
been	O
so	O
healthy	O
and	O
well	O
,	O
that	O
perhaps	O
all	O
England	O
can	O
not	O
shew	O
a	O
finer	O
Boy	O
,	O
as	O
any	O
Person	O
that	O
pleases	O
may	O
be	O
fully	O
satisfied	O
of	O
who	O
will	O
but	O
give	O
themselves	O
the	O
Trouble	O
to	O
come	O
or	O
send	O
any	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Child	O
.	O
Witness	O
our	O
Hands	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
August	O
1716.	O
Tho	B-pers
Griffiths	I-pers
,	O
Eliz	B-pers
Griffiths	I-pers
.	O
This	O
wonderful	O
Necklace	O
,	O
pr.5	O
s.	O
with	O
printed	O
Directions	O
in	O
English	O
and	O
French	O
for	O
wearing	O
it	O
,	O
is	O
only	O
to	O
be	O
had	O
up	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
at	O
the	O
Sugar-loaf	O
a	O
Confectioner	O
's	O
Shop	O
over	O
against	O
Old	O
Round	O
Court	O
near	O
the	O
New	O
Exchange	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
where	O
else	O
.	O
Where	O
(	O
for	O
the	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
the	O
World	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
real	O
Virtue	O
of	O
this	O
Sovereign	O
Necklace	O
)	O
is	O
given	O
Gratis	O
the	O
Philosophical	O
Essay	O
,	O
dedicated	O
to	O
Dr.	O
Chamberlen	O
and	O
the	O
Royal	O
Society	O
,	O
upon	O
this	O
Necklace	O
,	O
occasioned	O
by	O
the	O
great	O
Increase	O
of	O
late	O
Years	O
in	O
the	O
Bills	O
of	O
Mortality	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
it	O
appears	O
,	O
that	O
in	O
and	O
about	O
London	O
only	O
,	O
above	O
12000	O
Children	O
yearly	O
die	O
of	O
their	O
Teeth	O
;	O
whereas	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
great	O
Numbers	O
of	O
Children	O
who	O
in	O
time	O
have	O
worn	O
this	O
Necklace	O
,	O
we	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
of	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
one	O
that	O
has	O
died	O
,	O
but	O
on	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
has	O
bred	O
and	O
cut	O
them	O
without	O
any	O
Pain	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
thriv	O
'd	O
extreamly	O
.	O
Note	O
,	O
At	O
the	O
same	O
Place	O
is	O
also	O
given	O
Gratis	O
in	O
English	O
and	O
French	O
,	O
The	O
16th	O
Edition	O
,	O
dedicated	O
to	O
Dr.	O
Chamberlen	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Practical	O
Scheme	O
of	O
secret	O
Injuries	O
and	O
broken	O
Constitutions	O
,	O
by	O
fast	O
living	O
,	O
former	O
ill	O
Cures	O
,	O
Salivations	O
,	O
and	O
Mercury	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Good	O
of	O
the	O
Publick	O
.	O
Whereas	O
several	O
Gentlewomen	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
that	O
Sex	O
,	O
in	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
have	O
contracted	O
an	O
evil	O
Habit	O
of	O
Body	O
,	O
wherein	O
the	O
vicious	O
Humours	O
,	O
at	O
first	O
dispers	O
'd	O
thro	O
the	O
Whole	O
,	O
come	O
at	O
length	O
to	O
be	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
one	O
Part	O
or	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
times	O
,	O
for	O
Causes	O
too	O
long	O
to	O
be	O
here	O
mentioned	O
,	O
are	O
thrown	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Womb	O
,	O
occasioning	O
a	O
dangerous	O
Weakness	O
in	O
that	O
Part	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
neglected	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
turns	O
Cancerous	O
,	O
and	O
often	O
proves	O
Fatal	O
.	O
I	O
cure	O
the	O
Diabetes	O
when	O
given	O
over	O
by	O
all	O
other	O
Persons	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
to	O
acquaint	O
all	O
such	O
as	O
may	O
have	O
occasion	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
speedy	O
Relief	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
had	O
from	O
an	O
Experienc	O
'd	O
Midwife	O
,	O
dwelling	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Arms	O
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Smith	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
near	O
Exeter	O
Exchange	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
who	O
perform	O
'd	O
a	O
Cure	O
upon	O
a	O
Lady	O
at	O
the	O
Bath	O
,	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
given	O
over	O
by	O
the	O
Physicians	O
,	O
and	O
since	O
has	O
Cured	O
several	O
Gentlewomen	O
and	O
others	O
in	O
the	O
City	O
and	O
Suburbs	O
of	O
London	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
put	O
my	O
self	O
in	O
Publick	O
Print	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
satisfy	O
the	O
Afflicted	O
where	O
they	O
may	O
have	O
speedy	O
Relief	O
after	O
they	O
are	O
given	O
over	O
by	O
all	O
other	O
Persons	O
.	O
At	O
her	O
House	O
the	O
Red	O
Ball	O
in	O
Queen-street	O
,	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Three	O
Cranes	O
,	O
Liveth	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
that	O
hath	O
a	O
most	O
incomparable	O
Wash	O
to	O
beautifie	O
the	O
Face	O
;	O
which	O
far	O
exceeds	O
all	O
that	O
are	O
extant	O
,	O
as	O
abundance	O
of	O
the	O
greatest	O
Quality	O
have	O
found	O
by	O
Experience	O
,	O
to	O
their	O
great	O
Satisfaction	O
.	O
It	O
takes	O
out	O
all	O
manner	O
of	O
Wrinkles	O
,	O
Freckles	O
,	O
pimples	O
,	O
Redness	O
,	O
Morphew	O
,	O
Sun-burn	O
,	O
Yellowness	O
,	O
caus	O
'd	O
by	O
Mercurial	O
poisonous	O
Washes	O
:	O
It	O
also	O
plumps	O
and	O
softens	O
the	O
Skin	O
,	O
making	O
it	O
as	O
smooth	O
and	O
tender	O
as	O
a	O
sucking	O
Child	O
's	O
:	O
The	O
Young	O
it	O
always	O
keeps	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Old	O
it	O
makes	O
appear	O
Fair	O
and	O
Young	O
to	O
Admiration	O
.	O
It	O
has	O
nothing	O
of	O
Paint	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
neither	O
doth	O
any	O
Person	O
know	O
the	O
Secret	O
.	O
You	O
may	O
have	O
from	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
to	O
Five	O
Pounds	O
the	O
Bottle	O
.	O
You	O
may	O
have	O
Pomatums	O
,	O
White	O
pots	O
,	O
the	O
like	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
compared	O
with	O
;	O
also	O
a	O
Powder	O
for	O
the	O
Teeth	O
,	O
which	O
makes	O
them	O
as	O
white	O
as	O
snow	O
.	O
She	O
hath	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Secret	O
to	O
prevent	O
Hair	O
from	O
falling	O
,	O
causing	O
it	O
to	O
grow	O
wherever	O
it	O
is	O
wanting	O
.	O
She	O
alters	O
Red	O
or	O
Grey	O
Hair	O
to	O
a	O
delicate	O
light	O
or	O
dark	O
Brown	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
never	O
change	O
.	O
She	O
shapes	O
the	O
Eye-brows	O
,	O
and	O
makes	O
them	O
beautiful	O
:	O
She	O
hath	O
a	O
delicate	O
Paste	O
to	O
whiten	O
the	O
Hands	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Red	O
Pomatum	O
to	O
colour	O
the	O
Lips	O
,	O
and	O
prevents	O
their	O
chopping	O
in	O
Winter	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
a	O
certain	O
and	O
infallible	O
Cure	O
for	O
the	O
Toothach	O
,	O
without	O
drawing	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Pain	O
will	O
not	O
return	O
.	O
Note	O
,	O
Remov	O
'd	O
from	O
the	O
Cheshire-Cheese	O
in	O
Walbrook	O
.	O
