TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
'S	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
During	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
the	O
Rt	O
.	O
Honble	O
Sir	O
William	O
Lewen	O
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
4th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
1718	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
PHILLIPS	O
,	O
by	O
M.	O
Jencter	O
,	O
against	O
St.	O
Sepulchre	O
's	O
Back	O
Gate	O
,	O
in	O
Gilt	O
Spur	O
Street	O
,	O
near	O
Newgate	O
.	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
'S	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
Termminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
,	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
and	O
Thursday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
16th	O
and	O
17th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October,1717	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Fourth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
JAMES	B-pers
BATEMAN	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
and	O
Bart	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Worshipful	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Tracy	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
;	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
Names	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hodson	I-pers
Sinoon	B-pers
Mayo	I-pers
Eleazar	B-pers
Evanson	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Fielder	I-pers
Joshna	B-pers
Feree	I-pers
James	B-pers
Man	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
Thainas	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
Christopher	B-pers
Garraway	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Leppige	I-pers
John	B-pers
Futerell	I-pers
William	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
Bruce	B-pers
Randal	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Bavon	I-pers
John	B-pers
Curtis	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
George	B-pers
Barns	I-pers
John	B-pers
Prater	I-pers
William	B-pers
Clements	I-pers
John	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Elford	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
William	B-pers
Giles	I-pers
The	O
proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Henry	B-pers
Banister	I-pers
(	O
a	O
Boy	O
of	O
13	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
)	O
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Canvas	O
Bag	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
3	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
latter	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
said	O
Money	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stollen	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Banister	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
and	O
bought	O
half	O
an	O
Onnce	O
of	O
Thread	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
paid	O
for	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
returning	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
the	O
Gentlewoman	O
he	O
fetch	O
'd	O
the	O
Thread	O
for	O
liked	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
half	O
a	O
Pound	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
(	O
making	O
use	O
of	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
)	O
saying	O
likewise	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
stay	O
there	O
till	O
the	O
Gentlewoman	O
sent	O
her	O
Daughter	O
with	O
the	O
Money	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
about	O
Dinner-time	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
back	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
to	O
Dinner	O
,	O
left	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
who	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
took	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
reach	O
over	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
open	O
the	O
Money-Drawer	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Gentlewoman	O
whose	O
Name	O
he	O
made	O
use	O
off	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
answered	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
sent	O
any	O
such	O
Boy	O
,	O
but	O
directed	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
might	O
get	O
some	O
Intelligence	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
looking	O
for	O
him	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
Southmark-Fair	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
upon	O
his	O
Apprehension	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
at	O
first	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
yet	O
he	O
afterwards	O
owned	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
about	O
27	O
s.	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Shaw	O
had	O
put	O
him	O
upon	O
the	O
Fact	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
the	O
Money	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
back	O
35	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
same	O
Purpose	O
he	O
owned	O
at	O
his	O
Trial	O
:	O
But	O
Shaw	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
other	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Shaw	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
Banister	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Marshal	I-pers
alias	I-pers
John	I-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
Ludgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Thimble	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
25	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Man	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Man	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
going	O
through	O
the	O
Postern	O
at	O
Ludgate	B-place
,	O
having	O
her	O
Brother	O
by	O
the	O
Arm	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
cut	O
her	O
Pocket	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
feeling	O
some	O
body	O
have	O
hold	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
catch	O
'd	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
other	O
Person	O
there	O
;	O
that	O
her	O
Money	O
dropped	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
15	O
s.	O
was	O
picked	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
10	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Her	O
Brother	O
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Purpose	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
were	O
other	O
Persons	O
there	O
besides	O
himself	O
;	O
however	O
this	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
positive	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
180	O
Yards	O
of	O
Tammy	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Vokins	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
by	O
Trade	O
a	O
Plumber	O
,	O
employed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
as	O
a	O
Labourer	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Wife	O
keeping	O
a	O
Shop	O
and	O
dealing	O
in	O
Tammys	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Wife	O
having	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
missed	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Tammy	O
,	O
and	O
particularly	O
one	O
Piece	O
that	O
Morning	O
,	O
they	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
making	O
Search	O
,	O
found	O
one	O
Piece	O
of	O
Tammy	O
put	O
under	O
the	O
Steps	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
near	O
the	O
Street	O
(	O
where	O
were	O
Iron	O
Bars	O
to	O
let	O
in	O
Light	O
)	O
in	O
such	O
manner	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
might	O
come	O
at	O
Night	O
and	O
take	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
by	O
putting	O
his	O
Hand	O
in	O
between	O
the	O
Bars	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
he	O
resolved	O
to	O
watch	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
privately	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
about	O
II	O
a	O
Clock	O
that	O
Night	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
to	O
take	O
out	O
the	O
Stuff	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
Moon-light	O
he	O
plainly	O
saw	O
him	O
and	O
knew	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
catched	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
got	O
it	O
away	O
from	O
him	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
came	O
next	O
Morning	O
to	O
work	O
as	O
usual	O
,	O
thinking	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
discovered	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
being	O
taxed	O
with	O
it	O
at	O
last	O
confessed	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
this	O
Piece	O
so	O
laid	O
not	O
being	O
the	O
Piece	O
that	O
was	O
missed	O
that	O
Morning	O
,	O
they	O
examined	O
him	O
about	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confessed	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
hid	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
under	O
some	O
Wood	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
of	O
;	O
that	O
turning	O
up	O
the	O
Wood	O
they	O
found	O
it	O
accordingly	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
confessed	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
and	O
pawned	O
other	O
Parcels	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
accordingly	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
so	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Murth	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Westerbane	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
steal	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
John	O
Wood	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Glass	O
of	O
a	O
back	O
Room	O
was	O
taken	O
down	O
,	O
the	O
Shutters	O
bored	O
and	O
afterwards	O
cut	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Bar	O
taken	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
getting	O
into	O
a	O
back	O
Parlour	O
,	O
where	O
was	O
nothing	O
but	O
a	O
Whip	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
s.	O
that	O
they	O
could	O
carry	O
off	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
boring	O
another	O
Part	O
of	O
his	O
House	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
get	O
further	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
discover	O
'd	O
as	O
follows	O
.	O
Leonard	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
they	O
must	O
snip	O
off	O
some	O
Cordage	O
,	O
they	O
sent	O
the	O
Boy	O
up	O
to	O
their	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Boy	O
coming	O
down	O
heard	O
the	O
Noise	O
of	O
their	O
boring	O
and	O
cutting	O
,	O
told	O
them	O
there	O
were	O
Thieves	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
thereupon	O
he	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
ran	O
to	O
the	O
back	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
saw	O
two	O
Persons	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
with	O
a	O
Light	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
perceiving	O
themselves	O
to	O
be	O
beset	O
,	O
put	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
over	O
three	O
Gardens	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
Pistols	O
and	O
Hangers	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
shot	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
take	O
to	O
be	O
John	B-pers
Murth	I-pers
;	O
that	O
he	O
pursued	O
them	O
,	O
seized	O
Wood	O
,	O
but	O
Murth	O
got	O
off	O
.	O
William	O
Thompson	O
confirmed	O
what	O
the	O
other	O
said	O
,	O
adding	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
upon	O
the	O
Wall	O
they	O
threw	O
Bricks	O
at	O
him	O
;	O
cut	O
at	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Hanger	O
,	O
and	O
endeavoured	O
with	O
a	O
Bar	O
to	O
knock	O
him	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
heard	O
them	O
cry	O
,	O
Damn	O
him	O
,	O
cut	O
him	O
to	O
pieces	O
,	O
shoot	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
slipping	O
down	O
from	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
him	O
rising	O
and	O
met	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Breast	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Slugs	O
were	O
still	O
in	O
his	O
Body	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
directly	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
Murth	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
least	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
;	O
which	O
Description	O
answer	O
'd	O
to	O
Murth	O
's	O
Stature	O
.	O
Several	O
of	O
these	O
Circumstances	O
were	O
confirmed	O
by	O
other	O
Evidences	O
.	O
They	O
added	O
likewise	O
,	O
that	O
Wood	O
did	O
endeavour	O
to	O
fire	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
Pistol	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
off	O
.	O
Wood	O
confessed	O
the	O
same	O
at	O
his	O
Apprehension	O
and	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
affirming	O
that	O
Murth	O
shot	O
Thompson	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
that	O
apprehended	O
,	O
Murth	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
,	O
Murth	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
telling	O
him	O
he	O
the	O
Man	O
who	O
was	O
shot	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
Murth	O
rep	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
Friend	O
that	O
had	O
assured	O
him	O
before	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Two	O
other	O
Evidences	O
that	O
assisted	O
in	O
carrying	O
him	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
shot	O
Thompson	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
confessed	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
three	O
loaden	O
Pistols	O
besides	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
fired	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
discharg	O
'd	O
them	O
all	O
before	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
taken	O
.	O
But	O
notwithstanding	O
this	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
his	O
Trial	O
:	O
However	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
John	O
Murth	O
and	O
John	O
Wood	O
were	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
James	B-pers
Chetwood	I-pers
(	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Roger	B-pers
Grant	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
11	O
pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.21	O
pewter	O
plates	O
,	O
value	O
21	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
Fork	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
Camblet	O
Riding-hood	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Bible	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
was	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
stole	O
between	O
the	O
Hours	O
of	O
12	O
and	O
5	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
Frame	O
of	O
the	O
Kitchen-window	O
being	O
broken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Iron-bars	O
forced	O
out	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
the	O
first	O
Notice	O
of	O
it	O
by	O
a	O
Gardner	O
that	O
came	O
to	O
cut	O
the	O
Grass	O
in	O
the	O
Garden	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he-being	O
put	O
in	O
possession	O
of	O
Murth	O
's	O
Goods	O
by	O
the	O
Lord	O
of	O
the	O
Mannor	O
,	O
found	O
a	O
Musick-book	O
,	O
with	O
Doctor	O
Grant	O
's	O
Name	O
to	O
it	O
behind	O
a	O
picture	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pocket	O
Book	O
,	O
wherein	O
was	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Robberies	O
committed	O
by	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1716	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
pleaded	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
how	O
the	O
Book	O
came	O
there	O
.	O
Other	O
Evidences	O
deposed	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
Mr.	O
Grant	O
's	O
Bible	O
in	O
John	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
's	O
Lodgings	O
.	O
Wood	O
alledged	O
that	O
Murth	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
the	O
Gang	O
,	O
constrained	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
hand	O
in	O
the	O
robbing	O
Mr.	O
Grant	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
Murth	O
and	O
Chetwood	O
did	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Bible	O
,	O
he	O
indeed	O
saw	O
Murth	O
have	O
it	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
sent	O
his	O
Wife	O
to	O
borrow	O
it	O
of	O
Murth	O
to	O
read	O
in	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
indeed	O
a	O
very	O
allowable	O
Action	O
to	O
borrow	O
a	O
Bible	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
good	O
one	O
to	O
read	O
in	O
so	O
good	O
a	O
Book	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
bad	O
Action	O
to	O
steal	O
it	O
.	O
But	O
this	O
pious	O
Pretence	O
did	O
not	O
skreen	O
him	O
from	O
the	O
Censure	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
who	O
,	O
though	O
they	O
were	O
so	O
favourable	O
as	O
to	O
acquit	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Chalkly	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White-Chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Baskets	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Head	O
of	O
a	O
Copper	O
Watering-pot	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Forster	I-pers
;	O
a	O
Blanket	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Marlow	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
John	O
Marlow	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
Stollen	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Garden-house	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
suspecting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
formerly	O
Servant	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
turn	O
'd	O
away	O
for	O
some	O
pilsering	O
Tricks	O
,	O
he	O
thereupon	O
searched	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
taking	O
one	O
Basket	O
with	O
some	O
Apples	O
,	O
but	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
Thereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Cloak	O
laced	O
with	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Underwood	I-pers
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
pay	O
her	O
a	O
Visit	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
the	O
Cloak	O
away	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
pulled	O
off	O
the	O
Lace	O
and	O
burnt	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
14	O
s.	O
and	O
the	O
Cloak	O
for	O
6	O
s.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4s.10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Rochford	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Follard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Alhallows	B-place
,	I-place
Lombard-street	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
l.6	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Dennis	B-pers
Langton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
Rochford	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
what	O
price	O
?	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
about	O
10	O
l.	O
that	O
he	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
one	O
about	O
that	O
price	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bid	O
him	O
5	O
l.	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
looking	O
in	O
the	O
Case	O
to	O
shew	O
him	O
one	O
of	O
5	O
l.	O
price	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pointed	O
at	O
several	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
five	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
immediately	O
in	O
comes	O
Follard	O
and	O
asks	O
for	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
proved	O
too	O
heavy	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
seeing	O
him	O
looking	O
for	O
the	O
Ring	O
,	O
was	O
very	O
urgent	O
to	O
be	O
shew	O
'd	O
other	O
Rings	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
haste	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
serve	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
another	O
Shop	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
two	O
others	O
,	O
and	O
weigh	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
for	O
23	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
paid	O
him	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
earnestly	O
looking	O
for	O
the	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
.	O
But	O
he	O
missing	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Rings	O
,	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
must	O
not	O
go	O
;	O
desiring	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
to	O
stand	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
to	O
prevent	O
their	O
going	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
of	O
five	O
Rings	O
that	O
he	O
laid	O
out	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
but	O
four	O
upon	O
the	O
Counter	O
till	O
Follard	O
clapping	O
his	O
Hand	O
upon	O
them	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
laying	O
them	O
down	O
there	O
was	O
five	O
.	O
The	O
Gentleman	O
who	O
was	O
waiting	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
suspecting	O
them	O
,	O
observed	O
,	O
that	O
though	O
they	O
took	O
no	O
Notice	O
one	O
of	O
another	O
,	O
yet	O
he	O
perceived	O
as	O
they	O
stood	O
by	O
one	O
another	O
,	O
side	O
by	O
side	O
,	O
they	O
both	O
put	O
their	O
Hands	O
down	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
suppose	O
,	O
that	O
Rechford	O
convey	O
'd	O
the	O
Ring	O
to	O
Follard	O
,	O
who	O
having	O
bought	O
and	O
paid	O
for	O
two	O
Rings	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
got	O
off	O
unsuspected	O
,	O
while	O
Rochford	O
was	O
treating	O
about	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Evidences	O
deposed	O
likewise	O
,	O
that	O
Rochford	O
being	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
had	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
a	O
Board-piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
10	O
l.	O
Ring	O
he	O
asked	O
for	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Follard	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
paid	O
for	O
his	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
had	O
about	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
left	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
Follard	O
said	O
he	O
only	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
four	O
Rings	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Beauty	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Their	O
Characters	O
were	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
best	O
,	O
nor	O
gave	O
they	O
any	O
satisfactory	O
Account	O
of	O
themselves	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Lawrence	I-place
Jewry	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
25	O
silver	O
Buttons	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
or	O
Samuel	B-pers
Osborn	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Osman	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Grandson	O
,	O
Samuel	O
Osborn	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
out	O
late	O
a	O
drinking	O
,	O
lay	O
down	O
to	O
sleep	O
on	O
a	O
Bench	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
cut	O
off	O
his	O
Buttons	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
having	O
secured	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
as	O
a	O
Night-walker	O
,	O
upon	O
searching	O
her	O
found	O
the	O
Buttons	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
But	O
Samuel	O
Osborn	O
being	O
since	O
gone	O
to	O
Sea	O
,	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
legal	O
Proof	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Callico	O
Pocket	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
three	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
Thimble	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
passing	O
along	O
Holborn	B-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pulled	O
off	O
her	O
Pocket	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
passing	O
along	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
catch	O
something	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
her	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
apprehended	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
getting	O
behind	O
a	O
Coach	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
behind	O
the	O
Coach	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
jump	O
'd	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
fling	O
something	O
like	O
a	O
Pocket	O
away	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
by	O
another	O
Boy	O
,	O
who	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
but	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
was	O
young	O
(	O
being	O
as	O
he	O
said	O
but	O
fourteen	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
)	O
was	O
known	O
to	O
have	O
made	O
too	O
great	O
a	O
Proficiency	O
in	O
that	O
Mystery	O
of	O
Iniquity	O
;	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
East-Cheap	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
thirty	O
Yards	O
of	O
Callico	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Lascelles	B-pers
Metcalf	I-pers
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
Several	O
Evidences	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
hearing	O
a	O
Cry	O
of	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
they	O
pursued	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
into	O
George-yard	O
in	O
Lombard-street	O
,	O
and	O
apprehended	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
just	O
before	O
his	O
Apprehension	O
,	O
they	O
saw	O
the	O
Callico	O
drop	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
a	O
Man	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
the	O
Bell	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
Grace-Church-street	O
.	O
But	O
that	O
Pretence	O
would	O
scarce	O
have	O
availed	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
good	O
Luck	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
dealing	O
with	O
a	O
Quaker	O
who	O
would	O
not	O
swear	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
that	O
lucky	O
Scrupulosity	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
probability	O
,	O
saved	O
him	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
Jury	O
were	O
obliged	O
to	O
acquit	O
him	O
upon	O
the	O
Deficiency	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Dimer	I-pers
Mary	B-pers
Maddox	I-pers
and	O
Will	B-pers
Maddox	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Pillowbear	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
three	O
Aprons	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Bridget	B-pers
Gasway	I-pers
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
had	O
a	O
Sister	O
that	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
coming	O
to	O
and	O
fro	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
,	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
abroad	O
,	O
to	O
open	O
her	O
Door	O
with	O
another	O
Key	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
William	B-pers
Maddox	I-pers
had	O
opened	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
taken	O
and	O
shared	O
amongst	O
them	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
upon'em	O
:	O
They	O
had	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Matter	O
also	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
which	O
Confession	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
themselves	O
,	O
therefore	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
all	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Clerkenwel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
bay	O
Mare	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Mare	O
in	O
Warwickshire	B-place
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
Bell-Inn	O
in	O
Islington	O
:	O
The	O
Man	O
that	O
kept	O
the	O
Inn	O
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Mare	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
4	O
l.	O
and	O
had	O
her	O
tolled	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
according	O
to	O
Law	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
black	O
Mare	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Coltor	I-pers
,	O
the	O
same	O
4th	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Mare	O
from	O
Birmingham	B-place
in	I-place
Warwickshire	I-place
,	O
and	O
having	O
got	O
some	O
Intelligence	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
and	O
apprehended	O
him	O
;	O
this	O
Mare	O
was	O
also	O
found	O
at	O
Islington	O
,	O
bought	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
bought	O
the	O
other	O
Mare	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
4	O
l.	O
for	O
her	O
likewise	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
her	O
vouch	O
'd	O
and	O
tolled	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
as	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
as	O
to	O
this	O
Robbery	O
as	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
therefore	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
also	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
seal	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
the	O
second	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
for	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
quartern	O
of	O
Geneva	O
,	O
leaving	O
a	O
Shilling	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
till	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
pot	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
growing	O
late	O
,	O
he	O
fell	O
asleep	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
having	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
eleven	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
pot	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
for	O
the	O
Change	O
of	O
his	O
Mony	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Body	O
there	O
but	O
her	O
Husband	O
and	O
she	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Husband	O
asleep	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
she	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
draw	O
the	O
Drink	O
,	O
she	O
supposed	O
he	O
picked	O
her	O
Husband	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
no	O
Body	O
else	O
there	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
her	O
Husband	O
missed	O
the	O
Mony	O
and	O
Seal	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
thinking	O
the	O
Evidence	O
sufficient	O
,	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
,	O
the	O
same	O
second	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodging	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
Apartment	O
to	O
ask	O
for	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
his	O
Room	O
left	O
by	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
while	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
pinchers	O
,	O
the	O
Ring	O
's	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Drawer	O
.	O
His	O
Serjeant	O
's	O
Wife	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
to	O
desire	O
her	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
a	O
Shilling	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
refusing	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
two	O
Rings	O
,	O
desiring	O
her	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
20	O
s.	O
upon	O
the	O
Rings	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
refused	O
to	O
do	O
likewise	O
:	O
She	O
described	O
the	O
Rings	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
a	O
red	O
Stone	O
Ring	O
,	O
with	O
three	O
white	O
Stones	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
.	O
The	O
red	O
Stone	O
,	O
which	O
exactly	O
answered	O
the	O
Description	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
gave	O
of	O
her	O
Ring	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Rings	O
he	O
offered	O
to	O
the	O
Serjeant	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
were	O
not	O
Gold	O
,	O
but	O
Bath	O
Mettal	O
;	O
he	O
called	O
his	O
Serjeant	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
so	O
scurvy	O
a	O
Character	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
better	O
have	O
let	O
him	O
alone	O
;	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Will	B-pers
Geer	I-pers
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Longley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Undershaft	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
15	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
going	O
to	O
Mr	B-place
.	I-place
Brag	I-place
's	I-place
Meeting	I-place
in	I-place
Lyme-street	I-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Geer	O
stopped	O
up	O
the	O
Meeting-house	O
Door	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
,	O
he	O
or	O
his	O
Accomplices	O
picked	O
her	O
pocket	O
,	O
they	O
husling	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
that	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
Make	O
way	O
for	O
the	O
Gentlewoman	O
,	O
so	O
let	O
her	O
pass	O
and	O
made	O
off	O
;	O
that	O
immediately	O
she	O
missed	O
her	O
Mony	O
,	O
and	O
telling	O
some	O
Persons	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
pursued	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
Longly	O
standing	O
not	O
far	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Person	O
who	O
pursued	O
them	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
Gentlewoman	O
told	O
him	O
her	O
pocket	O
was	O
pick	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
immediately	O
pursued	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
an	O
Officer	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
them	O
as	O
Pick-pockets	O
,	O
and	O
especially	O
Geer	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
to	O
haunt	O
Churches	O
and	O
Meetings	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
seen	O
turn	O
'd	O
out	O
upon	O
that	O
very	O
score	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
swear	O
positively	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Milbank	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
forging	O
a	O
Letter	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Oldner	I-pers
,	O
and	O
cheating	O
thereby	O
Jane	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
of	O
47	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
A	O
Letter	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Jane	O
Lane	O
,	O
signed	O
George	B-pers
Oldner	I-pers
,	O
advising	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
a	O
Person	O
brought	O
a	O
Parcel	O
,	O
she	O
should	O
pay	O
for	O
him	O
47	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
A	O
Parcel	O
was	O
brought	O
(	O
tho	O
'	O
of	O
no	O
Value	O
)	O
the	O
Mony	O
paid	O
;	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Oldner	O
being	O
told	O
of	O
it	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
some	O
Evidences	O
wanting	O
to	O
fix	O
the	O
Matter	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
Coverlid	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
Pillow-case	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Moss	I-pers
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
rented	O
a	O
Room	O
ready	O
furnished	O
,	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
her	O
several	O
Months	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
missed	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
acknowledged	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
necessitated	O
,	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
for	O
the	O
Support	O
of	O
her	O
self	O
and	O
Child	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
intend	O
to	O
redeem	O
them	O
and	O
bring	O
them	O
home	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
given	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
write	O
down	O
to	O
a	O
Brother	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
.	O
(	O
who	O
used	O
to	O
send	O
her	O
Mony	O
for	O
Subsistance	O
)	O
for	O
Mony	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
some	O
things	O
in	O
pawn	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
redeem	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
rather	O
the	O
Effect	O
of	O
Necessity	O
and	O
Impudence	O
than	O
Dishonesty	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Joanna	B-pers
Manning	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Randal	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
'	I-place
,	I-place
Westminister	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Pillow-case	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Bilut	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
11	O
Bottles	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Estwick	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
Joanna	O
Manning	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecution	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
having	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
upon	O
his	O
Return	O
,	O
missed	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
that	O
Joanna	B-pers
Manning	I-pers
lived	O
with	O
him	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
informed	O
,	O
that	O
Thomas	B-pers
Randal	I-pers
was	O
let	O
in	O
by	O
her	O
a	O
Nights	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
again	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
suspecting	O
him	O
,	O
searched	O
his	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
Joanna	O
Manning	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
home	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
by	O
till	O
she	O
called	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
other	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Chalkworthy	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Ashton	I-pers
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Ashton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
proof	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
was	O
seen	O
in	O
her	O
Shop	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
alledged	O
that	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
at	O
a	O
Market	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
for	O
a	O
Shilling	O
profit	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Caleb	B-pers
Auperson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Alhallows	I-place
on	I-place
the	I-place
Wall	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
5	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Oven	I-pers
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Shop	O
desiring	O
her	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
a	O
Queen	O
Anne	O
's	O
Sixpence	O
for	O
Sixpence	O
in	O
Halfpence	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
another	O
for	O
more	O
Halfpence	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
looking	O
in	O
a	O
Bag	O
for	O
one	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
thrust	O
his	O
Hand	O
into	O
the	O
Bag	O
and	O
catch	O
'd	O
out	O
the	O
Guinea	O
and	O
Silver	O
,	O
blew	O
out	O
the	O
Candle	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
made	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
immediately	O
stopped	O
and	O
brought	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Candle	O
was	O
lighted	O
the	O
Silver	O
and	O
Guinea	O
lay	O
upon	O
the	O
Counter	O
(	O
which	O
as	O
she	O
supposed	O
It	O
was	O
laid	O
there	O
by	O
him	O
while	O
the	O
Candle	O
was	O
lighting	O
;	O
)	O
But	O
she	O
not	O
swearing	O
it	O
positively	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Hugh	B-pers
Oakley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Katharine	I-place
Creed	I-place
Church	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Mary	B-pers
Dowse	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
with	O
a	O
Silver	O
Chain	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
ringing	O
at	O
the	O
Gate	O
of	O
Bricklayers-Hall	B-place
to	O
go	O
in	O
,	O
some	O
body	O
came	O
behind	O
her	O
and	O
threw	O
Ashes	O
in	O
her	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
her	O
Watch	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
her	O
side	O
.	O
Obadiah	B-pers
Leman	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
himself	O
threw	O
the	O
Ashes	O
in	O
the	O
Gentlewoman	O
's	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
6	O
l.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
which	O
Leman	O
mentioned	O
some	O
corroborating	O
Circumstances	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Manner	O
of	O
the	O
committing	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
which	O
Mrs.	O
Dowse	O
said	O
were	O
true	O
.	O
He	O
added	O
likewise	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
twenty	O
Facts	O
more	O
to	O
charge	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
committing	O
of	O
;	O
adding	O
,	O
that	O
by	O
throwing	O
Ashes	O
in	O
Persons	O
Eyes	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
stollen	O
twenty	O
Hats	O
and	O
Wigs	O
,	O
and	O
particularly	O
from	O
a	O
Quaker	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
Milk	O
Street	O
,	O
when	O
both	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
were	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Danly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Cole	I-place
Church	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
5	O
Holland	O
Frocks	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Noon	I-pers
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Barbara	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
carrying	O
the	O
Frocks	O
home	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Noon	O
's	O
in	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
;	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
knocking	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
snatched	O
them	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
ran	O
down	O
Bucklers-bury	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
stopped	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
Frocks	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
stopped	O
him	O
running	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
positive	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
some	O
Persons	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
by	O
Trade	O
,	O
a	O
Smith	O
and	O
Founder	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
work	O
at	O
the	O
said	O
Calling	O
;	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Character	O
that	O
made	O
it	O
look	O
probable	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
followed	O
this	O
Practice	O
long	O
.	O
However	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Longstaff	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
forging	O
and	O
publishing	O
a	O
Note	O
for	O
15l	O
.	O
under	O
the	O
Hand	O
of	O
,	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
to	O
his	O
Aunt	O
's	O
House	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
a	O
Barber	O
,	O
who	O
lives	O
in	O
the	O
Temple	O
discours	O
'd	O
of	O
helping	O
him	O
to	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
talk	O
'd	O
very	O
big	O
of	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
procure	O
Money	O
upon	O
Note	O
of	O
any	O
Housekeeper	O
;	O
for	O
considerable	O
Sums	O
very	O
easily	O
;	O
and	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
being	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
mighty	O
Business	O
,	O
as	O
an	O
Attorney	O
having	O
forty	O
or	O
fifty	O
Causes	O
to	O
come	O
on	O
the	O
next	O
Term	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
advising	O
with	O
his	O
Aunt	O
(	O
who	O
kept	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
some	O
Occasion	O
for	O
an	O
Attorney	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
Cause	O
)	O
they	O
proposed	O
the	O
Matter	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
In	O
answer	O
to	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
himself	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
so	O
fair	O
a	O
Dealer	O
that	O
way	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
took	O
any	O
Money	O
of	O
his	O
Clients	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
had	O
perform	O
'd	O
their	O
Business	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
help	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
20	O
or	O
25	O
l.	O
upon	O
his	O
Note	O
for	O
three	O
Months	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
glad	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
undertook	O
to	O
do	O
;	O
wrote	O
two	O
Notes	O
,	O
one	O
for	O
12	O
l.	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
13	O
l.	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
get	O
discounted	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
coming	O
afterwards	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
looking	O
over	O
some	O
Papers	O
that	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
a	O
Note	O
drawn	O
for	O
15	O
l.	O
payable	O
in	O
three	O
Months	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Character	O
imitating	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
sign	O
'd	O
with	O
his	O
Name	O
:	O
Upon	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
knowing	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
no	O
such	O
Note	O
began	O
to	O
be	O
uneasy	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
desire	O
the	O
two	O
other	O
Notes	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
But	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
hunted	O
in	O
a	O
Drawer	O
,	O
tumbled	O
over	O
Papers	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
pretended	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
them	O
to	O
his	O
Partner	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
needs	O
have	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
pretended	O
Partner	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
great	O
Business	O
,	O
too	O
)	O
whose	O
Name	O
was	O
Archbole	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Soldier	O
;	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
them	O
,	O
first	O
to	O
a	O
Man	O
at	O
Kensington	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
to	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
Hay-market	O
;	O
and	O
first	O
to	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
to	O
another	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
He	O
hunting	O
them	O
daily	O
for	O
the	O
Notes	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
very	O
pressing	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
,	O
Archbole	O
told	O
him	O
plainly	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
for	O
the	O
12	O
l.	O
Note	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
must	O
pay	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
13	O
l.	O
Note	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
Power	O
;	O
asking	O
him	O
,	O
What	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
it	O
again	O
?	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
the	O
15	O
l.	O
Note	O
was	O
not	O
of	O
his	O
Writing	O
;	O
and	O
this	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
others	O
that	O
knew	O
his	O
Hand	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
gain	O
'd	O
a	O
very	O
ill	O
Character	O
by	O
tricking	O
Practices	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
and	O
Joanna	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
for	O
Counterfeiting	O
the	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
and	O
making	O
of	O
Tinn	O
and	O
Copper	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
eighteen	O
counterfeit	O
Pieces	O
in	O
the	O
Likeness	O
of	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
forty	O
counterfeit	O
Piece	O
in	O
the	O
Likeness	O
of	O
Six	O
pences	O
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bowder	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Joanna	O
Wood	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
his	O
Mother	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
Tichbourn-Court	B-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
Mary	O
Hunt	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
frequently	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
Notice	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
,	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
kept	O
close	O
shut	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
busy	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
clinking	O
,	O
like	O
that	O
of	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shears	O
clipping	O
something	O
of	O
Mettaly	O
upon	O
which	O
suspecting	O
some	O
ill	O
Practices	O
to	O
be	O
carried	O
on	O
,	O
he	O
cut	O
a	O
Chink	O
in	O
the	O
Partition	O
,	O
resolving	O
to	O
make	O
an	O
Observation	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
that	O
accordingly	O
,	O
she	O
coming	O
the	O
twentieth	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Wood	O
with	O
her	O
Gown	O
off	O
and	O
a	O
Leather	O
Apron	O
before	O
her	O
,	O
rubbing	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
12	O
s.	O
lying	O
by	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
white	O
Stuff	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Materials	O
,	O
but	O
Hunt	O
's	O
Back	O
being	O
toward	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
discover	O
what	O
she	O
was	O
doing	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
discovered	O
the	O
Matter	O
to	O
his	O
Mother	O
,	O
who	O
advising	O
with	O
some	O
Neighbours	O
what	O
they	O
should	O
do	O
;	O
being	O
counselled	O
for	O
their	O
own	O
Safety	O
,	O
went	O
and	O
informed	O
Capt	O
.	O
Mills	O
,	O
the	O
High-Constable	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
who	O
sent	O
Mr.	O
Wootton	O
to	O
search	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wootton	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
sent	O
by	O
Capt	O
.	O
Mills	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
one	O
to	O
his	O
Assistance	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
and	O
forcing	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
on	O
a	O
sudden	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
had	O
any	O
Intimation	O
of	O
their	O
coming	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
Hunt	O
sitting	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
who	O
starting	O
back	O
at	O
the	O
opening	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
some	O
Pieces	O
of	O
the	O
counterfeit	O
Money	O
sell	O
from	O
her	O
(	O
he	O
supposed	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Lap	O
)	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Fire	O
a	O
Crucible	O
,	O
half	O
full	O
of	O
Mettal	O
melted	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
ordered	O
a	O
Watchman	O
to	O
take	O
off	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
hot	O
;	O
he	O
spilt	O
it	O
among	O
the	O
Coals	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Flask	O
lay	O
by	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
kicked	O
to	O
break	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
Mold	O
,	O
the	O
counterfeit	O
Money	O
flew	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
That	O
Wood	O
was	O
indeed	O
sitting	O
by	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
doing	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
The	O
Utensils	O
and	O
counterfeit	O
Money	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
were	O
broken	O
to	O
Pieces	O
by	O
Order	O
of	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
broke	O
by	O
the	O
Warden	O
of	O
the	O
Mint	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
Act	O
of	O
Parliament	O
.	O
Joanna	O
Wood	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
;	O
that	O
indeed	O
she	O
had	O
let	O
Hunt	O
be	O
in	O
her	O
Room	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
she	O
was	O
doing	O
,	O
till	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
to	O
fetch	O
out	O
some	O
Napkins	O
to	O
make	O
Clouts	O
of	O
,	O
Hunt	O
turn	O
'd	O
the	O
Key	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
lock	O
'd	O
her	O
in	O
.	O
Hunt	O
acknowledged	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
indeed	O
herself	O
was	O
guilty	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
Joanna	O
Wood	O
said	O
was	O
true	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
wholly	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Goldsmith	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
contrary	O
to	O
the	O
Acts	O
of	O
Parliament	O
made	O
in	O
the	O
eighth	O
and	O
ninth	O
Years	O
of	O
King	O
William	O
,	O
for	O
ascertaining	O
the	O
Fineness	O
of	O
wrought	O
Plate	O
,	O
did	O
make	O
a	O
silver	O
Salve	O
and	O
two	O
Cups	O
of	O
less	O
Fineness	O
than	O
11	O
Oz.10	O
,	O
d.	O
weight	O
per	O
1	O
Troy	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
affix	O
to	O
them	O
Stamps	O
,	O
counterfeiting	O
the	O
Stamp	O
of	O
the	O
Hallow	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
the	O
Offence	O
was	O
committed	O
before	O
the	O
Commencement	O
of	O
the	O
Act	O
of	O
Grace	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
like	O
Offence	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
Offence	O
likewise	O
being	O
committed	O
before	O
the	O
Act	O
of	O
Grace	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
like	O
Offence	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
before	O
the	O
Act	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
like	O
Offence	O
,	O
committed	O
about	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Court	O
being	O
of	O
Opinion	O
,	O
that	O
whereas	O
the	O
Act	O
of	O
Parliament	O
inflicts	O
a	O
Penalty	O
of	O
500	O
l.	O
on	O
such	O
Offenders	O
,	O
they	O
should	O
rather	O
be	O
prosecuted	O
at	O
Common	O
Law	O
than	O
by	O
Indictment	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death,13	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Banister	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Marshal	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Rochford	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Follard	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
Hugh	B-pers
Oakley	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Danly	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Murth	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Mason	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
and	O
Joanna	O
Wood	O
to	O
be	O
drawn	O
on	O
a	O
Sledge	O
and	O
Burnt	O
.	O
Buret	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
;	O
3.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Young	I-pers
alias	O
Saunders	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
Joanne	B-pers
Manning	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt,4	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Chalkley	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Maddox	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Maddox	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Dimer	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Longstass	I-pers
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
,	O
and	O
Fined	O
40	O
Marks	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
Women	O
pleaded	O
their	O
Bellies	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
being	O
impanelled	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
brought	O
in	O
with	O
Quick	O
Child	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
Some	O
BOOKS	O
printed	O
for	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
Edmund	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
and	O
Crown	O
in	O
Lombard	O
Street	O
,	O
near	O
Stocks	O
Market	O
.	O
THE	O
London	O
New	O
Method	O
and	O
Art	O
of	O
Teaching	O
Children	O
to	O
Spell	O
and	O
Read	O
;	O
so	O
as	O
they	O
may	O
,	O
without	O
the	O
Help	O
of	O
any	O
other	O
Books	O
,	O
read	O
the	O
Bible	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
twelve	O
Month	O
.	O
Note	O
,	O
This	O
Way	O
of	O
Teaching	O
is	O
approved	O
by	O
School	O
Masters	O
as	O
the	O
best	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
6	O
d.	O
with	O
great	O
allowance	O
to	O
those	O
who	O
sell	O
or	O
give	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
Note	O
,	O
There	O
are	O
some	O
printed	O
on	O
fine	O
Paper	O
,	O
bound	O
up	O
with	O
Cuts	O
;	O
pt.8	O
d.	O
For	O
the	O
Compleating	O
of	O
Psalmody	O
.	O
The	O
Deout	O
Singer	O
's	O
Guide	O
;	O
cantaining	O
all	O
the	O
Common	O
Tunes	O
How	O
in	O
the	O
with	O
select	O
Portions	O
of	O
the	O
Plns	O
adopted	O
to	O
each	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
Rules	O
for	O
singing	O
:	O
Treble	O
and	O
Bals	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
presis	O
'd	O
,	O
Directions	O
for	O
Parish	O
Clarks	O
in	O
the	O
Choice	O
of	O
proper	O
Plan	O
's	O
on	O
most	O
Occasions	O
.	O
Recommended	O
by	O
the	O
best	O
Singing	O
Masters	O
.	O
The	O
Second	O
Edition,8	O
s.	O
Price	O
bound	O
1	O
s.	O
The	O
Daily	O
Self-Examinant	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
An	O
earnest	O
Persuade	O
to	O
the	O
Duty	O
of	O
Daily	O
Selfexamination	O
;	O
with	O
Devout	O
Prayers	O
,	O
Meditations	O
,	O
Directions	O
and	O
Ejaculations	O
for	O
an	O
Holy	O
Life	O
and	O
Happy	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
6th	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
6	O
l.	O
The	O
Devout	O
Christian	O
's	O
Preparative	O
to	O
Death	O
Written	O
by	O
Enamus	O
now	O
render	O
'd	O
into	O
English	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
are	O
added	O
Meditations	O
,	O
Prayers	O
and	O
Directions	O
for	O
Sick	O
and	O
Dying	O
Persons	O
.	O
Recommended	O
as	O
proper	O
to	O
be	O
given	O
at	O
rals	O
.	O
The	O
6th	O
Edit	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
6	O
d.	O
Both	O
by	O
Robert	O
Watchred	O
D.	O
D.	O
Rector	O
of	O
Claston	O
on	O
in	O
Kent	O
.	O
Maximum	O
in	O
Minimo	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Dextertity	O
compleated	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Method	O
of	O
writing	O
Short-Hand.10	O
which	O
are	O
added	O
the	O
Terms	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Law	O
compleat	O
in	O
Characters	O
use	O
to	O
all	O
Lawyers	O
and	O
others	O
who	O
take	O
Truth	O
at	O
Never	O
done	O
till	O
now	O
.	O
By	O
Sames	O
.	O
The	O
oble	O
curi	O
ously	O
engrav	O
'd	O
on	O
30	O
Copper-plates	O
,	O
Price	O
1	O
s.6	O
d.	O
The	O
Benefit	O
of	O
Early	O
Piety	O
,	O
recommended	O
to	O
the	O
Young	O
Persons	O
,	O
and	O
particularly	O
to	O
those	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
Lisdon	O
.	O
By	O
W.	O
smythioes	O
,	O
late	O
Morning	O
Lecturer	O
of	O
St.	O
Michied	O
to	O
Marshel	O
,	O
London	O
.	O
The	O
Third	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
6	O
d.	O
Mr.	O
Jurdaine	O
's	O
Dyodecimal	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
most	O
Concise	O
and	O
Exact	O
Method	O
extant	O
.	O
In	O
Three	O
Books	O
Containing	O
Notation	O
,	O
Addition	O
,	O
Subtraction	O
,	O
Matciplicatision	O
,	O
Division	O
,	O
Reduction	O
,	O
Extraction	O
of	O
the	O
Square	O
and	O
Cube	O
Roots	O
,	O
Rule	O
of	O
Proportion	O
Direct	O
and	O
Reverse	O
,	O
Ddodecimally	O
performed	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
Practically	O
applied	O
to	O
the	O
measuring	O
of	O
all	O
sorts	O
on	O
Superficies	O
,	O
and	O
Solids	O
,	O
as	O
Board	O
,	O
Glass	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Timber	O
,	O
Stone	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Guaging	O
of	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
Brewers	O
Toub	O
and	O
Casks	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
that	O
with	O
more	O
Ease	O
and	O
Expedition	O
,	O
than	O
by	O
Voiger	O
or	O
Decimal	O
Arithmetick	O
.	O
Very	O
useful	O
for	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
Men	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
Gentlemen	O
as	O
others	O
,	O
but	O
especially	O
for	O
Machanus	O
,	O
Writing	O
Masters	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
Measuring	O
Artifiter	O
.	O
And	O
all	O
the	O
Rules	O
made	O
Plain	O
,	O
and	O
Basnest	O
for	O
the	O
deanest	O
Capacity.8	O
s.	O
Price	O
Bound	O
2	O
s.6	O
d.	O
THE	O
Child	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Hillyard	O
Glasiee	O
in	O
Baldwins	O
Gridens	O
near	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
in	O
such	O
extream	O
Danger	O
by	O
the	O
hard	O
Breeding	O
and	O
Curting	O
of	O
its	O
Teeth	O
;	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
given	O
over	O
by	O
every	O
one	O
as	O
a	O
dead	O
Child	O
.	O
All	O
Means	O
,	O
that	O
could	O
be	O
thought	O
of	O
were	O
tried	O
to	O
relieve	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
no	O
Purpose	O
,	O
it	O
lying	O
as	O
every	O
has	O
thought	O
ready	O
to	O
Expire	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
the	O
Celebrated	O
NECKLACE	O
for	O
Childrens	O
Teeth	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
:	O
It	O
was	O
no	O
sooner	O
about	O
his	O
Neck	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
very	O
sensible	O
Change	O
vilibly	O
appeared	O
,	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
presently	O
or	O
cut	O
its	O
Teeth	O
easily	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Blessing	O
of	O
God	O
perfectly	O
well	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Amazement	O
of	O
all	O
who	O
saw	O
it	O
,	O
Of	O
the	O
Truth	O
of	O
which	O
any	O
Person	O
may	O
be	O
farther	O
fully	O
satisfied	O
at	O
the	O
Place	O
abovementioned	O
,	O
This	O
wonderful	O
.	O
ANODINE	O
NECKLACE	O
,	O
Price	O
5	O
s.	O
with	O
Ditections	O
for	O
wearing	O
it	O
,	O
is	O
sold	O
up	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
this	O
Necklace	O
without	O
Temple-Bar	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
Golden	O
Key	O
is	O
King-trees	O
,	O
Westminster	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Cooper	O
's	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Charles	O
Court	O
in	O
the	O
strand	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Garway	O
's	O
at	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
Cornhill	O
.	O
But	O
those	O
Persons	O
who	O
go	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Garway	O
Shop	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
are	O
desired	O
to	O
ask	O
expresry	O
for	O
this	O
Anodyne	O
Necklace	O
,	O
least	O
they	O
have	O
another	O
sold	O
them	O
instead	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Culus	O
,	O
There	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
seen	O
:	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
George	O
,	O
over	O
against	O
the	O
King	O
on	O
Holibon	O
at	O
Stocks	O
Market	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
the	O
most	O
wonderful	O
Piece	O
that	O
in	O
Europe	O
;	O
being	O
an	O
Astonomical	O
And	O
Musical	O
CLOCK	O
,	O
Far	O
exceeding	O
the	O
Original	O
,	O
and	O
valu	O
'd	O
at	O
1000	O
Guineas	O
.	O
The	O
chief	O
Performances	O
of	O
this	O
most	O
Noice	O
and	O
Famous	O
Machine	O
,	O
are	O
as	O
follow	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
every	O
three	O
Hours	O
,	O
or	O
it	O
phasure	O
,	O
it	O
plays	O
variety	O
of	O
j	O
gr.Minners	O
,	O
Marches	O
,	O
Country	O
Dauces	O
,	O
and	O
Opera	O
Tunes	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
og	O
m	O
,	O
Here	O
,	O
flagolet	O
,	O
single	O
or	O
if	O
Cen	O
fort	O
,	O
with	O
such	O
rogllar	O
Shakes	O
and	O
proper	O
Graces	O
,	O
that	O
its	O
Performance	O
is	O
infinitely	O
beyond	O
what	O
can	O
be	O
imagin	O
'd	O
.	O
But	O
what	O
most	O
agreeably	O
for	O
prizes	O
all	O
that	O
hear	O
it	O
,	O
is	O
,	O
the	O
sweet	O
Hirmony	O
that	O
follows	O
from	O
an	O
Avery	O
of	O
Birds	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
indicted	O
to	O
such	O
wonderful	O
Perfection	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
's	O
one	O
to	O
be	O
distinguish	O
'd	O
from	O
Nature	O
itself	O
.	O
It	O
shows	O
the	O
Golden	O
Number	O
,	O
Spact	O
,	O
the	O
Cicle	O
of	O
the	O
Sun	O
,	O
and	O
Dominical	O
Letterisor	O
over	O
both	O
Old	O
and	O
New	O
Style	O
,	O
by	O
2	O
Hidlex	O
or	O
Hands	O
;	O
the	O
one	O
makes	O
Revoluctuon	O
once	O
in	O
10	O
Years	O
,	O
the	O
28	O
Years	O
.	O
Likewise	O
it	O
they-th	O
the	O
Digrnal	O
and	O
A	O
poeal	O
at	O
Motion	O
of	O
the	O
Sun	O
with	O
the	O
exact	O
Time	O
of	O
his	O
and	O
Setting	O
,	O
the	O
Length	O
of	O
the	O
Day	O
and	O
Night	O
at	O
all	O
Times	O
also	O
his	O
Meridian	O
Altitude	O
;	O
the	O
Increase	O
.	O
Decrease	O
,	O
Full	O
and	O
Change	O
of	O
the	O
Moon	O
,	O
lites	O
Surching	O
;	O
Likewise	O
Eighteen	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
noted	O
Fixed	O
with	O
there	O
,	O
Time	O
of	O
coming	O
on	O
the	O
Meridian	O
.	O
It	O
's	O
shows	O
the	O
Time	O
of	O
High	O
Water	O
at	O
thirty	O
several	O
passed	O
with	O
tho	O
'	O
Aspects	O
of	O
the	O
woodgeate	O
;	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Ceriosities	O
too	O
redious	O
to	O
mention	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
seen	O
from	O
Nine	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
to	O
Nine	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
without	O
life	O
of	O
Time	O
.	O
The	O
Prices	O
are.1	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
lowest	O
.	O
vivat	O
Rex	O
.	O
Not	O
This	O
Famous	O
C	O
L	O
O	O
C	O
K	O
was	O
never	O
shown	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
made	O
by	O
Cduthef	O
Pischbeck	O
living	O
at	O
Smithfield	O
.	O
Bars	O
,	O
that	O
made	O
the	O
sober	O
which	O
was	O
shown	O
this	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
by	O
a	O
Noble	O
Peer	O
of	O
this	O
Realin	O
.	O
By	O
to	O
be	O
Duke	O
of	O
boroghs	O
Head	O
feetstreet	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Cloth	O
A	O
German	O
,	O
born	O
without	O
Hands	O
,	O
Feet	O
,	O
or	O
Thighs	O
,	O
(	O
that	O
Acyee	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Kingdom	O
before	O
)	O
who	O
does	O
such	O
Actions	O
,	O
as	O
none	O
else	O
can	O
do	O
with	O
Hands	O
and	O
Feet	O
:	O
He	O
has	O
perform	O
'd	O
belive	O
most	O
Kings	O
Princess	O
and	O
Nobles	O
of	O
Foreign	O
Countries	O
:	O
He	O
makes	O
a	O
Pen	O
,	O
and	O
writes	O
several	O
Hands	O
as	O
quick	O
and	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
any	O
Writing	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
will	O
write	O
with	O
any	O
for	O
a	O
Wiger	O
:	O
He	O
draws	O
Paces	O
to	O
the	O
Life	O
,	O
Coa	O
's	O
of	O
Arms	O
.	O
Pictures	O
,	O
Flowers	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
with	O
a	O
Pen	O
very	O
clriously	O
:	O
He	O
threads	O
a	O
fine	O
Needle	O
very	O
quick	O
;	O
shuttles	O
a	O
Pack	O
of	O
Cards	O
,	O
and	O
deals	O
them	O
very	O
(	O
wise	O
:	O
He	O
plays	O
)	O
upon	O
the	O
Dulcioner	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
any	O
Musician	O
:	O
He	O
does	O
many	O
surprizing	O
Things	O
with	O
Cups	O
and	O
Balls	O
,	O
and	O
gives	O
the	O
Curlous	O
great	O
Satisfaction	O
thereby	O
:	O
He	O
plays	O
at	O
Skittles	O
several	O
Ways	O
very	O
well	O
:	O
He	O
charges	O
a	O
,	O
and	O
discharges	O
it	O
at	O
a	O
Mark	O
:	O
He	O
shaves	O
himself	O
very	O
dexterously	O
:	O
He	O
cuts	O
several	O
curious	O
Fancies	O
in	O
Wood	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
puts	O
into	O
Bottles	O
with	O
each	O
art	O
,	O
that	O
none	O
can	O
comprehend	O
;	O
and	O
many	O
other	O
Things	O
too	O
tedions	O
to	O
insert	O
here	O
.	O
He	O
waits	O
on	O
Gentlemen	O
and	O
Ladies	O
as	O
their	O
own	O
Houses	O
,	O
as	O
any	O
Hour	O
of	O
the	O
Day	O
,	O
if	O
desis	O
'd	O
.	O
VIVAT	O
REX	O
For	O
the	O
Good	O
of	O
the	O
Publish	O
.	O
WHereas	O
several	O
Gentlewomen	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
that	O
Sex	O
,	O
in	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
have	O
contrased	O
evil	O
Habit	O
of	O
Body	O
,	O
wherein	O
the	O
vicious	O
Humours	O
,	O
at	O
first	O
dispers	O
'd	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Whole	O
come	O
at	O
length	O
to	O
be	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
one	O
Part	O
or	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
times	O
,	O
for	O
Causes	O
too	O
long	O
to	O
be	O
hear	O
mentioned	O
;	O
are	O
thrown	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Womb	O
,	O
occationing	O
a	O
dangerous	O
Weakness	O
in	O
that	O
Part	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
neglected	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
turns	O
Cancerous	O
,	O
add	O
often	O
prove	O
.	O
Iscure	O
the	O
Diabetes	O
when	O
when	O
over	O
by	O
all	O
other	O
Persons	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
to	O
acquaint	O
all	O
such	O
in	O
may	O
have	O
occasion	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
speedy	O
Relief	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
had	O
from	O
a	O
exprences	O
's	O
Midwife	O
,	O
dwelling	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Arms	O
,	O
a	O
Watch-Makers	O
,	O
near	O
Excess	O
Exchange	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
who	O
perform	O
'd	O
a	O
Coler	O
upon	O
a	O
Lady	O
at	O
the	O
Bub	O
,	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
given	O
over	O
by	O
the	O
Physicians	O
,	O
and	O
frace	O
has	O
Cured	O
several	O
Gentlewomen	O
and	O
others	O
in	O
the	O
City	O
and	O
Suburbs	O
of	O
London	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
put	O
my	O
self	O
in	O
Publick	O
Print	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
satisfy	O
the	O
Assicted	O
where	O
they	O
may	O
have	O
present	O
and	O
Relief	O
.	O
Next	O
Door	O
to	O
the	O
Tin	O
Shop	O
near	O
Exeter-Exchange	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
LIveth	O
a	O
Doctor	O
that	O
sells	O
a	O
pleasant	O
Cordial	O
Cathartick	O
Medicine	O
,	O
which	O
hath	O
neither	O
Take	O
nor	O
smell	O
,	O
nor	O
composed	O
of	O
any	O
Mercurial	O
Preparation	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
most	O
effectual	O
Cure	O
against	O
all	O
Cholicks	O
:	O
It	O
gives	O
present	O
Relief	O
in	O
the	O
Gravel	O
,	O
Dropsy	O
,	O
Scorvy	O
and	O
Rheumatiod	O
;	O
destroying	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
Worms	O
in	O
Young	O
or	O
Old	O
,	O
and	O
sweetens	O
the	O
whole	O
Mals	O
of	O
Blood	O
.	O
It	O
likewise	O
cares	O
Dizinels	O
and	O
Swimings	O
in	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
Vapours	O
and	O
Pains	O
in	O
the	O
Stomach	O
.	O
Three	O
Papers	O
will	O
cure	O
any	O
of	O
these	O
Diff	O
taking	O
one	O
every	O
third	O
Day	O
.	O
Those	O
that	O
take	O
it	O
may	O
go	O
abroad	O
,	O
work	O
or	O
play	O
;	O
without	O
any	O
manner	O
of	O
Confinement	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
Paper	O
.	O
Those	O
that	O
are	O
really	O
poor	O
may	O
have	O
theirs	O
for	O
nothing	O
.	O
And	O
also	O
sold	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Garraway	O
's	O
Shop	O
at	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
London	O
.	O
LONDON	O
