TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDING	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
,	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
Thursday	O
Friday	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
4th	O
5th	O
6th	O
and	O
7th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
December,1718	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Fourth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign.12	O
.	O
Dec.1717	O
.	O
BEfore	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
LEWEN	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Worshipful	O
Sir	O
Peter	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Blencoe	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Eyers	O
,	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Midlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
Names	O
there	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Oliver	B-pers
Cambes	I-pers
John	B-pers
Peak	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
Mark	B-pers
Newth	I-pers
William	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
Peter	B-pers
Wardell	I-pers
Pargeter	B-pers
Aussin	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Hinks	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Tomlins	I-pers
John	B-pers
Patch	I-pers
William	B-pers
Butterworth	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cliff	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Curbert	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Ingrans	I-pers
Abraham	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Billing	I-pers
John	B-pers
Cash	I-pers
John	B-pers
Meard	I-pers
William	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
William	B-pers
Tame	I-pers
Alexandar	B-pers
Kilgore	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
John	B-pers
Willson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Robert	B-pers
Whitlock	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Faiths	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Still	O
Head	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Hugh	B-pers
Massam	I-pers
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
sitting	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
he	O
perceived	O
the	O
Still	O
Head	O
,	O
slide	O
off	O
from	O
the	O
Shop	O
Window	O
and	O
immediately	O
pursued	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
fact	O
and	O
pleaded	O
it	O
was	O
given	O
him	O
to	O
hold	O
by	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
.	O
The	O
fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Wett	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Dear	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
felonionsly	O
stealing	O
a	O
Frock	O
value	O
2	O
Shillings	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
John	B-pers
Gumly	I-pers
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
being	O
in	O
Stepney	B-place
Fields	I-place
near	O
the	O
half-way	O
House	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
2	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
a	O
ditch	O
doing	O
something	O
to	O
John	O
James	O
,	O
(	O
a	O
Boy	O
of	O
about	O
5	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
)	O
and	O
Suspecting	O
them	O
,	O
examined	O
them	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
doing	O
there	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
gave	O
him	O
ill	O
Language	O
,	O
flinging	O
a	O
brick	O
bat	O
at-him	O
,	O
but	O
another	O
Lad	O
coming	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
ran	O
away	O
and	O
Rubard	O
West	O
drop	O
'd	O
the	O
Childs	O
Cloths	O
and	O
the	O
Buckles	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
confirmed	O
by	O
the	O
other	O
Lad	O
that	O
was	O
there	O
likewise	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
that	O
coming	O
by	O
,	O
knew	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
following	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
they	O
apprehended	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Johns	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
dwelling	O
Home	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Ridly	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
and	O
Stealing	O
from	O
thence	O
30	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
val.20l	O
.	O
24	O
pair	O
of	O
Buckles	O
value	O
12	O
l.5	O
Silver	O
Snuff	O
boxes	O
val.5	O
L	O
and	O
a	O
show	O
Glass	O
5s	O
.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mary	O
Ridly	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
Ruth	B-pers
Willoughby	I-pers
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
deposed	O
her	O
Mistress	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
ordered	O
her	O
to	O
shut	O
up	O
the	O
Shop	O
and	O
make	O
21	O
last	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
bolting	O
the	O
Shop	O
Door	O
about	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
,	O
setting	O
the	O
show	O
Glass	O
upon	O
the	O
further	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
setting	O
a	O
Candle	O
lighted	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
backward	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchin	O
,	O
staying	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
her	O
return	O
found	O
the	O
Shop	O
Door	O
open	O
and	O
the	O
show	O
Glass	O
and	O
forementiond	O
Plate	O
and	O
Rings	O
s	O
gone	O
.	O
Obadiah	B-pers
Leman	I-pers
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
himself	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
one	O
Henry	B-pers
Chickley	I-pers
,	O
went	O
about	O
the	O
time	O
specified	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
into	O
Wapping	B-place
,	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
what	O
they	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
fixing	O
upon	O
this	O
house	O
,	O
they	O
all	O
stood	O
over	O
against	O
the	O
door	O
to	O
cover	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
was	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
that	O
Walker	O
,	O
the	O
Younger	O
,	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
saying	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
Bax	O
man	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
a	O
Latin	O
word	O
,	O
which	O
with	O
them	O
signified	O
the	O
way	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
commission	O
of	O
the	O
fact	O
)	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
brought	O
out	O
the	O
Glass	O
case	O
and	O
goods	O
.	O
Pulled	O
off	O
his	O
Coat	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
over	O
the	O
Glass	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
might	O
not	O
be	O
seen	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
Carry	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
into	O
White	O
Chappel	O
Fields	O
,	O
broke	O
the	O
Glass	O
to	O
pieces	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
also	O
found	O
there	O
)	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Plate	O
and	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
for	O
20l	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
fact	O
and	O
were	O
old	O
Offenders	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Proof	O
but	O
that	O
of	O
Obediah	O
Loman	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gurney	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Game	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stanmore	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
4	O
Cows	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
and	O
1	O
Heifer	O
value	O
5	O
L	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Aldwin	I-pers
the	O
9th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Cow	O
and	O
Heifer	O
were	O
feeding	O
in	O
the	O
Grounds	O
and	O
he	O
missing	O
them	O
followed	O
the	O
Track	O
till	O
he	O
heard	O
of	O
them	O
and	O
found	O
then	O
at	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Scrivener	O
's	O
at	O
Lambeth	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Scrivener	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
Cattle	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
set	O
up	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
driving	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Horns	O
at	O
Newington	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Earl	B-pers
of	I-pers
Carnarvan	I-pers
,	O
he	O
suspecting	O
then	O
;	O
stopp	O
'd	O
the	O
Cows	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
and	O
that	O
upon	O
his	O
taking	O
them	O
strictly	O
with	O
not	O
coming	O
honestly	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
Gurney	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
favourable	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
they	O
had	O
stolen	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Earle	B-place
of	I-place
Carnarvan	I-place
's	I-place
Grounds	I-place
.	O
They	O
Confest	O
the	O
fact	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
body	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Blewett	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Child	O
's	O
holland	O
Shifts	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Frock	O
1	O
s.6	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Hyatt	I-pers
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
going	O
along	O
in	O
Cornhill	B-place
with	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Jostle	O
and	O
presently	O
he	O
missed	O
the	O
Things	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
immediately	O
seised	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
running	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
3	O
Boys	O
who	O
threw	O
down	O
the	O
things	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
not	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
,	O
but	O
notwithstanding	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lemmy	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Stephen	I-place
's	I-place
Coleman	I-place
street	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Benjaman	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
wife	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
serving	O
a	O
Customer	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
comes	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
stooping	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Shoes	O
off	O
from	O
a	O
seat	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
Crying	O
out	O
her	O
Daughter	O
stop	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
The	O
daughter	O
deposed	O
that	O
at	O
her	O
stoping	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
one	O
pair	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Son	O
deposed	O
he	O
follow	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
got	O
him	O
apprehended	O
and	O
brought	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Shop	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
pleaded	O
he	O
was	O
only	O
passing	O
by	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
so	O
was	O
apprehended	O
but	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
But	O
notwithstanding	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Le	I-place
Bow	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Farmer	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sheet	O
value	O
2	O
s	O
and	O
4	O
Yards	O
of	O
printed	O
Linen	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
43	O
Culgee	O
Handkerchiefs	O
value	O
45	O
s	O
20	O
Ells	O
of	O
Garlick	O
Holland	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Belch	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Son	O
deposed	O
the	O
Wall	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
broken	O
down	O
large	O
enough	O
for	O
a	O
person	O
to	O
get	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
lost	O
.	O
A	O
Watchman	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
apprehended	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
same	O
Morning	O
between	O
4	O
and	O
5	O
a-Clock	O
,	O
and	O
examining	O
him	O
about	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
answer	O
'd	O
he	O
brought	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
carrying	O
them	O
to	O
Drury	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
telling	O
him	O
he	O
must	O
go	O
before	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
down	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
Richard	O
Farmer	O
added	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
Servant	O
to	O
his	O
Father	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
dismiss	O
'd	O
for	O
being	O
a	O
loose	O
person	O
,	O
wereupon	O
they	O
made	O
search	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
got	O
him	O
apprehended	O
.	O
The	O
Watchman	O
was	O
positive	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
before	O
apprehended	O
with	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
swore	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecuters	O
Son	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
the	O
Fact	O
and	O
brought	O
some	O
persons	O
who	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
prove	O
him	O
Lunatick	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
so	O
effectually	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
acquited	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Bartholomew	I-place
the	I-place
Lesser	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
value	O
30	O
s	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Horseman	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
an	O
Acquaintance	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Wilson	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Wigg	O
.	O
The	O
Wigg	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
by	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
for	O
5	O
s.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
nothing	O
material	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
5	O
l.	O
of	O
Brass	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Beedle	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
Sept	O
.	O
last	O
,	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bingley	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Shettier	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Mott	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Dopham	I-pers
of	O
Acton	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Silvester	B-pers
Proud	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
.	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
4l.2s	O
.	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
all	O
Three	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
and	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
3	O
s.6	O
d.	O
They	O
were	O
also	O
all	O
Three	O
indicted	O
the	O
third	O
time	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Blackwell	I-pers
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
and	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
a	O
fourth	O
time	O
for	O
assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Green	I-pers
at	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
and	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
5	O
s.	O
Silvester	O
Proud	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
coming	O
with	O
3	O
Waggons	O
towards	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
set	O
upon	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
near	O
Action	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
asleep	O
in	O
his	O
Waggon	O
(	O
it	O
being	O
about	O
One	O
a	O
.	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
)	O
was	O
waked	O
by	O
his	O
Wife	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
believ	O
'd	O
somebody	O
was	O
taking	O
away	O
his	O
Horse	O
from	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
jumped	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Waggon	O
and	O
was	O
immediately	O
set	O
upon	O
by	O
Bingley	O
,	O
who	O
cutting	O
him	O
over	O
the	O
Head	O
several	O
times	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
kill	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
presently	O
deliver	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
cutting	O
him	O
Edward	O
Mott	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
4	O
l.2	O
s.	O
and	O
also	O
robbed	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
rob	O
the	O
other	O
Persons	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
Bingley	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
with	O
Sword	O
and	O
Pistol	O
in	O
hand	O
,	O
bidding	O
him	O
stand	O
and	O
give	O
him	O
his	O
Money	O
threatning	O
to	O
Kill	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
answered	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
searching	O
him	O
took	O
out	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
leaving	O
some	O
Half-pence	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
Silvester	B-pers
Proud	I-pers
,	O
immediately	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Waggon	O
Bingley	O
left	O
him	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
rob	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
and	O
demanded	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
feeling	O
his	O
Breeches	O
felt	O
the	O
Money	O
that	O
was	O
left	O
hastning	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
it	O
him	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
he	O
bid	O
him	O
be	O
easy	O
and	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
reply	O
'd	O
it	O
wasno	O
time	O
to	O
be	O
easy	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Blackwell	I-pers
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
Evidence	O
before	O
given	O
,	O
adding	O
that	O
Sherrier	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
making	O
at	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
swearing	O
he	O
would	O
shoot	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
him	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
thereupon	O
gave	O
him	O
4	O
s.	O
William	O
Green	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
Blackwell	O
's	O
Waggon	O
Joseph	B-pers
Sherrier	I-pers
came	O
to	O
him	O
demanding	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
threatning	O
him	O
to	O
kill	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
2	O
Half	O
Crowns	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
asking	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
Shilling	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
G	O
-	O
J	O
D	O
-	O
m	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
away	O
to	O
the	O
next	O
Waggon	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Kettle	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
her	O
Landlady	O
's	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
them	O
all	O
say	O
they	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
them	O
there	O
again	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
full	O
of	O
Money	O
.	O
Silvester	O
Proud	O
added	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
having	O
gotten	O
some	O
Inteligence	O
of	O
them	O
and	O
a	O
Warrant	O
went	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
them	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
heard	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
be	O
came	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
into	O
the	O
Fields	O
to	O
decide	O
the	O
Dispute	O
as	O
to	O
sharing	O
the	O
Money	O
by	O
the	O
Dint	O
of	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
bearing	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
thence	O
to	O
Mary-bone	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
chither	O
and	O
found	O
only	O
Bingley	O
who	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
sight	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
took	O
to	O
his	O
Heels	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
pursued	O
and	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
2	O
were	O
afterwards	O
apprechended	O
at	O
Westwinster	O
.	O
The	O
Facts	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
each	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
all	O
three	O
guilty	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
four	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Perdue	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Foden	I-pers
about	O
11	O
a-Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
13	O
th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
being	O
in	O
Bed	O
and	O
asleep	O
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
heard	O
the	O
Bolt	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
fall	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
waked	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
called	O
out	O
to	O
know	O
who	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
answer	O
'd	O
a	O
Friend	O
,	O
her	O
Brother	O
:	O
His	O
Wife	O
confirm	O
'd	O
this	O
,	O
adding	O
,	O
she	O
immediately	O
jump	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
Bed	O
,	O
running	O
into	O
the	O
next	O
Room	O
in	O
her	O
Shift	O
,	O
catching	O
hold	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
Men	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
by	O
the	O
Coat	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
got	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
slipping	O
by	O
her	O
ran	O
away	O
and	O
got	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
seeing	O
the	O
Petticoat	O
hang	O
up	O
at	O
a	O
Broker	O
's	O
challeng	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
who	O
sent	O
for	O
one	O
Jane	B-pers
Preston	I-pers
of	O
whom	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
bought	O
it	O
.	O
Jane	O
Preston	O
depos	O
'd	O
the	O
Coat	O
was	O
given	O
her	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
Woman	O
in	O
Holmes	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
being	O
present	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
6	O
d	O
for	O
selling	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
carried	O
the	O
Money	O
to	O
Holme	O
's	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
but	O
Holmes	O
bid	O
her	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
denied	O
their	O
knowing	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
Holmes	O
called	O
one	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
so	O
scurvy	O
a	O
Character	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
better	O
have	O
let	O
him	O
a	O
lone	O
,	O
he	O
telling	O
the	O
Court	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
scandalous	O
Person	O
,	O
a	O
Thief-Taker	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
a	O
common	O
Receptacle	O
for	O
Thieves	O
and	O
Pick-pockets	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Proof	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
the	O
Fact	O
charged	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Merry	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Anne	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Brocaded	O
Silk	O
Wastecoat	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
Embroider	O
'd	O
Housings	O
and	O
Holster	O
Caps	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
40	O
L	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Chetwynd	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
the	O
26	O
th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
served	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
in	O
the	O
Quality	O
of	O
a	O
Valet	O
de	O
Ghambre	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
Things	O
several	O
of	O
them	O
being	O
committed	O
to	O
his	O
Charge	O
,	O
he	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
saying	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
own	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
not	O
willing	O
to	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
any	O
more	O
than	O
a	O
Breach	O
of	O
Trust	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Court	O
were	O
of	O
another	O
Opinion	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
accordingly	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Simon	B-pers
Nibbs	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
steal	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
Sept	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Lock	O
of	O
his	O
Yard	O
Door	O
had	O
been	O
open	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Glass	O
broke	O
,	O
a	O
Bar	O
taken	O
out	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
Window	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
living	O
at	O
next	O
Door	O
,	O
being	O
up	O
about	O
12	O
a-Clock	O
,	O
perceived	O
some	O
persons	O
about	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
suspected	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Watch	O
man	O
coming	O
his	O
round	O
she	O
inform	O
'd	O
him	O
of	O
her	O
Suspicion	O
.	O
who	O
called	O
up	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
Watchman	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
they	O
apprehended	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
dark	O
Lanthorn	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Materials	O
for	O
dark	O
Work	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
was	O
much	O
in	O
Drink	O
and	O
knew	O
not	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
thing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
;	O
but	O
could	O
give	O
no	O
good	O
Account	O
of	O
himself	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nicholson	I-pers
(	O
2	O
little	O
Boys	O
)	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
pocket	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Daby	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
value	O
2	O
s.6	O
d.	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
Nov	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
Street	O
near	B-place
the	I-place
Temple	I-place
gate	I-place
,	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
apprehended	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
Clerk	O
having	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
about	O
his	O
Neck	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Handkerchiefs	O
a	O
piece	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Pitts	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
felonously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Kettle	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Willmot	I-pers
the	O
18th	O
of	O
Nov	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
the	O
Kettle	O
was	O
stolen	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
and	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
However	O
he	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
alledging	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
given	O
him	O
by	O
his	O
Sister	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
her	O
Landlord	O
's	O
seizing	O
her	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
believing	O
him	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Abigail	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Gotier	I-pers
2	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
and	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Kemp	O
passing	O
along	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
,	O
who	O
ask	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
invited	O
them	O
to	O
their	O
Lodging	O
,	O
telling	O
them	O
their	O
Landlord	O
sold	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
good	O
Brandy	O
:	O
That	O
accordingly	O
they	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Thompson	O
's	O
had	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
more	O
:	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
telling	O
him	O
the	O
beliv	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
Money	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
to	O
pay	O
his	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
about	O
15	O
or	O
16	O
Shillings	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
God	O
:	O
To	O
convince	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
singled	O
our	O
2	O
Guineas	O
,	O
laying	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Palm	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
snatch	O
'd	O
them	O
out	O
,	O
putting	O
one	O
into	O
her	O
Mouth	O
,	O
and	O
dropping	O
the	O
other	O
into	O
her	O
Bosom	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
he	O
demanded	O
his	O
Money	O
:	O
Which	O
she	O
not	O
returning	O
,	O
he	O
knoked	O
for	O
the	O
Landlord	O
;	O
who	O
was	O
so	O
far	O
from	O
taking	O
his	O
Part	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
vindicted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
calling	O
him	O
Rogue	O
,	O
and	O
stalking	O
him	O
,	O
demanded	O
his	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
5	O
s.	O
for	O
4	O
Drams	O
of	O
Cherry-Brandy	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Companion	O
Mr.	O
Kemp	O
paid	O
;	O
and	O
going	O
down	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
secur	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
acknowledg	O
'd	O
her	O
being	O
pick	O
'd	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
drinking	O
together	O
,	O
but	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
saying	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
near	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
Mr.	O
Kemp	O
's	O
Confort	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
:	O
Adding	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Kemp	O
being	O
asleep	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
would	O
needs	O
have	O
sent	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
Penniworth	O
of	O
Rods	O
to	O
have	O
flogg	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
;	O
which	O
because	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
,	O
he	O
charg	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
robbing	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Kemp	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
could	O
say	O
little	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
taking	O
the	O
Guineas	O
:	O
Whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Sanditch	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Snelgrove	I-pers
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
some	O
Time	O
since	O
been	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
needs	O
have	O
a	O
Tankard	O
,	O
scrap	O
'd	O
Acquaintance	O
with	O
some	O
Persons	O
that	O
were	O
drinking	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Tankad	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
with	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
before	O
they	O
mis	O
'd	O
either	O
Tankard	O
or	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
happening	O
to	O
stop	O
near	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
saw	O
a	O
Person	O
come	O
running	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
something	O
like	O
Drink	O
or	O
Water	O
fall	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
as	O
thrown	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Pot	O
,	O
and	O
suspecting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
who	O
running	O
along	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Tankard	O
rattle	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
apprehended	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
intend	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
but	O
having	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
saw	O
an	O
Acquaintance	O
go	O
by	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
went	O
out	O
in	O
a	O
Hurry	O
to	O
overtake	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Tankard	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
But	O
this	O
phusible	O
Pretence	O
did	O
not	O
prevent	O
the	O
Jury	O
from	O
finding	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
35	O
s.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
2	O
Corolus	O
Broad	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
valu	O
'd	O
at	O
23	O
s.6	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Brinny	I-pers
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
having	O
been	O
at	O
Market	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Loin	O
of	O
Mutton	O
in	O
one	O
Hand	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
in	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Goose	O
thrown	O
over	O
his	O
Shoulder	O
;	O
and	O
going	O
up	O
the	O
Alley	O
where	O
he	O
dwelt	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
She	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
parlying	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
needs	O
be	O
busy	O
about	O
his	O
Breeches	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Money	O
.	O
But	O
he	O
not	O
swearing	O
positively	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Hollywell	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Day	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
at	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
de	O
pos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
having	O
lock	O
'd	O
his	O
Chamber	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Street	O
Door	O
on	O
the	O
Latch	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
to	O
work	O
;	O
and	O
some	O
small	O
Time	O
after	O
going	O
up	O
Stains	O
,	O
saw	O
his	O
Chamber	O
open	O
;	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Good	O
;	O
and	O
running	O
out	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
speaking	O
to	O
a	O
Friend	O
that	O
had	O
seen	O
a	O
Person	O
carrying	O
a	O
Bundle	O
they	O
persu	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
she	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
ease	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
Shop-Mares	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
carrying	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
nothing	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Bundle	O
,	O
nor	O
how	O
it	O
was	O
come	O
by	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Presence	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Whippy	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pauls	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
old	O
Iron	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Atchinson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
a	O
Boat	O
to	O
the	O
Ship	O
,	O
entred	O
the	O
Ship	O
,	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Carpenter	O
's	O
Cabbin	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Gurnd	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
off	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
not	O
being	O
carry	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Ship	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquited	O
him	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White	I-place
chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bevis	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
Linnen	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
30	O
s.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
7	O
a-Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
not	O
staying	O
above	O
half	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hours	O
but	O
at	O
her	O
Return	O
found	O
her	O
Window	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
gone	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Custom	O
house	O
Officer	O
,	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
gotten	O
run	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
Examination	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
flung	O
them	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
immediately	O
peru	O
'd	O
and	O
taken	O
;	O
and	O
not	O
giving	O
a	O
satisfactory	O
Account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
saying	O
sometimes	O
one	O
thing	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
other	O
times	O
another	O
,	O
he	O
secur	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
upon	O
his	O
Trial	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
hir	O
'd	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
there	O
upon	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Raven	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
stuff	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Apparel	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
30	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Katherine	B-pers
Platt	I-pers
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
She	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
her	O
Stairs	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
her	O
Apron	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
old	O
preserve	O
that	O
she	O
washir	O
'd	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Canvas	O
Bag	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
6	O
Gunieas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
26	O
th	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Drawer	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
that	O
two	O
Men	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
missing	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
one	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
farther	O
Proof	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Carlisle	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pocket	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.2	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
19	O
s.	O
a	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s	O
and	O
2	O
s.6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Susan	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
her	O
Pocket	O
was	O
with	O
great	O
Violence	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
by	O
a	O
Boy	O
,	O
which	O
tearing	O
down	O
her	O
Petticoat	O
in	O
doing	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
oblig	O
'd	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
could	O
not	O
follow	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
be	O
got	O
off	O
:	O
She	O
verily	O
believ	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
not	O
positive	O
enough	O
to	O
influence	O
the	O
Jury	O
to	O
find	O
him	O
guilty	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Harrow	B-place
of	I-place
the	I-place
Hill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
felonously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Black	O
Mare	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Joanna	B-pers
Sexton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
for	O
stealing	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time,4	O
Ducks	O
and	O
a	O
Drake	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
.	O
Also	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing,2	O
Geese	O
and	O
a	O
Gander	O
,	O
value	O
5l	O
he	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Herth	I-pers
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
a	O
fourth	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
10	O
Geese	O
and	O
a	O
Gander	O
,	O
value	O
22s	O
.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Joanna	O
Sexton	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prison	O
and	O
another	O
Person	O
lurking	O
about	O
,	O
they	O
fore	O
,	O
ected	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
examining	O
their	O
Poultry	O
,	O
miss	O
'd	O
their	O
Ge	O
So	O
getting	O
Horses	O
they	O
follow	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
ller	O
and	O
seeing	O
a	O
Horse	O
with	O
two	O
Men	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
rode	O
past	O
them	O
,	O
(	O
but	O
before	O
they	O
over	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
jump	O
'd	O
off	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
they	O
spoke	O
to	O
force	O
Carriers	O
on	O
the	O
Road	O
to	O
assist	O
there	O
.	O
They	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
seiz	O
'd	O
them	O
both	O
;	O
but	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
apprehending	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Carriers	O
let	O
the	O
other	O
Person	O
make	O
his	O
Escape	O
.	O
That	O
upon	O
their	O
apprehending	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
not	O
only	O
their	O
Fowls	O
,	O
but	O
their	O
Mare	O
too	O
,	O
before	O
they	O
knew	O
they	O
had	O
lost	O
her	O
.	O
However	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
his	O
Trial	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
they	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
own	O
'd	O
upon	O
his	O
being	O
apprehended	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Fowls	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
borrow	O
'd	O
the	O
Mare	O
only	O
to	O
cafe	O
their	O
Shoulders	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
each	O
Indictment	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Fowls	O
;	O
but	O
hoping	O
they	O
delign	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
honest	O
as	O
when	O
they	O
had	O
brought	O
their	O
Geese	O
and	O
Ducks	O
to	O
a	O
good	O
Market	O
,	O
to	O
have	O
let	O
the	O
Mare	O
gone	O
home	O
to	O
Harrow	O
to	O
Supper	O
,	O
acquitted	O
him	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Stealing	O
hen	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Fulham	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
Plate	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
40	O
l.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
but	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Faulkener	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Accomplice	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Hayes	I-pers
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Dunn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Hampton	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
his	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
silver	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
value	O
8l	O
.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Snuffers	O
and	O
Snuff-pan	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
repeating	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Gasper	I-pers
,	O
Baron	O
Bothmar	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Prough	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Silver	O
Candlestick	O
was	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
young	O
Prince	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he,5	O
or	O
6	O
Minutes	O
before	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
who	O
enquir	O
'd	O
of	O
him	O
if	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
of	O
some	O
strange	O
sort	O
of	O
Name	O
lodg	O
'd	O
there	O
.	O
Omen	B-pers
Macharel	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Sullivans	O
Tent	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
in	O
a	O
Silver	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
3e	O
Shillings	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
Coronet	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Cypher	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
also	O
confirmed	O
by	O
Thomas	B-pers
Greenwood	I-pers
,	O
who	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Dun	O
and	O
Hayes	O
,	O
were	O
talking	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
heard	O
Hayes	O
tell	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
deliver	O
what	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
trouble	O
her	O
.	O
Colonel	O
Sullivan	B-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Hayes	O
brought	O
a	O
Silver	O
Candlestick	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
refused	O
it	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
heard	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
safe	O
to	O
keep	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
any	O
Plate	O
that	O
belonged	O
to	O
any	O
Nobleman	O
.	O
Lewis	B-pers
Luny	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Hayes	O
brought	O
3	O
pieces	O
of	O
a	O
Silver	O
Candlestick	O
to	O
him	O
sell	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
perceiving	O
the	O
Kings	O
Coat	O
of	O
Arms	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
scratched	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
apprehended	O
him	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Metheir	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Jane	O
Dun	O
brought	O
to	O
her	O
the	O
41b	O
piece	O
of	O
the	O
Candlestick	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
telling	O
her	O
she	O
had	O
found	O
that	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
old	O
Silver	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
bad	O
her	O
bring	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
came	O
not	O
again	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Metimellows	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Hayes	O
said	O
that	O
himself	O
had	O
given	O
the	O
Candlestick	O
to	O
Dun	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
Anne	O
Merbier	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Hayes	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
and	O
demanded	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
the	O
Candlestick	O
that	O
Dun	O
had	O
brought	O
,	O
telling	O
her	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Silversmith	O
in	O
the	O
Strant	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
straightned	O
for	O
money	O
,	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Candlestick	O
of	O
Jane	O
Dun	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
prove	O
nothing	O
,	O
nor	O
had	O
any	O
to	O
appear	O
for	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
Hayes	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
but	O
Anne	O
Dun	O
they	O
acquitted	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
1st	O
indictment	O
in	O
relation	O
to	O
Baron	B-pers
Bothmar	I-pers
,	O
Anthony	B-pers
Bolt	I-pers
deposed	O
the	O
Goods	O
before	O
mentioned	O
were	O
lost	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
Anne	O
Mace	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Jane	O
Dun	O
brought	O
her	O
such	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Candlesticks	O
as	O
had	O
been	O
described	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
refused	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
there	O
were	O
Coats	O
of	O
Arms	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Axtol	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Hayes	O
had	O
offer	O
'd	O
her	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
accept	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
things	O
not	O
being	O
produced	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
proved	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
both	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cranteloe	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anne	I-place
in	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Theophilas	B-pers
Hastings	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
the	O
Shirt	O
hanging	O
upon	O
a	O
Line	O
,	O
two	O
Persons	O
came	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
the	O
Shirt	O
of	O
from	O
the	O
Line	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
he	O
flung	O
the	O
Shirt	O
behind	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
passing	O
by	O
,	O
somebody	O
threw	O
the	O
Shirt	O
upon	O
his	O
Heels	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Petrey	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
in	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
3	O
pieces	O
of	O
Leather	O
,	O
value	O
20s	O
.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
November	O
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
the	O
Leather	O
,	O
putting	O
it	O
under	O
his	O
Coat	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
but	O
several	O
Persons	O
appeared	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
very	O
old	O
,	O
was	O
us	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
New	O
and	O
Full	O
of	O
the	O
Moon	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
disorder	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
thereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pocket	O
Book	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
November	O
;	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
having	O
been	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
at	O
Kensington	O
,	O
and	O
received	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
paid	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Bank	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
Note	O
for	O
a	O
Hundred	O
Pound	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket-Book	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
passing	O
along	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
sell	O
into	O
Company	O
of	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Tarly	I-pers
,	O
who	O
invited	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
her	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
the	O
same	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
they	O
being	O
Bed-fellows	O
,	O
that	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
sometime	O
,	O
he	O
missed	O
his	O
Pocket-Book	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
saying	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Bank	O
and	O
stop	O
Payment	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
set	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
agreed	O
that	O
for	O
2	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Bowl	O
of	O
Punch	O
of	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
procure	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
having	O
given	O
the	O
2	O
Guineas	O
,	O
she	O
pretended	O
to	O
send	O
a	O
Person	O
out	O
to	O
fetch	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
bring	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
brought	O
Answer	O
the	O
Gentlewoman	O
would	O
not	O
part	O
it	O
unless	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Guineas	O
more	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
him	O
his	O
Book	O
and	O
Note	O
,	O
taking	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Bosom	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
another	O
Evidence	O
,	O
the	O
Messenger	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
to	O
Mary	O
Tarly	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
her	O
go	O
and	O
stay	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
come	O
in	O
and	O
bring	O
such	O
an	O
Answer	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Book	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
brought	O
Mary	O
Tarly	O
thither	O
,	O
saying	O
she	O
was	O
his	O
Cousin	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
give	O
her	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
a	O
Guinea	O
(	O
saying	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
might	O
guess	O
for	O
what	O
)	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
Mary	O
Tarly	O
together	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
Room	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
Chest	O
of	O
Dram	O
Bed	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
pulled	O
down	O
and	O
the	O
Cloths	O
tumbled	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
they	O
did	O
together	O
she	O
new	O
not	O
but	O
that	O
might	O
be	O
guessed	O
at	O
.	O
That	O
though	O
the	O
procur	O
'd	O
the	O
Book	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Celiar	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
proof	O
that	O
Charged	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
directly	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
Book	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Isham	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Dick	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Cullam	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
Ludgate	I-place
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
20	O
l.	O
of	O
Coney	O
Wooll	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
Sarah	O
Cullam	O
,	O
had	O
worked	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
as	O
a	O
hired	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Elizabeth	O
Isham	O
served	O
in	O
that	O
capacity	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
present	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecuters	O
Maid	O
Servant	O
,	O
at	O
her	O
locking	O
up	O
the	O
Doors	O
at	O
9	O
a	O
Clock	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
the	O
Lost	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
missing	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
bought	O
the	O
said	O
Wool	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
;	O
their	O
Examination	O
were	O
Read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
they	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
by	O
them	O
both	O
;	O
that	O
Cullam	O
lay	O
conceal	O
'd	O
under	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
handed	O
down	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
Isham	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
:	O
However	O
they	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
upon	O
their	O
Trial	O
alledging	O
that	O
they	O
receiv	O
'd	O
it	O
of	O
one	O
Betty	B-pers
Moor	I-pers
in	O
Fetter	O
Lane	O
,	O
but	O
cold	O
not	O
produce	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4s.10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Clington	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Canvas	O
Bag	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
2	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
10	O
Broad	O
Fioors	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Sumpter	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
in	O
Long	B-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
that	O
they	O
saluted	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
how	O
do	O
you	O
Countryman	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Josel.	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Money	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
went	O
into	O
the	O
Pear	O
and	O
Ragged	O
Staff	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
one	O
Pint	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
Sarah	O
Walker	O
called	O
for	O
another	O
;	O
that	O
Mary	O
Clington	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
step	O
,	O
and	O
away	O
she	O
went	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
missing	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
charg	O
'd	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
apprehended	O
Sarah	O
Walker	O
,	O
she	O
charged	O
the	O
Constable	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Counter	O
together	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
positive	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
must	O
have	O
his	O
Money	O
;	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
which	O
,	O
Walker	O
pleaded	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
took	O
acquaintance	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
having	O
used	O
her	O
House	O
when	O
she	O
kept	O
an	O
Inn	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Drink	O
for	O
old	O
acquaintance	O
,	O
she	O
considering	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
her	O
Customer	O
,	O
would	O
return	O
the	O
civility	O
of	O
giving	O
him	O
another	O
Pint	O
of	O
Drink	O
;	O
saying	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
was	O
never	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
from	O
him	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
none	O
of	O
it	O
about	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	O
Clington	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
Sarah	O
Walker	O
in	O
her	O
life	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
not	O
sufficient	O
Proof	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Jasper	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Goddard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
in	O
tearing	O
2	O
Leaves	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Register-Book	O
for	O
Marriages	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Church	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
.	O
The	O
Evidences	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Goddard	O
having	O
been	O
marry	O
'd	O
there	O
in	O
the	O
Month	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
1711	O
to	O
one	O
Rachel	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
marry	O
'd	O
to	O
another	O
,	O
his	O
first	O
being	O
alive	O
they	O
were	O
employ	O
'd	O
to	O
take	O
out	O
a	O
Certificate	O
of	O
the	O
Marriage	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
it	O
entred	O
in	O
the	O
Register	O
,	O
did	O
so	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
going	O
about	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
after	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
Book	O
,	O
found	O
no	O
such	O
Entry	O
:	O
Upon	O
which	O
they	O
apply	O
'd	O
themselves	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hopley	O
,	O
Doctor	O
Sacheverel	O
's	O
Clark	O
,	O
acuring	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Reason	O
,	O
that	O
whereas	O
there	O
was	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
in	O
the	O
Register-Book	O
an	O
Entry	O
of	O
the	O
Marriage	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Goddard	O
with	O
Rachel	B-pers
Small	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Month	O
of	O
June,17th	O
,	O
there	O
could	O
none	O
be	O
found	O
now	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hopley	O
,	O
Doctor	O
Sacheverel	O
's	O
Clark	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
upon	O
this	O
Occasion	O
he	O
examin	O
'd	O
the	O
Register-Book	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
find	O
no	O
such	O
Entry	O
,	O
but	O
observ	O
'd	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Vacancy	O
in	O
the	O
Book	O
from	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
May	O
to	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
that	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
a	O
whole	O
Leaf	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Leaf	O
that	O
answer	O
'd	O
to	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
also	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
Vacancy	O
from	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
February	O
to	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
March	O
;	O
which	O
making	O
him	O
very	O
uneasy	O
,	O
he	O
acquainted	O
Doctor	O
Sacheverel	B-pers
with	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Jasper	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
was	O
his	O
Deputy	O
,	O
and	O
under	O
Clerk	O
of	O
the	O
Temple	O
,	O
and	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
have	O
free	O
recourse	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Register-Book	O
at	O
all	O
Times	O
,	O
to	O
enter	O
or	O
fill	O
up	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Absence	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
questioning	O
him	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
with	O
Oaths	O
and	O
imprecations	O
.	O
The	O
Doctor	O
sent	O
for	O
Thomas	B-pers
Herring	I-pers
,	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
That	O
Arnold	O
had	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
tore	O
out	O
the	O
Leaves	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
Note	O
of	O
Goddard	O
's	O
Hand	O
of	O
5	O
l.	O
for	O
doing	O
it	O
:	O
That	O
thereupon	O
Arnold	O
being	O
urg	O
'd	O
to	O
confess	O
the	O
Truth	O
,	O
did	O
acknowledge	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
show	O
'd	O
the	O
Note	O
for	O
5	O
l.	O
that	O
Goddard	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
Goddard	O
had	O
burnt	O
the	O
Leaves	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Goddard	O
had	O
own	O
'd	O
Arnold	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
several	O
Times	O
and	O
solicited	O
him	O
to	O
employ	O
him	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
Arnold	O
a	O
Note	O
of	O
5	O
l.	O
to	O
tear	O
out	O
the	O
Leaves	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
himself	O
was	O
by	O
at	O
the	O
doing	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
both	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
their	O
Trials	O
;	O
and	O
Arnold	O
pretended	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lent	O
Goddard	O
Money	O
at	O
several	O
Times	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Note	O
upon	O
that	O
Consideration	O
.	O
But	O
notwithstanding	O
their	O
Evasions	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Benson	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Susanna	B-pers
Holt	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
silver	O
Buckle	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Headcloaths	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
one	O
Catherine	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
telling	O
her	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
within	O
Doors	O
would	O
speak	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
going	O
in	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
others	O
,	O
fell	O
upon	O
her	O
and	O
beat	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
barbarous	O
Manner	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Things	O
mention	O
'd	O
taken	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
But	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
positively	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Still	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Saddles	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Moor	I-pers
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Stable	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Carter	O
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Thistlemarsh	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
48	O
Yards	O
of	O
Stuff	O
,	O
and	O
48	O
Yards	O
of	O
Poplin	O
,	O
and	O
30	O
Yards	O
of	O
Sarsnet	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
l	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Willard	I-pers
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Waggoner	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Sarah	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
came	O
to	O
desire	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
Gentlewomen	O
to	O
Hounslow	O
that	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
Twickenham	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
accordingly	O
did	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
carry	O
'd	O
in	O
with	O
them	O
a	O
large	O
Bandbox	O
,	O
which	O
weigh	O
'd	O
light	O
when	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Waggon	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
down	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
their	O
Stage	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
:	O
But	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
suspecting	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
examin	O
'd	O
the	O
Waggon	O
,	O
found	O
a	O
Pack	O
cut	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
gone	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
his	O
Horse	O
and	O
pursu	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
taking	O
it	O
upon	O
herself	O
,	O
saying	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
were	O
not	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
hardly	O
probable	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
Sarah	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4s.10d	O
.	O
and	O
acquitted	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Cedes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pauls	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Yard	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
China	O
Ware	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
24	O
Guineas	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Barrow	I-pers
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
several	O
Times	O
miss	O
'd	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
,	O
and	O
particularly	O
6	O
Guineas	O
the	O
Beginning	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
another	O
Time	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
Week	O
after,18	O
more	O
;	O
that	O
no	O
Body	O
could	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
Drawers	O
but	O
herself	O
,	O
it	O
always	O
being	O
kept	O
lock	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Keys	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
;	O
that	O
at	O
last	O
suspecting	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
who	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
examin	O
'd	O
her	O
Boxes	O
,	O
Ec	O
.	O
and	O
found	O
several	O
Vessels	O
of	O
China	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
lock	O
'd	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
demanding	O
her	O
Keys	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
two	O
Keys	O
which	O
would	O
open	O
all	O
her	O
Drawers	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
the	O
Keys	O
she	O
found	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
;	O
and	O
brought	O
a	O
Person	O
who	O
us	O
'd	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
heard	O
her	O
say	O
she	O
found	O
three	O
Keys	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
them	O
down	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
mind	O
em	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
those	O
were	O
the	O
Keys	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
liv	O
'd	O
there	O
a	O
considerable	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
many	O
considerable	O
Persons	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
;	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
such	O
a	O
Character	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Coats	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Garish	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
160	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Scaring	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
them	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
about	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
a	O
Year	O
;	O
during	O
which	O
Time	O
she	O
behav	O
'd	O
herself	O
very	O
diligently	O
,	O
which	O
engag	O
'd	O
them	O
so	O
much	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
coming	O
to	O
them	O
so	O
bare	O
in	O
Cloaths	O
they	O
were	O
asham	O
'd	O
to	O
send	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
an	O
Errand	O
,	O
they	O
therefore	O
let	O
her	O
have	O
Money	O
before-hand	O
to	O
buy	O
her	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
;	O
and	O
also	O
a	O
Demand	O
being	O
made	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Menace	O
of	O
Arresting	O
her	O
for	O
30	O
s.	O
(	O
which	O
she	O
said	O
was	O
for	O
curing	O
her	O
of	O
the	O
King's-Evil	O
,	O
which	O
which	O
they	O
suppos	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
true	O
;	O
but	O
were	O
since	O
inform	O
'd	O
it	O
was	O
more	O
her	O
own	O
Evil	O
than	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
flux	O
'd	O
for	O
it	O
at	O
Kingsland	O
)	O
they	O
offer	O
'd	O
her	O
the	O
Money	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Demand	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
easy	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
happen	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
Time	O
before-mention	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
7	O
a-Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
to	O
take	O
leave	O
of	O
some	O
Friends	O
that	O
were	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
leaving	O
only	O
her	O
and	O
a	O
Child	O
at	O
Home	O
;	O
that	O
returning	O
about	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
not	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
Home	O
,	O
but	O
suspected	O
nothing	O
.	O
Supposing	O
she	O
might	O
have	O
gone	O
out	O
upon	O
some	O
necessary	O
Occasion	O
or	O
other	O
;	O
till	O
expecting	O
her	O
some	O
considerable	O
Time	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
trying	O
the	O
Hasp	O
of	O
the	O
Trunk	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
,	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
thought	O
,	O
fast	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
search	O
'd	O
no	O
farther	O
;	O
But	O
she	O
not	O
returning	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
examin	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Hasp	O
had	O
been	O
unnail	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
hung	O
on	O
again	O
with	O
a	O
Nail	O
or	O
two	O
of	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
opening	O
the	O
Trunk	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
Rings	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
thereupon	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
quest	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
hear	O
of	O
her	O
for	O
some	O
considerable	O
Time	O
.	O
Till	O
at	O
last	O
,	O
being	O
directed	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
her	O
at	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Lloyd	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
Whitechappel-Cours	O
Officer	O
,	O
near	O
Ratoliff-Highway	O
.	O
Upon	O
his	O
going	O
thither	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
on	O
Lloyd	O
's	O
Maid	O
's	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
inform	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
for	O
Lloyd	O
's	O
Sister	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
directed	O
by	O
Lloyd	O
to	O
Poplar	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
found	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
furnish	O
'd	O
it	O
with	O
good	O
Goods	O
,	O
all	O
new	O
,	O
the	O
Pewter	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
mark	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Name	O
,	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
must	O
be	O
bought	O
with	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
in	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
Shilling	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
apprehended	O
her	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
apprehended	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
sorry	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
press	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
Master	O
what	O
Restitution	O
she	O
could	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
but	O
one	O
Farthing	O
left	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
Newgate	O
would	O
make	O
a	O
Confession	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Hearts	O
Content	O
;	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
she	O
might	O
be	O
sent	O
to	O
Newgate	O
rather	O
than	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
had	O
some	O
Accomplices	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
Persons	O
that	O
were	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
apprehend	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
were	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
apprehend	O
that	O
her	O
Master	O
would	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
her	O
as	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
would	O
be	O
the	O
inore	O
shy	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
she	O
were	O
sent	O
to	O
Newgate	O
would	O
think	O
themselves	O
more	O
out	O
of	O
danger	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
appear	O
more	O
publickly	O
.	O
But	O
,	O
notwithstanding	O
,	O
she	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
all	O
upon	O
her	O
Trial	O
,	O
only	O
that	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
chose	O
rather	O
to	O
go	O
Newgate	O
than	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
,	O
because	O
it	O
stood	O
more	O
convenient	O
for	O
her	O
Friends	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
,	O
asking	O
her	O
,	O
Why	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
in	O
that	O
manner	O
?	O
She	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
Because	O
she	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
being	O
Arrested	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
for	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
another	O
Person	O
's	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Katherine	B-pers
Matt	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Matt	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Savoy	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Common-Prayer	O
Books	O
and	O
3	O
Brass-Candlesticks	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Chappel	O
of	O
St.	O
John	O
Baptist	O
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Mother	O
was	O
Sexton	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Chappel	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
gotten	O
in	O
at	O
a	O
Window	O
and	O
stol'n	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Candlesticks	O
were	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
Sale	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
stopp	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Books	O
sold	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Buyers	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
appear	O
'd	O
in	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
Behalf	O
,	O
threw	O
herself	O
upon	O
the	O
Mercy	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Emmanuel	B-pers
Kendal	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
6	O
Chairs	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Table	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Skilbeck	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Matter	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
such	O
as	O
should	O
be	O
rather	O
decided	O
at	O
Common	O
Law	O
than	O
by	O
way	O
of	O
Indictment	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Bun	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Day-time	O
,	O
no	O
Body	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
3	O
flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Linnen	O
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Proof	O
not	O
being	O
fall	O
enough	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Miles	I-pers
the	O
Younger	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Clogs	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Miles	I-pers
the	O
Elder	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Thomas	O
Miles	O
the	O
Elder	O
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
going	O
up	O
Stairs	O
for	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
,	O
upon	O
her	O
coming	O
down	O
she	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
running	O
out	O
,	O
was	O
told	O
by	O
some	O
Neighbours	O
Children	O
,	O
that	O
two	O
Women	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Door	O
with	O
some	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
directed	O
her	O
which	O
way	O
they	O
went	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
follow	O
'd	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
overtook	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Things	O
in	O
Elizabeth	O
Jones	O
's	O
Apron	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
Woman	O
that	O
uses	O
to	O
buy	O
Things	O
about	O
the	O
Street	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Matter	O
was	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
.	O
found	O
Jones	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.10	O
d.	O
but	O
acquitted	O
Elizabeth	O
White	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Woodburn	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bartholomew	I-place
the	I-place
Great	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
and	O
robbing	O
Mary	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Cypher	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.2	O
.	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.4	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Buckles	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
having	O
acquaintance	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
met	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
saying	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
fetch	O
something	O
for	O
her	O
Husband	O
:	O
That	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
Strong-Water	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Dram	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
where	O
were	O
her	O
Rings	O
?	O
She	O
answer	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
,	O
it	O
raining	O
,	O
and	O
drink	O
'd	O
and	O
then	O
to	O
another	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
carried	O
her	O
to	O
another	O
Brandy	O
Shop	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
she	O
was	O
set	O
down	O
at	O
a	O
Dour	O
,	O
and	O
sell	O
asleep	O
.	O
The	O
Mother	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
hearing	O
of	O
her	O
Daughter	O
,	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
so	O
fast	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
affraid	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
dead	O
;	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
waking	O
her	O
,	O
got	O
her	O
home	O
and	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
receiv	O
'd	O
some	O
Refreshment	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
her	O
who	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
.	O
She	O
search	O
'd	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
found	O
it	O
cut	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Coat	O
likewise	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
forementich	O
'd	O
Things	O
gone	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Priosner	O
,	O
challenged	O
her	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
who	O
stiffly	O
deny	O
'd	O
knowing	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
getting	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
Box	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Lace	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
except	O
the	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
found	O
at	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
desir	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
lend	O
her	O
a	O
Crown	O
upon	O
the	O
Lace	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
Rings	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
But	O
this	O
was	O
all	O
deny	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
West	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
200	O
Yards	O
of	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
Value	O
30	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Pelham	I-pers
the	O
8th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Shop	O
,	O
she	O
seeing	O
no	O
body	O
there	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Box	O
.	O
from	O
off	O
a	O
Shelf	O
behind	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
and	O
charging	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
she	O
dropt	O
them	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
therefore	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Hawks	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver-hilted	O
Sword	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Bramer	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
was	O
12	O
Months	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
being	O
within	O
the	O
Act	O
of	O
Grace	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Strickland	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bow	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
felonously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Flaxen	O
Sheet	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Randal	B-pers
Pemberton	I-pers
the	O
8th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
fact	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.10	O
d.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
flaxen	O
Sheet	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Callico	O
Gown	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
James	I-pers
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
full	O
enough	O
,	O
of	O
this	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstans	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Spoon	O
value	O
5	O
s	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Franks	I-pers
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
sufficiently	O
proved	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Acton	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Anthony	B-pers
Rouse	I-pers
upon	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
High	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
a	O
Snuff-Box	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
Mare	O
val	O
4	O
l.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
Sept	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
near	O
the	O
Turn-pike	O
about	O
9	O
a-Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
by	O
2	O
Men	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
dark	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
it	O
was	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Coulthurst	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
himself	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
committed	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
depending	O
on	O
his	O
single	O
Evidence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cryer	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
perriwing	O
val.6	O
l.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Gregory	B-pers
Spinney	I-pers
the	O
20th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
but	O
Obadiah	O
Lemon	O
who	O
was	O
Accomplice	O
in	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Jepherson	I-pers
alias	I-pers
White	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White-Chappel	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
marrying	O
a	O
Second	O
Husband	O
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
her	O
first	O
Husband	O
being	O
alive	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
within	O
the	O
Act	O
of	O
Grace	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Loncheter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Can	O
,	O
value	O
24	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
destitute	O
of	O
Employment	O
,	O
was	O
entertain	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
gratis	O
,	O
but	O
ungratefully	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
Which	O
probably	O
had	O
been	O
sufficiently	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
a	O
material	O
Evidence	O
was	O
sick	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
legal	O
Evidence	O
he	O
was	O
aquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Thenlis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Linnen	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Tudor	I-pers
,	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
Nov	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Box	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolphs	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hichman	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
Nov	O
.	O
last	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
Steal	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Flap	O
over	O
the	O
Shop-Door	O
being	O
open	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
getting	O
in	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
sufficient	O
Proof	O
of	O
a	O
Burglary	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolphs	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Cheeses	O
.	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Coley	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
Nov	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
percieving	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
lurking	O
about	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
he	O
watch	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Comrade	O
say	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Go	O
it	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
go	O
in	O
and	O
bring	O
out	O
the	O
Cheeses	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
and	O
Seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
throwing	O
the	O
Cheeses	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
got	O
off	O
.	O
Yet	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
in	O
publishing	O
a	O
false	O
Power	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
receive	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
2000	O
l.	O
and	O
upwards	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
Pay	O
due	O
to	O
a	O
Regiment	O
.	O
The	O
indictment	O
was	O
read	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Prosecutor	O
appearing	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Kensington	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
5	O
Silver-hilted	O
Knives	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
a	O
material	O
Evidence	O
being	O
gone	O
into	O
Wales	O
,	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
sufficient	O
Proof	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Bowen	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Savoy	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
Hood	O
and	O
Scarf	O
,	O
value	O
21	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Camdry	I-pers
the	O
2d	O
of	O
Nov	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
his	O
Wife	O
's	O
Nurse	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
they	O
were	O
put	O
into	O
her	O
Hands	O
to	O
alter	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
pawn	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
intended	O
to	O
redeem	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
return	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
not	O
being	O
there	O
to	O
contradict	O
it	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
probability	O
of	O
the	O
Plea	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Barbara	B-pers
Downly	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Downing	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
in	O
uttering	O
counterfeit	O
Money	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
counterfeit	O
.	O
One	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
Shop	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Ounce	O
of	O
Nutmegs	O
,	O
giving	O
her	O
a	O
Crown	O
Piece	O
to	O
change	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
giving	O
her	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
and	O
two	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
in	O
Half-pence	O
:	O
After-which	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
but	O
Two	O
pence	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
requir	O
'd	O
her	O
Crown	O
Piece	O
,	O
laying	O
down	O
a	O
counterfeit	O
Shilling	O
.	O
which	O
she	O
taxing	O
her	O
with	O
,	O
she	O
insisted	O
upon	O
it	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Money	O
that	O
she	O
gave	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
saving	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
other	O
Money	O
:	O
But	O
when	O
she	O
saw	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
so	O
serv	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
clappn	O
her	O
Hand	O
to	O
her	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
believe	O
,	O
she	O
swallow	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
laying	O
down	O
her	O
own	O
good	O
Shilling	O
,	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
Prescipitation	O
.	O
Katherine	B-pers
Mackoon	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
New-Prison	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
thither	O
for	O
putting	O
off	O
a	O
false	O
Shilling	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
swallow	O
'd	O
one	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
stuck	O
in	O
her	O
Throat	O
so	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
eat	O
her	O
Victuals	O
for	O
several	O
Days	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
Shop	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
Pound	O
of	O
Sugar-Cakes	O
,	O
giving	O
her	O
a	O
counterfeit	O
Shilling	O
:	O
Which	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
sworn	O
positively	O
to	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
her	O
quandam	O
Acquaintance	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
her	O
usual	O
Way	O
of	O
Living	O
was	O
by	O
such	O
like	O
Practices	O
,	O
either	O
picking	O
Pockets	O
,	O
or	O
putting	O
off	O
counterfeit	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
affirming	O
she	O
had	O
never	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Houses	O
,	O
and	O
labour	O
'd	O
to	O
invalidate	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
Mary	O
James	O
,	O
by	O
charging	O
her	O
with	O
following	O
the	O
same	O
Trade	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
improbable	O
but	O
some	O
part	O
of	O
what	O
she	O
said	O
might	O
be	O
true	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Facts	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
by	O
other	O
Evidences	O
than	O
that	O
of	O
Mary	O
James	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolphs	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
35	O
of	O
Hemp	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
Nov	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Body	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Reed	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
9	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cloth	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
unknown	O
,	O
the	O
11	O
th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
in	O
the	O
Second	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
present	O
Majesty	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
being	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Aldridge	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Commons	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
a	O
Bay-Horse	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
two	O
Saddles	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Fredricks	I-pers
,	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Lock	O
was	O
taken	O
off	O
from	O
the	O
Iron	O
Bar	O
which	O
barred	O
the	O
Gates	O
and	O
the	O
Scable-Door	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Horse	O
and	O
saddle	O
stolen	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Scables	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Son	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Evening	O
before	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
and	O
scables	O
viewing	O
the	O
Horses	O
and	O
asking	O
about	O
their	O
age	O
,	O
strength	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
likewise	O
,	O
that	O
missing	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
in	O
.	O
The	O
Hottler	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
that	O
Horse	O
between	O
5	O
and	O
6	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Aborning	O
,	O
badding	O
him	O
for	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
belong	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
for	O
him	O
again	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
and	O
accordingly	O
due	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
waiting	O
his	O
coming	O
apprenended	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
c	O
diable	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
upon	O
apprehending	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
him	O
aside	O
,	O
and	O
devices	O
not	O
to	O
decun	O
him	O
setting	O
him	O
,	O
That	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
he	O
was	O
used	O
the	O
,	O
the	O
Horse	O
being	O
a	O
checquir	O
'd	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
four	O
there	O
were	O
used	O
in	O
the	O
smugling	O
Trade	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
three	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
already	O
.	O
He	O
used	O
likewise	O
,	O
The	O
Axan	O
who	O
employed	O
him	O
to	O
being	O
it	O
thither	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Kagygs-Tavern	O
in	O
B	O
popsgutt-Street	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
see	O
,	O
but	O
heard	O
of	O
no	O
such	O
portion	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
told	O
than	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
be	O
Tssorn	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
Stores	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
his	O
tryal	O
pleaded	O
he	O
was	O
hired	O
by	O
two	O
Men	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
Six-pence	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
Horse	O
from	O
street	O
to	O
the	O
.	O
Upon	O
hearing	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Monntsieures	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bow	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hemingdale	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
several	O
Wounds	O
on	O
the	O
lots	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
parting	O
him	O
by	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
17th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
upon	O
the	O
coroners	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Fact	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
third	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
Hemingdale	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
perriwing	O
value	O
2	O
s	O
6	O
s	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings,1	O
piece	O
of	O
Danise	O
Gold,2	O
silver	O
Medals	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
Ann	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
lodged	O
with	O
her	O
about	O
4	O
Months	O
ago	O
,	O
went	O
away	O
to	O
Hallond	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
to	O
Return	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
brought	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
a	O
young	O
Gentleman	O
of	O
about	O
20	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
to	O
lodge	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
not	O
speaking	O
English	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bargained	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
.	O
him	O
7	O
Week	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
used	O
often	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
October	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
what	O
was	O
due	O
to	O
her	O
and	O
paid	O
her	O
,	O
desired	O
2	O
proper	O
might	O
be	O
called	O
to	O
carry	O
away	O
the	O
Deceased	O
.	O
and	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
full	O
pot	O
at	O
Drink	O
to	O
carry	O
then	O
into	O
the	O
strand	O
to	O
a	O
Corch	O
,	O
going	O
away	O
about	O
4	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternon	O
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Vannar	I-pers
deposed	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Deceased	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
about	O
4	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
agreed	O
with	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
Lodging	O
for	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
desired	O
to	O
have	O
something	O
to	O
eat	O
,	O
had	O
come	O
Beer	O
Seakes	O
and	O
eat	O
together	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
6	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
came	O
not	O
home	O
to	O
lodge	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
no	O
did	O
she	O
see	O
him	O
any	O
more	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
were	O
again	O
about	O
8	O
a-Clock	O
,	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
Washerwoman	O
,	O
gave	O
out	O
some	O
Linen	O
to	O
be	O
washed	O
which	O
linen	O
was	O
swon	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
by	O
the	O
Washerwoman	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
wer	O
,	O
duty	O
and	O
bloody	O
when	O
he	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
said	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Hours	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
out	O
again	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
by	O
use	O
who	O
added	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
at	O
10	O
a-clock	O
at	O
night	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
Half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
desiring	O
Silver	O
for	O
it	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
3	O
nillings	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
left	O
the	O
Half	O
guinna	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
come	O
in	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
he	O
heard	O
him	O
walk	O
about	O
the	O
Chamber	O
,	O
as	O
in	O
a	O
Hurry	O
,	O
and	O
making	O
a	O
rumbling	O
walked	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
stairs	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
his	O
going	O
out	O
asked	O
for	O
more	O
money	O
of	O
the	O
Change	O
of	O
the	O
Half	O
Guinea	O
and	O
that	O
about	O
in	O
Hour	O
and	O
a	O
Half	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
the	O
Ale	O
house	O
,	O
where	O
was	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Bakr	O
,	O
the	O
constable	O
and	O
Headle	O
who	O
enquired	O
of	O
him	O
for	O
his	O
Lodger	O
,	O
calling	O
him	O
they	O
suspected	O
his	O
lodger	O
had	O
murder	O
'd	O
the	O
deceased	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
be	O
replyed	O
,	O
it	O
so	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
gone	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
doobred	O
whether	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
home	O
again	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
But	O
that	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
his	O
Room	O
being	O
up	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
they	O
pleased	O
they	O
should	O
go	O
on	O
and	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
carried	O
away	O
all	O
changed	O
of	O
any	O
value	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
found	O
a	O
Pocket-Book	O
written	O
in	O
Frenchs	O
and	O
Dutch	O
,	O
got	O
one	O
Mr	O
.	O
Wave	O
to	O
read	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
some	O
Accounts	O
relating	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
as	O
having	O
served	O
as	O
a	O
Couchman	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
de	O
Avila	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Note	O
of	O
2s	O
Pipeles	O
on	O
account	O
as	O
having	O
been	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Count	O
de	O
shods	O
,	O
as	O
Vakes	O
as	O
chambre	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
brought	O
away	O
the	O
Book	O
,	O
look	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
hung	O
up	O
the	O
Key	O
,	O
waiting	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
again	O
or	O
not	O
;	O
that	O
in	O
a	O
small	O
time	O
while	O
they	O
and	O
some	O
Neighbours	O
were	O
talking	O
about	O
the	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
spyed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
comming	O
to	O
take	O
no	O
notice	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
with	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Came	O
in	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
rock	O
the	O
Key	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Saying	O
small	O
time	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
asking	O
him	O
if	O
any	O
Body	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
his	O
Lodging	O
and	O
demanding	O
the	O
Pocket	O
Book	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
talking	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
one	O
or	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Sega	O
his	O
Hand	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Sword	O
and	O
secure	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
another	O
clapped	O
him	O
upon	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
secur	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
told	O
him	O
they	O
supported	O
him	O
on	O
apprehanded	O
him	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
a	O
Murder	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
reply	O
'd	O
.	O
a	O
Marthers	O
!	O
a	O
Marther	O
!	O
What	O
you	O
mean	O
by	O
dat	O
?	O
Thus	O
they	O
told	O
him	O
they	O
would	O
him	O
like	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
a	O
he	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
would	O
not	O
expose	O
him	O
publickly	O
till	O
further	O
Satisfaction	O
was	O
obtained	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
might	O
go	O
up	O
into	O
his	O
Chember	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
sent	O
away	O
immediately	O
for	O
an	O
Officer	O
.	O
In	O
his	O
Lodging	O
were	O
found	O
the	O
Deceased	O
Beleand	O
Wagg	O
,	O
the	O
Lasser	O
wrapper	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Sheet	O
of	O
Paper	O
,	O
but	O
wet	O
and	O
bloody	O
.	O
and	O
with	O
Several	O
Holes	O
in	O
it	O
which	O
answered	O
to	O
the	O
Wounds	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Body	O
was	O
found	O
and	O
also	O
a	O
Poket	O
Book	O
and	O
Lasser	O
Case	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
in	O
which	O
were	O
Two	O
cut	O
Paper	O
but	O
they	O
also	O
wer	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
and	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
by	O
his	O
Landlady	O
to	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
Snuff	O
out	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
the	O
Morning	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
murdered	O
.	O
From	O
thence	O
he	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
and	O
being	O
searched	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
Two	O
large	O
silver	O
Medals	O
,	O
and	O
piece	O
of	O
Old	O
which	O
were	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
sworn	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
by	O
the	O
Landlady	O
and	O
another	O
Evidence	O
to	O
whom	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
several	O
times	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
likewise	O
Two	O
gold	O
Rings	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
went	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
bid	O
to	O
put	O
them	O
on	O
,	O
One	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
being	O
bear	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
all	O
being	O
on	O
his	O
Finger	O
a	O
Gentelman	O
asked	O
whar	O
was	O
the	O
Posies	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
answer	O
'd	O
itwas	O
all	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
viewed	O
had	O
no	O
Poesy	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
of	O
these	O
the	O
Leudrs	O
L.U.R	O
.	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
marked	O
with	O
the	O
M.V.A	O
.	O
the	O
same	O
with	O
which	O
the	O
Deceased	O
I	O
,	O
was	O
marked	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
likewise	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
Sword	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Cloth	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
that	O
about	O
Seven	O
of	O
Eight	O
Thursday	O
the	O
17th	O
,	O
He	O
going	O
toward	O
about	O
Hundred	O
Yards	O
beyond	O
pound	O
on	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
found	O
a	O
Coat	O
wet	O
and	O
bloody	O
,	O
but	O
most	O
on	O
the	O
inside	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
carried	O
it	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Pocket	O
's	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
Ticket	O
of	O
the	O
Company	O
of	O
signed	O
and	O
supporting	O
that	O
the	O
Owner	O
of	O
the	O
Coat	O
had	O
come	O
by	O
some	O
misfortune	O
,	O
went	O
away	O
immediately	O
and	O
enquire	O
him	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
showing	O
him	O
the	O
Note	O
and	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
He	O
owned	O
into	O
be	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
adn	O
directed	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Lodging	O
whether	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
ulmost	O
Hapedicron	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
taken	O
of	O
a	O
two	O
from	O
the	O
Coast	O
he	O
found	O
,	O
showing	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Landlady	O
.	O
immediately	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
Button	O
beginning	O
to	O
her	O
Lodger	O
's	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Cost	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
sight	O
of	O
the	O
Cost	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
,	O
that	O
thereupon	O
Market	O
,	O
and	O
enquiring	O
farther	O
he	O
had	O
very	O
great	O
reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
procured	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
apprehended	O
as	O
has	O
been	O
before	O
related	O
.	O
The	O
dead	O
Body	O
not	O
being	O
found	O
,	O
several	O
Persons	O
went	O
in	O
Quest	O
of	O
it	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
Hat	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
Field	O
not	O
very	O
far	O
from	O
where	O
the	O
Cost	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Gold	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
a	O
Creeper	O
and	O
crept	O
the	O
Food	O
in	O
the	O
Field	O
,	O
near	O
where	O
the	O
Cost	O
was	O
found	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
the	O
Decreased	O
'd	O
Hat	O
,	O
which	O
has	O
several	O
Cuts	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
answered	O
to	O
those	O
in	O
the	O
Wig	O
and	O
Head	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
Hat	O
was	O
also	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
)	O
that	O
there	O
being	O
some	O
Chick-weed	O
on	O
the	O
Coat	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
told	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
Ponds	O
in	O
some	O
farther	O
Fields	O
where	O
was	O
chickweed	O
,	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
Third	O
Freid	O
be	O
found	O
Ponds	O
,	O
and	O
near	O
the	O
Pond	O
side	O
he	O
perceived	O
the	O
Ground	O
had	O
been	O
trampled	O
,	O
and	O
perceived	O
Blood	O
,	O
followed	O
the	O
Track	O
,	O
and	O
near	O
the	O
Edge	O
of	O
the	O
Pond	O
saw	O
a	O
great	O
Quantity	O
of	O
clotted	O
Blood	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
's	O
Sword	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
but	O
broken	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
Knife	O
was	O
there	O
taken	O
up	O
by	O
another	O
Person	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
sworn	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Knife	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
he	O
owned	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Knife	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
show	O
'd	O
him	O
and	O
that	O
creeping	O
that	O
Pond	O
his	O
Creeper	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Breeches	O
,	O
the	O
Body	O
lying	O
at	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Pond	O
under	O
some	O
Bushes	O
as	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
stamped	O
in	O
the	O
Mud	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
all	O
his	O
Cloath	O
on	O
but	O
Coat	O
,	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wigg	O
,	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
turned	O
inside	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
knife	O
and	O
Fork	O
,	O
the	O
Body	O
was	O
afterwards	O
view	O
'd	O
by	O
several	O
that	O
knew	O
the	O
Deceased	O
and	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
John	O
Hoemg	O
R.in	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
deposed	O
.	O
That	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
Wounds	O
on	O
the	O
temporal	O
muscles	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
between	O
all	O
to	O
that	O
opening	O
the	O
Head	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
Concustion	O
of	O
Blood	O
upon	O
the	O
Brain	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
the	O
Wounds	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
first	O
what	O
Weapon	O
He	O
could	O
not	O
lay	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
suffocated	O
in	O
the	O
Pond	O
.	O
Many	O
of	O
the	O
these	O
Curcumstances	O
were	O
confirmed	O
by	O
Vuiety	O
of	O
Evidence	O
and	O
many	O
more	O
too	O
long	O
here	O
to	O
relate	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
being	O
called	O
to	O
make	O
Defence	O
,	O
denied	O
his	O
knowing	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
Murther	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
asked	O
since	O
,	O
about	O
Six	O
a-Clock	O
,	O
as	O
had	O
been	O
proved	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
what	O
be	O
use	O
of	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
answered	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
to	O
Halborn	O
,	O
adn	O
there	O
Parted	O
,	O
he	O
going	O
one	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
another	O
.	O
Being	O
asked	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
paid	O
be	O
all	O
Night	O
at	O
the	O
Night	O
Cellar	O
at	O
appeared	O
,	O
they	O
having	O
sent	O
to	O
enquire	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
after	O
Ton	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
till	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
drinking	O
with	O
Porten	O
,	O
Chairmen	O
,	O
and	O
such	O
like	O
which	O
did	O
for	O
his	O
Diversion	O
,	O
but	O
probably	O
to	O
divert	O
the	O
Horror	O
of	O
his	O
Mind	O
.	O
)	O
But	O
being	O
called	O
upon	O
to	O
prove	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
from	O
Six	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
all	O
Eight	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
House	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
preduce	O
the	O
least	O
proof	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Being	O
asked	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Rings	O
,	O
Medals	O
,	O
Belts	O
,	O
Pocket-Book	O
,	O
Letter-Cafe	O
and	O
Cane	O
,	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
paid	O
a	O
Guineas	O
for	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Passage	O
from	O
Holland,7	O
Stuling	O
,	O
per	O
With	O
for	O
his	O
Diet	O
,	O
and	O
lent	O
him	O
Money	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceded	O
had	O
put	O
all	O
his	O
Effects	O
into	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
on	O
that	O
Account	O
,	O
Being	O
asked	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
Wig	O
that	O
it	O
appeared	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
murdered	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
no	O
other	O
Answer	O
.	O
Being	O
asked	O
how	O
his	O
Knife	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
Pond-side	O
where	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
found	O
murdered	O
he	O
alleged	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
to	O
rowed	O
it	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
only	O
Evidences	O
he	O
celled	O
were	O
two	O
foreign	O
Women	O
,	O
and	O
Van	O
;	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
whole	O
Evidences	O
amounted	O
only	O
to	O
this	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
had	O
known	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
has	O
sometimes	O
used	O
