TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
,	O
.	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
1st,2d,3d	O
and	O
4th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
.	O
May,1717	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Third	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
14	O
.	O
May.1717	O
.	O
BEfore	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
JAMES	B-pers
BATEMAN	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
and	O
Bart	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
Parker	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Worshipful	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Price	O
,	O
Baron	O
of	O
the	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
cy	O
;	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
Names	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Keable	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Grinstead	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Brookhouse	I-pers
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
William	B-pers
Bigsky	I-pers
John	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
Ralph	B-pers
Stirrap	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Harton	I-pers
John	B-pers
Peechey	I-pers
John	B-pers
Bloss	I-pers
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Whitfield	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Bateman	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Kern	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Orbel	I-pers
Benjamin	B-pers
Jakeman	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Hayes	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Newland	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Kingsman	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Weely	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch-Case	O
,	O
value	O
17	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Dial-Plate	O
,	O
val.7	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Humphreys	I-pers
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
day-time	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
shop	O
to	O
treat	O
with	O
him	O
about	O
mending	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
at	O
the	O
next	O
Door	O
the	O
Boy	O
called	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
gone	O
he	O
missed	O
the	O
Watch-Case	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
The	O
Apprentice	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
to	O
look	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
thought	O
he	O
had	O
laid	O
it	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
missing	O
it	O
,	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
threw	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
Cheesemonger	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
whom	O
he	O
thought	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
Watch-Case	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
But	O
this	O
pretence	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Martha	B-pers
Pillow	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
6	O
Guineas	O
and	O
15	O
s	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
a	O
Nurse	O
,	O
kept	O
a	O
Parish-house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
cured	O
of	O
the	O
foul	O
disease	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
intrusting	O
her	O
in	O
her	O
house	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
opportunity	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
abroad	O
to	O
break	O
open	O
the	O
chest	O
of	O
draws	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
money	O
and	O
go	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
at	O
her	O
apprehension	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Lincoln	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Mantle	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
3	O
l.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Barnell	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
his	O
hired	O
servant	O
,	O
took	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
conveigh	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
Broker	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
that	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Broker	O
's	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Frock	O
,	O
he	O
encouraged	O
him	O
to	O
bring	O
him	O
goods	O
of	O
any	O
sort	O
,	O
howsoever	O
come	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
buy	O
them	O
.	O
But	O
this	O
was	O
not	O
sufficient	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
He	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
6	O
Guineas	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hartly	I-pers
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
and	O
sold	O
him	O
an	O
old	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
on	O
him	O
several	O
times	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
taking	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
poor	O
fellow	O
,	O
had	O
him	O
into	O
his	O
back	O
room	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
broth	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
opportunity	O
of	O
his	O
wife	O
's	O
absence	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Guineas	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
box	O
and	O
go	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Proof	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Panks	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Salver	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Can	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.2	O
Silver	O
Salts	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.6	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
15	O
l.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Hammond	I-pers
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
to	O
drink	O
the	O
waters	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Spoons	O
at	O
her	O
apprehension	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
for	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
indictment	O
:	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
in	O
the	O
night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
8	O
Wheaten	O
Loaves	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Halfpence	O
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
shop	O
being	O
broken	O
,	O
he	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
appointed	O
to	O
watch	O
some	O
shops	O
and	O
stalls	O
in	O
Newgate-Market	O
)	O
and	O
thereupon	O
apprehended	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
his	O
being	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
there	O
were	O
four	O
of	O
them	O
concerned	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
threaten	O
'd	O
to	O
knock	O
him	O
down	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
their	O
accomplice	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
bread	O
was	O
divided	O
amongst	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
value	O
being	O
small	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
evidence	O
of	O
his	O
committing	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Rose	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
120	O
Guineas	O
and	O
3	O
Gold-Rings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Forman	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
latter	O
for	O
receiving	O
19	O
of	O
the	O
Guineas	O
and	O
3	O
Rings	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stollen	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
employed	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
to	O
go	O
of	O
errands	O
,	O
and	O
heat	O
irons	O
for	O
the	O
workmen	O
(	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Taylor	O
)	O
and	O
having	O
been	O
gone	O
3	O
weeks	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
the	O
night	O
the	O
robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
receiving	O
some	O
small	O
matter	O
of	O
money	O
due	O
to	O
him	O
from	O
the	O
journey-men	O
for	O
the	O
cleaning	O
their	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
opportunity	O
of	O
stealing	O
his	O
money	O
,	O
breaking	O
open	O
a	O
chest	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
closet	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Boy	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Chamber	O
about	O
10	O
a	O
clock	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
happening	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
company	O
at	O
the	O
Tavern	O
and	O
other	O
places	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
junketing	O
,	O
observed	O
they	O
were	O
very	O
full	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
fared	O
sumptuously	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
Plays	O
,	O
bought	O
new	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
liv	O
'd	O
merrily	O
,	O
treating	O
all	O
the	O
Company	O
;	O
and	O
thereupon	O
application	O
being	O
made	O
to	O
him	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
he	O
apprehended	O
them	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
there	O
were	O
2	O
Guineas	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Boy	O
,	O
and	O
19	O
and	O
the	O
Rings	O
upon	O
the	O
Woman	O
with	O
a	O
Trunk	O
of	O
new	O
Cloaths	O
reposited	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
their	O
new	O
acquaintance	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
the	O
fact	O
in	O
part	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
take	O
43	O
Guineas	O
whereof	O
about	O
8	O
were	O
laid	O
out	O
in	O
Rigging	O
for	O
him	O
and	O
his	O
Mistress	O
;	O
19	O
she	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
(	O
tho	O
'	O
but	O
four	O
days	O
time	O
)	O
he	O
had	O
spent	O
upon	O
the	O
Guards	O
.	O
The	O
Woman	O
likewise	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
19	O
Guineas	O
of	O
the	O
Boy	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
not	O
of	O
his	O
robbing	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
they	O
were	O
sent	O
him	O
by	O
an	O
Uncle	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
some	O
evidences	O
that	O
confirmed	O
that	O
circumstance	O
:	O
so	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
she	O
was	O
privy	O
to	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
nor	O
proved	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Boy	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Knolls	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Derrick	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Duscoby	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Longepee	I-pers
of	O
10	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
having	O
been	O
at	O
Limehouse	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
home	O
,	O
near	O
Stepney	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
fell	O
into	O
his	O
company	O
,	O
and	O
pretended	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
buy	O
gold-colour	O
'd	O
Silk	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
Weaver	O
,	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
sell	O
her	O
;	O
That	O
she	O
came	O
with	O
him	O
near	O
his	O
own	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
bid	O
her	O
go	O
into	O
a	O
neighbouring	O
Ale-house	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
fetch	O
her	O
gold-colour	O
'd	O
Silk	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
went	O
home	O
and	O
put	O
a	O
purse	O
with	O
20	O
Guineas	O
into	O
his	O
Wast-coat	O
pocket	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Ale-house	O
to	O
show	O
it	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
sent	O
his	O
boy	O
for	O
her	O
to	O
come	O
home	O
to	O
see	O
it	O
;	O
That	O
she	O
being	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Chamber	O
,	O
took	O
his	O
Purse	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
out	O
a	O
Guinea	O
bid	O
the	O
Boy	O
fetch	O
a	O
bottle	O
of	O
Cyder	O
and	O
a	O
quartern	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
put	O
his	O
Purse	O
again	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
that	O
afterwards	O
examining	O
his	O
Purse	O
,	O
expecting	O
to	O
find	O
the	O
remaining	O
19	O
Guineas	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
but	O
9	O
.	O
Whereupon	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
to	O
apprehend	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
interim	O
she	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
do	O
her	O
Occasions	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
the	O
Officer	O
came	O
made	O
an	O
Elopement	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Boy	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
master	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
beforementioned	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
bag	O
of	O
Guineas	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
seat	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Sugar	O
Loaf	O
in	O
Coverlays	O
Fields	O
to	O
call	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
admitted	O
into	O
his	O
chamber	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
very	O
familiar	O
with	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
taking	O
his	O
Purse	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
thence	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
bidding	O
him	O
fench	O
a	O
bottle	O
of	O
Cyder	O
and	O
a	O
quartern	O
of	O
Brandy	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
refusing	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
willing	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
and	O
leave	O
them	O
together	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
suspected	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
ill	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
master	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
capable	O
,	O
therefore	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
so	O
the	O
Liquors	O
were	O
fetch	O
'd	O
by	O
another	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
desir	O
'd	O
his	O
absence	O
,	O
threating	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
speak	O
a	O
word	O
against	O
their	O
Conversation	O
she	O
would	O
kill	O
him	O
upon	O
the	O
spot	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
when	O
his	O
mistress	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
inform	O
'd	O
her	O
what	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
Companion	O
his	O
master	O
had	O
gotten	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
interrupted	O
their	O
Conversation	O
,	O
and	O
examining	O
her	O
Husband	O
's	O
purs	O
missed	O
10	O
Guineas	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
defence	O
gave	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
to	O
this	O
purpose	O
:	O
That	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
selling	O
Oranges	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
bought	O
a	O
dozen	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
giving	O
her	O
a	O
,	O
Shilling	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
liked	O
his	O
bargain	O
and	O
her	O
so	O
well	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
carried	O
her	O
to	O
a	O
Publick	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
treated	O
her	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
very	O
generously	O
with	O
Beer	O
,	O
Cyder	O
and	O
Brandy	O
;	O
staying	O
out	O
all	O
night	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
several	O
places	O
,	O
and	O
particularly	O
at	O
Stepney	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
sweet	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
courting	O
her	O
,	O
telling	O
her	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
single	O
Man	O
,	O
importuning	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
be	O
his	O
Housekeeper	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
prevail	O
'd	O
upon	O
by	O
his	O
Importunity	O
and	O
fair	O
Offers	O
:	O
At	O
length	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
making	O
use	O
of	O
that	O
conveniency	O
,	O
convey	O
'd	O
her	O
into	O
Coverlays	O
Fields	O
near	O
his	O
own	O
house	O
,	O
gave	O
her	O
money	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Sugar	O
Loaf	O
Ale-house	O
to	O
stay	O
there	O
till	O
she	O
heard	O
further	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
Accordingly	O
she	O
attended	O
at	O
the	O
Ale-house	O
as	O
he	O
directed	O
,	O
till	O
his	O
Servant	O
came	O
to	O
call	O
her	O
home	O
,	O
whither	O
she	O
went	O
,	O
was	O
well	O
receiv	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
kindly	O
admitted	O
into	O
his	O
Chamber	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
former	O
civilities	O
were	O
repeated	O
;	O
he	O
puiling	O
out	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
sending	O
for	O
a	O
bottle	O
of	O
Cyder	O
and	O
quartern	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
showing	O
her	O
his	O
cupboard	O
of	O
plate	O
:	O
and	O
that	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
pleasing	O
her	O
self	O
with	O
the	O
thoughts	O
of	O
what	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
be	O
mistress	O
of	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
to	O
her	O
great	O
surprize	O
,	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
such	O
a	O
noise	O
in	O
her	O
Ears	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
not	O
sustaining	O
the	O
storm	O
any	O
longer	O
,	O
got	O
away	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
she	O
could	O
,	O
to	O
her	O
no	O
small	O
mortification	O
at	O
the	O
great	O
Disappointment	O
she	O
had	O
met	O
with	O
,	O
incoming	O
to	O
a	O
Nest	O
so	O
well	O
feather	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
putting	O
the	O
question	O
home	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
whether	O
in	O
truth	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
pick	O
up	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
he	O
frankly	O
acknowledg	O
'd	O
he	O
did	O
pick	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
to	O
pick	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
But	O
was	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
considering	O
the	O
Years	O
he	O
always	O
bore	O
abroad	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Wife	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
him	O
loss	O
of	O
10	O
Guineas	O
(	O
were	O
they	O
lost	O
)	O
was	O
not	O
too	O
great	O
a	O
punishment	O
for	O
his	O
scandalous	O
Practices	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
that	O
would	O
not	O
excuse	O
her	O
could	O
the	O
Felony	O
be	O
proved	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Tho	O
'	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
thing	O
remarkable	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
treated	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
with	O
a	O
modesry	O
unusual	O
to	O
such	O
Practitioners	O
,	O
in	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
10	O
Guineas	O
out	O
of	O
20	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
commonly	O
take	O
all	O
if	O
they	O
can	O
get	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
only	O
leave	O
their	O
Cully	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
It	O
plainly	O
appearing	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
so	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
drink	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
possibly	O
mistake	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
his	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Compton	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Crumpton	I-pers
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
24	O
Bath-mettal	O
Knife-hafts	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
shop	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Shoe-Clasps	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
fetching	O
them	O
he	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Knife-hafts	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
apprehended	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
sending	O
for	O
an	O
Officer	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
Maid	O
carrying	O
her	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
search	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
them	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Maid	O
coming	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
saw	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Hafts	O
dropp	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Boy	O
following	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
took	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Hafts	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
,	O
all	O
but	O
two	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
no	O
body	O
to	O
appear	O
for	O
her	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
matter	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Carol	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Pocket	O
,	O
val.2	O
d.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Seal	O
,	O
val.1	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
s.6	O
d.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
Strand	B-place
she	O
was	O
thrown	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
dirt	O
and	O
her	O
Pocket	O
pulled	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
Another	O
Person	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
passing	O
by	O
the	O
Woman	O
and	O
seeing	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
she	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
follow	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Burlington-House	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
Pocket	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
that	O
the	O
Pocket	O
was	O
dropp	O
'd	O
by	O
two	O
Men	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
:	O
but	O
this	O
pretence	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
10	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.23	O
Guineas,6	O
Broad	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Mony	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Hubbard	I-pers
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
Carpenter	O
,	O
was	O
employed	O
to	O
help	O
her	O
remove	O
;	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
private	O
place	O
in	O
the	O
Floor	O
under	O
the	O
bed	O
:	O
That	O
having	O
a	O
Search-Warrant	O
she	O
found	O
two	O
of	O
her	O
Rings	O
on	O
his	O
Wife	O
's	O
finger	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
in	O
a	O
Chest	O
of	O
Draws	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
remarkable	O
Silver	O
penny	O
,	O
all	O
which	O
she	O
swore	O
to	O
be	O
hers	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
for	O
other	O
Mony	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
that	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
appear	O
'd	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
't	O
is	O
probable	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
first	O
Fact	O
:	O
but	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
before	O
made	O
some	O
Acknowledgment	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Martha	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
11	O
Yards	O
of	O
Callico	O
val.24	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
shop	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
buying	O
a	O
Night-gown	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
opportunity	O
of	O
taking	O
the	O
Calliko	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
missing	O
it	O
called	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
drop	O
from	O
under	O
Sutton	O
's	O
Ridinghood	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
pleaded	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Gown	O
for	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
sick	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
Sutton	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
her	O
taking	O
the	O
Callico	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
proved	O
he	O
was	O
privy	O
to	O
her	O
taking	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
:	O
but	O
the	O
matter	O
being	O
plain	O
as	O
to	O
Dutton	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Corbett	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
2	O
sugar-loaves	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
Susannah	B-pers
Miler	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Loaves	O
off	O
from	O
a	O
shelf	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
dropped	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
half	O
penny	O
worth	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
in	O
drink	O
,	O
might	O
perhaps	O
brush	O
the	O
Loaves	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
roll	O
'd	O
into	O
the	O
Hreet	O
.	O
But	O
this	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Baxter	I-pers
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Jasper	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Manson	I-pers
the	O
9th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
at	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
2	O
Shirts	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
5	O
Shirts	O
,	O
val.20	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
30	O
s.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
shutters	O
of	O
the	O
windows	O
were	O
taken	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
goods	O
stollen	O
.	O
Another	O
evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
her	O
the	O
goods	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
paid	O
the	O
money	O
to	O
Andrews	O
and	O
Ward	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
saying	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
goods	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
Lane	O
near	O
Ratcliff	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
nevertheless	O
found	O
Andrews	O
and	O
Ward	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
;	O
and	O
nothing	O
appearing	O
against	O
Baxter	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
being	O
at	O
the	O
selling	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Love	I-pers
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
pocket	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
5	O
Guineas	O
and	O
16	O
s.6	O
d.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
in	O
Smithfield	B-place
selling	O
Calves	O
,	O
he	O
observed	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
brushing	O
to	O
and	O
tro	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
them	O
if	O
they	O
designed	O
to	O
pick	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
busy	O
about	O
his	O
Cattle	O
,	O
was	O
not	O
careful	O
enough	O
to	O
prevent	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
a	O
boy	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
his	O
pocket	O
was	O
picked	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
The	O
Boy	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
informed	O
they	O
were	O
Pick-pockets	O
,	O
he	O
watch	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Love	O
take	O
the	O
bag	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
inform	O
'd	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
immediately	O
apprehended	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
not	O
the	O
bag	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
carry	O
'd	O
off	O
by	O
some	O
of	O
their	O
Conveys	O
.	O
The	O
evidence	O
not	O
being	O
so	O
full	O
against	O
Wright	O
as	O
against	O
Love	O
;	O
Wright	O
was	O
acquitted	O
and	O
Love	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pocket	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Gold-Ring	O
value	O
22	O
s.	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
a	O
quarter	O
Moidore	O
,	O
and	O
8	O
shillings	O
in	O
Silver	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Featherstone	I-pers
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
her	O
Pocket	O
was	O
pulled	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
following	O
the	O
thief	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
an	O
alley	O
,	O
then	O
upon	O
enquiry	O
no	O
body	O
had	O
passed	O
that	O
way	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
her	O
.	O
For	O
want	O
of	O
proof	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hartwood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
14	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
a	O
Colander	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
Eben	B-pers
Bray	I-pers
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
the	O
day	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
executed	O
the	O
last	O
session	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
drink	O
,	O
went	O
backwards	O
as	O
tho	O
'	O
to	O
make	O
water	O
,	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
comes	O
in	O
,	O
takes	O
the	O
Pewter	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
doors	O
;	O
the	O
Maid	O
hearing	O
the	O
Pewter	O
ring	O
,	O
follows	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
lays	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Pewter	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anthony	B-pers
Elson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Night-Gown	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
a	O
Satin	O
Shift	O
,	O
val.4	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
goods	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barber	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
to	O
London	O
in	O
the	O
Barnet	O
Coach	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
Hackney-Coach	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
goods	O
into	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
alighting	O
in	O
Fleetstreet	B-place
bid	O
the	O
Coachman	O
take	O
out	O
the	O
bundle	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
.	O
Another	O
evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
passing	O
along	O
he	O
heard	O
one	O
man	O
say	O
to	O
another	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
Coach	O
stops	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
suspecting	O
them	O
,	O
watch	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
immediately	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
thereo	O
'	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
out	O
the	O
bundle	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
plain	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Matth.ew	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
val.6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Fort	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Lodger	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
promised	O
to	O
return	O
it	O
him	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
farther	O
evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Guy	B-pers
Meswin	I-pers
,	O
the	O
22nd	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
2	O
Silver	O
Cups	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.7	O
Spoons	O
,	O
val.55	O
s.	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
val.6	O
l.	O
and	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
25	O
l.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
shutters	O
of	O
his	O
house	O
broken	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
goods	O
stollen	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Goodson	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
,	O
did	O
the	O
robbery	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
shutters	O
,	O
and	O
Wells	O
and	O
Price	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
coming	O
out	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
goods	O
when	O
Price	O
found	O
out	O
the	O
Closet	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
valuing	O
himself	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
upon	O
the	O
evidence	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Womens	O
Shoes	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Cloggs	O
val.1	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
.	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Apprentice	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
the	O
Shoes	O
and	O
Cloggs	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
a	O
Shilling	O
more	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
but	O
pleaded	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
consider	O
the	O
illness	O
of	O
the	O
act	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
sorry	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Anne	B-pers
(	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
George	I-pers
)	I-pers
Steed	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
pound	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Caleb	B-pers
Carot	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
lodging-room	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Mackbride	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
her	O
door	O
was	O
broken	O
open	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
abroad	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Silk	O
stollen	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
Anne	B-pers
Steed	I-pers
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
and	O
Steed	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
by	O
the	O
door	O
her	O
garter	O
untied	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
stept	O
in	O
the	O
door	O
to	O
tie	O
it	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
not	O
sufficient	O
evidence	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
25	O
s.	O
from	O
Rich	B-pers
.	I-pers
Hewet	I-pers
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
an	O
Iron-bar	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
dwel-ling-house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Ripley	I-pers
;	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
unbook	O
the	O
Bar	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
did	O
not	O
hinder	O
the	O
Jury	O
from	O
finding	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Beril	I-pers
and	I-pers
Sarah	I-pers
his	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Isleworth	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
5	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
38	O
s.	O
a	O
Wig	O
.	O
val.25	O
s.4	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
val.40	O
s.	O
a	O
Pail	O
,	O
val.1	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sarson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
had	O
been	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
house	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
had	O
both	O
been	O
his	O
servants	O
;	O
that	O
a	O
Sheet	O
and	O
Pail	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
his	O
Wife	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Rebeccah	B-pers
Maling	I-pers
in	O
the	O
night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
Linen	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
her	O
house	O
was	O
broken	O
and	O
the	O
goods	O
stollen	O
,	O
Abel	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
himself	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
one	O
Robert	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
got	O
over	O
a	O
wall	O
,	O
sat	O
in	O
a	O
chariot	O
while	O
the	O
watch	O
were	O
gone	O
their	O
rounds	O
,	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
wrung	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
out	O
of	O
water	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
away	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
Deborah	B-pers
Stens	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
nevertheless	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Hannah	B-pers
Woodall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Stuff-Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Stomacher	O
,	O
val.3	O
s.	O
3	O
Aprons	O
,	O
val.3	O
s.	O
the	O
wearing	O
apparel	O
of	O
Mary	O
wife	O
of	O
William	O
Crawford	O
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Crawford	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
carried	O
away	O
her	O
Cloaths	O
betimes	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
her	O
having	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
having	O
lost	O
her	O
own	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Husband	O
being	O
drinking	O
at	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
bid	O
her	O
wear	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
should	O
have	O
them	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
do	O
so	O
and	O
so	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
agreable	O
to	O
his	O
humour	O
,	O
but	O
going	O
into	O
Southark	O
,	O
fell	O
into	O
some	O
trouble	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
part	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Husband	O
never	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
contradict	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
whether	O
she	O
did	O
so	O
and	O
so	O
to	O
purchase	O
them	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
:	O
however	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
:	O
Margaret	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Chapman	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Cecil	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
6	O
l	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Siggins	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
and	O
staid	O
there	O
all	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
night	O
he	O
having	O
used	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
lock	O
'd	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Draw	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchin	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
sat	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
draw	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Draw	O
broken	O
open	O
and	O
the	O
Tankard	O
and	O
Prisoners	O
gone	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
Margaret	O
Pritchard	O
saying	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
a	O
House	O
of	O
a	O
resort	O
for	O
Thieves	O
and	O
other	O
ill	O
Persons	O
,	O
where	O
were	O
continual	O
Disturbances	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
coming	O
to	O
reckon	O
with	O
her	O
Landlady	O
,	O
she	O
asked	O
her	O
to	O
stay	O
all	O
night	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
there	O
to	O
and	O
fro	O
all	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
Thieves	O
drinking	O
out	O
of	O
this	O
Tankard	O
that	O
day	O
;	O
that	O
indeed	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Tankard	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
and	O
tho	O
'	O
their	O
Reputation	O
was	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
best	O
,	O
yet	O
it	O
was	O
probable	O
there	O
might	O
be	O
some	O
truth	O
in	O
what	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Joanna	B-pers
Revel	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Saddles	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Bridle	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Drinkwater	I-pers
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
Saddles	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
afterwards	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
Revel	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
they	O
were	O
left	O
there	O
by	O
a	O
person	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
her	O
house	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
servant	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
no	O
body	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Dyer	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Frances	B-pers
Knether	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
7	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
val.10	O
s.	O
a	O
Night-gown	O
,	O
val.10	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Arthur	O
Pines	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Loggin	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Loggin	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Mary	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
was	O
her	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Pine	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
her	O
house	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Hudson	O
let	O
in	O
the	O
two	O
other	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
amongst	O
them	O
carried	O
off	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
They	O
confessed	O
where	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
pawned	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
found	O
them	O
accordingly	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
Hudson	O
and	O
Dyer	O
were	O
the	O
Managers	O
of	O
the	O
intrigue	O
,	O
and	O
Knether	O
only	O
brought	O
into	O
the	O
Scrape	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
having	O
nothing	O
material	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
Knether	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Hudson	O
and	O
Dyer	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Furrow	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
3	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
36	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
Servant	O
to	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
that	O
used	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
pretty	O
much	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchin	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
frequently	O
lost	O
things	O
,	O
gave	O
his	O
Servants	O
order	O
to	O
be	O
watchful	O
to	O
discover	O
those	O
that	O
stole	O
them	O
;	O
That	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
being	O
missing	O
,	O
he	O
order	O
'd	O
his	O
Drawers	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
Spoons	O
were	O
in	O
use	O
in	O
the	O
several	O
Companies	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
time	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
goes	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
suspected	O
,	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
perceiving	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
enquiry	O
made	O
after	O
the	O
Spoon	O
,	O
steps	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
and	O
throws	O
it	O
down	O
the	O
Vault	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
Drawer	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
heard	O
it	O
ring	O
against	O
the	O
Wall	O
in	O
falling	O
:	O
The	O
Spoon	O
was	O
seen	O
lying	O
upon	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
Soil	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
confessed	O
at	O
his	O
Apprehention	O
he	O
had	O
stollen	O
three	O
,	O
but	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
:	O
However	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Rutton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
3	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
36	O
s.2	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
val.25	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
Floor	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
broke	O
a	O
hole	O
in	O
a	O
plaistered	O
Partition	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
Bed	O
's	O
head	O
,	O
putting	O
up	O
a	O
Board	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
go	O
in	O
and	O
come	O
out	O
at	O
pleasure	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
found	O
where	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
pawned	O
them	O
.	O
Upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
he	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
:	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Revel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Looking-Glass	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
small	O
value	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Blackwell	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
deposed	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
stollen	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Room	O
and	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Apron	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
that	O
was	O
sufficient	O
to	O
hinder	O
the	O
Jury	O
from	O
finding	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
19	O
Yards	O
of	O
Linnen	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ashmead	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
Waggon	O
loaded	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
of	O
the	O
Serjeants	B-place
Head	I-place
Inn	I-place
in	I-place
Friday-Street	I-place
,	O
the	O
Mistriss	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
suspecting	O
them	O
,	O
called	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
Servants	O
to	O
shut	O
the	O
Wicket	O
;	O
one	O
immediately	O
running	O
to	O
shut	O
it	O
,	O
a	O
person	O
brush	O
'd	O
before	O
him	O
and	O
slipt	O
out	O
:	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
further	O
up	O
,	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
opportunity	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
.	O
That	O
examining	O
the	O
Waggon	O
they	O
found	O
two	O
Packs	O
cut	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
Linnen	O
and	O
another	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Piece	O
of	O
Linnen	O
taken	O
out	O
.	O
That	O
taxing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
them	O
in	O
menacing	O
Language	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
Character	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
Knight	O
Baroner	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
expect	O
Satisfaction	O
for	O
such	O
Scandal	O
;	O
bar	O
however	O
they	O
not	O
believing	O
him	O
,	O
persisted	O
to	O
search	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
is	O
usual	O
to	O
common	O
Criminals	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
Pistols	O
;	O
&	O
c.	O
he	O
had	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
neither	O
Arms	O
nor	O
Mony	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
dangerous	O
Weapon	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
a	O
small	O
Knife	O
and	O
a	O
Tooth-pick-Case	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Edwards	O
of	O
Bristol	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
upper	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Inn-yard	O
to	O
enquire	O
of	O
the	O
Hostler	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
making	O
use	O
of	O
his	O
pretence	O
of	O
being	O
a	O
Knight	O
Baronet	O
not	O
in	O
his	O
favour	O
,	O
he	O
affirmed	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
;	O
and	O
this	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
some	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Hornsby	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pocket	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Gloves	O
.	O
and	O
22	O
d.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
Foot	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
May	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
passing	O
along	O
Ironmonger-Lane	B-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pull	O
'd	O
of	O
her	O
pocket	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
following	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
seized	O
and	O
held	O
him	O
while	O
Assistance	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Pocket	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
bosom	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
make	O
no	O
Defence	O
but	O
a	O
Newgate	O
one	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
,	O
a	O
lucky	O
Faculty	O
of	O
finding	O
things	O
the	O
very	O
Instant	O
that	O
they	O
are	O
lost	O
;	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bowen	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
in	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
Church-yard	B-place
in	I-place
St.	I-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Bisbopsgate	I-place
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Childers	I-pers
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
its	O
being	O
dissected	O
.	O
Several	O
Evidences	O
deposed	O
they	O
were	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
Interment	O
of	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
Rose	O
Inn	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
with	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Kersey	I-pers
,	O
Chirurgeon	O
at	O
Oxford	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Hamper	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
Guinea	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
suspected	O
as	O
Accomplices	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Counter	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
owned	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
another	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
dead	O
Body	O
,	O
put	O
it	O
first	O
into	O
a	O
Sack	O
and	O
then	O
into	O
a	O
Hamper	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
convey	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
Smithfield	O
.	O
So	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
and	O
since	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Fraternity	O
are	O
grown	O
such	O
common	O
Disturbers	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Dead	O
ca	O
n't	O
rest	O
quietly	O
in	O
their	O
Graves	O
for'em	O
,	O
is	O
sentenced	O
to	O
a	O
condign	O
Punishment	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edmund	B-pers
Bury	I-pers
Godfrey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Gould	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
134	O
pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Squire	I-pers
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Bury	I-pers
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
Stockings	O
were	O
lost	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
abroad	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Edward	B-pers
Gould	I-pers
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
inspecting	O
him	O
pressed	O
him	O
very	O
hard	O
to	O
declare	O
the	O
Truth	O
,	O
which	O
after	O
some	O
urgency	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
declar	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
before	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Abney	I-pers
.	O
That	O
he	O
and	O
Godfrey	O
having	O
contrived	O
to	O
rob	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
the	O
latter	O
came	O
the	O
Friday	O
before	O
and	O
enquired	O
when	O
he	O
might	O
come	O
that	O
there	O
would	O
be	O
Goods	O
ready	O
to	O
carry	O
off	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
following	O
about	O
8	O
a	O
clock	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Signal	O
was	O
to	O
whistle	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
;	O
that	O
accordingly	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
whistled	O
and	O
he	O
let	O
him	O
in	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
lay	O
hid	O
till	O
Gould	O
getting	O
his	O
Fellow-Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Godfrey	O
had	O
the	O
opportunity	O
to	O
carry	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
This	O
Examination	O
to	O
this	O
effect	O
was	O
Read	O
in	O
Court	O
:	O
but	O
notwithstanding	O
this	O
he	O
now	O
used	O
the	O
common	O
Newgate	O
Argument	O
,	O
an	O
universal	O
Negative	O
.	O
However	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
took	O
him	O
at	O
his	O
first	O
word	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
not	O
sufficient	O
Proof	O
against	O
Godfrey	O
,	O
him	O
they	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Abigail	B-pers
Dale	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
4	O
Drugget-Curtains	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
35	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
her	O
Lodger	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bray	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
inticeing	O
John	B-pers
Barber	I-pers
to	O
take	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
his	O
Master	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Whisley	I-pers
,	O
knowing	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Servant	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Barber	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
carry	O
'd	O
him	O
one	O
Sunday	O
to	O
a	O
Bawdy-house	O
and	O
debauched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
persuaded	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
some	O
Hair	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
but	O
a	O
trifling	O
defence	O
,	O
wherefore	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Cliff	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
4	O
Yards	O
of	O
Black	O
Silk	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Bagshaw	I-pers
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
two	O
others	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
shop	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Nermich	O
Crape	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
stepping	O
to	O
reach	O
down	O
some	O
goods	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Silk	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Counter	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
the	O
Crape	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
off	O
.	O
The	O
fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Leman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
12	O
Yards	O
of	O
Callicoe	O
,	O
value	O
36	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
shop	O
to	O
cheapen	O
some	O
Callicoe	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
said	O
goods	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
dropped	O
from	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
charged	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Tortoise-shell	O
Snuff-box	O
with	O
a	O
Silver	O
Lid	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
to	O
a	B-place
general	I-place
Court	I-place
at	I-place
the	I-place
East-India-House	I-place
,	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Box	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
hearing	O
an	O
outcry	O
of	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
he	O
seized	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
the	O
Snuff-box	O
in	O
his	O
Glove	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Box	O
going	O
up	O
stairs	O
in	O
the	O
India-House	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
pretence	O
did	O
not	O
hinder	O
the	O
Jury	O
from	O
finding	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
48	O
Moidores,4	O
Half-Moidores,1	O
Quadruple	O
piece	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.8	O
s.	O
pistols	O
and	O
bread	O
pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
78	O
l.19	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Capis	I-pers
,	O
the	O
day	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
place	O
abovementioned	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
in	O
the	O
India-House	B-place
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
bearing	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Pickpocket	O
at	O
the	O
East-India-House	O
,	O
he	O
seized	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
the	O
Swan	O
and	O
Griffin	O
Tavern	O
,	O
inspecting	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
person	O
by	O
some	O
signs	O
of	O
guilt	O
he	O
perceived	O
in	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
the	O
bag	O
of	O
money	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
bosom	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
as	O
before	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
bag	O
of	O
money	O
in	O
the	O
East-India-House	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Court	O
observed	O
he	O
was	O
unfortunately	O
lucky	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
likewife	O
two	O
Persons	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
they	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
up	O
something	O
like	O
a	O
Bag	O
in	O
the	O
India-House	O
.	O
There	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
brought	O
as	O
casually	O
as	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
dropped	O
out	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Clouds	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
fortunate	O
;	O
but	O
had	O
so	O
little	O
influence	O
upon	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
this	O
indictment	O
also	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Conibach	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Whitney	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anne	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Ray	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
3	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
Smock	O
,	O
val.4	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
was	O
12	O
Months	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
his	O
house	O
was	O
broken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
goods	O
stollen	O
.	O
Abel	B-pers
Downs	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Jeves	O
did	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
the	O
goods	O
to	O
Debor	O
ab	O
stens	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
Would	O
he	O
have	O
been	O
such	O
a	O
Rogne	O
as	O
Abel	O
Downs	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
have	O
hang	O
'd	O
him	O
4	O
years	O
ago	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
apprehended	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
lost	O
his	O
life	O
in	O
taking	O
him	O
again	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
an	O
old	O
offender	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Arabella	B-pers
Vickars	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Sheet	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
Blanket	O
,	O
val.4	O
s.	O
a	O
Saucepan	O
,	O
val.7	O
s.	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
small	O
value	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
she	O
let	O
a	O
room	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
lodged	O
there	O
five	O
nights	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
carried	O
off	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
came	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
and	O
her	O
Companion	O
had	O
quarrell	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
should	O
lodge	O
with	O
her	O
no	O
longer	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
became	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
.	O
Whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Darney	I-pers
in	O
the	O
night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
Pewter	O
,	O
Brass,16	O
Stone	O
of	O
Park	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Charity	B-pers
Dorney	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
stollen	O
.	O
A	O
Watchman	O
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
Pewter	O
upon	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
it	O
down	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
matter	O
depending	O
purely	O
upon	O
the	O
Watchman	O
's	O
evidence	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
old	O
and	O
his	O
sight	O
dark	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquited	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstans	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Edward	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
on	O
the	O
highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
5	O
Guineas	O
and	O
14	O
s.6	O
d.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
An	O
it	O
please	O
your	O
Excellency	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
received	O
the	O
Money	O
at	O
Chelsea-College	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
drinking	O
in	O
a	O
Brandy-Shop	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	O
,	O
having	O
the	O
Guineas	O
in	O
my	O
Phobb	O
and	O
the	O
Silver	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
conduct	O
me	O
so	O
my	O
lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
led	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
where	O
,	O
into	O
a	O
by	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
above	O
drew	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
money	O
.	O
Being	O
ahead	O
whother	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
Brandy	O
that	O
threw	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
An	O
it	O
please	O
your	O
Excellency	O
perhaps	O
that	O
was	O
a	O
help	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
positive	O
evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
sent	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
Concerns	O
(	O
meaning	O
her	O
Conforts	O
)	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
offer	O
him	O
2	O
Guineas	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
)	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
about	O
10	O
a	O
clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
sight	O
perhaps	O
as	O
dark	O
as	O
the	O
season	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
(	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
)	I-pers
Laud	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
2	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
val.8	O
s.	O
5	O
Holland	O
Sheets	O
,	O
val.3	O
l.	O
and	O
other	O
goods	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
proof	O
being	O
deficient	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
being	O
given	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass-Pot	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Baily	I-pers
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
lost	O
her	O
Pot	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
at	O
a	O
Brazier	O
's	O
Door	O
.	O
The	O
Brazier	O
's	O
Man	O
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
the	O
Woman	O
that	O
sold	O
it	O
him	O
.	O
This	O
being	O
all	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Tailor	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Dalton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
shop	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Buckles	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
agreed	O
for	O
,	O
leaving	O
six	O
pence	O
earnest	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
fetch	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
he	O
missed	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Buckles	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
thinking	O
the	O
proof	O
of	O
the	O
fact	O
full	O
enough	O
,	O
of	O
that	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
Second	O
time	O
with	O
one	O
Charles	B-pers
Cambel	I-pers
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
val.7	O
s	O
6	O
d.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Andrew	B-pers
Dalton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
same	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
John	O
Tailor	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
shop	O
and	O
Cambel	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
raise	O
Mony	O
enough	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
Buckles	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
desired	O
he	O
would	O
change	O
'em	O
for	O
a	O
less	O
pair	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Charles	B-pers
Cambel	I-pers
pretended	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
pair	O
likewise	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
threw	O
down	O
several	O
pair	O
at	O
once	O
upon	O
the	O
Counter	O
to	O
giv	O
them	O
an	O
opportunity	O
,	O
watching	O
them	O
narrowly	O
;	O
that	O
Cambel	O
stole	O
one	O
pair	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
:	O
he	O
apprehended	O
them	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Buckles	O
upon	O
Cambel	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
had	O
no	O
Defence	O
but	O
the	O
denial	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
Tailor	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Cambel	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Crisp	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
3	O
oz	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Human	O
Hair	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Whistler	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Journeyman	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Hair	O
was	O
his	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
he	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Hinchley	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
misdemeanour	O
,	O
in	O
Publishing	O
a	O
false	O
Will	O
to	O
receive	O
the	O
Wages	O
due	O
to	O
Quinton	B-pers
Archbuckle	I-pers
:	O
To	O
which	O
indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
,	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Phyllis	B-pers
Ayres	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
an	O
Assault	O
:	O
To	O
which	O
indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Christian	B-pers
Griffth	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
val.15	O
s.3	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
val.10	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
58	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Cartiss	I-pers
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
Decemb	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
employed	O
to	O
help	O
her	O
Wash	O
,	O
carried	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
alias	I-pers
Thomas	I-pers
Conner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Pancrass	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
,	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Perkins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Cambrick	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
val:1	O
s.	O
and	O
1	O
s.3	O
d.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Perkins	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
coming	B-place
from	I-place
Kentish	I-place
Town	I-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
Pancrass-Bridge	I-place
a	O
Person	O
met	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
Ridinghood	O
,	O
whom	O
she	O
took	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
just	O
passing	O
through	O
the	O
Posts	O
he	O
struck	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
breast	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Bitch	O
,	O
deliver	O
;	O
she	O
taking	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
Creater	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
?	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
struggled	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Head	O
of	O
the	O
Ridinghood	O
fell	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
young	O
Woman	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Perkins	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
Man	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
Man	O
.	O
That	O
upon	O
this	O
she	O
cried	O
out	O
for	O
Help	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
whistled	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Man	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
assist	O
her	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Constable	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
rather	O
justifying	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
than	O
assisting	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
suspected	O
him	O
for	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Gang	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
Help	O
came	O
he	O
walked	O
off	O
.	O
She	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
from	O
her	O
Handkerchief	O
and	O
Mony	O
.	O
The	O
young	O
Woman	O
deposed	O
much	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
adding	O
,	O
that	O
upon	O
her	O
crying	O
out	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
her	O
Bitch	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
would	O
stop	O
her	O
mouth	O
presently	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gemings	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
with	O
his	O
Wife	O
not	O
far	O
off	O
,	O
heard	O
the	O
Outcry	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
his	O
Wife	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Town	O
to	O
call	O
one	O
smith	O
to	O
their	O
assistance	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
aid	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
than	O
they	O
secured	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
this	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
:	O
That	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
Friends	O
of	O
his	O
that	O
were	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
by	O
whom	O
he	O
sent	O
a	O
Letter	O
to	O
his	O
Father	O
;	O
that	O
after	O
having	O
drank	O
together	O
in	O
Town	O
they	O
agreed	O
to	O
bear	O
them	O
company	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
about	O
dozen	O
or	O
14	O
in	O
all	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Highgate	O
,	O
drinking	O
very	O
freely	O
at	O
several	O
places	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
Horns	O
at	O
Highgate	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
sworn	O
;	O
That	O
leaving	O
their	O
friends	O
at	O
Highgate	O
they	O
were	O
returning	O
to	O
London	O
;	O
That	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
Woman	O
in	O
company	O
that	O
could	O
not	O
walk	O
so	O
fast	O
as	O
the	O
Men	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
before	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
he	O
,	O
enquiring	O
of	O
some	O
Persons	O
he	O
met	O
,	O
was	O
inform	O
'd	O
that	O
his	O
Company	O
was	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
,	O
had	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
overtake	O
them	O
to	O
get	O
them	O
to	O
stav	O
while	O
the	O
Woman	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
her	O
Ridinghood	O
upon	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
purpose	O
to	O
make	O
some	O
sport	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
being	O
elevated	O
with	O
Drinking	O
did	O
attempt	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
little	O
Game	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
whereupon	O
there	O
arose	O
a	O
little	O
Scuffle	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
seiz	O
'd	O
and	O
dragg	O
'd	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Town	O
,	O
sent	O
to	O
New	O
Prison	O
and	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
but	O
took	O
nothing	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
And	O
as	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
by	O
those	O
that	O
search	O
'd	O
him	O
at	O
his	O
Apprehention	O
,	O
had	O
but	O
Two	O
pence	O
Half-penny	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Woman	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
testified	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Circumstances	O
of	O
his	O
having	O
her	O
Riding-hood	O
.	O
A	O
great	O
many	O
Persons	O
of	O
credit	O
appeared	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
industrious	O
Fellow	O
:	O
And	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
but	O
a	O
dangerous	O
drunken	O
Frolick	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
as	O
if	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
was	O
levelled	O
at	O
40	O
l	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Dalton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Printer	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Printing	O
and	O
Publishing	O
a	O
seditious	O
Libel	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
are	O
contained	O
many	O
false	O
and	O
scandalous	O
Expressions	O
against	O
his	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
,	I-pers
the	I-pers
Prince	I-pers
and	I-pers
Princess	I-pers
of	I-pers
Wales	I-pers
,	I-pers
and	I-pers
present	I-pers
Government	I-pers
,	O
intitled	O
,	O
Advise	O
to	O
the	O
Freeholders	O
of	O
England	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Mexey	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
introduced	O
by	O
one	O
Derbyshire	O
,	O
a	O
fort	O
of	O
a	O
Pacquet-Bearer	O
from	O
France	O
to	O
the	O
Disaffected	O
in	O
England	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Flint	O
's	O
Room	O
in	O
Newgate	B-place
the	O
9th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
last	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
Libel	O
call	O
'd	O
The	O
Battle	O
of	O
Sherifmore	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
there	O
,	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
dispose	O
of	O
the	O
Advice	O
to	O
the	O
Freeholder	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
sold	O
him	O
10	O
of	O
them	O
at	O
18	O
d.	O
a	O
piece	O
(	O
being	O
about	O
the	O
size	O
of	O
a	O
penny	O
Book	O
)	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
mark	O
'd	O
and	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
sent	O
for	O
Drink	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drank	O
the	O
Pretender	O
's	O
Health	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
James	O
the	O
IIId	O
,	O
and	O
success	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
of	O
Sweden	O
's	O
Expedition	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
soon	O
be	O
here	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
should	O
be	O
all	O
glorious	O
Fellows	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
have	O
Commissions	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
reveng	O
'd	O
of	O
that	O
Rogue	O
Buckley	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
print	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
print	O
against	O
this	O
damn	O
'd	O
Government	O
he	O
would	O
print	O
it	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
Captain	O
Moor	B-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
present	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
full	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
invalidate	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Publishing	O
this	O
Libel	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Chessey	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Cheshire	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Chiswick	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Honour	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
one	O
Strawberry	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
and	O
one	O
Black	O
Gelding	O
,	O
val	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bowcher	I-pers
,4	O
Mails	O
,	O
val.8	O
l.	O
and	O
50	O
Leather	O
Bags	O
,	O
val	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
this	O
Indictment	O
Franscis	O
Williams	O
pleaded	O
Not	O
guilty	O
.	O
But	O
Matthew	O
Chessey	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
plead	O
,	O
unless	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Tankard	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
things	O
restored	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
from	O
him	O
(	O
which	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
was	O
his	O
share	O
of	O
the	O
35	O
l	O
Bank-Note	O
which	O
his	O
wife	O
and	O
Hollyday	O
's	O
pot	O
off	O
,	O
as	O
below	O
)	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
obstinately	O
persisted	O
in	O
refusing	O
to	O
plead	O
,	O
the	O
Executioner	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
and	O
order	O
'd	O
to	O
bring	O
Cords	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
force	O
him	O
to	O
plead	O
,	O
by	O
tying	O
his	O
Thumbs	O
together	O
and	O
so	O
drawing	O
the	O
Noose	O
hard	O
by	O
violent	O
pulling	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
the	O
Forerunner	O
of	O
the	O
Press	O
.	O
But	O
before	O
the	O
Executioner	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
at	O
last	O
told	O
the	O
Court	O
he	O
would	O
plead	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
promise	O
him	O
afterwards	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
them	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
answered	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
what	O
was	O
legally	O
his	O
:	O
So	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Not	O
guilty	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Honour	I-pers
the	O
Post-boy	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
between	B-place
Turnham-Green	I-place
and	I-place
Branford	I-place
there	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
three	O
men	O
,	O
that	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
pass	O
'd	O
by	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
horse	O
's	O
bridle	O
,	O
and	O
led	O
the	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
drove	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
field	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
told	O
him	O
they	O
wanted	O
the	O
Bristol	O
and	O
Exeter	O
Mails	O
,	O
threatning	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
them	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
cut	O
the	O
straps	O
,	O
and	O
opening	O
the	O
Mail	O
,	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Western	O
and	O
Bristol	O
Packets	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
bound	O
him	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
off	O
.	O
Hollyday	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoners	O
and	O
he	O
met	O
at	O
the	O
Harpin	O
Grays-Inn-Lane	O
,	O
to	O
console	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
rob	O
the	O
Mail	O
,	O
agreed	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
pretence	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
Commission	O
from	O
the	O
Pretender	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
at	O
Bristol	O
;	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
put	O
in	O
execution	O
the	O
Sunday	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
disappointed	O
of	O
their	O
Horses	O
;	O
that	O
on	O
Tuesday-night	O
they	O
met	O
at	O
about	O
9	O
a	O
clock	O
,	O
took	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
towards	O
Branford	O
said	O
till	O
about	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
seeing	O
the	O
Post-boy	O
thought	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
gone	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
for	O
returning	O
;	O
but	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
covering	O
their	O
horses	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
at	O
the	O
Post-boy	O
had	O
before	O
related	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
Packets	O
to	O
Chessey	O
's	O
house	O
in	O
Fetter-lane	O
.	O
Holiday	O
's	O
Wife	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
8	O
of	O
the	O
clock	O
on	O
Wednesday-morning	O
one	O
Smith	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
Chessey	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
all	O
over	O
dirt	O
,	O
like	O
frighted	O
men	O
,	O
opening	O
Letters	O
;	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
up	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
Williams	O
said	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
him	O
,	O
why	O
would	O
he	O
not	O
came	O
up	O
?	O
he	O
has	O
put	O
us	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
be	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
seen	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
they	O
thought	O
themselves	O
unsafe	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
saying	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
friend	O
at	O
the	O
Black	O
Dog	O
in	O
shoreditch	O
,	O
whom	O
be	O
had	O
trusted	O
very	O
considerably	O
,	O
and	O
believing	O
they	O
might	O
be	O
safe	O
under	O
his	O
roof	O
,	O
the	O
Letters	O
were	O
accordingly	O
carried	O
thither	O
:	O
That	O
they	O
found	O
no	O
booty	O
in	O
the	O
Letters	O
they	O
opened	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
:	O
that	O
one	O
concern	O
'd	O
having	O
business	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
attend	O
on	O
Thursday	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
lock	O
'd	O
up	O
at	O
the	O
Black	O
Dog	O
till	O
Friday-morning	O
;	O
that	O
on	O
Friday-morning	O
they	O
met	O
there	O
,	O
eat	O
a	O
Breakfast	O
;	O
till	O
the	O
man	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
up	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
had	O
a	O
fire	O
made	O
,	O
a	O
large	O
table	O
set	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
hung	O
up	O
her	O
Ridinghood	O
against	O
the	O
key-hole	O
,	O
Chessey	O
fetch	O
'd	O
out	O
the	O
bag	O
,	O
laid	O
it	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
to	O
opening	O
the	O
Letters	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
found	O
3	O
Chequer-Notes	O
of	O
an	O
100	O
l.	O
each	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
Bank-	O
Notes	O
of	O
20	O
l.	O
each	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
distributed	O
equally	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
likewise	O
a	O
Bank-Note	O
of	O
35	O
l	O
which	O
being	O
an	O
odd	O
sum	O
,	O
they	O
sent	O
her	O
and	O
Chessey	O
's	O
wife	O
to	O
lay	O
it	O
out	O
in	O
Plate	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
did	O
,	O
buying	O
2	O
Tankards,6	O
Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
which	O
also	O
were	O
divided	O
amongst	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
took	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
their	O
parts	O
of	O
the	O
Letters	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
and	O
dropt	O
them	O
in	O
Moor-fields	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Chessey	O
's	O
wife	O
and	O
she	O
going	O
before	O
to	O
see	O
all	O
safe	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
found	O
likewise	O
a	O
Bank-Note	O
of	O
25	O
l.	O
which	O
her	O
husband	O
had	O
to	O
receive	O
the	O
money	O
at	O
the	O
Bank	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
deposed	O
he	O
carried	O
into	O
Cannon-street	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
at	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Cripple	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
for	O
a	O
Porter	O
,	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Bank	O
to	O
receive	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Reeves	O
the	O
Porter	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
plying	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
was	O
called	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Holliday	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
25	O
l.	O
Note	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Bank	O
to	O
receive	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
the	O
Note	O
and	O
he	O
were	O
stopped	O
(	O
notice	O
having	O
been	O
given	O
of	O
it	O
before	O
)	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
came	O
Holliday	O
's	O
Wife	O
and	O
one	O
Peacock	O
a	O
porter	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Cripple	O
,	O
and	O
enquired	O
for	O
the	O
Porter	O
that	O
a	O
North-Country	O
Gentleman	O
had	O
sent	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
with	O
a	O
Bank-Note	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
that	O
last	O
night	O
he	O
got	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
could	O
not	O
come	O
for	O
it	O
himself	O
.	O
Peacock	O
the	O
Porter	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
plying	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
was	O
called	O
to	O
Holliday	O
and	O
sent	O
along	O
with	O
his	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Cripple	O
on	O
this	O
errand	O
.	O
The	O
Porter	O
Reeves	B-pers
appeared	O
that	O
had	O
carry	O
'd	O
the	O
Note	O
to	O
the	O
Bank	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
'em	O
,	O
the	O
Landlord	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
had	O
the	O
money	O
in	O
his	O
hands	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
demanding	O
he	O
fetch	O
'd	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
telling	O
it	O
out	O
to	O
Peacok	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
but	O
telling	O
it	O
wrong	O
,	O
sometimes	O
19	O
for	O
20	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
22	O
for	O
20	O
,	O
on	O
purpose	O
to	O
protract	O
the	O
time	O
while	O
he	O
sent	O
word	O
to	O
the	O
Bank	O
,	O
some	O
persons	O
came	O
from	O
there	O
and	O
apprehended	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
fact	O
being	O
charged	O
home	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
promises	O
of	O
indemnity	O
to	O
her	O
husband	O
.	O
she	O
at	O
last	O
discovered	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
;	O
so	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Coach	O
and	O
Horses	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
and	O
apprehended	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
his	O
direction	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
sworn	O
likewise	O
,	O
that	O
Chessey	O
had	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Letters	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Mail	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
.	O
Several	O
of	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
confirmed	O
by	O
a	O
variety	O
of	O
Evidences	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
Said	O
they	O
were	O
innocent	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
them	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
Chessey	O
deny	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
upon	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
a	O
Horse	O
or	O
Mare	O
for	O
twelve	O
months	O
last	O
past	O
.	O
Williams	O
labour	O
'd	O
to	O
invalidate	O
the	O
evidence	O
of	O
Holliday	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
Rogue	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
all	O
the	O
Goals	O
in	O
England	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
perjur	O
'd	O
,	O
Villain	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
convicted	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
a	O
legal	O
Evidence	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
charge	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
Copy	O
of	O
his	O
Pardon	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
in	O
1711	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
fulfilled	O
the	O
Conditions	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
flood	O
still	O
convict	O
.	O
But	O
he	O
neither	O
proving	O
his	O
Conviction	O
,	O
nor	O
the	O
Nonperformance	O
of	O
the	O
Conditions	O
of	O
his	O
Pardon	O
it	O
bore	O
no	O
weight	O
with	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
being	O
asked	O
what	O
they	O
had	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
Arrest	O
of	O
Judgement	O
,	O
Chessey	O
insisted	O
upon	O
a	O
promise	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
the	O
Tankard	O
;	O
but	O
was	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
promised	O
so	O
such	O
thing	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
he	O
should	O
after	O
Tryal	O
have	O
what	O
was	O
his	O
Rights	O
:	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
,	O
being	O
convict	O
,	O
had	O
no	O
legal	O
Right	O
to	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
all	O
being	O
forfeited	O
;	O
much	O
less	O
had	O
be	O
any	O
to	O
the	O
Tackard	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
Purchased	O
with	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
gotten	O
by	O
the	O
Robbery	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
stood	O
convicted	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
owned	O
he	O
was	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
fact	O
after	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
but	O
deny	O
'd	O
his	O
being	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
pleaded	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
examined	O
the	O
Letters	O
,	O
the	O
rest	O
were	O
all	O
illiterate	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
read	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
burnt	O
all	O
the	O
Letters	O
and	O
Writings	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
great	O
fire	O
was	O
made	O
,	O
to	O
whose	O
flames	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
to	O
be	O
committed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
might	O
not	O
rise	O
up	O
in	O
judgement	O
against	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
,	O
being	O
sensible	O
of	O
the	O
consequences	O
,	O
and	O
shock	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
barbarity	O
of	O
their	O
design	O
,	O
opposed	O
it	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
Children	O
unborn	O
,	O
and	O
Generation	O
to	O
come	O
,	O
would	O
be	O
bound	O
to	O
Curse	O
them	O
for	O
so	O
Villainous	O
an	O
Action	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
they	O
should	O
have	O
their	O
Titles	O
to	O
Estates	O
and	O
Debts	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
destroyed	O
,	O
asserting	O
there	O
were	O
Packets	O
of	O
Bonds	O
,	O
Obligations	O
and	O
Deeds	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
prevented	O
so	O
great	O
a	O
calamity	O
,	O
that	O
would	O
have	O
affected	O
all	O
the	O
Western	O
parts	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
even	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
the	O
Land	O
's	O
End	O
,	O
he	O
hoped	O
the	O
Recorder	O
would	O
represent	O
him	O
as	O
an	O
object	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
mercy	O
.	O
But	O
he	O
was	O
answered	O
,	O
that	O
tho	O
'	O
Writings	O
should	O
be	O
by	O
such	O
accidents	O
destroyed	O
,	O
persons	O
did	O
not	O
therefore	O
lose	O
their	O
Estates	O
;	O
nor	O
was	O
it	O
credible	O
that	O
Deeds	O
of	O
Estates	O
,	O
or	O
such	O
like	O
things	O
,	O
were	O
,	O
or	O
could	O
be	O
sent	O
inclos	O
'd	O
in	O
Letters	O
by	O
the	O
Post	O
.	O
However	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
represent	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
the	O
case	O
as	O
it	O
really	O
was	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ash	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.Martin	B-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Gent	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Abbot	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Belly	O
near	O
the	O
Navel	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
and	O
depth	O
of	O
8	O
Inches	O
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languish	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
March	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
inquest	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Mr.Rendal	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
having	O
a	O
Warrant	O
to	O
Arrest	O
one	O
Robinson	O
in	O
an	O
Action	O
of	O
200	O
l.	O
himself	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
being	O
together	O
,	O
they	O
saw	O
him	O
go	O
into	O
a	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	B-place
with	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Tavern	O
not	O
being	O
in	O
their	O
Liberty	O
,	O
they	O
waited	O
his	O
coming	O
out	O
and	O
arrested	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Woman	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
An	O
Arrest	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
them	O
and	O
asked	O
them	O
,	O
how	O
they	O
dar	O
'd	O
to	O
arrest	O
any	O
person	O
so	O
near	O
the	O
Play-house	O
?	O
and	O
immediately	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
Go	O
it	O
(	O
a	O
Term	O
which	O
they	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
upon	O
such	O
Occasions	O
)	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
drew	O
their	O
Swords	O
,	O
and	O
Walker	O
cut	O
Randal	O
over	O
the	O
Eye	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
likewise	O
made	O
several	O
passes	O
at	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Wound	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
died	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
Abbot	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Walker	O
had	O
murder	O
'd	O
him	O
barbarously	O
.	O
And	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Evidences	O
produced	O
which	O
Interfer	O
'd	O
as	O
to	O
some	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
but	O
far	O
the	O
greater	O
number	O
agreed	O
in	O
this	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
struck	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
before	O
their	O
5	O
words	O
were	O
drawn	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
lost	O
his	O
Stick	O
,	O
ran	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
,	O
got	O
a	O
Broom	O
,	O
beat	O
of	O
Mr.Walker	O
's	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
;	O
afterwards	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
lay	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
beat	O
him	O
in	O
an	O
unmerciful	O
manner	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Spectators	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
against	O
the	O
Barbarity	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
would	O
he	O
murder	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
?	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
sharp	O
Reacounters	O
betwixt	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
Rendal	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
sometimes	O
Abbot	O
enagaged	O
with	O
Mr.Walker	O
,	O
and	O
Randal	O
with	O
Mr	O
.	O
Ask	O
sometimes	O
a	O
;	O
sometimes	O
both	O
upon	O
one	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
lying	O
;	O
upon	O
Mr.	O
Walker	O
and	O
beating	O
him	O
very	O
barbarously	O
,	O
Randal	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
violently	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Walker	O
as	O
he	O
lay	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
often	O
striking	O
his	O
own	O
Partner	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
instaid	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
till	O
at	O
last	O
having	O
been	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
sharply	O
engaged	O
,	O
besmear	O
'd	O
with	O
Blood	O
,	O
and	O
wallow	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Dirt	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
help	O
'd	O
off	O
the	O
Ground	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
being	O
lifted	O
up	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
d	O
-	O
mn	O
the	O
Reseal	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
hurt	O
my	O
self	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
going	O
into	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
to	O
wash	O
himself	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
him	O
,	O
how	O
come	O
1	O
to	O
fall	O
upon	O
Walker	B-pers
Sward	I-pers
?	O
however	O
,	O
pleas	O
'd	O
himself	O
with	O
this	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
manl	O
'd	O
him	O
sufficiently	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Walker	O
called	O
several	O
Gentlemen	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
for	O
a	O
quiet	O
Person	O
that	O
was	O
more	O
inclin	O
'd	O
to	O
take	O
then	O
give	O
Affronts	O
.	O
However	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Jame	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Horse	O
,	O
val	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Brock	I-pers
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
horse	O
in	O
Cambridgeshire	B-place
2	O
Years	O
and	O
3	O
quarters	O
dace	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
never	O
heard	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
lately	O
;	O
that	O
his	O
Son	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
an	O
Uncle	O
in	O
Hertfordshire	O
,	O
on	O
his	O
Uncle	O
's	O
Son	O
came	O
likewise	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
to	O
see	O
his	O
Father	O
upon	O
that	O
Horse	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
also	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
and	O
Challenged	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
affirming	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Pleaded	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Horse	O
of	O
The	O
.	O
Blakesly	O
for	O
10	O
l.	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
vouch	O
'd	O
and	O
told	O
according	O
to	O
Custom	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
went	O
and	O
searched	O
the	O
Book	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
so	O
.	O
The	O
person	O
that	O
sold	O
the	O
Horse	O
appear	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
affirm	O
'd	O
he	O
bought	O
him	O
last	O
Summer	O
at	O
Reading	O
Fair	O
of	O
one	O
Canon	O
,	O
who	O
knew	O
the	O
breeding	O
of	O
him	O
up	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
it	O
did	O
appear	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Horse	O
,	O
the	O
Seller	O
,	O
Voucher	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
appeared	O
in	O
Court	O
and	O
justified	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
offering	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
place	O
and	O
prove	O
all	O
they	O
had	O
said	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
very	O
good	O
Repute	O
and	O
Worth	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
knew	O
all	O
this	O
before	O
he	O
indicted	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
so	O
obstinate	O
and	O
malicious	O
a	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Court	O
ordered	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
his	O
Indictment	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hodges	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
an	O
Ingot	O
of	O
Silver	O
,	O
weight	O
12	O
oz	O
val.3	O
d.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
October,1715	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
shop	O
to	O
bespeak	O
two	O
plates	O
of	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
at	O
night	O
to	O
fetch	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
be	O
afterwards	O
missed	O
the	O
ingot	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
's	O
Servant	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
a	O
Pawnbroker	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Pawnbro-ker	O
's	O
Son	O
shewed	O
him	O
an	O
Ingot	O
of	O
Silver	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
suppos	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
,	O
bearing	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
one	O
;	O
that	O
claiming	O
the	O
Ingot	O
,	O
the	O
Pawnbroker	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
promising	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
secure	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
afterwards	O
did	O
but	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
having	O
receiv	O
'd	O
the	O
Money	O
that	O
was	O
lent	O
on	O
the	O
Ingot	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
apprehend	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
him	O
,	O
till	O
it	O
happen	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
arrested	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
one	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
get	O
the	O
person	O
arrested	O
,	O
at	O
liberty	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
apprehending	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
agree	O
the	O
matter	O
with	O
his	O
Debtor	O
.	O
The	O
Pawnbrnker	O
's	O
Son	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
lent	O
the	O
Mony	O
,	O
viz.48	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
Ingot	O
,	O
unknown	O
to	O
his	O
Father	O
,	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
owned	O
be	O
pawned	O
an	O
Ingot	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Broker	O
's	O
Son	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
It	O
was	O
an	O
Ingot	O
he	O
had	O
cast	O
of	O
the	O
Filings	O
and	O
Parings	O
of	O
Plate	O
and	O
some	O
Silver	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
by	O
Trade	O
an	O
Ingraver	O
and	O
Snuff-box	O
Maker	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
having	O
apprehended	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Stratagem	O
before	O
mentioned	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
Note	O
for	O
6	O
l.	O
of	O
the	O
Man	O
he	O
had	O
arrested	O
,	O
Instead	O
of	O
20	O
l.	O
that	O
was	O
owing	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
likewise	O
produced	O
an	O
Evidence	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Lewis	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
to	O
desire	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
favourable	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Lewis	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
favour	O
him	O
all	O
he	O
could	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Broker	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
the	O
Man	O
he	O
aimed	O
at	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
spend	O
100	O
l.	O
to	O
plague	O
him	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Mughouse-man	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
having	O
considered	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Rhodes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Street	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
was	O
12	O
months	O
.	O
Abel	B-pers
Downs	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Whittle	I-pers
,	O
did	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
that	O
Rhodes	O
first	O
went	O
upon	O
the	O
speak	O
(	O
i.e	O
to	O
see	O
in	O
what	O
Disposition	O
matters	O
were	O
)	O
and	O
perceiving	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
leaving	O
the	O
Door	O
upon	O
the	O
latch	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
sheets	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
for	O
12	O
s.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
Second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Walter	B-pers
Heddy	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
Nov.1714	O
.The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
this	O
indictment	O
likewise	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Meakins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
40	O
Yards	O
of	O
Flanel	O
,	O
val.50	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Oakly	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
Jan.	O
in	O
the	O
1st	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
Flanel	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shop-window	O
.	O
Abel	B-pers
Downs	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
lent	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
he	O
cut	O
the	O
strings	O
that	O
tied	O
the	O
Flanel	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
Deborah	B-pers
Stent	I-pers
for	O
16	O
s.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
to	O
10	O
d.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
val.15	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
Jan.	O
in	O
the	O
1	O
st	O
year	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Abel	O
Dawns	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
going	O
out	O
a	O
thieving	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
used	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
they	O
fixed	O
upon	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
body	O
in	O
it	O
and	O
the	O
Window	O
half	O
open	O
:	O
but	O
perceiving	O
a	O
Woman	O
in	O
a	O
shop	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
looking	O
toward	O
it	O
,	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
this	O
Conviance	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
should	O
go	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
buying	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
to	O
divert	O
her	O
while	O
he	O
went	O
is	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
Deborah	O
Stent	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Giles	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
,	O
value,35	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
Matth.ew	B-pers
Biner	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
April	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
year	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
reign	O
.	O
Abel	O
Downs	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Giles	I-pers
lately	O
executed	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
lifted	O
up	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
patting	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
hole	O
of	O
the	O
shutter	O
,	O
broke	O
the	O
sash	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Perriwig	O
off	O
from	O
a	O
block	O
that	O
stood	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
making	O
a	O
noise	O
,	O
they	O
heard	O
some	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
stirring	O
,	O
so	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
they	O
into	O
Drury-lane	O
and	O
himself	O
into	O
Long-Acre	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
Wigg	O
on	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
use	O
to	O
wear	O
,	O
thought	O
they	O
had	O
sunk	O
him	O
in	O
that	O
shop	O
(	O
i.e	O
.	O
stollen	O
more	O
than	O
they	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
)	O
asked	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
lappy	O
Gager	O
take	O
a	O
Ratler	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
loped	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
snabbled	O
his	O
Poll	O
:	O
That	O
is	O
,	O
He	O
saw	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
drink	O
take	O
Coach	O
;	O
and	O
be	O
following	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
looking	O
out	O
,	O
be	O
snatch	O
'd	O
off	O
his	O
Wigg	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Katherine	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Westbury	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sparks	I-pers
.	O
The	O
fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
val	O
.	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
Val.8	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Gobel	I-pers
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
to	O
lodge	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
carried	O
away	O
the	O
Sheets	O
of	O
the	O
Bed	O
;	O
he	O
missing	O
them	O
,	O
immediately	O
following	O
him	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
put	O
them	O
at	O
his	O
back	O
,	O
unbuttoning	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
let	O
them	O
drop	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
