TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
,	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
27th,28th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
and	O
1st	O
,	O
and	O
2d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
March,1716/17	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Third	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
JAMES	B-pers
BATEMAN	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
and	O
Bart	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Worshipful	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Powys	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Dormer	O
;	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fortescue-Aland	I-pers
,	O
Baron	O
of	O
the	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
Duncan	B-pers
Dee	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
;	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
Names	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Edes	I-pers
George	B-pers
Harst	I-pers
Gabriel	B-pers
Halt	I-pers
John	B-pers
Sharp	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Godfrey	I-pers
John	B-pers
Blithe	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Mullins	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Membrey	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Scattergood	I-pers
John	B-pers
Hore	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Cock	I-pers
Walter	B-pers
Man	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
Arhem	B-pers
White	I-pers
William	B-pers
Grimts	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Duck	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Whitely	I-pers
Guy	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
William	B-pers
Smithies	I-pers
William	B-pers
Gilmore	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Wigg	I-pers
Isaak	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
John	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Francis	B-pers
Leatherwood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Marrying	O
Ann	B-pers
Combs	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
the	O
24	O
th	O
Day	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
present	O
Majesty	O
,	O
while	O
his	O
former	O
Wife	O
Mary	B-pers
Nelson	I-pers
,	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
married	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
11th	O
Year	O
of	O
King	O
William	O
,	O
was	O
living	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Proof	O
of	O
his	O
last	O
Marriage	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
own	O
Confession	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
;	O
for	O
his	O
first	O
Wife	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
her	O
for	O
4	O
Pipes	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
and	O
2	O
full	O
Pots	O
of	O
Beer	O
.	O
So	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
withal	O
receiv	O
'd	O
the	O
Friendly	O
Advice	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
that	O
he	O
married	O
no	O
more	O
Wives	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Polson	I-pers
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
an	O
unlawful	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Day-time	O
,	O
no	O
body	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
steal	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
pick	O
'd	O
the	O
Padlock	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
,	O
had	O
not	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
main	O
Lock	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
Picklock-Keys	O
and	O
a	O
Chisel	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
at	O
her	O
Apprehension	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
a	O
Trespass	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Tooley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
3	O
Holland	O
Smocks	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
3	O
Aprons	O
,	O
val.8	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Abigail	B-pers
Ray	I-pers
.	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
not	O
positive	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
stole	O
them	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Aprons	O
was	O
found	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
depositing	O
.	O
She	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
Evidence	O
that	O
she	O
stole	O
them	O
,	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pauls	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
100	O
of	O
Hamborough	O
Pipe-Staves	O
,	O
val.30	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Comb	I-pers
deposed	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Pipe-Staves	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
own	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
upon	O
the	O
River	O
for	O
10	O
s.	O
But	O
this	O
appearing	O
but	O
a	O
Pretence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
other	O
Evidence	O
against	O
George	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
sold	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Seymour	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
4	O
Linnen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Morrice	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
down	O
Stairs	O
with	O
3	O
of	O
the	O
Sheets	O
in	O
her	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
about	O
her	O
Wast	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
no	O
body	O
to	O
appear	O
for	O
her	O
Reputation	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Matter	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Katharine	B-pers
Strong	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
26	O
Ells	O
of	O
Dowlass	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Percival	B-pers
Chaundler	I-pers
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Shop	O
under	O
the	O
Pretence	O
of	O
buying	O
some	O
Cloth	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
being	O
informed	O
by	O
2	O
other	O
Customers	O
who	O
were	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Cloth	O
privately	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
her	O
Riding-hood	O
,	O
he	O
informed	O
his	O
Mistress	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
whereupon	O
they	O
apprehended	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
examining	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
under	O
her	O
Riding-hood	O
,	O
she	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
nothing	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
her	O
own	O
,	O
but	O
turning	O
aside	O
her	O
Riding-hood	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Piece	O
of	O
Dowlass	O
.	O
The	O
2	O
Customers	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
deposed	O
,	O
they	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
the	O
Cloth	O
and	O
conceal	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Cloth	O
for	O
a	O
Shirt	O
for	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
only	O
took	O
the	O
Piece	O
of	O
Cloth	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
to	O
look	O
upon	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Light	O
.	O
But	O
this	O
,	O
as	O
plausible	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
a	O
Pretence	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
2	O
Yards	O
and	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
Embossed	O
Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Child	O
's	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Stelles	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
An	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
out	O
,	O
said	O
to	O
two	O
of	O
his	O
Accomplices	O
,	O
By	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
them	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
apprehended	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
a	O
Cry	O
of	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
assist	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
charg	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Pretence	O
being	O
but	O
trifling	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Plat	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Nut	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Guineas	O
and	O
31	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Dalling	I-pers
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
her	O
Daughter	O
both	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
their	O
Shop	O
under	O
Pretence	O
of	O
buying	O
Halfpenny-worth	O
of	O
Packthread	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
some	O
of	O
King	O
Charles	O
's	O
Farthings	O
and	O
Half-pence	O
,	O
offering	O
them	O
Profit	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
New-England	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
could	O
make	O
a	O
considerable	O
Advantage	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
desired	O
some	O
K.	O
Charles	O
's	O
Half-Crowns	O
,	O
Crowns	O
,	O
and	O
Guineas	O
:	O
Upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
if	O
Queen	O
Ann	O
's	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
as	O
well	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
worth	O
a	O
Farthing	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
the	O
Money	O
being	O
laid	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Counter	O
to	O
pick	O
them	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
snatch	O
'd	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
night	O
,	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
overtake	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
expected	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
more	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Daughter	O
being	O
abroad	O
about	O
two	O
Months	O
after	O
,	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
Cock	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
going	O
into	O
Morefields	O
to	O
merchandize	O
in	O
that	O
barbarous	O
way	O
of	O
Traffick	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
got	O
him	O
apprehended	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
both	O
very	O
positive	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
but	O
could	O
make	O
no	O
other	O
Defence	O
,	O
nor	O
had	O
any	O
Person	O
to	O
appear	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
;	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Phillip	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
100	O
Yards	O
of	O
Pomerania	O
Linnen	O
,	O
value	O
54	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sir	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Ailoff	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
had	O
lock	O
'd	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
about	O
two	O
Hours	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
an	O
adjacent	O
Necessary-house	O
,	O
perceived	O
the	O
Warehouse-door	O
had	O
been	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
the	O
Premises	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
Pack	O
had	O
been	O
cut	O
and	O
3	O
Pieces	O
of	O
the	O
Linnen	O
laid	O
down	O
behind	O
the	O
Warehouse-door	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
been	O
employ	O
'd	O
as	O
a	O
Labourer	O
to	O
work	O
in	O
that	O
Warehouse	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
alledg	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
only	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
Necessary-house	O
to	O
ease	O
himself	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
positive	O
that	O
he	O
broke	O
it	O
open	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
300	O
lb	O
.	O
Weight	O
of	O
Smirna	O
Raisons	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Fry	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Leachmere	I-pers
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
John	B-pers
Day	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Accomplice	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
.	O
That	O
himself	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
two	O
others	O
,	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
about	O
5	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
off	O
half	O
of	O
the	O
Cask	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
the	O
Saturday	O
following	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
the	O
Remainder	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
He	O
brought	O
one	O
Martha	B-pers
Letts	I-pers
and	O
another	O
Person	O
,	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
when	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
done	O
with	O
her	O
at	O
Greensteed	O
in	O
Kent	O
,	O
selling	O
Earthen	O
Ware	O
:	O
But	O
there	O
appearing	O
some	O
Inconsistencies	O
in	O
their	O
Evidence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.10	O
d.	O
but	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Hutchins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Violin	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
see	O
him	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
and	O
take	O
it	O
from	O
off	O
a	O
Nail	O
where	O
it	O
hung	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
he	O
apprehended	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
Drinking	O
;	O
and	O
no	O
body	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joanna	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
Stuff	O
Manteau-Gown	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
depos	O
'd	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
two	O
others	O
came	O
into	O
her	O
Shop	O
under	O
pretence	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
trying	O
one	O
upon	O
the	O
Back	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Oppurtunity	O
to	O
put	O
another	O
Gown	O
under	O
her	O
Ridinghood	O
and	O
under	O
her	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
That	O
she	O
missing	O
the	O
Gown	O
,	O
called	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
several	O
Persons	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
so	O
good	O
a	O
Character	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
probable	O
that	O
this	O
might	O
be	O
the	O
first	O
Fact	O
:	O
So	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Still	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Cutterel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stoke-Newington	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
an	O
Assault	O
and	O
Murder	O
committed	O
on	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
Left	O
side	O
of	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
near	O
his	O
Left	O
Eye	O
,	O
the	O
5	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
Five	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Hedging-Bill	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languish	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
February	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
Second	O
time	O
indicted	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
Council	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
had	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Cause	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Howland	I-pers
,	O
Fellow-servant	O
with	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
being	O
Servants	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Carpenter	I-pers
upon	O
the	O
Day	O
and	O
time	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
be	O
heard	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
cry	O
out	O
for	O
Help	O
.	O
he	O
looking	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
ran	O
to	O
his	O
Assitance	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
near	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
House	O
struggling	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
gotten	O
him	O
fast	O
hold	O
by	O
the	O
Hand	O
and	O
the	O
Collar	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
had	O
then	O
receiv	O
'd	O
a	O
Wound	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
bloody	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
tho	O
'	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
sturdy	O
Villain	O
,	O
he	O
held	O
him	O
till	O
Thomas	B-pers
Meers	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Watchman	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
their	O
Assistance	O
,	O
having	O
heard	O
the	O
Outcries	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
in	O
vain	O
to	O
result	O
,	O
he	O
surrendred	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
in	O
part	O
confirmed	O
by	O
Thomas	B-pers
Meers	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Watchman	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Hedging-Bill	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
all	O
bloody	O
:	O
And	O
they	O
likewise	O
depos	O
'd	O
they	O
saw	O
a	O
Ladder	O
reared	O
up	O
against	O
Mr.	O
Carpenter	O
's	O
Garden-Wall	O
and	O
Candle	O
and	O
Matches	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
The	O
Affidavit	O
of	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
and	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
spying	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Garden	O
,	O
who	O
,	O
seeing	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
ran	O
to	O
get	O
over	O
the	O
Wall	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Garden	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
a	O
nearer	O
Way	O
and	O
met	O
him	O
just	O
coming	O
down	O
the	O
Ladder	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
of	O
the	O
Garden-Wall	O
in	O
an	O
adjoining	O
Field	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
following	O
him	O
to	O
seize	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
G	O
-	O
mn	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
touch	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
murder	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
said	O
Blow	O
on	O
his	O
Head	O
with	O
the	O
Bill	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Field	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
the	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
dress	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Wound	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
in	O
his	O
Instrument	O
,	O
found	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Roughness	O
upon	O
the	O
Skull	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
fear	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
fractur	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
calling	O
in	O
the	O
Assitance	O
of	O
Mr.Green	O
,	O
took	O
out	O
some	O
Pieces	O
of	O
the	O
Skull	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
Quantity	O
of	O
corrupted	O
Matter	O
come	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
verily	O
believe	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
Mr.Carpenter	O
gave	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
of	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
lamentaing	O
the	O
Loss	O
of	O
the	O
best	O
Servant	O
ever	O
had	O
,	O
or	O
feared	O
ever	O
should	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
deny	O
'd	O
he	O
ever	O
was	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Carpenter	O
's	O
Garden	O
;	O
but	O
said	O
the	O
Reason	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
out	O
so	O
soon	O
was	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Sister	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
sent	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
the	O
Wound	O
;	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Defence	O
.	O
And	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
Business	O
he	O
had	O
with	O
the	O
Hedging-Bill	O
,	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
defend	O
himself	O
from	O
Rogues	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
it	O
seems	O
he	O
need	O
not	O
have	O
been	O
under	O
much	O
Apprehension	O
of	O
meeting	O
any	O
greater	O
than	O
himself	O
,	O
either	O
in	O
Person	O
or	O
Impiety	O
.	O
For	O
besides	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Reputation	O
of	O
being	O
a	O
long	O
Practitioner	O
in	O
such	O
Deeds	O
of	O
Darkness	O
,	O
a	O
Record	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
of	O
his	O
having	O
been	O
Convicted	O
at	O
Hereford	O
Affizes	O
,	O
and	O
burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
for	O
robbing	O
the	O
Lady	O
Butterfield	O
;	O
and	O
several	O
Person	O
's	O
came	O
many	O
Miles	O
to	O
do	O
him	O
and	O
themselves	O
Justice	O
,	O
in	O
ridding	O
themselves	O
of	O
so	O
troublesome	O
and	O
dangerous	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
as	O
plain	O
as	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
barbarous	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Westminister	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Silk-Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.6	O
d	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
at	O
Church	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
told	O
by	O
a	O
Friend	O
of	O
his	O
(	O
Mr.	O
William	B-pers
Hender	I-pers
)	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
back	O
into	O
the	O
Church	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
suspected	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
carrying	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
Vestry	O
,	O
where	O
was	O
a	O
Justice	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
up	O
two	O
Handkerchiefs	O
dropt	O
at	O
her	O
Feet	O
at	O
the	O
Vestry	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
another	O
under	O
her	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Bible	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
given	O
to	O
her	O
by	O
a	O
Women	O
in	O
the	O
Church	O
,	O
whom	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
apprehended	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
found	O
more	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
not	O
positive	O
that	O
she	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Mark	B-pers
Burgess	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Silk-Handkerchief	O
,	O
val.1	O
s.6	O
d.	O
in	O
the	O
Place	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
manner	O
aforesaid	O
:	O
But	O
of	O
this	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
likewise	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hender	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Holland-Handkerchief	O
,	O
val.2	O
s.	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
,	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Manner	O
aforesaid	O
:	O
And	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
she	O
was	O
also	O
aquitted	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
fourth	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Appleby	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Bible	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
at	O
the	O
Place	O
and	O
Time	O
aforesaid	O
:	O
Of	O
which	O
Indictment	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Rossiter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminister	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
an	O
Assault	O
upon	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Jewel	I-pers
(	O
a	O
Boy	O
)	O
the	O
10	O
th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Blow	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
Side	O
of	O
his	O
Head	O
with	O
a	O
Stick	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
died	O
within	O
a	O
few	O
Hours	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
throwing	O
at	O
a	O
Cock	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
receiv	O
'd	O
the	O
said	O
Blow	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
designed	O
;	O
therefore	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Hillingdon	B-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
County	I-place
of	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Callico	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Nicols	I-pers
the	O
a	O
23d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Nicols	I-pers
deposed	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
hers	O
.	O
A	O
Carrier	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Warehouse	B-place
at	I-place
the	I-place
Bell	I-place
in	I-place
Warewick-lane	I-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
Mary	O
Ward	O
,	O
offering	O
them	O
to	O
Sale	O
at	O
Hillingdon	O
.	O
Mary	O
Ward	O
pleaded	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
offered	O
it	O
to	O
Sale	O
by	O
the	O
Order	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
her	O
Mistress	O
;	O
and	O
She	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
Employ	O
to	O
buy	O
and	O
sell	O
at	O
Markets	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	O
for	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
brought	O
a	O
Person	O
who	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
buying	O
of	O
them	O
depose	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Several	O
reputable	O
Persons	O
appear	O
'd	O
in	O
her	O
behalf	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
for	O
Industry	O
,	O
Honesty	O
and	O
Piety	O
;	O
whereupon	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
aquitted	O
.	O
Tench	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
with	O
George	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
of	O
the	O
same	O
Place	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
200	O
l.	O
Weight	O
of	O
Spanish	O
Wool	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Merry	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Tench	O
Young	O
,	O
accompany	O
'd	O
by	O
George	B-pers
Backer	I-pers
,	O
brought	O
29	O
l.	O
of	O
Spanish	O
Wool	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
Nicholas	O
de	O
Barce	O
,	O
the	O
Master	O
of	O
the	O
Ship	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Wool	O
was	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
a	B-place
Lighter	I-place
upon	I-place
the	I-place
River	I-place
of	I-place
Thames	I-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
Union-Stairs	I-place
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Wool	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
rowing	O
upon	O
the	O
River	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
bought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
Baker	O
.	O
Andrew	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
8	O
Copper	O
Nails	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Carpenter	I-pers
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
Nails	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Nails	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
were	O
his	O
.	O
One	O
Mr.	O
Ballamy	O
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
to	O
Mr	O
Barnet	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Barnet	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
Nails	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Nails	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
alledg	O
'd	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
deal	O
in	O
such	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Persons	O
appeared	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
for	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
industrious	O
Man	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Keys	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Frances	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Ticking	O
Pocket	O
,	O
value	O
6d.6	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
7s	O
.	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
17s	O
.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Murray	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
having	O
been	O
out	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
Minories	B-place
about	O
7a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
she	O
perceived	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
follow	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
at	O
some	O
distance	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
being	O
afraid	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
just	O
stopping	O
into	O
a	O
Shop	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
behind	O
her	O
,	O
tripped	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
off	O
her	O
Pocket	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
.	O
Another	O
,	O
a	O
Woman	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
immediately	O
turn	O
'd	O
back	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
running	O
cross	O
the	O
Way	O
.	O
Another	O
Person	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
going	O
along	O
in	O
the	O
Interim	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
cry	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
!	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
run	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
he	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
Guinea	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
he	O
would	O
satisfy	O
for	O
the	O
whole	O
that	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
provided	O
they	O
would	O
discharge	O
him	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
another	O
Evidence	O
who	O
was	O
present	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
alledge	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
passing	O
along	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
heard	O
a	O
Cry	O
of	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
!	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
assist	O
in	O
the	O
Apprehension	O
,	O
was	O
apprehended	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Mob	O
raised	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
But	O
this	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
.	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Callico	O
Pocket	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
,	O
Five	O
Guineas	O
,	O
a	O
Half	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
27s	O
.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
and	O
6d	O
.	O
in	O
Copper	O
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
and	O
her	O
Mother	O
were	O
passing	O
through	O
Well-Close	B-place
Square	I-place
about	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
his	O
Hand	O
under	O
her	O
Ridinghood	O
and	O
Coat	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
pursued	O
him	O
him	O
,	O
crying	O
out	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
!	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
turning	O
again	O
,	O
she	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
and	O
struggled	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
got	O
away	O
.	O
Her	O
Mother	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
afterwards	O
siezed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
throwing	O
her	O
down	O
,	O
got	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Howel	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
hearing	O
the	O
Outcry	O
,	O
pursued	O
him	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
throw	O
the	O
Pocket	O
over	O
the	O
Wall	O
in	O
the	O
Square	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
apprehended	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Pocket	O
was	O
there	O
taken	O
up	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
Mony	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
afraid	O
of	O
an	O
Arrest	O
ran	O
to	O
avoid	O
the	O
Officers	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
what	O
he	O
threw	O
away	O
was	O
a	O
Pipe	O
.	O
But	O
this	O
appearing	O
but	O
a	O
Pretence	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
a	O
notorious	O
Offender	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
positive	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Burgess	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosector	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
about	O
5	O
Days	O
before	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
him	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
asking	O
for	O
the	O
Tankard	O
to	O
draw	O
some	O
Drink	O
for	O
a	O
Company	O
,	O
having	O
filled	O
it	O
twice	O
he	O
being	O
to	O
have	O
filled	O
it	O
the	O
third	O
time	O
,	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
too	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
that	O
a	O
Woman	O
came	O
in	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
set	O
the	O
Tankard	O
upon	O
the	O
Bar	O
while	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
draw	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Several	O
Persons	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Patience	B-pers
Kite	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
7	O
Guineas	O
,	O
several	O
Pieces	O
of	O
foreign	O
Coin	O
,	O
val.9s	O
6d	O
.	O
a	O
Half	O
Spanish	O
Pistol	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
double	O
Stiver	O
,	O
val.2	O
d.from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Howpwell	I-pers
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
passing	O
along	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
fell	O
into	O
Conversation	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
enquiring	O
of	O
him	O
whither	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
Town	O
,	O
she	O
reply	O
'd	O
so	O
was	O
she	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
which	O
he	O
,	O
thinking	O
her	O
a	O
civil	O
Woman	O
,	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
fitting	O
over	O
against	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
raised	O
her	O
self	O
from	O
her	O
Seat	O
,	O
falling	O
upon	O
him	O
into	O
his	O
Arms	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
set	O
her	O
down	O
again	O
in	O
her	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
enquiring	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jolting	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
made	O
her	O
Sick	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
so	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
times	O
,	O
attempting	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
familiar	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
refused	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
fit	O
by	O
him	O
upon	O
the	O
same	O
Seat	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
consented	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
set	O
her	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
feeling	O
for	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
:	O
whereupon	O
he	O
followed	O
her	O
,	O
overtook	O
her	O
,	O
charged	O
the	O
Watch	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
her	O
Bosom	O
.	O
Being	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
none	O
but	O
them	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
he	O
owned	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
Woman	O
who	O
was	O
her	O
Acquaintance	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
charge	O
her	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
pick	O
'd	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
invited	O
her	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
refused	O
,	O
but	O
accepted	O
of	O
the	O
Conveniency	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
to	O
save	O
her	O
Legs	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
her	O
a	O
Guinea	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
home	O
to	O
her	O
Lodging	O
and	O
lie	O
with	O
her	O
all	O
Night	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
modestly	O
refused	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
given	O
her	O
by	O
her	O
Mother	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
of	O
London	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Fustian	O
Frock	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Taster	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Draper	I-pers
,	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Wine-Cooper	O
and	O
at	O
Work	O
at	O
the	O
Castle	B-place
Tavern	I-place
in	I-place
Fleetstreet	I-place
,	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
his	O
Frock	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
down	O
upon	O
a	O
Cask	O
of	O
Wine	O
;	O
and	O
going	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
at	O
his	O
Return	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
Mr.	O
White	O
a	O
Broker	O
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
brought	O
the	O
Frock	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
lent	O
them	O
6	O
s.	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
laying	O
it	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
something	O
in	O
the	O
Pocket	O
hit	O
against	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
feeling	O
in	O
the	O
Pocket	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Taster	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
pleaded	O
,	O
their	O
Father	O
was	O
a	O
Wine-Cooper	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
urgent	O
Necessity	O
for	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
forgot	O
in	O
the	O
Hurry	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
Pockets	O
;	O
he	O
thinking	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
true	O
,	O
gave	O
them	O
the	O
Taster	O
:	O
But	O
recollecting	O
himself	O
,	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
not	O
to	O
have	O
come	O
by	O
it	O
honestly	O
;	O
and	O
order	O
'd	O
his	O
Man	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
to	O
stop	O
them	O
;	O
which	O
(	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
coming	O
again	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
following	O
)	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
informed	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
proved	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
of	O
London	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Langford	I-pers
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Bockles	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
and	O
paid	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
gone	O
,	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
two	O
pair	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
sending	O
after	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
having	O
dropp	O
'd	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
pair	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
pair	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Abel	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Mary	B-pers
Pomfree	I-pers
two	O
Handkerchiefs	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
going	O
along	O
Aldersgate	B-place
street	I-place
with	O
her	O
Daughter	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
knock	O
'd	O
her	O
down	O
and	O
pulled	O
off	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Daughter	O
deposed	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
followed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Daniel	I-pers
5	O
Jacobus	O
's	O
each	O
25	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
five	O
Broad	O
Pieces	O
,	O
each	O
23	O
s.6	O
d.	O
seven	O
Guineas	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Daniel	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Lambert	I-pers
,	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
Bull-Head	B-place
Tavern	I-place
in	I-place
Fleet-street	I-place
,	O
and	O
bring	O
with	O
her	O
Money	O
to	O
lend	O
upon	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Plate	O
of	O
a	O
Friend	O
of	O
his	O
;	O
that	O
being	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Mony	O
being	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
he	O
catch	O
'd	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
fetch	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
went	O
his	O
Way	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
acknowledg	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Mony	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
Mony	O
she	O
lent	O
him	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
since	O
paid	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
he	O
would	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
able	O
.	O
It	O
did	O
not	O
by	O
the	O
Circumstances	O
appear	O
a	O
Robbery	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
too	O
easy	O
Credulity	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
New	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Bromly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Fulham	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Calimanco	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Gideon	B-pers
Devenoy	I-pers
,	O
from	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Clayton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
hanging	O
on	O
a	O
Line	O
to	O
dry	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
taken	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Back	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
off	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
off	O
the	O
Line	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Necessity	O
made	O
her	O
wear	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
tho	O
'	O
the	O
last	O
appeared	O
very	O
probable	O
,	O
yet	O
this	O
neither	O
being	O
a	O
sufficient	O
Excuse	O
,	O
nor	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
her	O
Necessity	O
had	O
led	O
her	O
to	O
these	O
Irregularities	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Haley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
three	O
Books	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Meers	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
said	O
Books	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
told	O
to	O
one	O
-	O
Taylor	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
likewise	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
Woman	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
not	O
producing	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michaels	I-place
Crooked-lane	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Mug	O
,	O
val.55	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Tailor	I-pers
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
set	O
in	O
the	O
Counting-house	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
wife	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
Neighbours	O
shop	O
cross	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Counting-House	O
,	O
and	O
supposing	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
bid	O
her	O
Servant	O
follow	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
who	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
within	O
a	O
few	O
doors	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Mug	O
standing	O
down	O
by	O
him	O
close	O
to	O
the	O
wall	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
full	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Sherman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
's	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
5	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
43	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Spoon	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
and	O
the	O
Family	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
standing	O
near	O
the	O
Door	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
funeral	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
likewise	O
,	O
latching	O
the	O
outward	O
Door	O
after	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
going	O
in	O
,	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Entry	O
with	O
a	O
candle	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
who	O
swearing	O
he	O
would	O
murther	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
flopp	O
'd	O
him	O
or	O
made	O
any	O
Noise	O
,	O
and	O
flinging	O
the	O
Candlestick	O
at	O
her	O
,	O
cut	O
her	O
Arm	O
with	O
it	O
and	O
ran	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
,	O
she	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
showing	O
him	O
to	O
her	O
Master	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
immediately	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
perceiving	O
,	O
threw	O
the	O
Spoons	O
up	O
,	O
designing	O
to	O
throw	O
them	O
over	O
a	O
wall	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
went	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
rest	O
falling	O
down	O
just	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
nothing	O
material	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Morton	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Pits	I-pers
of	O
St	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Murrey	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Yard	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Stanly	I-pers
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
seeing	O
three	O
Men	O
run	O
along	O
shifting	O
some	O
Linnen	O
one	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
he	O
suspected	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
hearing	O
that	O
a	O
Person	O
at	O
Hatton	O
had	O
lost	O
some	O
Linnen	O
,	O
he	O
follow	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
in	O
Moorfields	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Shirt	O
upon	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Howel	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
in	O
publishing	O
a	O
seditious	O
and	O
scandalous	O
Libel	O
,	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
The	O
Case	O
of	O
Schism	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
of	O
England	O
.	O
Wherein	O
are	O
contain	O
'd	O
Expressions	O
denying	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Title	O
to	O
the	O
Crown	O
of	O
this	O
Realm	O
,	O
and	O
asserting	O
the	O
Pretender	O
's	O
Right	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
highly	O
reflecting	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
Body	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
of	O
England	O
as	O
by	O
Law	O
Establish	O
'd	O
,	O
Bishop	O
's	O
,	O
inferior	O
Clergy	O
and	O
Larty	O
,	O
denying	O
the	O
Validity	O
of	O
their	O
Ordination	O
and	O
all	O
their	O
Offices	O
,	O
and	O
representing	O
them	O
all	O
Schismaticks	O
excommunicated	O
info	O
facto	O
,	O
and	O
saying	O
they	O
ought	O
to	O
be	O
all	O
treated	O
as	O
such	O
;	O
asserting	O
,	O
that	O
whosoever	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Parish-Church	O
,	O
and	O
performed	O
Holy	O
Duties	O
with	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
their	O
Prayers	O
,	O
Sacraments	O
,	O
and	O
Holy	O
Duties	O
were	O
all	O
Sin	O
;	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Things	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Nature	O
:	O
and	O
that	O
none	O
were	O
of	O
the	O
True	O
Church	O
of	O
England	O
but	O
the	O
Nonjurors	O
;	O
that	O
none	O
are	O
true	O
Minsters	O
but	O
they	O
that	O
have	O
their	O
Ordination	O
from	O
true	O
Bishops	O
,	O
and	O
none	O
were	O
true	O
Bishops	O
but	O
the	O
Pretenders	O
;	O
and	O
several	O
things	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Nature	O
.	O
The	O
instrument	O
of	O
his	O
Ordination	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Course	O
,	O
sign	O
'd	O
Georgin	O
Hictes	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
Denomination	O
of	O
Bishop	O
of	O
ford	O
.	O
The	O
Council	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Kettleby	O
,	O
who	O
indeed	O
did	O
not	O
at	O
all	O
go	O
about	O
to	O
justify	O
any	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
seditions	O
and	O
scandalous	O
Patlages	O
contained	O
in	O
the	O
Libel	O
;	O
but	O
only	O
argued	O
against	O
the	O
Libel	O
's	O
being	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
Publication	O
according	O
to	O
Law	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Roberts	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Bilssington	O
,	O
two	O
Messengers	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
having	O
receiv	O
'd	O
Orders	O
to	O
take	O
Mr.	O
Howel	O
into	O
Custody	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
and	O
seized	O
about	O
a	O
1000	O
of	O
those	O
seditious	O
Libels	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Manuscript	O
Copy	O
from	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
composed	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
tore	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Manuscript	O
Copy	O
in	O
pieces	O
before	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
secured	O
some	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Original	O
Manuscript	O
from	O
which	O
the	O
Libel	O
was	O
composed	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Nost	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
attend	O
the	O
Poets	O
,	O
and	O
Correct	O
the	O
said	O
Libel-while	O
it	O
was	O
printing	O
,	O
Which	O
was	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
notorious	O
Publication	O
according	O
to	O
Law	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Tomkins	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Judith	B-pers
Spoonly	I-pers
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
her	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
side	O
of	O
her	O
Belly	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Breadth	O
of	O
1	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
7	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
upon	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
Stabbing	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bean	I-pers
,	O
Colonel	O
Clayean	B-pers
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
having	O
been	O
abroad	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
his	O
Master	O
and	O
Lady	O
in	O
the	O
Entry	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
the	O
Butler	O
had	O
done	O
to	O
the	O
Cook	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
Condition	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Deceased	O
sitting	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
supported	O
by	O
others	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
no	O
Blood	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
Life	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
speak	O
;	O
but	O
removing	O
her	O
to	O
another	O
Place	O
,	O
they	O
saw	O
some	O
Blood	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
searched	O
by	O
a	O
Maid	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
she	O
was	O
wounded	O
in	O
the	O
Belly	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
immediately	O
in	O
quest	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
at	O
his	O
Brother	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
Short's-Gardens	O
:	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
the	O
Maid	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
he	O
(	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
the	O
more	O
easily	O
)	O
told	O
him	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
only	O
given	O
her	O
a	O
slight	O
Wound	O
in	O
the	O
Thigh	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
enquiring	O
the	O
Reason	O
of	O
his	O
doing	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
provoking	O
Language	O
:	O
When	O
they	O
came	O
near	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
People	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
said	O
the	O
Maid	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
upon	O
hearing	O
which	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
gotten	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
secured	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Coachman	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
dressing	O
his	O
Hourses	O
,	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
for	O
something	O
he	O
wanted	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
told	O
by	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Parrot	I-pers
,	O
that	O
the	O
Butler	O
and	O
Cook	O
were	O
quarrelling	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
concern	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
went	O
not	O
in	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Deceased	O
cry	O
out	O
Murther	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
running	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
patting	O
a	O
Sword	O
into	O
the	O
Scabbord	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Maid	O
holding	O
her	O
Hand	O
upon	O
her	O
Belly	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
spoke	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Parrot	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
swear	O
at	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
her	O
Business	O
for	O
her	O
:	O
That	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
on	O
a	O
Errand	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
in	O
the	O
Space	O
of	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
dead	O
.	O
The	O
surgeon	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
Wound	O
in	O
her	O
Belly	O
,	O
which	O
Wound	O
was	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
her	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
very	O
provoking	O
Language	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
throw	O
something	O
at	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
drew	O
the	O
Sword	O
designing	O
only	O
to	O
frighten	O
her	O
,	O
intending	O
only	O
to	O
run	O
it	O
between	O
her	O
Arm	O
and	O
Body	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
ran	O
upon	O
the	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
forced	O
it	O
into	O
her	O
Belly	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
all	O
three	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver-hilted	O
Sword	O
,	O
val	O
40	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cars	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Park	I-place
to	O
see	O
his	O
Majesty	O
come	O
from	O
the	O
Parliament-	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Sword	O
taken	O
from	O
his	O
Side	O
,	O
which	O
afterwards	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Sword	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
thrown	O
there	O
by	O
a	O
Boy	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Marshal	O
's	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
apprehended	O
by	O
the	O
Way	O
.	O
This	O
appearing	O
but	O
a	O
Pretence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Barns	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Covent-Garden	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Catland	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
3	O
Stuff-Gowns	O
,	O
val.20	O
s.5	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
val.10	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hobday	I-pers
,	O
the	O
22nd	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
stollen	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Young	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
get	O
some	O
Mony	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
pitch	O
'd	O
open	O
any	O
House	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
reply	O
'd	O
he	O
knew	O
of	O
a	O
House	O
(	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
Round-house	O
)	O
where	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
matter	O
of	O
70	O
l.	O
But	O
considering	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
very	O
strong	O
,	O
we	O
thought	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
difficult	O
to	O
break	O
it	O
;	O
so	O
we	O
contrive	O
'd	O
that	O
my	O
self	O
and	O
one	O
Ned	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
should	O
breed	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
be	O
carry	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
should	O
come	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
with	O
proper	O
Materials	O
.	O
Accordingly	O
we	O
did	O
quarrel	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
there	O
,	O
desired	O
to	O
have	O
Beds	O
,	O
paying	O
for	O
them	O
:	O
That	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
Barns	O
comes	O
with	O
a	O
Chissel	O
and	O
an	O
Iron	O
Crow	O
,	O
gets	O
upon	O
the	O
Shed	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
to	O
the	O
Window	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
the	O
Tools	O
broke	O
it	O
open	O
,	O
broke	O
open	O
a	O
Trunk	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
no	O
Mony	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
then	O
they	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
:	O
That	O
the	O
Shed	O
being	O
old	O
,	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
fell	O
into	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
getting	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
off	O
likewise	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Catland	I-pers
confirm	O
'd	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
Persons	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
(	O
as	O
had	O
been	O
said	O
)	O
that	O
Night	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
get	O
away	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
Person	O
jump	O
off	O
from	O
the	O
Shed	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
saying	O
the	O
Denial	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Giles	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
himself	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stole	O
the	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Thorold	I-pers
for	O
15	O
s.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
,	O
val.35	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Matth.ew	B-pers
Biner	I-pers
,	O
the	O
first	O
Day	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Wig	O
hung	O
upon	O
a	O
high	O
Block	O
in	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
hearing	O
a	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
but	O
saw	O
no	O
body	O
,	O
but	O
next	O
Morning	O
found	O
the	O
Glass	O
of	O
the	O
Sash	O
broke	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
against	O
the	O
Light	O
hole	O
of	O
the	O
Shutter	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Wig	O
gone	O
.	O
Abel	B-pers
Downs	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Brother	O
,	O
did	O
the	O
Fact	O
:	O
That	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
two	O
lifted	O
up	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
through	O
the	O
Shutter,25	O
before	O
mentioned	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
Deborah	B-pers
Stent	I-pers
.	O
He	O
said	O
likewise	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
dark	O
ty	O
'd	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
thinking	O
he	O
had	O
sunk	O
him	O
(	O
as	O
he	O
pharas	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
taken	O
more	O
than	O
that	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
know	O
of	O
it	O
)	O
he	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
that	O
Wig	O
he	O
wore	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
answer	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
spying	O
a	O
Gager	O
that	O
was	O
Lapps	O
,	O
going	O
along	O
in	O
a	O
Rattler	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
snabbled	O
his	O
Poll	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
got	O
that	O
Wig	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
also	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Riding-hood	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
Jan	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
tho	O
'	O
she	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
Evidence	O
being	O
clear	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Reddington	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Day-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Cloth	O
Breeches	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
val.10	O
s	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
Jan	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
That	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
he	O
lock	O
'd	O
his	O
Door	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
his	O
Return	O
found	O
it	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
stollen	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
having	O
a	O
Search	O
Warrant	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
a	O
Bag	O
in	O
Ann	O
Gregery	O
's	O
Cellar	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Gregary	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Hall	O
left	O
them	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
Proof	O
of	O
Ann	O
Knight	O
's	O
being	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
;	O
and	O
Elizabeth	O
Hall	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Frensham	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
,	I-place
Pauls	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Roycross	I-pers
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
to	O
sell	O
a	O
Ring	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
his	O
Companion	O
wanted	O
to	O
see	O
some	O
Buckles	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
show	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
one	O
Pair	O
;	O
and	O
taxing	O
them	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
and	O
laid	O
them	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Counter	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
that	O
his	O
Companion	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
but	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
paid	O
for	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
10	O
Wheaten	O
Loaves	O
,	O
val.8	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Basket	O
,	O
val.6	O
d	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Burham	I-pers
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
Jan	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
deposed	O
;	O
That	O
he	O
carrying	O
out	O
Bread	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Customers	O
had	O
set	O
his	O
Basket	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
delivering	O
a	O
Loaf	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
up	O
his	O
Basket	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
into	O
Covent-Garden-Market	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
set	O
down	O
the	O
Basket	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
Bread	O
;	O
he	O
sent	O
a	O
Woman	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Loaf	O
,	O
giving	O
her	O
Mony	O
to	O
pay	O
him	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
apprehended	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
enquiring	O
of	O
a	O
Baker	O
's	O
Man	O
for	O
Business	O
,	O
he	O
promised	O
to	O
help	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
look	O
after	O
his	O
Basket	O
while	O
he	O
carried	O
a	O
Loaf	O
to	O
a	O
Customer	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
jury	O
notwithstanding	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
William	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
6	O
Callico-Gowns	O
,	O
val.3	O
l.2	O
Stuff-Gown	O
,	O
val.20	O
s.	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Black	I-pers
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
was	O
12	O
Months	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
stollen	O
:	O
Abel	B-pers
Downs	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Plant	I-pers
went	O
together	O
;	O
that	O
Clark	O
with	O
a	O
Chissel	O
raised	O
a	O
Board	O
,	O
put	O
in	O
Will	O
.	O
Plant	O
,	O
who	O
handed	O
out	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
himself	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
sold	O
them	O
for	O
4	O
l.	O
to	O
Jane	B-pers
Revel	I-pers
,	O
Plant	O
and	O
he	O
concealed	O
40	O
s.	O
of	O
the	O
Mony	O
,	O
and	O
shared	O
the	O
other	O
40	O
s.	O
equally	O
between	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
themselves	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Matth.ew	B-pers
Adcock	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Batchelor	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
9	O
pair	O
of	O
Linnen	O
Sheets,24	O
Linnen	O
Shirts	O
and	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
Jan.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
her	O
House	O
was	O
broken	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Goods	O
stolen	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Britton	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Charles	B-pers
Lodge	I-pers
,	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
the	O
Pest-house	O
,	O
digged	O
down	O
the	O
Peer	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
carried	O
off	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
having	O
so	O
many	O
they	O
were	O
forced	O
to	O
leave	O
some	O
behind	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
one	O
Eliz	B-pers
Ran	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Burnel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
an	O
Iron	O
Grate	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Arnold	B-pers
Rookby	I-pers
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
Jan	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
Second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Wire	O
Grate	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
Jan	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Stapleton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Henry	B-pers
Banks	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
him	O
of	O
3	O
Half	O
Crowns	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Wife	O
Lying-in	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
going	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Provisions	O
,	O
and	O
invite	O
the	O
Gossips	O
to	O
the	O
Gossiping	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
opposed	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
two	O
Men	O
,	O
who	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
held	O
a	O
Sword	O
pointed	O
to	O
his	O
Breast	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
Woman	O
kneel	O
'd	O
down	O
and	O
rammag	O
'd	O
his	O
Pockets	O
:	O
That	O
when	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
he	O
pursued	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
made	O
some	O
Passes	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
followed	O
them	O
so	O
close	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
her	O
apprehended	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
pick	O
'd	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
her	O
into	O
a	O
Brandy-shop	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
artern	O
of	O
Cherry-Brandy	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
would	O
needs	O
go	O
into	O
a	O
private	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
gave	O
her	O
another	O
,	O
offering	O
her	O
a	O
Shilling	O
to	O
lie	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
9	O
d.	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
his	O
Mony	O
again	O
,	O
which	O
because	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
fell	O
a	O
swearing	O
she	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
.	O
She	O
brought	O
the	O
Mistriss	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Girl	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
So	O
her	O
Story	O
being	O
not	O
only	O
more	O
probable	O
,	O
but	O
better	O
attested	O
than	O
his	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Elton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Spurling	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
divers	O
Goods	O
,	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
Linnen	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
double	O
lock	O
'd	O
his	O
Door	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
broken	O
open	O
and	O
his	O
Goods	O
stollen	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Tricker	I-pers
,	O
his	O
Brother	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
coming	O
home	O
and	O
finding	O
his	O
Brother	O
's	O
Door	O
broke	O
open	O
and	O
his	O
Goods	O
gone	O
,	O
ran	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
enquiring	O
of	O
a	O
Coachman	O
,	O
was	O
told	O
that	O
two	O
Persons	O
went	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
loaded	O
with	O
Goods	O
;	O
he	O
pursued	O
and	O
overtook	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Monmouth	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
apprendael	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Britton	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
himself	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
went	O
in	O
he	O
loaded	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Patting	O
the	O
Goods	O
into	O
his	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
pick	O
up	O
what	O
he	O
dropp	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
picking	O
up	O
one	O
dropp	O
'd	O
two	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
parted	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
carried	O
his	O
Parcel	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
Britton	O
employ	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
Which	O
was	O
so	O
poor	O
an	O
Excuse	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Brush	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
was	O
identified	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Grimshaw	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
a	O
Brass	O
Porridge-pot	O
.	O
value	O
28	O
s.	O
pewter	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
glass	O
of	O
his	O
Window	O
was	O
broken	O
,	O
the	O
Casement	O
unhalped	O
,	O
the	O
Shutter	O
bored	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bar	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Goods	O
stollen	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Britton	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
one	O
Lodge	O
,	O
broke	O
the	O
House	O
in	O
the	O
Manner	O
before	O
described	O
,	O
slote	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
Jane	B-pers
Revel	I-pers
for	O
16	O
s.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Pardoe	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Mary	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
and	O
Stealing	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Hair-Shag-Pocket	O
value	O
1	O
s.2	O
Muslin	O
Turnovers	O
,	O
val.3	O
s.	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
val.1	O
s.	O
and	O
nine	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
along	O
Great	B-place
Queen-Street	I-place
,	O
a	O
man	O
pulled	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Pocket	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
it	O
turn	O
'd	O
her	O
round	O
in	O
pulling	O
off	O
,	O
she	O
cryd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
Stop	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Man	O
who	O
stopped	O
him	O
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
attempted	O
to	O
trip	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
apprehended	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Pocket	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
just	O
by	O
where	O
he	O
apprehended	O
him	O
.	O
All	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
hearing	O
some	O
cry	O
out	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
to	O
apprehended	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
apprehended	O
himself	O
.	O
But	O
this	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Hutchins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
's	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Shirt	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
Cap	O
val.9	O
d.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Braddle	I-pers
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
that	O
was	O
gone	O
from	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hargate	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dike	I-pers
,	O
(	O
all	O
boys	O
)	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Callico	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
17	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
,	O
too	O
young	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Evidence	O
.	O
But	O
Hargate	O
had	O
acknowledged	O
the	O
taking	O
them	O
off	O
from	O
a	O
Line	O
;	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hargate	I-pers
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Quilt	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
val.55	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Flip	I-pers
,	O
the	O
16	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
Second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
and	O
Linnen	O
to	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
5	O
l	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Scalrack	I-pers
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Williams	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
the	O
cellar	O
after	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
acquited	O
,	O
and	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Hall	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Sweetbones	I-pers
of	O
Acton	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Trafford	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
thence	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Cloath	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
val.4	O
s.	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
of	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
his	O
Daughter	O
saw	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Stockings	O
on	O
his	O
Legs	O
and	O
his	O
Shirt	O
on	O
his	O
Back	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
and	O
his	O
Assistant	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
they	O
apprehended	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
confest	O
the	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
and	O
promised	O
,	O
that	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
should	O
have	O
his	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
never	O
come	O
to	O
Acton	O
more	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
desperate	O
and	O
mischievously	O
bent	O
,	O
attempting	O
to	O
catch	O
up	O
a	O
Hedging-Bill	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
catched	O
up	O
a	O
Smoothing-Plain	O
,	O
and	O
knocking	O
out	O
the	O
Chisel	O
,	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
Split	O
the	O
Man	O
down	O
that	O
should	O
come	O
near	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
made	O
his	O
Escape	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
Second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
an	O
Assault	O
and	O
Murder	O
committed	O
on	O
the	O
body	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Mims	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Hammer	O
on	O
the	O
Left	O
side	O
of	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
24th	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
dyed	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Peacock	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
about	O
6	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
the	O
22nd	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
his	O
Son	O
having	O
been	O
out	O
,	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
Hollowing	O
in	O
the	O
Field	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
heard	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Hollowing	O
still	O
continued	O
;	O
he	O
thought	O
at	O
last	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
somebody	O
in	O
Distress	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
get	O
some	O
Neighbours	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
all	O
refusing	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Hollowing	O
still	O
continuing	O
he	O
was	O
confirmed	O
in	O
his	O
Opinion	O
,	O
and	O
observed	O
that	O
the	O
voice	O
grew	O
weaker	O
and	O
weaker	O
,	O
took	O
a	O
Candle	O
and	O
Lanthorn	O
and	O
Pitchfork	O
and	O
prevailed	O
with	O
one	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
so	O
having	O
Company	O
he	O
made	O
towards	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
Voice	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Mr.	O
Mims	O
standing	O
leaning	O
upon	O
the	O
Stile	O
,	O
all	O
over	O
of	O
a	O
gore	O
Blood	O
;	O
his	O
Pockets	O
were	O
turned	O
inside	O
out	O
,	O
his	O
Shirt	O
.	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
seemed	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
dragg	O
'd	O
along	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
supposed	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
who	O
left	O
him	O
in	O
that	O
Condition	O
,	O
thought	O
they	O
left	O
him	O
Dead	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
recovering	O
himself	O
,	O
had	O
gotten	O
in	O
the	O
Stile	O
.	O
By	O
that	O
time	O
they	O
got	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
Spent	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
lead	O
him	O
home	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
before	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
him	O
4	O
Yards	O
he	O
fainted	O
;	O
and	O
asking	O
him	O
who	O
had	O
made	O
him	O
in	O
that	O
Condition	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
only	O
Strength	O
to	O
say	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
no	O
more	O
;	O
they	O
with	O
much	O
Difficulty	O
got	O
him	O
home	O
,	O
being	O
then	O
Saturday-night	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
he	O
dyed	O
.	O
Thomas	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
5	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
Mile	O
and	O
half	O
from	O
that	O
place	O
,	O
going	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
Hat	O
on	O
when	O
he	O
met	O
him	O
;	O
which	O
Hat	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Custody	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Barnel	I-pers
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
that	O
Hat	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
Christmas	O
day	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Lewis	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Hat	O
was	O
flung	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Alloway	I-pers
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Alloway	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
going	O
down	O
into	O
her	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Sweetbones	O
said	O
the	O
Hat	O
was	O
his	O
and	O
he	O
flung	O
it	O
down	O
there	O
out	O
of	O
Roguery	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Prince	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
lodged	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
away	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
the	O
21st	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Acton	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
his	O
Mother	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
home	O
about	O
8	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
22d	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
away	O
on	O
Friday	O
the	O
21st	O
,	O
be	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
borrow	O
'd	O
6	O
d.	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
They	O
deposed	O
likewise	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
he	O
asked	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Prince	O
what	O
he	O
owned	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Guinea	O
to	O
change	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
received	O
between	O
16	O
and	O
17	O
s.	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Guinea	O
to	O
lay	O
by	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
his	O
Mother	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
that	O
Mony	O
,	O
i.e	O
.	O
two	O
Guineas	O
out	O
of	O
3	O
.	O
They	O
deposed	O
like	O
wife	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Sleeve	O
of	O
his	O
Frock	O
was	O
torn	O
almost	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Hands	O
all	O
Bloody	O
:	O
they	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
,	O
he	O
replyed	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
Fighting	O
with	O
a	O
Friend	O
that	O
he	O
loved	O
as	O
dearly	O
as	O
his	O
own	O
Brother	O
in	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
Hay	O
.	O
Market	O
.	O
They	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
happened	O
to	O
have	O
2	O
Hats	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
his	O
Friends	O
Hat	O
and	O
his	O
own	O
too	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
likewise	O
deposed	O
by	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Cheesebrook	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Beal	I-pers
,	O
Grandaughter	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
swore	O
positively	O
,	O
that	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
he	O
owned	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
Key	O
of	O
her	O
Grandfathers	O
that	O
he	O
usually	O
carryed	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
denyed	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Acton	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Mony	O
of	O
his	O
Mother	O
In	O
the	O
Hay-market	O
;	O
likewise	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Hat	O
was	O
the	O
Hat	O
of	O
his	O
Friend	O
(	O
who	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
his	O
Cousin	O
,	O
)	O
and	O
with	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
fighting	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Key	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
it	O
5	O
Years	O
.	O
Being	O
asked	O
,	O
why	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
produce	O
that	O
Friend	O
with	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
Fighting	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Scotland	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Parks	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
January	O
he	O
lifted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
as	O
a	O
Dragoon	O
;	O
that	O
hearing	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
like	O
to	O
be	O
charg	O
'd	O
with	O
this	O
Murther	O
,	O
advised	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Reigment	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
answered	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
nothing	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
fear	O
.	O
After	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
these	O
Matters	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
Third	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
Robbing	O
John	B-pers
Mims	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Key	O
,	O
val.1	O
s.	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ogaleshaw	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Hattor	O
,	O
who	O
sold	O
the	O
Deceased	O
the	O
Hat	O
,	O
deposed	O
;	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
with	O
this	O
Hat	O
upon	O
his	O
Head	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
murdered	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
a	O
mile	O
and	O
half	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Farnel	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
that	O
Hat	O
the	O
Monday	O
before	O
Christmas	O
day	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Lewis	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Lewis	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Allaway	I-pers
brought	O
this	O
Hat	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Cellar	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Alloway	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Hat	O
which	O
John	B-pers
Sweetbones	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
throwd	O
down	O
her	O
Cellar	O
,	O
she	O
fold	O
to	O
Christopher	B-pers
Farmel	I-pers
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Beal	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Gandaughter	O
,	O
swore	O
positively	O
that	O
the	O
Key	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
was	O
her	O
Grandfathers	O
John	O
Mins	O
's	O
Key	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Peacock	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
try	O
'd	O
that	O
Key	O
and	O
it	O
did	O
open	O
and	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Box	O
,	O
where	O
his	O
Writings	O
and	O
such	O
things	O
Lay	O
.	O
His	O
Mother	O
being	O
in	O
Court	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
any	O
Mony	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
said	O
his	O
Sister	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
it	O
him	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
prove	O
any	O
one	O
thing	O
he	O
had	O
said	O
,	O
nor	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
but	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
said	O
upon	O
the	O
last	O
Indictment	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
This	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Nathanael	B-pers
Saltonstal	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
thence	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.3	O
Silver	O
Salts	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.8	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
8	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
very	O
full	O
and	O
positive	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Richard	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hare	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
Sept	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
coming	O
over	O
Hounslow-Heath	B-place
,	O
with	O
a	O
Hare	O
ty	O
'd	O
at	O
his	O
Girdle	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
say	O
,	O
Damn	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
the	O
Hare	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
coming	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
demanded	O
his	O
Mony	O
and	O
his	O
Hare	O
;	O
his	O
Horse	O
being	O
mettleson	O
would	O
not	O
stand	O
still	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
threaten	O
'd	O
to	O
shoot	O
him	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Head	O
:	O
He	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
favourable	O
,	O
since	O
they	O
saw	O
his	O
Horse	O
would	O
not	O
stand	O
;	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
catch	O
'd	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Hare	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
String	O
broke	O
and	O
the	O
Hare	O
came	O
off	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
rode	O
away	O
,	O
being	O
better	O
mounted	O
than	O
they	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Leather	O
Bottle	O
,	O
halted	O
,	O
supposing	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
Danger	O
;	O
and	O
seeing	O
a	O
Coach	O
coming	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
they	O
made	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
rode	O
within	O
a	O
small	O
distance	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
they	O
would	O
do	O
,	O
and	O
perceived	O
some	O
body	O
hand	O
a	O
Watch	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Young	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
did	O
go	O
out	O
a	O
Robbing	O
,	O
hiring	O
Horses	O
for	O
that	O
Purpose	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
upon	O
Hounslow-Heath	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
feeing	O
a	O
Coach	O
a	O
coming	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
riding	O
before	O
,	O
imagin	O
'd	O
he	O
might	O
belong	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
therefore	O
upon	O
Consultation	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
their	O
best	O
way	O
to	O
secure	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
rode	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
Young	O
swearing	O
at	O
him	O
bid	O
him	O
deliver	O
his	O
Money	O
and	O
the	O
Hare	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
it	O
for	O
his	O
supper	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
swore	O
if	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
did	O
not	O
presently	O
deliver	O
he	O
would	O
shoot	O
him	O
through	O
the	O
Brains	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
catch	O
'd	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Hare	O
,	O
designing	O
by	O
that	O
means	O
to	O
unhorse	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
mount	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
better	O
than	O
his	O
own	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
String	O
that	O
ty	O
'd	O
the	O
Hare	O
's	O
Feet	O
together	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
rode	O
away	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
they	O
attacked	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
took	O
2	O
Watches	O
from	O
2	O
Gentlemen,2	O
Rings	O
from	O
2	O
Gentlewomen,27	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
10	O
l	O
in	O
Money	O
besides	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
knowing	O
or	O
ever	O
having	O
seen	O
the	O
Evidence	O
and	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
called	O
persons	O
to	O
disprove	O
the	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Capt	O
.	O
Lashly	O
deposed	O
that	O
Thomas	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
formerly	O
a	O
Master	O
of	O
the	O
Frier-Gally	O
,	O
which	O
by	O
reason	O
of	O
Running	O
Goods	O
was	O
seized	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
serviceable	O
in	O
discovering	O
where	O
these	O
Goods	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
afterwards	O
made	O
an	O
extraordinary	O
Tide-waiter	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
behaving	O
himself	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
sick	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
he	O
went	O
abroad	O
he	O
used	O
daily	O
to	O
attend	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
thought	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
every	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
consequently	O
that	O
Day	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
:	O
he	O
called	O
other	O
Evidence	O
to	O
corroberate	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
particular	O
enough	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Jones	O
,	O
likewise	O
called	O
two	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
one	O
(	O
whose	O
Name	O
was	O
Stanly	O
)	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
Williams	O
was	O
apprehended	O
upon	O
Young	O
's	O
Information	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
near	O
Hicknes	O
's	O
Hall	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
Young	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
and	O
they	O
three	O
there	O
,	O
being	O
asked	O
which	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
he	O
informed	O
against	O
,	O
he	O
fixed	O
upon	O
Stanly	O
,	O
calling	O
him	O
Jones	O
,	O
and	O
swearing	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
him	O
.	O
But	O
not	O
only	O
Young	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
swearing	O
positively	O
to	O
both	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
them	O
in	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Dodson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
an	O
Assault	O
on	O
Katherine	B-pers
Gravener	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Pocket	O
,	O
a	O
Handkerchief,18	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
own	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
wherein	O
he	O
owned	O
it	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
made	O
himself	O
and	O
Evidence	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Phips	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pauls	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
an	O
Assault	O
on	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cherwood	I-pers
,	O
and	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Would	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
on	O
his	O
left	O
Side	O
of	O
his	O
Body	O
,	O
near	O
his	O
left	O
Arm-pit	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
1	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
5	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
,	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Riddock	I-pers
a	O
Link-Boy	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
lighting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
through	O
Covent-Garden	B-place
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
quarrelling	O
with	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
beating	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
asked	O
the	O
Deceased	O
why	O
he	O
abused	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
where	O
upon	O
the	O
Deceased	O
gave	O
him	O
abusive	O
Language	O
,	O
demanding	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
who	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
Officer	O
.	O
And	O
several	O
other	O
Witness	O
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
still	O
persisted	O
in	O
giving	O
affronting	O
Language	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
Officer	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
Sixpence	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
see	O
him	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
saucy	O
Fellow	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
thought	O
he	O
might	O
take	O
the	O
liberty	O
to	O
abuse	O
People	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
told	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
again	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
Officer	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
Sixpeace	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
see	O
him	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Plough	O
and	O
Horrow	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
Lane	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
informed	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
but	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
his	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
his	O
;	O
or	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
there	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
go	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
followed	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Rails	O
,	O
and	O
pushed	O
him	O
through	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
undrawn	O
,	O
bidding	O
him	O
.	O
If	O
he	O
were	O
an	O
Officer	O
,	O
draw	O
,	O
and	O
shew	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
handle	O
his	O
Sword	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Deaceased	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
struck	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
his	O
Hand	O
before	O
he	O
drew	O
;	O
that	O
than	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
retreated	O
back	O
and	O
did	O
draw	O
,	O
having	O
no	O
other	O
Way	O
to	O
decide	O
himself	O
from	O
being	O
cut	O
to	O
Pieces	O
.	O
Several	O
Evidences	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
cut	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
laying	O
on	O
with	O
great	O
Violence	O
and	O
Fury	O
,	O
as	O
thou	O
'	O
he	O
were	O
knocking	O
down	O
an	O
Ox	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
warding	O
off	O
the	O
Blow	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
.	O
now	O
and	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
Deceased	O
and	O
the	O
Duplicate	O
was	O
very	O
sharp	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
receiving	O
several	O
Cuts	O
,	O
till	O
at	O
length	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Wound	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
fell	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
then	O
the	O
Deased	O
stood	O
full	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
walked	O
softly	O
away	O
;	O
Persons	O
wing	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
back	O
,	O
being	O
told	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
,	O
enting	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
so	O
unfortunate	O
,	O
de	O
their	O
to	O
find	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
surrendred	O
himself	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
some	O
few	O
Evidences	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
an	O
Account	O
something	O
different	O
as	O
to	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
in	O
Favour	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
;	O
but	O
a	O
far	O
greater	O
Number	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
of	O
good	O
Reputation	O
agreed	O
,	O
that	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
so	O
defended	O
himself	O
;	O
he	O
must	O
in	O
all	O
Probability	O
have	O
undergone	O
the	O
same	O
Fate	O
from	O
the	O
Fury	O
of	O
his	O
Adversary	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
therefore	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	I-pers
and	I-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
his	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
in	O
publishing	O
a	O
false	O
Will	O
to	O
receive	O
the	O
Wages	O
due	O
to	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Ship	O
Chathan	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
proved	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
sign	O
'd	O
it	O
as	O
an	O
Evidence	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Underwood	I-pers
,	O
two	O
Guineas	O
and	O
11	O
s	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
passing	O
along	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
a	O
Woman	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Ale	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
telling	O
her	O
he	O
would	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
over	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
she	O
presumed	O
upon	O
the	O
new	O
contracted	O
Acquaiutance	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
hold	O
by	O
the	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
led	O
him	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
where	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
Place	O
where	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
Life	O
.	O
That	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
they	O
drank	O
;	O
but	O
however	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
(	O
whether	O
by	O
his	O
own	O
Inclinations	O
or	O
their	O
Persuasions	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
but	O
)	O
undrest	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Bed	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
his	O
Female	O
Attendants	O
put	O
the	O
Candle	O
out	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
suffer	O
;	O
but	O
telling	O
them	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
lye	O
in	O
Bed	O
it	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
light	O
the	O
Candle	O
,	O
they	O
obliged	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
light	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
and	O
by	O
put	O
it	O
out	O
again	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
done	O
several	O
times	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Chamber-Maids	O
came	O
and	O
lay	O
down	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
Being	O
asked	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
or	O
sober	O
,	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
enough	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
that	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
;	O
her	O
enough	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
:	O
for	O
he	O
laid	O
his	O
Breeches	O
under	O
his	O
Boster	O
to	O
secure	O
his	O
Mony	O
;	O
but	O
however	O
they	O
found	O
means	O
to	O
get	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
put	O
them	O
there	O
again	O
.	O
He	O
felt	O
for	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
missing	O
it	O
,	O
would	O
have	O
risen	O
and	O
gone	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
was	O
told	O
,	O
it	O
he	O
took	O
any	O
Notice	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
be	O
gone	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
moved	O
off	O
the	O
Premises	O
by	O
Morning	O
:	O
She	O
lay	O
all	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
and	O
got	O
an	O
Officer	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
broken	O
up	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
almost	O
(	O
out	O
not	O
quite	O
)	O
got	O
all	O
off	O
;	O
but	O
lighting	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
saluted	O
her	O
with	O
a	O
Mrs.	O
Mary	O
!	O
have	O
I	O
caught	O
you	O
?	O
and	O
so	O
secured	O
her	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
being	O
secured	O
,	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
easy	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
send	O
for	O
a	O
Friend	O
and	O
make	O
him	O
Satisfaction	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
a	O
Brandy	O
Man	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
him	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
indeed	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
must	O
needs	O
have	O
Variety	O
of	O
fresh	O
Bits	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
3	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
would	O
needs	O
,	O
have	O
the	O
Mistress	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
for	O
a	O
Bedfellow	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
abed	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
and	O
lay	O
in	O
another	O
Place	O
.	O
That	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
apprehended	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
consent	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
Satisfaction	O
rather	O
than	O
come	O
into	O
Trouble	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
receiv	O
'd	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
rest	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Week	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
Weekly	O
Payments	O
a	O
Default	O
being	O
trade	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
this	O
Indictment	O
against	O
her	O
.	O
But	O
as	O
the	O
Indictment	O
was	O
laid	O
for	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
Person	O
,	O
when	O
by	O
his	O
own	O
Account	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
when	O
his	O
Money	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
were	O
not	O
on	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
aquited	O
her	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Guineas	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Hosliver	I-pers
,	O
and	O
3	O
Pieces	O
of	O
foreign	O
Silver	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Newberry	I-pers
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutors	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
from	O
the	O
Antwerp-Tavern	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
;	O
they	O
answered	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
matter	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
is	O
was	O
late	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
telling	O
them	O
it	O
was	O
soon	O
enough	O
,	O
took	O
each	O
of	O
than	O
a	O
her	O
Mate	O
,	O
conducting	O
them	O
Arm	O
in	O
Arm	O
into	O
the	O
Cross-keys	B-place
in	I-place
Grace-church-street	I-place
;	O
but	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
there	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
them	O
,	O
being	O
ugly	O
and	O
impedent	O
,	O
yet	O
would	O
give	O
them	O
a	O
Shilling	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
since	O
they	O
wanted	O
it	O
so	O
much	O
;	O
and	O
feeling	O
for	O
Mony	O
,	O
found	O
they	O
had	O
rifled	O
their	O
Pockets	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
calling	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Foreign	O
Pieces	O
found	O
upon	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Guineas	O
upon	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
confirmed	O
the	O
finding	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Jacob	B-pers
Forden	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Musket-Ball	O
on	O
the	O
Right	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Breast	O
near	O
the	O
Collar-Bone	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Breadth	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
twelve	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
,	O
the	O
10th	O
Day	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Chad	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
within	O
Doors	O
near	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
Warwick-lane	B-place
,	O
heard	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
a	O
Gun	O
go	O
off	O
;	O
that	O
running	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
staggering	O
and	O
fall	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Town	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
as	O
Constable	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
Watchmen	O
,	O
were	O
coming	O
from	O
Ludgate	O
Watch-house	O
up	O
Warwick-lane	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
some	O
Soldiers	O
marching	O
along	O
without	O
any	O
Drum	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
being	O
co	O
near	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
an	O
Outcry	O
of	O
Down	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
down	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
heard	O
the	O
Piece	O
go	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
Street	O
bleeding	O
,	O
being	O
supported	O
by	O
others	O
.	O
The	O
Watchmen	O
with	O
him	O
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
.	O
Colonel	O
Oughton	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
saw	O
when	O
this	O
Accident	O
happen	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
laid	O
Orders	O
to	O
attend	O
the	O
Council	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
