TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
'S	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
During	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
the	O
Rt	O
.	O
Honble	O
Sir	O
John	O
Ward	O
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
5th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
1719	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
PHILLIPS	O
,	O
by	O
M.	O
Jenour	O
,	O
against	O
St.	O
Sepulchre	O
's	O
Back	O
Gate	O
,	O
in	O
Gilt	O
Spur	O
Street	O
,	O
near	O
Newgate	O
.	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
,	O
ON	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
5th,6th	O
,	O
and	O
8th	O
,	O
of	O
December,1718	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Fifth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
12	O
.	O
Decemb.1718	O
.	O
BEfore	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
WARD	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Sir	O
Peter	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
of	O
the	O
Common-Pleas	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Montague	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Ayres	O
;	O
The	O
Worshipful	O
John	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
Names	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Lowe	I-pers
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Pettifor	I-pers
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Burridge	I-pers
.	O
James	B-pers
Hilliard	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
West	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Lawes	I-pers
.	O
Tho	B-pers
Tacks	I-pers
.	O
Geo	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
.	O
James	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
.	O
Sam	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
Benj	B-pers
Betts	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Tho	B-pers
Cliff	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Hargrave	I-pers
.	O
Abr	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Pashley	I-pers
.	O
Robt	B-pers
Chadd	I-pers
.	O
Alex	B-pers
Kilgore	I-pers
.	O
Edw	B-pers
Percival	I-pers
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
.	O
Tho	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
.	O
Tho	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Kinch	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Anne	B-pers
Buncher	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
her	O
Female	O
Bastard	O
Infant	O
,	O
by	O
throwing	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
,	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Taylor	O
her	O
Mistress	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
complain	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
Gripes	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
but	O
did	O
help	O
her	O
make	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
afterwards	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
Church	O
leaving	O
her	O
to	O
dress	O
Dinner	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
from	O
Church	O
she	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
was	O
so	O
ill	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
take	O
up	O
Dinner	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
thereupon	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
lye	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Dinner	O
up	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
the	O
Boy	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
with	O
some	O
hot	O
Ale	O
,	O
but	O
all	O
this	O
while	O
suspected	O
nothing	O
of	O
her	O
being	O
deliver	O
'd	O
of	O
a	O
Child	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Boy	O
brought	O
her	O
word	O
down	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
something	O
better	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
after	O
Dinner	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
down	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
Mop	O
,	O
saying	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
very	O
ill	O
and	O
had	O
vomited	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
the	O
Mop	O
to	O
wipe	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
that	O
at	O
Night	O
the	O
Boy	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Vault	O
brought	O
her	O
word	O
he	O
saw	O
something	O
uncommon	O
in	O
the	O
Vault	O
,	O
whereupon	O
she	O
sent	O
away	O
for	O
a	O
Midwife	O
to	O
examine	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Night	O
Man	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
Child	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Vault	O
:	O
This	O
was	O
also	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pool	I-pers
the	O
Apprentice	O
;	O
the	O
Midwife	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
sent	O
for	O
examin	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
deliver	O
'd	O
of	O
a	O
Child	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
tho	O
'	O
she	O
at	O
first	O
deny	O
'd	O
,	O
yet	O
soon	O
after	O
own	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Vault	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
she	O
did	O
believe	O
was	O
at	O
its	O
full	O
time	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
there	O
any	O
marks	O
of	O
Violence	O
or	O
Hurt	O
appear	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
asking	O
her	O
who	O
was	O
the	O
Father	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
it	O
was	O
got	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
she	O
going	O
up	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Lodgers	O
Bed	O
in	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
liv	O
'd	O
before	O
,	O
he	O
laid	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
and	O
did	O
there	O
get	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
since	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
People	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
her	O
Master	O
and	O
Mistress	O
were	O
remov	O
'd	O
above	O
100	O
Miles	O
off	O
.	O
She	O
owned	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Vault	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
alive	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
Apron	O
to	O
have	O
carryed	O
down	O
when	O
the	O
Boy	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Drink	O
,	O
but	O
put	O
it	O
away	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
then	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
till	O
she	O
had	O
another	O
opportunity	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
pleaded	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
fall	O
about	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
felt	O
the	O
Child	O
stir	O
within	O
her	O
since	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
still	O
born	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Portor	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Gabriel	I-place
's	I-place
Fenchurch-street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
China	O
Perfume-Pot	O
set	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Jacob	B-pers
Alvarez	I-pers
the	O
15th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Landlord	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Perfume-pot	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
off	O
an	O
Escrutore	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
broken	O
to	O
pieces	O
was	O
offered	O
to	O
sale	O
to	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
,	O
who	O
stopped	O
it	O
,	O
gave	O
notice	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
pleaded	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
to	O
fetch	O
Coals	O
,	O
the	O
Silver	O
catch	O
'd	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
looking	O
found	O
it	O
half	O
covered	O
with	O
Earth	O
,	O
and	O
thinking	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
thing	O
buried	O
there	O
that	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
no	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
she	O
thought	O
she	O
had	O
as	O
much	O
right	O
to	O
it	O
as	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
:	O
But	O
this	O
plea	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mildred	I-place
Poultry	I-place
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
2	O
l.	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
36	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Wagstaff	I-pers
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Shop	O
to	O
buy	O
an	O
Ounce	O
of	O
Silk	O
of	O
several	O
colours	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
body	O
but	O
a	O
Boy	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Customers	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
opportunity	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Silk	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
miss	O
'd	O
and	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Boy	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
his	O
Master	O
notice	O
of	O
at	O
his	O
coming	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
Sarah	O
Smith	O
being	O
search	O
'd	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
Mary	O
Mitchel	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Sarah	O
Smith	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
of	O
10.	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Easton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews-Undershaft	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
33	O
Guineas	O
and	O
other	O
Money	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
35	O
l.15	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Morley	I-pers
the	O
19th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
:	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Morley	O
at	O
the	O
King's-Arms	B-place
Inn	I-place
in	I-place
Leadenhall-street	I-place
,	O
but	O
being	O
gone	O
away	O
,	O
came	O
with	O
some	O
other	O
of	O
his	O
Accomplices	O
and	O
privately	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
broke	O
open	O
a	O
Door	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
the	O
Money	O
lay	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
a	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
a	O
Silk	O
Purse	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
out	O
gave	O
the	O
Purse	O
to	O
his	O
Comrades	O
,	O
who	O
afterwards	O
appointed	O
him	O
to	O
meet	O
them	O
at	O
a	O
certain	O
Place	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
have	O
his	O
dividend	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
told	O
him	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
so	O
much	O
in	O
the	O
Purse	O
as	O
he	O
imagin	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
8	O
l.	O
for	O
his	O
share	O
:	O
This	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
after	O
his	O
apprehension	O
,	O
but	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
all	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
however	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hawker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Holms	I-pers
,	O
no	O
body	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
,	O
value	O
24	O
s.	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hawley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Thomas	I-place
Apostles	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Carolus	O
broad	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
the	O
22d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
:	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Landlord	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
opportunity	O
of	O
getting	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Room	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
She	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
fact	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
but	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
at	O
her	O
Tryal	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
however	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Linne	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mildreds	I-place
Poultry	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
together	O
with	O
Obadiah	B-pers
Leman	I-pers
not	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
feloniously	O
steal	O
a	O
Perriwing	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Gilbert	B-pers
Malcher	I-pers
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
;	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
near	O
Stocks-Market	B-place
,	O
the	O
Coach	O
was	O
cut	O
and	O
his	O
Wigg	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Obadiah	B-pers
Leman	I-pers
,	O
Leman	O
got	O
up	O
behind	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
cutting	O
the	O
Coach	O
took	O
the	O
Wigg	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
appointed	O
before	O
if	O
they	O
lost	O
one	O
another	O
to	O
meet	O
at	O
the	O
3	O
Tuns	O
on	O
London	O
Bridge	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
did	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
the	O
Wigg	O
,	O
giving	O
them	O
a	O
Guinea	O
a	O
piece	O
for	O
their	O
share	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Wigg	O
they	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Marriot	I-pers
and	O
Eliz	B-pers
Day	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Magnes	I-place
the	I-place
Martyr	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Linnen	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
small	O
value	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
:	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
with	O
some	O
others	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
to	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
getting	O
into	O
a	O
Chamber	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Day	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Proof	O
not	O
being	O
strong	O
enough	O
against	O
;	O
Marriot	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Humphry	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Penknife	O
in	O
the	O
left	O
Buttock	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languish	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
November	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
Surgeon	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
sent	O
by	O
Justice	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
to	O
Humphry	O
Wild	O
,	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
6	O
Inches	O
deep	O
and	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
cut	O
several	O
Arteries	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
his	O
being	O
examined	O
had	O
confess	O
'd	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
the	O
Boy	O
having	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
fat-ars'd-Dick	O
,	O
and	O
given	O
him	O
very	O
provoking	O
language	O
he	O
did	O
borrow	O
a	O
Penknife	O
of	O
another	O
Boy	O
and	O
running	O
after	O
him	O
did	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
Wound	O
with	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Place	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
this	O
confession	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
in	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
pleaded	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
linking	O
near	O
the	O
Play-House	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	B-place
he	O
saw	O
the	O
deceased	O
pick	O
a	O
Gentlemans	O
Pocket	O
that	O
thereupon	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
charging	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
what	O
was	O
that	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
him	O
several	O
names	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
a	O
Penknife	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
stick	O
him	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
borrow	O
'd	O
a	O
Penknife	O
of	O
another	O
Boy	O
and	O
following	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
fell	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
but	O
falling	O
upon	O
him	O
might	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Wound	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
receiv	O
'd	O
also	O
a	O
Wound	O
in	O
his	O
Wrist	O
from	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Surgeon	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
before	O
complain	O
'd	O
of	O
any	O
Wound	O
,	O
answer	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
.	O
Upon	O
hearing	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
James	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
suit	O
of	O
Cloth	O
Clothes	O
lacd	O
with	O
Gold	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
The	O
Property	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Charles	B-pers
Dilks	I-pers
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
about	O
9	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
the	O
Cloths	O
were	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Chariot	O
in	O
the	B-place
Mews	I-place
,	O
and	O
while	O
the	O
Coachman	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
Wigg	O
were	O
stollen	O
away	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
immediately	O
acquainting	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
,	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
quest	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
Sale	O
about	O
Drury-Lane	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
out	O
a	O
Person	O
who	O
for	O
the	O
Reward	O
of	O
a	O
Guinea	O
undertook	O
to	O
conduct	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Person-that	O
had	O
them	O
,	O
accordingly	O
taking	O
Coach	O
they	O
went	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
staying	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
sent	O
the	O
Woman	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
to	O
bid	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
had	O
them	O
,	O
bring	O
the	O
Clothes	O
to	O
a	O
Person	O
who	O
would	O
give	O
more	O
Money	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
accordingly	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
secur	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Clothes	O
both	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
pleaded	O
that	O
he	O
going	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
to	O
a	O
Person	O
who	O
ow	O
'd	O
him	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
being	O
then	O
in	O
Labour	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
talking	O
with	O
the	O
Woman	O
about	O
the	O
Money	O
a	O
Woman	O
call	O
'd	O
Porter	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
him	O
told	O
him	O
she	O
would	O
,	O
give	O
him	O
6	O
d.	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
bundle	O
(	O
which	O
she	O
said	O
was	O
quilted	O
Petticoats	O
)	O
to	O
the	O
Bell	O
in	O
Vine-Street	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
willing	O
to	O
earn	O
the	O
Money	O
did	O
so	O
.	O
He	O
produc	O
'd	O
the	O
Woman	O
he	O
was	O
talking	O
with	O
in	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
two	O
Persons	O
who	O
swore	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
all	O
that	O
day	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
at	O
Labouring	O
work	O
in	O
Leveling	O
some	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Persons	O
appearing	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
together	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bewl	I-pers
not	O
taken	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstans	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Darby	I-pers
,	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
Linnen	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
s.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
stollen	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
taken	O
upon	O
suspicion	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
that	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
fastned	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hewson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstans	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
wearing	O
apparel	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
as	O
a	O
servant	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
following	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Gown	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Daughter	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
back	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
apprehended	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
she	O
bought	O
the	O
Gown	O
of	O
a	O
Woman	O
that	O
sold	O
old	O
Clothes	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
proving	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolphs	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Dram	O
Cup	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
a	O
Cawdle	O
Cup	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Painter	I-pers
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
stollen	O
the	O
Plate	O
off	O
from	O
the	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
apprehended	O
'	O
acknowledg	O
'd	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
for	O
45	O
s.	O
The	O
Plate	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
no	O
other	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
seeming	O
to	O
suspect	O
her	O
crime	O
was	O
not	O
enough	O
to	O
hang	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
fram	O
'd	O
she	O
broke	O
2	O
locks	O
to	O
come	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
as	O
positively	O
deny	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
.	O
However	O
the	O
Jury	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
fit	O
to	O
gratify	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
only	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gibbon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
22	O
l.	O
of	O
Beef	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Line	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Beef	O
from	O
his	O
stall	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
seeing	O
him	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
and	O
apprehended	O
him	O
immediately	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
first	O
thrown	O
it	O
down	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
Drunk	O
and	O
might	O
brush	O
it	O
off	O
the	O
stall	O
,	O
but	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
taking	O
it	O
:	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
swearing	O
positively	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
with	O
both	O
his	O
Hands	O
off	O
the	O
stall	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Brewin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
;	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
52	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Leather	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
quart	O
of	O
Brandy	O
value	O
2	O
s.6	O
d.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
14	O
Guineas	O
and	O
37	O
s.6	O
d.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
upon	O
his	O
going	O
away	O
the	O
Box	O
which	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
a	O
Society	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
broken	O
open	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
the	O
only	O
Person	O
besides	O
the	O
Man	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
that	O
knew	O
where	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Closet	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
hearing	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
offer	O
'd	O
some	O
Leather	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
which	O
by	O
some	O
circumstances	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
,	O
they	O
suspected	O
him	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
proof	O
not	O
being	O
strong	O
enough	O
to	O
fix	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
3	O
Hats	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
Walter	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
shop	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
Hats	O
,	O
and	O
privately	O
convey	O
'd	O
3	O
Hats	O
under	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
search	O
'd	O
the	O
Hats	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
pleaded	O
he	O
was	O
much	O
in	O
drink	O
and	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
alledg	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
receiv	O
'd	O
a	O
Wound	O
in	O
his	O
Head	O
which	O
had	O
hurt	O
his	O
brain	O
so	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
drank	O
a	O
little	O
he	O
was	O
disorder	O
'd	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
his	O
reason	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Persons	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sometimes	O
fits	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
his	O
reason	O
and	O
was	O
sober	O
when	O
he	O
did	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolphs	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
2	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Wall	I-pers
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Boy	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Shop	O
to	O
sell	O
a	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
and	O
would	O
afterwards	O
buy	O
another	O
;	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
put	O
2	O
Bath-Metal	O
Rings	O
in	O
the	O
place	O
of	O
the	O
2	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
carried	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
he	O
took	O
her	O
afterwards	O
selling	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Rings	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Marlow	O
's	O
Shop	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
acknowledged	O
she	O
had	O
2	O
Bath-Metal	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
leave	O
them	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
Gold	O
ones	O
by	O
mistake	O
.	O
Several	O
appeared	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
for	O
Honesty	O
and	O
Industry	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
they	O
believ	O
'd	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
first	O
Fact	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
might	O
probably	O
have	O
been	O
drawn	O
away	O
of	O
late	O
by	O
a	O
Person	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
but	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cane	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolph	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Hugh	B-pers
Monday	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
High-way	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
and	O
an	O
Apron	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
through	O
Hounsditch	B-place
about	O
six	O
o	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
Other	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
upon	O
an	O
Out-cry	O
of	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
running	O
away	O
without	O
his	O
Hat	O
;	O
but	O
a	O
material	O
Evidence	O
that	O
saw	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
by	O
some	O
means	O
gotten	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
strong	O
enough	O
to	O
fix	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Goulston	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
Chain	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
value	O
30	O
l.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Ann	B-pers
Earnly	I-pers
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Earnly	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
having	O
been	O
at	O
Sohoe-Church	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
her	O
Chariot	O
,	O
a	O
tall	O
Gentleman	O
seeming	O
to	O
be	O
well	O
drest	O
in	O
Black	O
,	O
was	O
very	O
officious	O
in	O
assisting-her	O
to	O
get	O
into	O
her	O
Chariot	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
taking	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
some	O
Neighbour	O
that	O
knew	O
her	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
suspect	O
him	O
:	O
but	O
he	O
lifting	O
up	O
to	O
both	O
her	O
Arms	O
higher	O
than	O
was	O
necessary	O
,	O
she	O
cast	O
her	O
Eye	O
down	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
her	O
Watch	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Grand-daughter	O
with	O
her	O
immediately	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
believed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
describing	O
her	O
)	O
had	O
it	O
:	O
she	O
thereupon	O
sent	O
her	O
Foot-man	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Foot-man	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
having	O
taken	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
carried	O
her	O
into	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
sat	O
down	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
got	O
up	O
(	O
they	O
being	O
about	O
to	O
carry	O
her	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
)	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Watch	O
lying	O
behind	O
the	O
Chair	O
where	O
she	O
sat	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Man	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Coachman	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
afterwards	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Footman	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
such	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
Black	O
as	O
has	O
been	O
before	O
described	O
,	O
who	O
with	O
another	O
was	O
resolutely	O
pressing	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
the	O
Woman	O
was	O
,	O
swearing	O
and	O
cursing	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
what	O
did	O
they	O
take	O
up	O
that	O
Woman	O
for	O
?	O
She	O
was	O
an	O
honest	O
Woman	O
:	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
Scuffle	O
in	O
preventing	O
his	O
coming	O
in	O
he	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
force	O
their	O
way	O
in	O
,	O
they	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Poulter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hesson	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
killing	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
tame	O
Buck	B-pers
Antelope	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
tame	O
Due	O
Antelope	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
tame	O
;	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Child	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
killing	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
tame	O
Doe	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
tame	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Child	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Facts	O
were	O
both	O
plainly	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
at	O
Osterly-House	B-place
,	O
and	O
Sworn	O
to	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Accomplices	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
catch	O
'd	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
with	O
Toyls	O
,	O
and	O
hunted	O
the	O
other	O
with	O
a	O
Dog	O
:	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
,	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
knew	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
tame	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Amy	B-pers
Barns	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstans	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
d.	O
and	O
also	O
5	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Ale	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Joshua	B-pers
Ironmonger	I-pers
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Raymond	I-pers
;	O
but	O
appearing	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Misunderstanding	O
between	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Portmanteau	O
Trunk	O
of	O
rich	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
Watch	O
,	O
Money	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
80	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Dionysius	B-pers
Hicky	I-pers
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
the	O
Trunk	O
was	O
Suddenly	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
from	O
him	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Church-Yard	I-place
about	O
ten	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
opened	O
one	O
Door	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
was	O
attempting	O
to	O
shut	O
it	O
he	O
opened	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Portmanteau-Trunk	O
and	O
went	O
and	O
shared	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
the	O
Trunk	O
over	O
the	O
Wall	O
into	O
Lincolns-Inn-Walks	O
;	O
Some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
However	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wardon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Flemming	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
Linnen	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
out	O
her	O
Window	O
was	O
opened	O
and	O
her	O
Goods	O
carried	O
away	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
Circumstances	O
that	O
gave	O
strong	O
Suspicion	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
sufficient	O
Proof	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bowes	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Hugh	B-pers
Ryly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pauls	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
not	O
having	O
God	O
before	O
their-Eyes	O
,	O
did	O
the	O
former	O
commit	O
that	O
horrible	O
and	O
detestable	O
Sin	O
called	O
Buggery	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
against	O
nature	O
carnally	O
know	O
Hugh	O
Ryly	O
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
latter	O
suffer	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
be	O
committed	O
on	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
was	O
Gerard	B-pers
Fitzgerald	I-pers
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
having	O
been	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Burridge	I-pers
,	O
and	O
going	O
late	O
home	O
between	O
1	O
and	O
2	O
O	O
'	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
being	O
in	O
Covent	B-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
William	O
Burridge	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
do	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
sport	O
going	O
on	O
,	O
shewing	O
him	O
as	O
they	O
thought	O
(	O
being	O
at	O
a	O
distance	O
)	O
a	O
Man	O
kissing	O
a	O
Woman	O
against	O
the	O
Church	O
Rails	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
let	O
's	O
go	O
see	O
what	O
for	O
a	O
Madam	O
he	O
has	O
got	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
answer	O
'd	O
no	O
,	O
since	O
we	O
make	O
no	O
sport	O
dont	O
let	O
's	O
spoil	O
any	O
,	O
they	O
staid	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
till	O
they	O
thought	O
they	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
then	O
making	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
found	O
the	O
two	O
Persons	O
Mr.	O
Riley	O
undermost	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Bowes	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Bowes	O
Breeches	O
being	O
down	O
about	O
his	O
Heeles	O
,	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Riley	O
being	O
nimbler	O
had	O
made	O
a	O
shift	O
to	O
shuffle	O
his	O
Breeches	O
up	O
by	O
that	O
time	O
they	O
got	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
Rallying	O
them	O
for	O
so	O
vile	O
a	O
practice	O
Mr.	O
Bowes	O
reply	O
'd	O
Sirrah	O
what	O
's	O
that	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
cant	O
I	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
Body	O
?	O
I	O
have	O
done	O
nothing	O
but	O
what	O
I	O
will	O
do	O
again	O
,	O
that	O
Riley	O
hearing	O
him	O
call	O
Fitzgerald	O
,	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
Irish	O
,	O
thinking	O
him	O
an	O
Irishman	O
by	O
his	O
name	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
understand	O
him	O
,	O
not	O
being	O
so	O
.	O
That	O
Riley	O
persuading	O
them	O
not	O
to	O
expose	O
them	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
a	O
Note	O
of	O
10	O
l.	O
to	O
forbear	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
Bowes	O
should	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
Twenty	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
unexperienc	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
thinking	O
of	O
delivering	O
them	O
up	O
at	O
the	O
Round-House	O
,	O
did	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
Womans	O
House	O
near	O
Charing-Cross	O
,	O
whom	O
Mr.	O
Bowes	O
knew	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
asking	O
the	O
Woman	O
if	O
she	O
knew	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
reply	O
'd	O
yes	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
for	O
these	O
Twenty	O
Years	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
requir	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
trust	O
him	O
half	O
a	O
Crowns	O
worth	O
of	O
Drink	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Person	O
drink	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
refusing	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
two	O
Pots	O
were	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
neither	O
of	O
them	O
having	O
money	O
they	O
were	O
forc	O
'd	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
themselves	O
,	O
that	O
from	O
thence	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Vickers	O
a	O
Constable	O
at	O
the	O
Angel	O
and	O
Crown	O
in	O
Hedge-Lane	O
,	O
where	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
offers	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Person	O
Burridge	O
,	O
inclining	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
hearken	O
to	O
their	O
Proposals	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
dubious	O
in	O
his	O
mind	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
being	O
an	O
offer	O
of	O
10	O
l.	O
Riley	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
Pen	O
Ink	O
and	O
Paper	O
,	O
and	O
began	O
to	O
draw	O
a	O
Note	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hours	O
time	O
they	O
were	O
carried	O
away	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Bowes	O
to	O
the	O
Gate-House	O
,	O
he	O
telling	O
the	O
Constable	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Housekeeper	O
,	O
and	O
Ryley	O
to	O
the	O
Round-House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
who	O
not	O
caring	O
to	O
Act	O
in	O
the	O
Case	O
without	O
assistance	O
of	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Brother	O
Justices	O
order	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
kept	O
till	O
the	O
Morrow	O
,	O
when	O
several	O
Justices	O
meeting	O
at	O
a	O
Vestry	O
they	O
were	O
committed	O
;	O
that	O
William	O
Burridge	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
Hicks	O
's	O
Hall	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
find	O
the	O
Bill	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
since	O
had	O
not	O
appear	O
'd	O
he	O
supposing	O
him	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
brib	O
'd	O
to	O
absent	O
himself	O
.	O
A	O
Surgeon	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
sent	O
by	O
the	O
Justice	O
to	O
examine	O
Mr.	O
Ryleys	O
Posteriers	O
,	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Spincter	O
Muscle	O
more	O
Lax	O
and	O
Dilated	O
than	O
usual	O
in	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
his	O
Age	O
,	O
which	O
in	O
Young	O
Persons	O
is	O
generally	O
more	O
close	O
and	O
contracted	O
,	O
but	O
how	O
it	O
might	O
come	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
determine	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bowes	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
deny	O
'd	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
Covert-Garden	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
of	O
his	O
having	O
newly	O
set	O
up	O
a	O
Tavern	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
thither	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Pint	O
or	O
two	O
of	O
Wine	O
with	O
a	O
Friend	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
there	O
till	O
almost	O
2	O
o	O
Clock	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Drawer	O
,	O
who	O
added	O
he	O
saw	O
no	O
immodesty	O
acted	O
by	O
them	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Ryley	O
,	O
were	O
coming	O
home	O
going	O
toward	O
Charing-Cross	O
,	O
two	O
Men	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
and	O
charged	O
them	O
with	O
being	O
Sodomites	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
them	O
abandance	O
of	O
names	O
,	O
and	O
follow	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Jacksons	O
Cellar	O
at	O
Charing-Cross	O
,	O
that	O
indeed	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
about	O
him	O
having	O
spent	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
formerly	O
a	O
Woollen-Draper	O
in	O
Pall-Mall	O
but	O
had	O
left	O
it	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
Salisbury	O
Street	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
a	O
Kinswoman	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
heard	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
demand	O
3	O
Guineas	O
in	O
Money	O
and	O
a	O
Note	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
15	O
l.	O
But	O
call	O
'd	O
none	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
Fitzgarald	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
but	O
Burridge	O
did	O
say	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
offer	O
10	O
l.	O
let	O
us	O
insist	O
upon	O
15	O
l.	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
directly	O
agree	O
,	O
being	O
suspicious	O
of	O
the	O
Justice	O
and	O
safety	O
of	O
doing	O
it	O
.	O
Hugh	O
Ryley	O
pleaded	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
to	O
his	O
Lodging	O
about	O
11	O
o	O
Clock	O
and	O
met	O
Mr.	O
Bowes	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Tavern	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
who	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
Mr.	O
Nugent	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
not	O
Nugent	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Bowes	O
,	O
made	O
answer	O
that	O
let	O
his	O
name	O
be	O
what	O
it	O
would	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
Quart	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
go	O
in	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
staid	O
there	O
till	O
1	O
or	O
2	O
o	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
Burridge	O
came	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
Buggerers	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
responsible	O
Men	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
Money	O
of	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
Collaring	O
of	O
us	O
carried	O
us	O
away	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
an	O
Evidence	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
Constables	O
House	O
at	O
the	O
Angle	O
and	O
Crown	O
in	O
Hedge-Lane	O
,	O
be	O
hearkened	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
them	O
talking	O
of	O
a	O
Note	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
Fitzgarald	O
telling	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
spell	O
'd	O
his	O
name	O
right	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
talk	O
of	O
drawing	O
the	O
Note	O
favourable	O
.	O
He	O
call	O
'd	O
some	O
Persons	O
that	O
had	O
lain	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
they	O
never	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
attempt	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
was	O
immodest	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
Servant	O
to	O
Collonel	O
Paget	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
good	O
character	O
and	O
fair	O
and	O
honest	O
in	O
his	O
dealings	O
.	O
He	O
added	O
that	O
as	O
to	O
what	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
had	O
said	O
be	O
had	O
been	O
under	O
an	O
indisposition	O
and	O
taken	O
Physick	O
,	O
which	O
might	O
cause	O
that	O
Laxness	O
in	O
his	O
Body	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
had	O
spoken	O
of	O
;	O
and	O
added	O
that	O
he	O
himself	O
desir	O
'd	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
might	O
search	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
the	O
Justice	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
Upon	O
hearing	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Reed	I-pers
and	O
Isaac	B-pers
Reed	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Hesson	B-place
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlex	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Shirts	O
value	O
6	O
l.10	O
s.3	O
Shirts	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Holland	O
Smocks	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
Printed	O
Callicoe	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
employ	O
'd	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Waddal	O
's	O
Book-keeper	O
to	O
find	O
out	O
the	O
Persons	O
who	O
committed	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
enquiry	O
had	O
his	O
suspicion	O
confirm	O
'd	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
inform	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
full	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
getting	O
intelligence	O
that	O
Francis	B-pers
Reed	I-pers
was	O
about	O
Hounslow	O
,	O
having	O
procured	O
a	O
Warrant	O
,	O
went	O
thither	O
with	O
some	O
other	O
Persons	O
in	O
quest	O
of	O
him	O
and	O
Isaac	O
Reed	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
riding	O
along	O
Pickadilly	O
saw	O
Isaac	O
Reed	O
,	O
and	O
telling	O
him	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
him	O
about	O
a	O
certain	O
Affair	O
,	O
Isaac	O
Reed	O
reply	O
'd	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
Brother	O
Francis	O
that	O
he	O
wanted	O
,	O
that	O
upon	O
this	O
he	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
discourse	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
of	O
his	O
Brothers	O
having	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
that	O
by	O
description	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Parcels	O
of	O
Goods	O
lost	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Hounslow	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
found	O
that	O
Francis	O
Reed	O
lodg	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Tuns	O
in	O
Hounslow	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
then	O
at	O
the	O
Royal-Oak	O
,	O
making	O
up	O
a	O
quarrel	O
with	O
some	O
Bayliffs	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
difference	O
between	O
him	O
and	O
a	O
Mistress	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
abused	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
having	O
arrested	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
he	O
founds	O
the	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
a	O
Pocket-Book	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
as	O
Inventory	O
of	O
several	O
sorts	O
of	O
Gold	O
pieces	O
of	O
Coyn	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
value	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Count	O
,	O
and	O
sworn	O
to	O
be	O
written	O
by	O
Madam	O
Hewet	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
sent	O
these	O
Goods	O
down	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Nottingham	O
.	O
Several	O
Persons	O
deposed	O
they	O
pack	O
'd	O
up	O
and	O
deliver	O
'd	O
these	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
other	O
rich	O
Apparel	O
belonging	O
to	O
two	O
different	O
Persons	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Blackmore	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Hewet	O
amounting	O
to	O
the	O
sum	O
of	O
200	O
l.	O
or	O
upwards	O
in	O
a	O
Portmanteau	O
,	O
and	O
Box	O
at	O
the	O
George	O
Inn	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
down	O
to	O
Nottingham	O
.	O
The	O
Carrier	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
carried	O
the	O
2	O
Portmanteau	O
Trunks	O
down	O
in	O
his	O
Waggon	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Waggon	O
was	O
set	O
up	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
August	O
at	O
Night	O
at	O
an	O
Inn	O
in	O
Brougham,40	O
Miles	O
from	O
London	O
and	O
2	O
from	O
Newport	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Waggon	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
that	O
the	O
Portmanteau	O
Trunk	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
some	O
Field	O
thereabouts	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
Francis	O
Reed	O
having	O
abused	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Mistresses	O
she	O
swore	O
the	O
Peace	O
against	O
him	O
for	O
an	O
Assault	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
arrested	O
gave	O
her	O
2	O
Guineas	O
to	O
make	O
up	O
the	O
Difference	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
robbing	O
the	O
Waggon	O
at	O
Broughton	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Neal	O
the	O
Mistress	O
of	O
the	O
Inn	O
at	O
Hounslow	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
lodg	O
'd	O
there	O
about	O
2	O
Months	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
had	O
the	O
Shirts	O
which	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
given	O
out	O
by	O
Francis	O
Reed	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
wash	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
Shirts	O
were	O
sworn	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Blackmore	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Shirts	O
the	O
Callicoe	O
that	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Homes	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
sworn	O
to	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Faith	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
who	O
pack	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
up	O
to	O
send	O
away	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
Mrs.	O
Hewest	O
.	O
Francis	O
Reed	O
in	O
Court	O
own	O
'd	O
these	O
Goods	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
pleaded	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
produc	O
'd	O
2	O
Evidences	O
,	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Burnham	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
on	O
Monday	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
August	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Sister	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
Ware	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
way	O
saw	O
Francis	O
Reed	O
on	O
Horseback	O
leading	O
another	O
spare	O
Horse	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Road	O
a	O
Woman	O
with	O
a	O
gilded	O
Trunk	O
and	O
a	O
Boy	O
with	O
a	O
Box	O
,	O
which	O
gave	O
Reed	O
2	O
s.	O
to	O
let	O
them	O
ride	O
to	O
Ware	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
all	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Bull	O
Inn	O
at	O
Ware	O
,	O
the	O
Woman	O
said	O
her	O
Husband	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
Linnen	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
Francis	O
Reed	O
fine	O
Shirts	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
for	O
6	O
l.10	O
s.	O
but	O
would	O
not	O
swear	O
the	O
Shirts	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
in	O
Court	O
were	O
the	O
very	O
same	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
Francis	O
Reed	O
sold	O
a	O
Horse	O
for	O
15	O
l.	O
the	O
young	O
Woman	O
she	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
likewise	O
pretended	O
to	O
prove	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
London	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
2	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
the	O
one	O
was	O
Sarah	B-pers
Lander	I-pers
,	O
keeping	O
a	O
Chandlers	O
Shop	O
in	O
Grub-stret	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
and	O
lodg	O
'd	O
there	O
the	O
18th,19th	O
and	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
how	O
she	O
could	O
be	O
so	O
particular	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
she	O
reply	O
'd	O
because	O
that	O
her	O
Landlady	O
had	O
borrow	O
'd	O
Money	O
of	O
Francis	O
Reed	O
that	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
set	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
the	O
Day	O
,	O
Sum	O
and	O
Time	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
being	O
desir	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
to	O
shew	O
them	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
set	O
down	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
could	O
not	O
write	O
,	O
but	O
having	O
Chalk	O
given	O
her	O
and	O
order	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
Marks	O
,	O
she	O
made	O
a	O
C	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
all	O
the	O
Characters	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
August	O
the	O
19th	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Lender	O
and	O
Borrower	O
;	O
to	O
confirm	O
this	O
,	O
an	O
Old	O
Woman	O
whom	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
Landlady	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
,	O
who	O
positively	O
affirm	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
the	O
order	O
of	O
the	O
Months	O
following	O
one	O
another	O
,	O
told	O
the	O
Court	O
the	O
Month	O
before	O
August	O
was	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Month	O
after	O
August	O
was	O
July	O
.	O
But	O
to	O
confront	O
these	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
August	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
the	O
Waggon	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
Francis	O
Reed	O
and	O
another	O
Person	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Ale	O
at	O
her	O
Father	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
Broughton	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
served	O
them	O
,	O
Harris	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
talking	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
positive	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
and	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
Francis	O
Reed	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
not	O
swear	O
in	O
positively	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
all	O
his	O
Evidences	O
appearing	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
to	O
be	O
of	O
but	O
slender	O
Credit	O
and	O
in	O
some	O
material	O
circumstances	O
contradictory	O
to	O
themselves	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
the	O
Evidences	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
many	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
better	O
reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
Francis	O
Reed	O
guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
not	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Isaac	O
Reed	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Broadstreet	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
34	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Gold	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
50	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Teresa	B-pers
Mannel	I-pers
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
James	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
was	O
left	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
the	O
Closet	O
in	O
the	O
Dressing-Room	O
,	O
and	O
Trunk	O
was	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
gon	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements-Danes	I-place
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Norcott	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
upon	O
3	O
indictments	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Sacks	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Rhodes	I-pers
,	O
and	O
4	O
Deal	O
Boards	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
latter	O
for	O
receiving	O
them	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
indicted	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
stealing	O
9	O
bushels	O
of	O
Coals	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Price	I-pers
and	O
the	O
latter	O
for	O
receiving	O
them	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
3	O
d	O
time	O
indicted	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Coals	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
Bigg	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
latter	O
for	O
receiving	O
them	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
:	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
the	O
Coals	O
were	O
stolen	O
at	O
different	O
times	O
,	O
from	O
a	O
Wharf	O
,	O
by	O
one	O
Price	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
sold	O
to	O
John	O
Norcott	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
prov	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
them	O
to	O
stolen	O
,	O
but	O
tho	O
'	O
one	O
Evidence	O
who	O
carried	O
the	O
Coals	O
swore	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
tell	O
them	O
whence	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
and	O
knew	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
2	O
other	O
Evidences	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
the	O
Coals	O
were	O
the	O
sweepings	O
of	O
a	O
Lighhter	O
which	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Man	O
gave	O
him	O
for	O
working	O
the	O
Coals	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
give	O
him	O
Money	O
to	O
drink	O
:	O
He	O
also	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Persons	O
to	O
his	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
but	O
Thomas	B-pers
Price	I-pers
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Indictments	O
:	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Wardrobe	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
60	O
yards	O
of	O
Mantua-Silk	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Risden	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Mumford	I-pers
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Wickes	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Shop	O
saying	O
she	O
came	O
from	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Bateman	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-Yard	O
,	O
desiring	O
them	O
to	O
send	O
some	O
Black	O
Mantua-Silk	O
thither	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
their	O
Servants	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
confirmed	O
by	O
two	O
other	O
Persons	O
who	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
and	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
positively	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
Woman	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
farther	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
carried	O
the	O
Piece	O
of	O
Mantua-Silk	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
into	O
Mr.Bateman	O
's	O
and	O
having	O
spoke	O
with	O
somebody	O
there	O
,	O
came	O
out	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
the	O
Gentlewoman	O
was	O
gone	O
a	O
little	O
farther	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
must	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
Wardrobe-Court	B-place
,	O
and	O
coming	O
there	O
she	O
told	O
her	O
the	O
Gentlewoman	O
was	O
above	O
Stairs	O
,	O
bid	O
her	O
give	O
her	O
the	O
Silk	O
to	O
shew	O
her	O
(	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
)	O
and	O
step	O
back	O
and	O
fetch	O
two	O
Yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
white	O
Sarsenet	O
,	O
which	O
when	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Risden	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
informed	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
make	O
enquiry	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
(	O
supposing	O
she	O
might	O
take	O
Water	O
)	O
was	O
informed	O
by	O
a	O
Waterman	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
ply	O
'd	O
such	O
a	O
Person	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
gone	O
over	O
the	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
gave	O
him	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
her	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
apprehended	O
.	O
The	O
Waterman	O
was	O
positive	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
Woman	O
that	O
he	O
ply	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
October	O
about	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
denied	O
that	O
she	O
ever	O
was	O
in	O
,	O
or	O
knew	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Evidences	O
that	O
had	O
swore	O
against	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Lodging	O
all	O
the	O
Day	O
that	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
committed	O
;	O
and	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Evidences	O
.	O
Her	O
Landlord	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
10	O
a	O
Clock	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
left	O
her	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
came	O
home	O
again	O
about	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
there	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
again	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
and	O
staid	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
,	O
and	O
returning	O
again	O
found	O
her	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
Her	O
Landlady	O
deposed	O
that	O
her	O
Mother	O
had	O
come	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
and	O
an	O
Unkle	O
,	O
who	O
being	O
an	O
Apothecary	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
not	O
being	O
well	O
,	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
must	O
take	O
some	O
Physick	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
accordingly	O
sent	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
all	O
Day	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
Her	O
Maid	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
from	O
her	O
own	O
House	O
from	O
the	O
4th	O
to	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Wigginton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
,	I-place
the	I-place
Field	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
,	O
first	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
7	O
s	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
d	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Elliot	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
And	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
for	O
sealing	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
James	B-pers
Elliot	I-pers
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
placed	O
one	O
Katherine	B-pers
Todd	I-pers
to	O
keep	O
a	O
Dary-Cellar	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
found	O
himself	O
continually	O
to	O
sink	O
in	O
his	O
Substance	O
,	O
but	O
knew	O
not	O
how	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
inform	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
certain	O
Person	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
having	O
sent	O
the	O
said	O
Kathrine	O
Todd	O
out	O
to	O
fetch	O
sometimes	O
Drink	O
and	O
sometimes	O
Meat	O
,	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Till	O
where	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
out	O
Money	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
Person	O
swore	O
in	O
Court	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
out	O
Money	O
twice	O
in	O
the	O
manner	O
before-said	O
,	O
and	O
asking	O
him	O
why	O
he	O
did	O
so	O
;	O
he	O
dam	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
What	O
was	O
that	O
to	O
him	O
?	O
threatning	O
him	O
:	O
he	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
several	O
times	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Night-Cellars	O
,	O
and	O
seen	O
him	O
pocket	O
Knives	O
and	O
Forks	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
another	O
time	O
having	O
sent	O
Katherine	O
Todd	O
out	O
for	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
open	O
the	O
Drawer	O
and	O
take	O
out	O
three	O
half	O
Crowns	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
told	O
Katherine	O
Todd	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
ruined	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
would	O
frequently	O
come	O
and	O
take	O
her	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
knew	O
not	O
how	O
she	O
should	O
make	O
up	O
her	O
Month	O
's	O
Account	O
with	O
her	O
Master	O
.	O
Katherine	O
Todd	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
several	O
times	O
attempted	O
to	O
lie	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
beat	O
her	O
and	O
knok	O
'd	O
her	O
down	O
because	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
consent	O
;	O
and	O
sent	O
one	O
to	O
tell	O
her	O
when	O
she	O
threatened	O
to	O
trouble	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
kill	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
all	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
insisted	O
that	O
both	O
she	O
and	O
her	O
Master	O
were	O
Persons	O
of	O
ill	O
Fame	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Whore	O
to	O
her	O
Master	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
was	O
malicious	O
,	O
in	O
that	O
her	O
Master	O
was	O
jealous	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
set	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
on	O
foot	O
because	O
he	O
had	O
arrested	O
her	O
for	O
Money	O
she	O
owed	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
some	O
Evidences	O
to	O
prove	O
these	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
several	O
Persons	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
:	O
so	O
it	O
appearing	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
a	O
litigious	O
Cause	O
,	O
they	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Hackney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coat	O
and	O
Wastcoat	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hannople	I-pers
the	O
29th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
Fellow	O
Servant	O
s	O
with	O
Samuel	B-pers
Woodfield	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Riding-Hood	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
Bencraft	I-pers
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Dorset	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Lanthorn	O
and	O
a	O
Riding-Hood	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Merideth	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
fact	O
not	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lord	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Lordwell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Grace	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Paxford	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
200	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Malt	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Sweetapple	I-pers
and	O
Partner	O
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
Miller	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
at	O
divers	O
times	O
carried	O
out	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Malt	O
,	O
(	O
as	O
he	O
said	O
)	O
encouraged	O
thereto	O
by	O
one	O
Haydon	O
in	O
Grays-Inn-Lane	O
,	O
who	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
confest	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
yet	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
well	O
tutor	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
College	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
denyed	O
it	O
as	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
by	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Order	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
believing	O
his	O
Master	O
had	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
steal	O
his	O
Malt	O
and	O
sell	O
it	O
for	O
an	O
under	O
Rate	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Pocket	O
;	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Skidder	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Perjury	O
,	O
but	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
Evidence	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Duhammel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Picture	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Lord	I-pers
Lansdown	I-pers
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
:	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Picture	O
being	O
the	O
Effigies	O
of	O
the	O
Lady	O
Lansdown	O
,	O
was	O
deliver	O
'd	O
to	O
a	O
Limner	O
to	O
Copy	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
stollen	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Harper	I-pers
and	O
Phillis	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hutton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
:	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lodging	O
in	O
Sarah	O
Harpers	O
Mothers	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
latter	O
betimes	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Clothes	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
both	O
the	O
Persons	O
,	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Poulston	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
6	O
Coach	O
Glasses	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
20	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Benson	I-pers
the	O
20th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
defective	O
in	O
fixing	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
value	O
;	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Higginson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
;	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
Lodge	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
marrying	O
a	O
2d	O
Wife	O
his	O
first	O
Wife	O
being	O
still	O
alive	O
;	O
the	O
Marriages	O
were	O
both	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Hackney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
pillowbiers	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stokes	I-pers
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
The	O
fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Crookshanks	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bed	O
,	O
Curtains	O
,	O
Fire-Irons	O
,	O
Sawce-pans	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Houshold	O
Fuirniture	O
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
:	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecuters	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
his	O
Landlord	O
and	O
Landlady	O
were	O
gone	O
out	O
,	O
gutted	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
on	O
Crispins	O
Day	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
Shoemaker	O
,	O
went	O
home	O
very	O
drank	O
and	O
remembered	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
neither	O
how	O
he	O
got	O
Home	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
nor	O
how-he	O
carried	O
out	O
the	O
Goods	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
nor	O
of	O
the	O
selling	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
nor	O
anything	O
else	O
,	O
however	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
with	O
standing	O
his	O
ignorance	O
and	O
bad	O
memory	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Emmery	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Emersly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
White-chappel	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Manson	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
to	O
a	O
Considerable	O
value	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Manson	I-pers
the	O
9th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
was	O
12	O
Months	O
;	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
her	O
shop	O
was	O
broken	O
open	O
and	O
her	O
Goods	O
stollen	O
on	O
the	O
Night	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
it	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Ash	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
himself	O
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
Jasper	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
did	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
concurring	O
circumstances	O
to	O
corroborate	O
Ash	O
's	O
Evidence	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
together	O
with	O
Paul	B-pers
Crony	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
Murder	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Asser	I-pers
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Mary	B-pers
Garret	I-pers
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
with	O
Paul	O
Crony	O
Rob	O
the	O
said	O
Nathaniel	O
Asser	O
of	O
10	O
Guineas	O
.	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
and	O
May	O
Garres	O
for	O
receiving	O
a	O
Ring	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Nathaniel	O
Asser	O
's	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stollen	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Worcester	O
the	O
High	O
Constable	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
making	O
diligent	O
Enquiry	O
after	O
the	O
Murtherers	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Asser	O
,	O
had	O
got	O
Intelligence	O
of	O
some	O
Persons	O
,	O
and	O
among	O
others	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
get	O
him	O
secured	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
get	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
discharged	O
.	O
Mr	O
Chapman	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
when	O
in	O
Custody	O
,	O
and	O
telling	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
then	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
of	O
discovering	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
his	O
Accomplices	O
,	O
and	O
Saving	O
himself	O
by	O
being	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
fell	O
to	O
cursing	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
outragious	O
manner	O
,	O
saying	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
him	O
,	O
twenty	O
times	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
High	O
Constable	O
too	O
;	O
he	O
should	O
see	O
them	O
all	O
in	O
Hell	O
;	O
did	O
they	O
think	O
to	O
pump	O
him	O
?	O
no	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
D	O
-	O
m	O
'em	O
,	O
they	O
should	O
get	O
nothing	O
out	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
Constable	O
,	O
Augustin	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
and	O
Cloudsly	B-pers
Chadwick	I-pers
,	O
Watchmen	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
a	O
Person	O
bringing	O
Intelligence	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
that	O
Ralph	B-pers
Emmery	I-pers
was	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
that	O
is	O
called	O
Snuffling	O
Joe	O
in	O
Star	O
Court	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
thither	O
to	O
apprehend	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
Bed	O
with	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
carrying	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
hear	O
him	O
say	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
-	O
that	O
as	O
on	O
the	O
Murther	O
he	O
was	O
clear	O
of	O
that	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
for	O
the	O
Robbery	O
-	O
(	O
there	O
he	O
paused	O
.	O
)	O
Oliver	B-pers
Fenn	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
himself	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Awdly	I-pers
,	O
Paul	B-pers
Crony	I-pers
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
drinking	O
all	O
Night	O
before	O
the	O
Murder	O
,	O
went	O
in	O
the	O
Forenoon	O
to	O
Saltpetre-Bank	O
and	O
having	O
drank	O
there	O
also	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
Fields	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
there	O
met	O
Sarah	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
(	O
since	O
executed	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Part	O
)	O
who	O
ask	O
'd	O
them	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
stand	O
true	O
,	O
telling	O
them	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
lay	O
Drunk	O
near	O
the	O
Half-way-house	O
to	O
Stepney	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
two	O
Rings	O
on	O
his	O
Finger	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
full	O
of	O
Money	O
;	O
that	O
upon	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
Sarah	O
Brown	O
pickt	O
his	O
Pocket	O
of	O
8	O
or	O
10	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
Ralph	O
Emmery	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
one	O
Ring	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
the	O
Deceased	O
snatch	O
'd	O
his	O
Hand	O
back	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
to	O
Will	B-pers
Awdley	I-pers
,	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
him	O
,	O
knock	O
his	O
Brains	O
out	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
Will	O
,	O
Awdley	O
(	O
since	O
executed	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
)	O
took	O
up	O
two	O
Stones	O
and	O
hit	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
:	O
that	O
Paul	O
Crony	O
took	O
off	O
the	O
other	O
Ring	O
:	O
that	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
searched	O
his	O
Pockets	O
,	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
Paper	O
of	O
Coffee	O
and	O
a	O
Pocket	O
Book	O
,	O
and	O
saying	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
quere	O
,	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
then	O
turning	O
him	O
on	O
his	O
face	O
he	O
sell	O
bleeding	O
at	O
the	O
Nose	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defences	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
indeed	O
been	O
with	O
Oliver	B-pers
Fenn	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Awdley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Paul	O
Crony	O
,	O
drinking	O
together	O
all	O
Night	O
,	O
as	O
Oliver	B-pers
Fans	I-pers
had	O
deposed	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
afterwards	O
go	O
to	O
Bank	O
,	O
and	O
out	O
into	O
White-Chappel-Fields	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
he	O
and	O
will	O
,	O
being	O
very	O
such	O
down	O
to	O
sleep	O
;	O
that	O
Oliver	B-pers
Fenn	I-pers
and	O
Paul	O
Crony	O
were	O
met	O
by	O
Sarah	O
Brown	O
,	O
who	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
true	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
not	O
knowing	O
but	O
she	O
might	O
mean	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
explained	O
her	O
meaning	O
,	O
telling	O
them	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
who	O
had	O
Rings	O
and	O
was	O
full	O
of	O
Money	O
lay	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Place	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
and	O
Awdley	O
having	O
slept	O
three	O
House	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
Bank	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
there	O
ask	O
'd	O
them	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
told	O
them	O
Oliver	O
Fenn	O
and	O
Paul	O
Crony	O
had	O
Bit	O
a	O
Blow	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
two	O
Rings	O
and	O
a	O
Hat	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
Oliver	O
Fenn	O
and	O
Paul	O
Crony	O
carried	O
them	O
and	O
shewed	O
them	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
near	O
the	O
Bank	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
away	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
stay	O
,	O
least	O
any	O
body	O
should	O
come	O
and	O
they	O
should	O
be	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
Murdering	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
having	O
fully	O
Confidence	O
thereof	O
the	O
Murder	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Garret	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Worcester	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
made	O
Enquiry	O
for	O
the	O
Ring	O
at	O
all	O
the	O
Goldsmiths	O
from	O
Ratcliff	O
to	O
St.	O
Giles	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
having	O
gotten	O
some	O
intimation	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
having	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
her	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
endeavour	O
to	O
make	O
some	O
Discovery	O
of	O
the	O
Murtherers	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Asser	O
thereby	O
;	O
but	O
found	O
and	O
would	O
the	O
Ring	O
at	O
such	O
les	O
the	O
did	O
that	O
is	O
use	O
and	O
promised	O
so	O
it	O
and	O
being	O
Check	O
that	O
Days	O
but	O
she	O
came	O
out	O
:	O
that	O
she	O
appointed	O
another	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
came	O
not	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
her	O
Son	O
In-law	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
lodg	O
'd	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
his	O
Mother	O
did	O
abscoud	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
procure	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
shou	O
'd	O
have	O
it	O
.	O
That	O
at	O
last	O
having	O
conceal	O
'd	O
her	O
self	O
several	O
Months	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
heard	O
that	O
the	O
matter	O
was	O
fully	O
discover	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
sent	O
the	O
Ring	O
by	O
her	O
Son-in-law	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Asser	O
's	O
Widow	O
,	O
who	O
produced	O
the	O
Ring	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
her	O
deceased	O
Husbands	O
,	O
and	O
deliver	O
'd	O
to	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Person	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
she	O
bought	O
the	O
Ring	O
of	O
Oliver	O
Fenn	O
for	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
it	O
not	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stollen	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
had	O
won	O
it	O
at	O
play	O
:	O
And	O
it	O
out	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stollen	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Emmery	O
:	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jacob	B-pers
William	I-pers
Harris	I-pers
alias	I-pers
James	I-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
in	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
deliver	O
several	O
counterfeit	O
Letters	O
to	O
Collonel	B-pers
Westal	I-pers
,	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ambrose	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Ludlem	I-pers
,	O
Chamberlain	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
pretending	O
the	O
Letters	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
written	O
by	O
the	O
Honourable	O
James	B-pers
Craigs	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
,	O
Secretary	O
of	O
State	O
;	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
he	O
did	O
obtain	O
several	O
Summs	O
of	O
Money	O
for	O
the	O
Printing	O
and	O
Publishing	O
a	O
Book	O
intitled	O
A	O
History	O
of	O
the	O
Royal	O
and	O
Illustrious	O
House	O
of	O
Hannover	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Collonel	O
Westal	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
produc	O
'd	O
a	O
Letter	O
under	O
a	O
Cover	O
directed	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
signed	O
James	O
Craigs	O
,	O
the	O
Purport	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
to	O
desire	O
him	O
to	O
encourage	O
the	O
Printing	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
Book	O
above	O
mentioned	O
,	O
signifying	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Secretary	O
Craigs	O
,	O
would	O
take	O
it	O
as	O
a	O
Respect	O
shew	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
thereupon	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Craigs	O
the	O
Post-Master	O
,	O
or	O
his	O
Son	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
reply	O
'd	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
Son	O
the	O
Secretary	O
of	O
State	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
thereupon	O
give	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Receipt	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Penberson	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
designed	O
to	O
have	O
kept	O
the	O
Letter	O
,	O
yet	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
shuffled	O
it	O
away	O
among	O
,	O
some	O
papers	O
that	O
be	O
then	O
had	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	O
Ambrose	O
depos	O
'd	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
same	O
Pretence	O
,	O
and	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
a	O
great	O
Work	O
carrying	O
on	O
by	O
one	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Bilk	I-pers
,	O
or	O
some	O
such	O
Name	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
given	O
him	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
he	O
kept	O
the	O
Letter	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
returning	O
again	O
desired	O
the	O
Letter	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
lost	O
a	O
Letter	O
that	O
was	O
for	O
another	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
that	O
would	O
serve	O
being	O
put	O
under	O
another	O
Corer	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
los	O
him	O
have	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
others	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
suspecting	O
him	O
,	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
that	O
Letter	O
was	O
writ	O
by	O
Secretary	O
Craigs	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
but	O
putting	O
the	O
matter	O
home	O
he	O
began	O
to	O
boggle	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
certainly	O
affirm	O
a	O
Letter	O
was	O
with	O
by	O
a	O
Person	O
unless	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
write	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
thereupon	O
secured	O
both	O
the	O
Letter	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
notice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Secretary	O
Craigs	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
the	O
Forgery	O
was	O
discovered	O
.	O
His	O
Examination	O
at	O
the	O
Secretary	O
's	O
was	O
read	O
In	O
Court	O
;	O
wherein	O
he	O
had	O
acknowledg	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
named	O
several	O
other	O
worthy	O
Persons	O
from	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
Money	O
by	O
the	O
same	O
fraudalent	O
means	O
;	O
owned	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
formerly	O
suffer	O
'd	O
the	O
Law	O
for	O
an	O
Offence	O
of	O
the	O
like	O
kind	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Intrigoe	O
was	O
carried	O
on	O
by	O
one	O
Michel	B-pers
Coner	I-pers
,	O
and	O
himself	O
,	O
yet	O
had	O
essroctory	O
enough	O
to	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
behave	O
himself	O
very	O
sancils	O
and	O
independantly	O
before	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
however	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
sentenc	O
'd	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
,	O
to	O
suffer	O
6	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
and	O
pay	O
a	O
Fine	O
of	O
20	O
Marks	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Riding	O
hood	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Poulsey	I-pers
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
House	O
to	O
ask	O
for	O
Lodging	O
,	O
took	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
carry	O
away	O
the	O
Riding-hood	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
alledg	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
by	O
mistake	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
design	O
to	O
return	O
it	O
again	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Fenwick	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Peers	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Gowns	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Adcock	I-pers
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodging	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Walley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Arthur	B-pers
Moor	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
and	O
Katherine	B-pers
Laybourn	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Linnen	O
value	O
33	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hodgkins	I-pers
the	O
20th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
Laybourn	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
:	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
affecting	O
Mary	O
Fowler	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
but	O
Laybourn	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Pancras	B-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
High	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Bag	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
the	O
22d	O
.	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
and	O
Robbing	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
4	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
and	O
a	O
Dutch	O
Stiver	O
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
November	O
Elizabeth	O
Griffith	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
having	O
been	O
at	O
Market	O
and	O
coming	O
home	O
about	O
4	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
met	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
second	O
Field	O
from	O
Pancrass-wells	B-place
,	O
where	O
she	O
liv	O
'd	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
pulling	O
out	O
a	O
Dagger	O
sause	O
violently	O
he	O
would	O
had	O
her	O
immediately	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
deliver	O
him	O
her	O
Money	O
;	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
very	O
much	O
affrighted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
November	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
at	O
Market	O
had	O
bought	O
some	O
Meat	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
occasion	O
to	O
a	O
point	O
,	O
laid	O
his	O
Meat	O
down	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
String	O
of	O
his	O
Breeches	O
breaking	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
pulled	O
off	O
his	O
Garter	O
and	O
ty	O
'd	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
suddenly	O
upon	O
him	O
(	O
with	O
the	O
Instrument	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Griffith	O
called	O
a	O
Dagger	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
swore	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
fine	O
File	O
ground	O
into	O
the	O
form	O
of	O
the	O
Blade	O
of	O
a	O
buyonett	O
of	O
about	O
8	O
Inches	O
in	O
length	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
into	O
an	O
Ivory	O
Handle	O
of	O
a	O
Knife	O
)	O
and	O
catching	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
threatend	O
to	O
stab	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Heart	O
immediately	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
deliver	O
his	O
Money	O
;	O
he	O
telling	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
none	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
he	O
pleas	O
'd	O
he	O
might	O
take	O
his	O
Meat	O
,	O
he	O
swore	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
want	O
his	O
Meat	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
his	O
Money	O
and	O
telling	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
be	O
kill	O
'd	O
for	O
his	O
Obllin	O
acy	O
,	O
thrust	O
his	O
Hand	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
his	O
Bag	O
,	O
and	O
seeling	O
about	O
it	O
for	O
Money	O
and	O
not	O
finding	O
any	O
,	O
was	O
about	O
to	O
thrust	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
again	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
drawing	O
back	O
his	O
Leg	O
,	O
caught	O
him	O
last	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Collar	O
,	O
threw	O
his	O
head	O
in	O
His	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
his	O
Leg	O
threw	O
him	O
,	O
hold	O
him	O
tight	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
securing	O
his	O
Dagger-Hand	O
,	O
keeping	O
his	O
hold	O
till	O
by	O
calling	O
out	O
some	O
Persons	O
who	O
were	O
of	O
his	O
Company	O
gone	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Assistance	O
.	O
Two	O
other	O
Evidences	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
hearing	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
call	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Assistance	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
strugling	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
that	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
first	O
,	O
disposed	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Weapon	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
Dagger	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
Hand	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Facts	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
so	O
plainly	O
Prov	O
'd	O
they	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Pool	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Box	O
of	O
Cutlery	O
Ware	O
val.28	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Tring	I-pers
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
stolen	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Cart	O
near	O
Holbourn-Bridge	B-place
,	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
stopt	O
by	O
a	O
Person	O
to	O
whom	O
they	O
were	O
offer	O
'd	O
in	O
sale	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
Plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Cordell	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Elliot	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Linnen	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Selby	I-pers
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gaggle	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Cheating	O
Richard	B-pers
Ladbrook	I-pers
of	O
2	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Brandy	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
Brandy	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
had	O
2	O
Gallons	O
sent	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
by	O
a	O
Boy	O
under	O
Pretence	O
of	O
carrying	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
Carriers	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
taking	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
Boy	O
,	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Misdemeanour	O
.	O
Fined	O
9	O
s.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Mist	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
in	O
Printing	O
and	O
Publishing	O
several	O
base	O
and	O
scandalous	O
Reflections	O
on	O
the	O
Government	O
in	O
his	O
Paper	O
Called	O
The	O
Weekly	O
Journal	O
:	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
appearing	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgments	O
:	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death,4	O
Richard	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
Mary	O
Gouldston	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
K	O
-	O
and	O
Ralph	B-pers
Emmery	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported,30	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Tho	B-pers
Casson	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Hawker	I-pers
,	O
Martha	B-pers
Hawley	I-pers
,	O
Sam	B-pers
Linne	I-pers
,	O
Eliz	B-pers
Day	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Hewson	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gibbons	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
,	O
Aaron	B-pers
Wilcox	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Reed	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Frances	B-pers
Fenwick	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Walls	I-pers
,	O
Katherine	B-pers
Loybourn	I-pers
alias	O
Phillips	O
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Cordell	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Poole	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Duhammel	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Harper	I-pers
,	O
Phillis	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
,	O
Tho	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Crookshanks	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Paxford	I-pers
,	O
Martha	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand,2	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
N	O
-	O
M	O
-	O
Jacob	B-pers
William	I-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
Fined	O
20	O
Marks,6	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gaggle	I-pers
,	O
Fined	O
5	O
l.	O
Mary	B-pers
Gouldston	I-pers
Pleaded	O
her	O
Belly	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
being	O
impannelled	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
with	O
Quick	O
Child	O
.	O
THE	O
First	O
and	O
Second	O
Volumes	O
of	O
Remarkable	O
Tryals	O
,	O
Behaviour	O
and	O
Dying	O
Speeches	O
,	O
of	O
notorious	O
Malefactors	O
,	O
having	O
met	O
with	O
so	O
kind	O
a	O
Reception	O
by	O
the	O
Publick	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
carry	O
off	O
the	O
First	O
Imprestion	O
:	O
There	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
Prets	O
and	O
will	O
speedily	O
be	O
Publish	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Third	O
and	O
Fourth	O
Volumes	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
continuation	O
of	O
them	O
down	O
to	O
this	O
present	O
Year,1718	O
.	O
Some	O
BOOKS	O
printed	O
for	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
Edmond	O
Parker	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
and	O
Crown	O
is	O
Lombard	O
Street	O
,	O
near	O
Stocks-Market	O
.	O
AESOP	O
's	O
Fables	O
,	O
with	O
Morals	O
and	O
Reflections	O
,	O
as	O
improv	O
'd	O
by	O
Sir	O
Roger	O
L'Estrange	O
,	O
done	O
into	O
Variety	O
of	O
English	O
Verie	O
.	O
Illustrated	O
with	O
Cuts	O
curiously	O
engrav	O
'd	O
on	O
Copper	O
Plates	O
.	O
The	O
Second	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
2	O
s.6	O
d.	O
The	O
London	O
New	O
Method	O
and	O
Art	O
of	O
Teaching	O
Children	O
to	O
Spell	O
and	O
Read	O
;	O
so	O
as	O
they	O
may	O
,	O
without	O
the	O
Help	O
of	O
any	O
other	O
Books	O
,	O
read	O
the	O
Bible	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
twelve	O
Months	O
Note	O
,	O
This	O
Way	O
of	O
Teaching	O
is	O
approved	O
by	O
most	O
School	O
Masters	O
as	O
the	O
best	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
6	O
d.	O
with	O
great	O
Allowance	O
to	O
those	O
who	O
sell	O
or	O
give	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
Note	O
,	O
There	O
are	O
some	O
printed	O
on	O
Fine	O
Paper	O
,	O
bound	O
up	O
with	O
Cuts	O
.	O
Pr.8	O
d.	O
M.	O
Jordain	O
's	O
Duodecimal	O
Arithmetick	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
must	O
Concise	O
and	O
Exact	O
Method	O
Exstant	O
.	O
In	O
Three	O
Books	O
.	O
Containing	O
Notation	O
,	O
Addition	O
,	O
Subtraction	O
,	O
Multiplication	O
,	O
Division	O
,	O
Reduction	O
,	O
Extraction	O
of	O
the	O
Square	O
and	O
Cube	O
Roots	O
,	O
Rule	O
of	O
Proportion	O
Direct	O
and	O
Reverse	O
,	O
Duodecimally	O
performed	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
Practicall	O
,	O
applied	O
to	O
the	O
measuring	O
of	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
Superficies	O
;	O
and	O
Solids	O
,	O
as	O
Board	O
,	O
Glass	O
,	O
Sec	O
.	O
Timber	O
,	O
Stone	O
,	O
etc	O
.	O
the	O
Ganging	O
of	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
Brewers	O
Tuns	O
and	O
Casks	O
,	O
etc	O
.	O
and	O
that	O
with	O
more	O
Ease	O
and	O
Expedition	O
,	O
than	O
by	O
Vulgar	O
or	O
Decimal	O
Arithmetick	O
.	O
Very	O
Useful	O
for	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
Men	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
Gentlemen	O
as	O
others	O
,	O
but	O
especially	O
for	O
Merchants	O
,	O
Writing	O
Masters	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
Measuring	O
Artificers	O
And	O
all	O
the	O
Rules	O
made	O
Plain	O
,	O
and	O
Easie	O
for	O
the	O
meanest	O
Capacity.800	O
.	O
Price	O
Bound	O
2	O
s.6	O
d.	O
The	O
Benefit	O
of	O
Early	O
Piety	O
,	O
recommended	O
to	O
all	O
Young	O
Persons	O
,	O
and	O
particularly	O
to	O
those	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
.	O
By	O
W.	O
Smythies	O
,	O
late	O
Morning	O
Lecturer	O
of	O
St.	O
Michael	O
in	O
Cornhil	O
,	O
London	O
.	O
The	O
Third	O
Edition	O
,	O
Price	O
bound	O
6	O
d.	O
For	O
the	O
Compleating	O
of	O
Psalmody	O
.	O
The	O
Devout	O
Singer	O
's	O
Guide	O
;	O
containing	O
all	O
the	O
Common	O
Times	O
now	O
in	O
life	O
,	O
with	O
Select	O
Portions	O
of	O
the	O
psalms	O
adapted	O
to	O
each	O
Tune	O
,	O
and	O
Rules	O
for	O
singing	O
Treble	O
and	O
bass	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
prefix	O
'd	O
,	O
Directions	O
for	O
Parish	O
Clerks	O
in	O
the	O
Chains	O
of	O
proper	O
Psalms	O
on	O
most	O
Occasions	O
.	O
Recommended	O
by	O
the	O
best	O
Singing	O
Masters	O
.	O
The	O
Second	O
Edition	O
,	O
Sev	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
1	O
s.	O
The	O
Pen	O
's	O
Dexterity	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
The	O
Ingenious	O
and	O
Useful	O
Art	O
of	O
Writing	O
Short-Hand	O
.	O
Containing	O
Twenty	O
Copper-Plates	O
(	O
curiously	O
engrav	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Author	O
's	O
Life-time	O
for	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
his	O
Scholars	O
)	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Letters	O
,	O
Characters	O
and	O
Contractions	O
used	O
therein	O
.	O
With	O
Rules	O
and	O
Directions	O
explaining	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
the	O
meanest	O
Capacity	O
.	O
Whereunto	O
are	O
added	O
Law-	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
Discourses	O
,	O
as	O
on	O
War	O
,	O
Trade	O
,	O
Birds	O
,	O
Beasts	O
,	O
Fruits	O
,	O
Vermim	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Approv	O
'd	O
by	O
both	O
Universities	O
,	O
Practis	O
'd	O
by	O
Honourable	O
Persons	O
,	O
Hminent	O
Lawyers	O
and	O
Gentlemen	O
;	O
and	O
is	O
of	O
special	O
use	O
for	O
Travellers	O
,	O
Historian	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
By	O
Jeremish	O
Rich	O
.	O
The	O
Sixth	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
Arithmetick	O
made	O
easie	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
New	O
Method	O
now	O
taught	O
and	O
practis	O
'd	O
in	O
London	O
.	O
Wherein	O
the	O
Rules	O
of	O
that	O
necessary	O
Art	O
are	O
briefly	O
explain	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
illustrated	O
with	O
such	O
samiliar	O
Examples	O
as	O
may	O
suit	O
the	O
meanest	O
Capacity	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
desire	O
to	O
learn	O
it	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
a	O
Succinct	O
Treatise	O
of	O
Des	O
Fra	O
,	O
with	O
Compleat	O
Ta	O
,	O
Rules	O
,	O
and	O
Examples	O
demonstrating	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
like	O
not	O
extant	O
in	O
any	O
other	O
Treatise	O
of	O
this	O
Nature	O
.	O
The	O
Fourth	O
Edition	O
.	O
By	O
John	B-pers
Copeland	I-pers
,	O
Writing-Master	O
,	O
Price	O
bound	O
1	O
s.	O
Ordess	O
.	O
By	O
Law	O
,	O
and	O
Ordinances	O
for	O
the	O
good	O
Government	O
and	O
Regulating	O
of	O
the	O
Persons	O
Licensed	O
to	O
Keep	O
and	O
Drive	O
Hickney	O
Coaches	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
and	O
Drivers	O
.	O
Made	O
,	O
Publish	O
'd	O
and	O
Declar	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Commissioners	O
;	O
and	O
Allowed	O
and	O
Approved	O
by	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chancellor	O
and	O
Judges	O
as	O
the	O
Law	O
directs	O
.	O
Price	O
3	O
d.	O
For	O
the	O
Good	O
of	O
the	O
Publick	O
.	O
WHereas	O
several	O
Gentlewomen	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
that	O
Sex	O
,	O
in	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
have	O
contrasted	O
an	O
Evil	O
Habit	O
of	O
Body	O
,	O
wherein	O
the	O
vicious	O
Humours	O
,	O
at	O
first	O
despos	O
'd	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Whole	O
,	O
come	O
at	O
length	O
to	O
be	O
lodged	O
in	O
one	O
Part	O
or	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
times	O
,	O
for	O
couses	O
the	O
long	O
to	O
be	O
here	O
mentioned	O
,	O
are	O
thrown	O
down	O
upon	O
that	O
the	O
occassionally	O
a	O
dangerous	O
in	O
that	O
which	O
being	O
at	O
last	O
Cancerous	O
,	O
and	O
often	O
proves	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
to	O
acqaint	O
all	O
such	O
as	O
may	O
have	O
occasion	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
speedy	O
Relief	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
hall	O
from	O
and	O
Experienc	O
'd	O
Mid	O
at	O
the	O
of	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Arts	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
the	O
Tin-Shop	O
near	O
Changes	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
who	O
perform	O
'd	O
a	O
wonderful	O
Care	O
a	O
Lady	O
the	O
,	O
after	O
given	O
over	O
by	O
the	O
Physician	O
,	O
and	O
face	O
has	O
Cared	O
several	O
Gentlewomen	O
and	O
others	O
in	O
the	O
City	O
and	O
of	O
I	O
not	O
five	O
put	O
my	O
self	O
in	O
the	O
Assis	O
where	O
they	O
may	O
have	O
Relief	O
,	O
if	O
not	O
,	O
no	O
Money	O
.	O
All	O
Melancholy	O
,	O
Hysterical	O
and	O
Hypoconblack	O
Distempers	O
,	O
WHich	O
variously	O
affect	O
the	O
Mind	O
,	O
with	O
strange	O
Fears	O
and	O
dismal	O
Apprehensions	O
;	O
Faintings	O
and	O
Sinkings	O
of	O
the	O
Spirits	O
,	O
great	O
Hurries	O
,	O
Restlesness	O
and	O
Disquitement	O
(	O
little	O
understood	O
and	O
seldom	O
cured	O
by	O
any	O
common	O
means	O
also	O
Pains	O
and	O
Giddiness	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
;	O
Risings	O
to	O
the	O
Thro	O
,	O
Sick	O
Fits	O
,	O
Tremblings	O
,	O
Oppressions	O
of	O
the	O
Heart	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
other	O
Disorders	O
caused	O
by	O
Vapours	O
;	O
are	O
successfully	O
cured	O
(	O
with	O
God	O
's	O
Blessing	O
)	O
by	O
a	O
Physician	O
well	O
experienced	O
therein	O
,	O
(	O
who	O
is	O
Son	O
and	O
Successor	O
to	O
a	O
late	O
eminant	O
Physician	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
of	O
more	O
than	O
30	O
Years	O
successful	O
Practise	O
in	O
those	O
Deplorahie	O
Cases	O
)	O
he	O
also	O
Cures	O
all	O
kind	O
of	O
Fits	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
strange	O
and	O
viclent	O
(	O
if	O
curable	O
)	O
which	O
he	O
will	O
justly	O
inform	O
you	O
;	O
living	O
at	O
No	O
I.	O
in	O
Burr-street	O
in	O
St.	O
Katherines	O
near	O
the	O
Tower	O
,	O
London	O
;	O
where	O
those	O
that	O
have	O
occasion	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
remote	O
,	O
direct	O
their	O
Letters	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
shall	O
be	O
speedily	O
answered	O
,	O
or	O
attened	O
on	O
it	O
desired	O
.	O
A	O
Water	O
that	O
perfectly	O
cures	O
the	O
Itch	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
Itching	O
Humour	O
in	O
a	O
short	O
time	O
,	O
without	O
necessary	O
of	O
Purging	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
dangerous	O
Use	O
of	O
Mercury	O
,	O
Price	O
1	O
s.6	O
d	O
Prepared	O
and	O
sold	O
only	O
by	O
A	O
Downing	O
Chymist	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
and	O
Ball	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Duck-lane	O
in	O
West-Smistfield	O
.	O
Where	O
also	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
,	O
the	O
true	O
Spirits	O
of	O
Scurvy-Grass	O
,	O
Purging	O
and	O
Plain	O
,	O
and	O
Spirits	O
of	O
Ground-lvy	O
at	O
1	O
s.	O
each	O
Bottle	O
Likewise	O
,	O
a	O
Pemedy	O
for	O
the	O
Tooth	O
ach	O
,	O
the	O
most	O
effectual	O
for	O
that	O
use	O
of	O
any	O
yet	O
known	O
,	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
To	O
prevent	O
and	O
cure	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
in	O
the	O
Gums	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
preserve	O
and	O
fallen	O
loose	O
Teeth	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
And	O
also	O
a	O
most	O
successful	O
Plaister	O
to	O
prevent	O
Miscarages	O
in	O
Women	O
,	O
which	O
has	O
help	O
'd	O
beyond	O
expectation	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
hope	O
of	O
Relief	O
Price	O
5	O
s.	O
At	O
her	O
House	O
as	O
the	O
Red	O
Ball	O
in	O
Queen-street	O
,	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
over	O
against	O
the	O
Glob-tavern	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
distant	O
from	O
the	O
Three-Cranes	O
.	O
LIveth	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
the	O
Doughter	O
of	O
an	O
eminent	O
Physician	O
,	O
who	O
practis	O
'd	O
in	O
London	O
upwards	O
o'40	O
Years	O
:	O
hath	O
an	O
Ointment	O
,	O
called	O
the	O
Royal	O
Ointment	O
for	O
the	O
Gent	O
.	O
and	O
Kheuwatick	O
Pains	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
great	O
Ease	O
and	O
Comford	O
to	O
both	O
Sexes	O
at	O
Home	O
and	O
Abroad	O
,	O
as	O
hath	O
been	O
experienced	O
by	O
many	O
who	O
have	O
carried	O
it	O
with	O
them	O
into	O
foreign	O
:	O
and	O
is	O
therefore	O
of	O
excellent	O
use	O
for	O
all	O
Travellers	O
.	O
Thus	O
is	O
the	O
Cure	O
compleated	O
;	O
as	O
is	O
well	O
known	O
to	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
Notility	O
and	O
Gentry	O
,	O
who	O
have	O
experienced	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
are	O
ready	O
to	O
testify	O
the	O
Truth	O
of	O
its	O
wonderful	O
Success	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
also	O
a	O
certain	O
and	O
infallible	O
Cure	O
for	O
the	O
Tootbath	O
,	O
without	O
drawing	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
effectually	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Pain	O
will	O
never	O
return	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
only	O
so	O
,	O
but	O
makes	O
the	O
Teeth	O
as	O
white	O
as	O
Ivory	O
,	O
and	O
fastens	O
those	O
that	O
are	O
loose	O
to	O
Admiration	O
.	O
She	O
changes	O
red	O
as	O
grey	O
Hair	O
to	O
a	O
delicate	O
light	O
or	O
dark	O
brown	O
.	O
She	O
cures	O
sore	O
Eyes	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
almost	O
blind	O
,	O
and	O
challenges	O
all	O
Europs	O
to	O
answer	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
that	O
kind	O
;	O
she	O
sels	O
the	O
Royal	O
Snuff	O
for	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
which	O
purges	O
the	O
Head	O
as	O
Physick	O
pur	O
Body	O
.	O
She	O
prevents	O
Miscarriages	O
.	O
She	O
prepares	O
proper	O
Medicines	O
for	O
Distempers	O
incident	O
to	O
her	O
own	O
Sex	O
.	O
She	O
cuts	O
Hair	O
very	O
fine	O
.	O
The	O
following	O
Books	O
are	O
given	O
Gratis	O
.	O
1st	O
,	O
THE	O
Practical	O
Scheme	O
of	O
the	O
Secret	O
Disease	O
and	O
Broken	O
Constitutions	O
,	O
by	O
East	O
Living	O
,	O
Former	O
ill	O
Cures	O
,	O
Salivations	O
and	O
Mercury	O
-	O
.	O
The	O
New	O
System	O
of	O
the	O
GOUT	O
and	O
Rhenmentision	O
,	O
dawn	O
from	O
Reason	O
,	O
Observations	O
and	O
Experience	O
-3ly	O
.	O
A	O
Rational	O
Account	O
Cause	O
,	O
Nature	O
,	O
and	O
Cure	O
of	O
WEAKNESS	O
ding	O
Persons	O
after	O
former	O
Cures	O
,	O
over	O
Abuses	O
,	O
Hard	O
Labours	O
,	O
Miscaraiges	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Wherein	O
a	O
full	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
horrid	O
Nature	O
,	O
and	O
most	O
sequences	O
of	O
Self	O
.	O
Abuses	O
in	O
particular	O
.	O
These	O
Books	O
(	O
all	O
New	O
Editions	O
)	O
are	O
given	O
Gratis	O
Up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
ANODYNE	O
.	O
NECK-LACE	O
,	O
without	O
Temple	O
Bar	O
.	O
At	O
M.	O
C.	O
Toyshop	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Charles	O
Court	O
by	O
Hungertord-Marker	O
in	O
the	O
Second	O
.	O
And	O
And	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Garraway	O
's	O
Shop	O
at	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms	O
at	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange-Gate	O
next	O
Council	O
.	O
THe	O
best	O
Water	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
,	O
so	O
called	O
by	O
many	O
who	O
have	O
experienced	O
it	O
to	O
he	O
so	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Itch	O
or	O
any	O
Itching	O
Humours	O
;	O
it	O
hath	O
been	O
taken	O
inwardly	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Exit	O
,	O
it	O
's	O
good	O
to	O
cure	O
Sore	O
E	O
or	O
any	O
other	O
Dicers	O
,	O
or	O
F	O
;	O
it	O
has	O
preserved	O
from	O
baring	O
their	O
Limbs	O
cut	O
off	O
,	O
when	O
all	O
other	O
means	O
have	O
failed	O
.	O
Sold	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gondge	O
at	O
the	O
Castle	O
in	O
Westminster-Hall	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Radford	O
's	O
for	O
shop	O
at	O
the	O
great	O
Golden	O
Spectacles	O
against	O
St.	O
Clements	O
Church-Yard	O
near	O
-Street	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
