TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commiffion	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Juslice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
,	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
23d,24th,25th	O
and	O
26th	O
of	O
April,1718	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Fourth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
BEfore	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
LEWEN	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
Parker	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Price	I-pers
;	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
Names	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Atkinson	B-pers
Bugbey	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Brookhouse	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Littlefield	I-pers
John	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
William	B-pers
Territ	I-pers
Rovler	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Word	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Katch	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
John	B-pers
Rowland	I-pers
Ralph	B-pers
Stmp	I-pers
John	B-pers
Peachy	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
Giles	B-pers
Riddle	I-pers
Thomos	B-pers
Baven	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Kern	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Peacock	I-pers
John	B-pers
Cartis	I-pers
George	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Prior	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Hayes	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Wheely	I-pers
John	B-pers
Word	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Burgess	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Davenish	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Simmerton	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
,	I-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
and	O
Percival	B-pers
Hutchinson	I-pers
,	O
(	O
not	O
taken	O
)	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
upon	O
two	O
indictments	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Peter-Anthony	B-pers
Motteux	I-pers
on	O
the	O
18th	O
Day	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
second	O
for	O
robbing	O
him	O
of	O
8	O
Guineas	O
.	O
The	O
Council	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
setting	O
forth	O
that	O
Murder	O
was	O
a	O
crime	O
of	O
that	O
heinous	O
matter	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
beyond	O
the	O
Power	O
of	O
words	O
to	O
aggravate	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
diffusive	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
Justice	O
were	O
not	O
executed	O
on	O
the	O
Offenders	O
the	O
Guilt	O
became	O
National	O
.	O
Adding	O
,	O
there	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Characters	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
it	O
did	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
as	O
followeth	O
;	O
that	O
Elizabeth	O
Simmerton	O
the	O
Mistress	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
the	O
Deceased	O
unfortunately	O
lost	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
very	O
ill	O
who	O
had	O
for	O
many	O
Years	O
kept	O
a	O
scandalous	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
Star-Court	B-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Butcher	I-place
Row	I-place
near	I-place
Temple	I-place
Bar	I-place
that	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
was	O
her	O
Daughter	O
by	O
a	O
former	O
who	O
with	O
her	O
as	O
a	O
that	O
Mary	O
Roberts	O
and	O
Elizabeth	O
Williams	O
did	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
Edward	O
Williams	O
and	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
That	O
Mary	O
Roberts	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
convicted	O
Mr.	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
after	O
found	O
Murther	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
indeed	O
they	O
had	O
no	O
Evidence	O
that	O
were	O
witness	O
of	O
the	O
Murther	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
Murthers	O
such	O
Evidences	O
were	O
hard	O
to	O
be	O
obtain	O
'd	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
in	O
dispensatily	O
necessary	O
to	O
give	O
Judgement	O
by	O
presumptive	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
would	O
shew	O
by	O
the	O
following	O
Evidences	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Evidence	O
call	O
'd	O
was	O
Mary	B-pers
Dow	I-pers
,	O
who	O
despose	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
living	O
just	O
by	O
Mr	O
Mottenx	O
,	O
did	O
about	O
5	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
the	O
18th	O
Day	O
of	O
February	O
see	O
a	O
Lady	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
Mr.	O
door	O
and	O
Motteux	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
Mr.	O
standing	O
at	O
his	O
own	O
door	O
in	O
a	O
Dark	O
colour	O
'd	O
Cloth	O
that	O
he	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
look	O
'd	O
very	O
and	O
was	O
counting	O
some	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
telling	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
in	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
look	O
'd	O
yellow	O
,	O
and	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
Guineas	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
indeed	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
pretty	O
many	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
Her	O
Evidence	O
was	O
by	O
who	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
pretty	O
many	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
did	O
belive	O
there	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
less	O
than	O
30	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Motteux	O
Put	O
them	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
Mr.	O
deposed	O
that	O
his	O
father	O
had	O
as	O
the	O
other	O
Evidences	O
had	O
describ	O
'd	O
with	O
in	O
Orange	O
colour	O
'd	O
Silk	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
between	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
a	O
Clock	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
White	O
's	O
some	O
for	O
a	O
lady	O
of	O
Quality	O
.	O
that	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
6	O
Mr.	O
Motteux	O
standing	O
at	O
his	O
own	O
Door	O
,	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
order	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
That	O
Mr	O
Motteux	O
put	O
his	O
Scarlet	O
Cloak	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
together	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
some	O
benefits	O
there	O
,	O
just	O
as	O
the	O
clock	O
7	O
they	O
parted	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Motteux	O
went	O
forward	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Arthur	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Motteux	O
came	O
to	O
White	O
's	O
9	O
a-Clock	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
staid	O
till	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
that	O
he	O
there	O
eat	O
a	O
Couple	O
Glasses	O
of	O
Jelley	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
Guinea	O
chang	O
'd	O
,	O
saying	O
had	O
not	O
more	O
than	O
in	O
Silver	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
a	O
in	O
and	O
enquir	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
that	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
the	O
Scarlet	O
that	O
after	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
by	O
Chairmen	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
that	O
was	O
a	O
Woman	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
St	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
near	O
White	O
's	O
house	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
came	O
into	O
her	O
house	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
drink	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
waited	O
for	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
a	O
Scarlet	O
who	O
was	O
into	O
that	O
the	O
staid	O
near	O
two	O
Hours	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
full	O
Pot	O
of	O
Beer	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
to	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
afterwards	O
return	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
of	O
carry	O
'd	O
instead	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Gibs	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
carried	O
a	O
of	O
Brandy	O
to	O
the	O
Coach	O
to	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
a	O
Scarlet	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
drank	O
the	O
Brandy	O
,	O
paid	O
for	O
it	O
and	O
the	O
Coach	O
drove	O
away	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Edwards	O
a	O
seller	O
of	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Coach	O
pass	O
'd	O
by	O
her	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
,	O
which	O
stop	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
with	O
a	O
Scarlet	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
talking	O
,	O
laughing	O
,	O
and	O
laying	O
out	O
very	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
told	O
Mary	B-pers
Dent	I-pers
there	O
was	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
and	O
his	O
gone	O
to	O
Star	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
afterwards	O
heard	O
the	O
Coachman	O
call	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
having	O
heard	O
Mrs.	O
Edwards	O
say	O
that	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
were	O
gone	O
to	O
Star-Court	O
,	O
knowing	O
House	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
House	O
Report	O
,	O
observ	O
'd	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
a	O
Scarlet	O
clock	O
hand	O
a	O
Woman	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
petticoat	O
hitch	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
as	O
she	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
coachman	O
clear	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
she	O
gave	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
a	O
clap	O
of	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
turn	O
'd	O
him	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
walk	O
up	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
followed	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
no	O
other	O
Persons	O
there	O
but	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
Woman	O
and	O
Coachman	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
walk	O
'd	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
seem	O
to	O
ail	O
anything	O
,	O
Mery	O
Bmer	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Merick	O
,	O
leaving	O
at	O
the	O
next	O
door	O
Mrs.	O
Simmerton	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
about	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
to	O
wash	O
a	O
Pot	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
into	O
Simmerton	O
's	O
House	O
saw	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
a	O
red	O
Cloak	O
and	O
Sword	O
,	O
standing	O
with	O
his	O
Face	O
towards	O
the	O
Fire	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
facing	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
stooped	O
down	O
and	O
kissed	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Woman	O
was	O
Mary	O
Roberts	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
Elizabeth	O
Shepberd	O
did	O
light	O
a	O
Candle	O
and	O
lighted	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
up	O
Stairs	O
and	O
Mary	O
Roberts	O
followed	O
him	O
up	O
;	O
that	O
Elizabeth	O
Shepherd	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
paid	O
the	O
Coachman	O
3	O
Shillings	O
,	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Simmerton	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
much	O
;	O
but	O
Elizabeth	O
Shepherd	O
cry	O
'd	O
Phoo	O
'	O
,	O
its	O
no	O
matter	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Merrick	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Maid	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
related	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
replyed	O
if	O
it	O
were	O
so	O
they	O
would	O
make	O
a	O
fine	O
Penny	O
of	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Coachman	O
that	O
carried	O
them	O
,	O
was	O
called	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
examined	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
what	O
he	O
knew	O
of	O
carrying	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
a	O
Scarler	O
Cloak	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
from	O
St.	O
Clement	O
's	O
Church	O
to	O
White	O
's	O
Chocolate-House	O
,	O
and	O
waiting	O
there	O
near	O
2	O
Hours	O
,	O
and	O
bringing	O
them	O
back	O
to	O
Star-Court	O
at	O
about	O
a	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
18th	O
February	O
.	O
He	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
forgetful	O
as	O
to	O
know	O
or	O
remember	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
be	O
intirely	O
ignorant	O
of	O
every	O
particular	O
Circumstance	O
;	O
may	O
,	O
was	O
sure	O
he	O
never	O
carried	O
such	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
.	O
But	O
his	O
Master	O
Richard	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
having	O
staid	O
out	O
that	O
Night	O
longer	O
than	O
ordinary	O
,	O
he	O
requiring	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
home	O
always	O
by	O
10	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
atgray	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
staying	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
carried	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
a	O
Scarlet	O
Cloak	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
to	O
and	O
waited	O
at	O
White	O
's	O
Chocolate	O
House	O
and	O
drove	O
them	O
back	O
and	O
set	O
them	O
down	O
at	O
Star-Court	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
went	O
up	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
any	O
more	O
than	O
a	O
Shilling	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
an	O
old	O
Bawd	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Tayler	O
she	O
also	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Thomas	B-pers
White	I-pers
when	O
he	O
was	O
examined	O
why	O
he	O
staid	O
out	O
so	O
late	O
,	O
answer	O
'd	O
as	O
before	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
carried	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
to	O
White	O
's	O
'chocolate-House	O
,	O
waited	O
there	O
,	O
brought	O
them	O
back	O
to	O
Star-Court	O
or	O
else	O
could	O
have	O
been	O
at	O
home	O
two	O
Hours	O
sooner	O
,	O
and	O
notwichstanding	O
could	O
get	O
but	O
a	O
Shilling	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Woman	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
gave	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
it	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
Bawdy-house	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
pray	O
'd	O
for	O
her	O
in	O
his	O
Heart	O
.	O
She	O
added	O
that	O
talking	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
at	O
another	O
time	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
had	O
a	O
brave	O
Scarlet	O
Cloak	O
,	O
he	O
wish	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
it	O
behind	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
why	O
!	O
would	O
he	O
have	O
kept	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Cloak	O
?	O
That	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
must	O
have	O
come	O
after	O
him	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
lead	O
his	O
Fair	O
,	O
and	O
added	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
come	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
brave	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
make	O
him	O
a	O
brave	O
Suit	O
:	O
To	O
which	O
his	O
Brother-Coachman	O
and	O
fellow-Servant	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
would	O
have	O
made	O
him	O
a	O
Bean	O
Officer	O
for	O
King	O
George	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
Ay	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
want	O
nothing	O
but	O
a	O
Sword	O
This	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
his	O
Fellow-Servant	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
the	O
Court	O
wondered	O
at	O
his	O
forgetfulness	O
of	O
so	O
many	O
remarkable	O
Passages	O
deposed	O
by	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
mistress	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Fellow-Servant	O
,	O
bid	O
him	O
recollect	O
himself	O
;	O
but	O
still	O
he	O
would	O
remember	O
nothing	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
then	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
perhaps	O
he	O
having	O
given	O
his	O
Master	O
Shilling	O
instead	O
of	O
three	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
his	O
denying	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
caught	O
to	O
consider	O
he	O
was	O
upon	O
his	O
Oath	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
Matter	O
of	O
Moment	O
,	O
advised	O
him	O
in	O
consider	O
and	O
speak	O
the	O
Truth	O
:	O
but	O
still	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
Evidences	O
that	O
saw	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
when	O
it	O
came	O
to	O
Star-Court	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Coachman	O
,	O
and	O
describ	O
'd	O
his	O
Clothes	O
,	O
which	O
agreed	O
to	O
the	O
Description	O
;	O
but	O
still	O
he	O
obstinately	O
denying	O
it	O
,	O
Mary	O
Roberts	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
carried	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
with	O
Mr.Montens	O
try	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
Coachman	O
that	O
carried	O
us	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
very	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
3s	O
for	O
carrying	O
us	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Raton	I-pers
who	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
Mrs.	O
Merrick	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
disposed	O
went	O
early	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
but	O
about	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
was	O
wak	O
'd	O
,	O
heard	O
a	O
Noise	O
and	O
Rustling	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
House	O
,	O
a	O
trampling	O
of	O
Feet	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
Fall	O
that	O
shaked	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
usual	O
to	O
have	O
such	O
disturbances	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
lay	O
still	O
and	O
took	O
no	O
notice	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
till	O
next	O
Day	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
was	O
dead	O
there	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Eloner	O
,	O
as	O
apothecry	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
a	O
Clock	O
his	O
Man	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
soldier	O
and	O
another	O
Man	O
wanted	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Star-Court	O
;	O
he	O
st	O
immediately	O
and	O
went	O
:	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
knew	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
had	O
he	O
known	O
where	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
he	O
should	O
hardly	O
have	O
troubled	O
himself	O
to	O
have	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Bed	O
to	O
have	O
gone	O
thither	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
so	O
ill	O
an	O
Opinion	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
however	O
he	O
did	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
thither	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
young	O
Woman	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
Elizabeth	O
Shepherd	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
a	O
Fit	O
above	O
Stairs	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
he	O
saw	O
Mrs.	O
Simmerton	O
,	O
Mary	O
Roberts	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
a	O
Leather	O
Apron	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
took	O
to	O
be	O
Simmerton	O
's	O
Husband	O
,	O
there	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
view	O
'd	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
looked	O
very	O
pale	O
and	O
ghastly	O
;	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Bed	O
;	O
that	O
Gentleman	O
had	O
two	O
Shirts	O
on	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Body	O
warm	O
,	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
ands	O
stiff	O
and	O
cold	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
seemed	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
so	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
perhaps	O
a	O
quarter	O
or	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
Papers	O
lying	O
upon	O
the	O
Table	O
in	O
a	O
Red	O
and	O
white	O
Handkerchief	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
enquired	O
who	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
who	O
he	O
belonged	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
made	O
answer	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
cousin	O
of	O
Mary	O
Robert	O
's	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Mrs	O
Simmerton	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Stranger	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
that	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
look	O
over	O
the	O
Papers	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
know	O
by	O
them	O
who	O
he	O
was	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
Letter	O
directed	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Peter	B-pers
Mott	I-pers
,	O
Merchant	O
,	O
in	O
Leadenball-street	O
:	O
That	O
upon	O
this	O
he	O
order	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
send	O
away	O
immediately	O
and	O
give	O
Notice	O
to	O
his	O
Family	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
two	O
Men	O
,	O
Williams	O
and	O
Hutchinson	O
,	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
go	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
thought	O
they	O
had	O
gone	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
Leather	O
Apron	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Soldier	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
there	O
came	O
up	O
another	O
Woman	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
who	O
brought	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
answered	O
,	O
Moll	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Woman	O
cursed	O
her	O
,	O
an	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
bought	O
her	O
self	O
into	O
a	O
fine	O
Scrape	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
seeing	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
to	O
be	O
dead	O
and	O
nothing	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
home	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
about	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
or	O
two	O
came	O
to	O
enquire	O
of	O
him	O
concerning	O
the	O
Deceased	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Bateman	I-pers
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Drivy	O
living	O
in	O
Shee-Lane	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
a	O
Clock	O
Mrs.	O
Simmerton	O
came	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
her	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
Surprize	O
,	O
saying	O
she	O
was	O
ruin	O
'd	O
and	O
undone	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Man	O
dead	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
.	O
That	O
her	O
Master	O
enquir	O
'd	O
who	O
he	O
was	O
she	O
said	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
a	O
Scarlet	O
Cloak	O
,	O
a	O
Merchant	O
in	O
Leadenball-street	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
asked	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
nor	O
Papers	O
.	O
She	O
replied	O
No	O
;	O
No	O
Money	O
!	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
very	O
strange	O
.	O
That	O
some	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
,	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
send	O
away	O
to	O
give	O
Notice	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
his	O
Effects	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
afterwards	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
8	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
clink	O
'd	O
them	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
back	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
again	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
Mrs.	O
Simmerton	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
That	O
about	O
8	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
she	O
,	O
to	O
satisfy	O
her	O
own	O
Curiosity	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Simmersot	O
's	O
view	O
'd	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
found	O
two	O
shirts	O
on	O
,	O
unbutton	O
'd	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
view	O
'd	O
the	O
Neck	O
and	O
observed	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
blackish	O
Circle	O
round	O
it	O
:	O
that	O
feeling	O
the	O
Body	O
warm	O
,	O
it	O
having	O
been	O
covered	O
in	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
believed	O
he	O
might	O
not	O
be	O
dead	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
he	O
were	O
,	O
she	O
feared	O
they	O
would	O
bring	O
him	O
in	O
stranged	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
answer	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
dead	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Coach	O
.	O
Williams	B-pers
Limmer	I-pers
,	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Mottenx	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
8	O
a	O
Clock	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
the	O
Soldier	O
Edward	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Percival	B-pers
Elutchips	I-pers
came	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Habit	O
was	O
Dead	O
at	O
such	O
a	O
House	O
;	O
that	O
thereupon	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
immediately	O
,	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
he	O
sealed	O
up	O
his	O
Papers	O
and	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
back	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
Family	O
,	O
they	O
sent	O
away	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Bridges	O
,	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
immediately	O
to	O
Simmerton	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Smarts	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
lodging	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Mottem	O
House	O
,	O
was	O
told	O
about	O
8	O
a-Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
by	O
William	O
Limmer	O
that	O
a	O
Soldier	O
and	O
another	O
Man	O
had	O
brought	O
the	O
Message	O
before	O
related	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
enquired	O
of	O
Williams	O
and	O
Hutchinson	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
Story	O
;	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
about	O
him	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
4	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
4	O
Shi	O
and	O
6	O
Peace	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Halfpence	O
,	O
some	O
Papers	O
,	O
but	O
all	O
was	O
safe	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
House	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bridges	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
there	O
;	O
that	O
enquiring	O
how	O
it	O
happen	O
'd	O
Mary	O
Roberts	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
coming	O
with	O
the	O
Deceased	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
against	O
St.	O
Martins	O
Lane	O
be	O
complained	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
well	O
,	O
desired	O
her	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
affrighted	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
used	O
to	O
have	O
fits	O
,	O
lean	O
'd	O
h	O
is	O
Head	O
upon	O
her	O
Shoulder	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Simmertons	O
they	O
got	O
him	O
brought	O
in	O
an	O
put	O
his	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
spoke	O
more	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
viewed	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
found	O
a	O
Circle	O
about	O
Bi	O
Neck	O
and	O
a	O
Bruise	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
sses	O
on	O
the	O
Breast	O
and	O
other	O
parts	O
of	O
the	O
Body	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
plain	O
enough	O
how	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
died	O
:	O
upon	O
which	O
Mrs.	O
Simmerton	O
cryed	O
out	O
,	O
O	O
Lord	O
!	O
I	O
hope	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
do	O
n't	O
suspect	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
had	O
soul	O
play	O
;	O
telling	O
a	O
long	O
Story	O
of	O
her	O
Care	O
and	O
Management	O
,	O
saying	O
the	O
had	O
sent	O
for	O
Two	O
Surgeons	O
;	O
he	O
acquir	O
'd	O
their	O
Names	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
told	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
Winnel	O
,	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Place	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
sent	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
never	O
find	O
him	O
,	O
nor	O
could	O
he	O
ever	O
hear	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
of	O
that	O
Name	O
,	O
That	O
upon	O
some	O
further	O
inquiry	O
Hutchinson	O
stepp	O
'd	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
heard	O
of	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
since	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
White	O
deposed	O
that	O
Elip	O
.	O
Shepherd	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
that	O
Day	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
apprehended	O
,	O
desiring	O
to	O
be	O
entertain	O
'd	O
,	O
telling	O
her	O
she	O
need	O
not	O
be	O
scrupal	O
of	O
entertaining	O
her	O
for	O
she	O
had	O
Gold	O
and	O
Silver	O
enough	O
.	O
Several	O
Persons	O
,	O
and	O
among	O
the	O
rest	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
appear	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Simmerson	O
had	O
been	O
very	O
notorious	O
for	O
keeping	O
a	O
disorderly	O
House	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
frequent	O
Disturbances	O
and	O
crying	O
out	O
Murder	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
pleaded	O
as	O
follows	O
:	O
Mary	O
Roberts	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
passing	O
along	O
near	O
Ludgate	O
the	O
Deceased	O
looked	O
very	O
hard	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
walking	O
before	O
her	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
over	O
against	O
St.	O
Dunstan	O
's	O
Church	O
,	O
halted	O
till	O
she	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
invited	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
Tavern	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
refused	O
;	O
but	O
afterwards	O
waited	O
on	O
her	O
to	O
her	O
Lodgings	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Simmerton	O
's	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
they	O
had	O
2	O
full	O
Pots	O
of	O
Ale	O
and	O
Brandy	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
Buisness	O
at	O
the	O
other	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
St.	O
Clement	O
's	O
Church	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
together	O
to	O
White	O
's	O
Chocolate-House	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
must	O
speak	O
with	O
some	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
lik	O
'd	O
her	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
assure	O
her	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
bilk	O
her	O
,	O
left	O
his	O
Scarlet	O
Cloak	O
and	O
Sword	O
with	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
.	O
(	O
But	O
this	O
was	O
contradicted	O
by	O
the	O
Servant	O
at	O
the	O
Chocolate-House	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
very	O
positive	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
Cloak	O
on	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
it	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
down	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
)	O
That	O
he	O
staying	O
there	O
about	O
an	O
Hour	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
,	O
she	O
then	O
sent	O
the	O
Coachman	O
into	O
the	O
Coffee-house	O
to	O
tell	O
him	O
she	O
liv	O
'd	O
a	O
great	O
way	O
off	O
,	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
Cloak	O
and	O
Sword	O
and	O
discharge	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
home	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
sent	O
her	O
word	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
in	O
a	O
Minute	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
soon	O
after	O
,	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
order	O
'd	O
the	O
Coach	O
to	O
drive	O
to	O
TempleBar	O
,	O
that	O
by	O
the	O
way	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
over	O
against	O
the	O
New	O
Exchange	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
he	O
complained	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
My	O
Dear	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
be	O
affrighted	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
into	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
Dumb	O
Fits	O
which	O
I	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
troubled	O
with	O
;	O
and	O
leaning	O
his	O
Head	O
upon	O
her	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
she	O
supported	O
him	O
till	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
Star-Court	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
sent	O
the	O
Coachman	O
to	O
tell	O
her	O
Landlady	O
to	O
bring	O
a	O
Candle	O
to	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
remained	O
speechless	O
and	O
helpless	O
that	O
they	O
got	O
a	O
Soldier	O
(	O
Edward	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
she	O
said	O
was	O
a	O
Stranger	O
)	O
coming	O
by	O
in	O
the	O
interim	O
of	O
time	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
upon	O
Simmerton's-house	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
the	O
Coachman	O
holding	O
up	O
his	O
Legs	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
they	O
sat	O
him	O
down	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
continued	O
Speechless	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
they	O
carried	O
him	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
put	O
him	O
into	O
Bed	O
,	O
hoping	O
that	O
might	O
bring	O
him	O
to	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
Apothecary	O
and	O
taking	O
a	O
Looking-Glass	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
he	O
breath	O
'd	O
,	O
found	O
he	O
was	O
dead	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
when	O
they	O
knew	O
where	O
to	O
send	O
they	O
sent	O
to	O
give	O
the	O
Family	O
Notice	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
was	O
satisfied	O
with	O
the	O
Account	O
they	O
gave	O
of	O
his	O
Father	O
's	O
Death	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
no	O
counter	O
nor	O
Jury	O
sit	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
promised	O
them	O
all	O
Satisfaction	O
for	O
their	O
Care	O
and	O
Honestly	O
in	O
delivering	O
him	O
all	O
his	O
Father	O
's	O
Papers	O
and	O
Gold	O
Seal	O
worth	O
12	O
l.	O
four	O
Guineas	O
,	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
two	O
Shillings	O
two	O
Pence	O
Halfpenny	O
in	O
Half	O
pence	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
all	O
he	O
had	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Simmerton	I-pers
was	O
much	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Story	O
,	O
adding	O
that	O
she	O
rallied	O
Mary	O
Roberts	O
for	O
bringing	O
Trouble	O
and	O
Scandal	O
upon	O
her	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
thereupon	O
Mary	O
Roberts	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
shame	O
on	O
her	O
for	O
being	O
so	O
cruel	O
to	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
Distress	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
into	O
her	O
own	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
she	O
believ	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
she	O
sent	O
for	O
an	O
Apothecary	O
and	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
all	O
the	O
care	O
she	O
could	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
Notice	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
she	O
could	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
only	O
going	O
by	O
accidentally	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
Stranger	O
,	O
(	O
tho	O
'	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
he	O
lodged	O
there	O
)	O
and	O
was	O
desired	O
to	O
help	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
staid	O
to	O
assist	O
them	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Williams	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
only	O
came	O
there	O
to	O
call	O
her	O
Husband	O
home	O
.	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Shepherd	O
deny	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
lighted	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
and	O
Mary	O
Roberts	O
up	O
Stairs	O
.	O
But	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
all	O
contradicted	O
by	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Evidences	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicated	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Set	O
of	O
China	O
Ware	O
,	O
value	O
30s	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
the	O
23rd	O
of	O
Feb.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
by	O
her	O
Direction	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
they	O
were	O
given	O
her	O
by	O
her	O
master	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
several	O
times	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
lie	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
(	O
Transportation	O
.	O
)	O
Robert	B-pers
Milksop	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Periwig	O
value	O
30s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Parks	I-pers
the	O
22nd	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
passing	O
along	O
Cheapside	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
putting	O
his	O
Hand	O
into	O
his	O
box	O
pull	O
'd	O
it	O
out	O
and	O
dropp	O
'd	O
it	O
(	O
he	O
turning	O
quick	O
upon	O
him	O
)	O
running	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
pursued	O
and	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Needham	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
130	O
Yards	O
of	O
Callicoe	O
value	O
13	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Divers	O
persons	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Odam	I-pers
the	O
20	O
th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Calender	O
,	O
set	O
the	O
Goods	O
off	O
from	O
divers	O
pieces	O
in	O
length	O
2	O
,	O
3	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
Yards	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
divers	O
Persons	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
Sarah	B-pers
Wharton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bennets	I-place
Paules	I-place
wharf	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Bristow	I-pers
the	O
6th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
employed	O
as	O
a	O
Chair-woman	O
carryed	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
alledged	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Wife	O
had	O
bid	O
her	O
carry	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Clear-starchers	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
having	O
occasion	O
for	O
Money	O
did	O
make	O
bold	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
spoon	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Rider	I-pers
,	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
but	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
(	O
Transportation	O
.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Watkinson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Pool	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cookflurt	I-pers
30	O
Yards	O
of	O
Tammey	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
under	O
presence	O
of	O
buying	O
Tammer	O
,	O
stole	O
the	O
peace	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
her	O
Clothes	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
was	O
called	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
Charg	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
it	O
fall	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
go	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.10	O
d	O
(	O
Transportation	O
.	O
)	O
Henry	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hanwel	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
upon	O
two	O
Indictments	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
Linnen	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Strudwick	I-pers
the	O
10th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
second	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
shirt	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
the	O
same	O
day	O
The	O
Prosecutors	O
deposed	O
the	O
Linnen	O
was	O
stollen	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
Yards	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
hanging	O
to	O
dry	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
proving	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
on	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
(	O
Transportation	O
.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Cunningham	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Guineas	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Bendelham	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
Feb.	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Proof	O
that	O
she	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Arthur	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bridle	O
and	O
Saddle	O
,	O
value	O
14s	O
.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Dent	I-pers
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
Feb	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Stable	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
putting	O
them	O
into	O
a	O
Sack	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found-him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
(	O
Transportation	O
.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Mackneal	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Shadwel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
val.8	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Proof	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Rouse	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
she	O
employed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
her	O
Child	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
she	O
found	O
them	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
throwing	O
out	O
Dirt	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s	O
(	O
Transportation	O
.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Mackfarndel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Linnen	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Katherine	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
(	O
Transportation	O
.	O
)	O
Edward	B-pers
Warburton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Can	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cort	I-pers
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Drink	O
in	O
the	O
Tankard	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Can	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
(	O
Transportation	O
.	O
)	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bone	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
10	O
Yards	O
of	O
Hooping	O
for	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
val.5	O
s.	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop-window	O
and	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
she	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
(	O
Transportation	O
.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Danford	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Helens	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
perceived	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
followed	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
(	O
Transportation	O
.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Towels	O
,	O
Napkins	O
and	O
Pewter	O
Platts	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
23	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Innocent	I-pers
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
Mary	O
Herbert	O
being	O
employed	O
to	O
wash	O
Dishes	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
a	O
Tavern	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
Elizabeth	O
Mills	O
.	O
Mary	O
Herbert	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
a	O
poor	O
Woman	O
had	O
carried	O
them	O
away	O
with	O
broken	O
Victuals	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Mills	O
alledg	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Mary	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
,	O
being	O
her	O
Mother	O
,	O
had	O
given	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	O
Herbert	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
(	O
Transportation	O
.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
Squire	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolph	I-place
's	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Linnen	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Summer	I-pers
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
her	O
Apprehension	O
confes	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.10	O
d	O
.	O
(	O
Transportation	O
.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Steel	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Lazarus	B-pers
Bradford	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Gamage	I-pers
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
100	O
Guineas,8	O
half	O
Guineas,3	O
Moidores	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
his	O
Compting-house	O
was	O
broken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
stollen	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Canechair-Maker	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-yard	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
his	O
Servants	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
his	O
Compting-house	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
being	O
bored	O
and	O
cut	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
own	O
Tools	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
fetched	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
stollen	O
;	O
that	O
a	O
Cellar-door	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
supposed	O
was	O
only	O
a	O
Feint	O
that	O
Thieves	O
had	O
gotten	O
in	O
that	O
Way	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
deep	O
Saw-pit	O
that	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
fallen	O
into	O
and	O
broke	O
their	O
Necks	O
:	O
He	O
proved	O
several	O
Circumstances	O
that	O
look	O
'd	O
very	O
suspiciously	O
concerning	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
:	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
fully	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Polson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Maggot	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
apprehended	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
bidding	O
her	O
go	O
in	O
and	O
take	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
seeing	O
no	O
Reason	O
to	O
believe	O
her	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.10	O
d	O
.	O
(	O
Transportation	O
.	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Spear	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Chelsea	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
Lady	O
Henrietta	B-pers
Windham	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Sauce-pan	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Lady	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
gone	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
House	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
at	O
the	O
Cellar	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Sauce-pan	O
stole	O
;	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
offer	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
and	O
attempted	O
to	O
prove	O
he	O
was	O
elsewhere	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
when	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
and	O
the	O
Sauce-pan	O
offered	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
but	O
failed	O
in	O
the	O
Attempt	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
(	O
Death	O
.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Moody	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
val.25	O
s.	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
an	O
Acquaintance	O
of	O
a	O
Lodger	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Trunk	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
the	O
Lodger	O
gave	O
them	O
her	O
to	O
pawn	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
proving	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
(	O
Transportation	O
.	O
)	O
Peter	B-pers
Atyon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
on	O
two	O
indictments	O
;	O
one	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pocket	O
and	O
a	O
Head-dress	O
,	O
val.2	O
s.	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
Street	O
she	O
was	O
thrown	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
pocket	O
pulled	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
torn	O
in	O
pieces	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
confined	O
in	O
the	O
Round-house	O
for	O
another	O
Fact	O
committed	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
.	O
The	O
2d	O
Indictment	O
was	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pocket	O
,	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
from	O
Frances	B-pers
Rowley	I-pers
the	O
same	O
Night	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
running	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
and	O
caught	O
him	O
immediately	O
.	O
The	O
Facts	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
(	O
Death	O
.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Culeden	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Enfield	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
27	O
Holland	O
Frocks	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
and	O
4	O
Pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
there	O
was	O
two	O
Quarrels	O
of	O
Glass	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Laundry-Window	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
stollen	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Walden	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
at	O
Enfield	B-place
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servants	O
Ironing	O
Clothes	O
,	O
and	O
resolved	O
to	O
rob	O
that	O
House	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
a	O
Ladder	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Yard	O
set	O
up	O
against	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
where	O
Culeden	O
got	O
in	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
out	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
carried	O
and	O
sold	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Rowel	I-pers
for	O
3	O
l.10	O
s.	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
bid	O
them	O
go	O
oftner	O
and	O
bring	O
her	O
more	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
had	O
before	O
made	O
himself	O
at	O
Evidence	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
(	O
Death	O
.	O
)	O
Jane	B-pers
Revel	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
as	O
an	O
Accessory	O
in	O
buying	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
he	O
stole	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
plainly	O
proved	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
being	O
notoriously	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
likewise	O
.	O
(	O
Transportation	O
.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	I-pers
the	I-pers
quondan	I-pers
Hangman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
the	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
William	I-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Evidence	O
,	O
Alexander	B-pers
Dufey	I-pers
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
over	O
Bunhill-fields	B-place
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
March	O
at	O
bout	O
10	O
a-Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
Man	O
's	O
Voice	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
Groan	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
Man	O
say	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
mn	O
you	O
for	O
a	O
Bitch	O
,	O
why	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
take	O
it	O
in	O
your	O
Field	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
?	O
if	O
you	O
wo	O
n't	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
I	O
'll	O
rip	O
you	O
up	O
.	O
And	O
immediately	O
after	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
mn	O
you	O
Bitch	O
,	O
where	O
is	O
your	O
Money	O
?	O
give	O
me	O
your	O
Money	O
.	O
And	O
presently	O
coming	O
up	O
with	O
another	O
Man	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
hear	O
the	O
Groaning	O
?	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
he	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
seem	O
'd	O
not	O
willing	O
to	O
venture	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
lend	O
me	O
your	O
Stick	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
stood	O
ready	O
to	O
assist	O
him	O
upon	O
occasion	O
.	O
That	O
going	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Woman	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
busy	O
about	O
her	O
.	O
That	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
near	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
mn	O
you	O
what	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
He	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
A	O
Man	O
.	O
He	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
mn	O
you	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
?	O
He	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
doing	O
there	O
.	O
He	O
reply	O
'd	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
but	O
a	O
Drunken	O
Women	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
Help	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
People	O
came	O
by	O
with	O
a	O
Lanthorn	O
and	O
Candle	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
lay	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
odd	O
Posture	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
Condition	O
,	O
with	O
her	O
Coats	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
Belly	O
,	O
Streams	O
of	O
Blood	O
issuing	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Eyes	O
and	O
Mouth	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
called	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
speak	O
,	O
but	O
made	O
a	O
gagling	O
Noise	O
as	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
something	O
in	O
her	O
Mouth	O
,	O
which	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
Blood	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
from	O
Work	O
over	O
Bunbil-fields	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
groaning	O
,	O
and	O
stooping	O
down	O
towards	O
the	O
Ground	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Groaning	O
;	O
he	O
replied	O
,	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
refused	O
,	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
stand	O
by	O
me	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
within	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
Yards	O
of	O
the	O
Place	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
with	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
the	O
Woman	O
's	O
Coats	O
were	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
Belly	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
D	O
-	O
mn	O
you	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
?	O
that	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
replied	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
nothing	O
but	O
a	O
Drunken	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
lifted	O
up	O
her	O
Foot	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Man	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
be	O
enquir	O
'd	O
of	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
met	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
first	O
at	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
then	O
at	O
a	O
Brandy-shop	O
,	O
another	O
time	O
at	O
the	O
Burying-Ground	O
Gate	O
;	O
so	O
they	O
seized	O
him	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
;	O
his	O
Hands	O
Coat	O
and	O
Apron	O
were	O
all	O
Bloody	O
;	O
he	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Woman	O
was	O
very	O
Bloody	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
Eyes	O
beat	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Head	O
;	O
be	O
added	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
damning	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
Bitch	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
Voice	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
two	O
former	O
Evidences	O
brought	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
all	O
over	O
very	O
Bloody	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
gone	O
away	O
;	O
saying	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
nothing	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Thief	O
and	O
a	O
Rogue	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
sit	O
down	O
he	O
would	O
knock	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
or	O
throw	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Fire	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
very	O
dark	O
the	O
Evidences	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Place	O
;	O
and	O
be	O
followed	O
in	O
the	O
Field	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
any	O
Body	O
was	O
in	O
Distress	O
they	O
were	O
come	O
to	O
assist	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Answer	O
made	O
;	O
but	O
a	O
Dog	O
he	O
had	O
barking	O
about	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
gave	O
them	O
notice	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
her	O
.	O
That	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
they	O
found	O
her	O
lying	O
in	O
a	O
sad	O
Condition	O
,	O
as	O
had	O
been	O
before	O
described	O
;	O
and	O
besides	O
some	O
of	O
her	O
Teeth	O
knock	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
shown	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
Arms	O
broke	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
got	O
her	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
some	O
Women	O
to	O
hold	O
her	O
forwards	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
was	O
choak	O
'd	O
with	O
Clots	O
of	O
Blood	O
in	O
her	O
Mouth	O
and	O
Throat	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
speak	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
he	O
sent	O
her	O
to	O
a	O
Nurse	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
Care	O
of	O
.	O
The	O
Nurse	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Condition	O
before	O
described	O
,	O
adding	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
speak	O
a	O
Word	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
she	O
lived	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
tho	O
'	O
you	O
ca	O
n't	O
speak	O
you	O
can	O
hear	O
,	O
make	O
some	O
Signs	O
how	O
you	O
came	O
by	O
your	O
Hurt	O
:	O
that	O
she	O
lifted	O
up	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
Hanes	O
,	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
stir	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
Head	O
,	O
Throat	O
and	O
Belly	O
,	O
signifying	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
Hurt	O
in	O
those	O
Parts	O
:	O
that	O
in	O
this	O
miserable	O
Condition	O
she	O
languished	O
4	O
Days	O
and	O
then	O
Died	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Goodman	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
he	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
sad	O
Condition	O
,	O
a	O
Wound	O
above	O
one	O
Eye	O
,	O
her	O
Eye	O
started	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Head	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
depressed	O
and	O
put	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
another	O
Wound	O
near	O
her	O
Nose	O
,	O
her	O
Throat	O
very	O
much	O
bruised	O
,	O
her	O
Scalp	O
of	O
her	O
Head	O
so	O
bruised	O
and	O
contused	O
he	O
had	O
scarce	O
ever	O
seen	O
the	O
like	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
upper	O
part	O
of	O
her	O
Womb	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
core	O
and	O
larated	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
Wounds	O
were	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
her	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
Woman	O
's	O
Husband	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Wife	O
used	O
to	O
sent	O
Cakes	O
and	O
Gingerbread	O
about	O
the	O
Streets	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
that	O
Morning	O
very	O
well	O
about	O
10	O
a-Clock	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Son	O
came	O
home	O
about	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
having	O
the	O
Key	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
sat	O
down	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
waiting	O
her	O
coming	O
home	O
and	O
fell	O
asleep	O
,	O
but	O
waking	O
and	O
she	O
not	O
being	O
come	O
home	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
in	O
Cheapside	O
(	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Watch-man	O
)	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
her	O
till	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
Accident	O
in	O
Bun	O
hill	O
fields	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
he	O
knew	O
anything	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Holloway-lane	O
he	O
saw	O
three	O
Men	O
crossing	O
the	O
Field	O
,	O
to	O
Chequer-Alley	O
,	O
found	O
something	O
lie	O
in	O
his	O
way	O
,	O
kick	O
'd	O
at	O
it	O
with	O
his	O
Foot	O
;	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
lifted	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
stand	O
upon	O
her	O
Legs	O
;	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
doing	O
this	O
was	O
apprehended	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Jury	O
were	O
so	O
well	O
satisfied	O
with	O
the	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
readily	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Murther	O
.	O
(	O
Death	O
.	O
)	O
Charles	B-pers
Plummer	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Coach	O
seat	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Man	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Coach-seat	O
was	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
turning	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
a	O
person	O
unknown	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Drink	O
to	O
leave	O
it	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
(	O
Transportation	O
.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
Black	O
)	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Copper	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Master	O
of	O
the	O
Ship	O
deposed	O
it	O
was	O
stole	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
ship	O
and	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Burrough	O
,	O
stopp	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
Brasier	O
,	O
being	O
offered	O
to	O
Sale	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
Sailor	O
at	O
Ratcliff	O
Cross	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
(	O
Death	O
.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Iron	O
:	O
belonging	O
to	O
a	O
Dray	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
from	O
Joseph	B-pers
Amsworth	I-pers
,	O
the	O
2	O
d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
(	O
Transportation	O
.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Giles	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Katharine	B-pers
Cason	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pocket	O
and	O
a	O
Snuffbox	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
coming	O
along	O
Drury	B-place
Lane	I-place
a	O
Person	O
stuck	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
affrighted	O
clapped	O
her	O
Hand	O
on	O
her	O
Watch	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
interim	O
he	O
pulled	O
off	O
her	O
Pocket	O
with	O
that	O
Violence	O
,	O
she	O
thought	O
he	O
pulled	O
off	O
her	O
Petticoat	O
also	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
going	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
to	O
stop	O
it	O
if	O
offered	O
to	O
pawn	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Note	O
for	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
,	O
a	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
been	O
carried	O
thither	O
for	O
another	O
Fact	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
Snuff	O
box	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
about	O
to	O
send	O
it	O
away	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Consorts	O
that	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Parson	O
having	O
lost	O
his	O
Way	O
,	O
he	O
cried	O
out	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
he	O
followed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
away	O
the	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Parson	O
had	O
it	O
:	O
but	O
he	O
pursued	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
cut	O
at	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
large	O
knife	O
and	O
cut	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
siezed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
threaten	O
'd	O
he	O
'd	O
shoot	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
:	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
(	O
Death	O
.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Ipsley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Rickets	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Eling	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
Mary	O
Ipsley	O
's	O
House	O
four	O
Days	O
before	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
there	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
for	O
her	O
Diet	O
and	O
Lodging	O
;	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
before	O
Christmass-Day	O
the	O
Deceased	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
Mistress	O
's	O
House	O
desiring	O
Lodging	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
called	O
for	O
some	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
eat	O
some	O
Bread	O
and	O
Cheese	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
that	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
she	O
heard	O
her	O
cry	O
out	O
for	O
Help	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
but	O
Mary	O
Ipsley	O
would	O
not	O
suffer	O
her	O
,	O
threatning	O
she	O
would	O
knock	O
out	O
her	O
Brains	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Street	O
door	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
lock	O
'd	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
;	O
that	O
her	O
Mistress	O
bidding	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
a	O
Candle	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
up	O
another	O
paid	O
of	O
Stairs	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
heard	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Woman	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
nor	O
ever	O
saw	O
her	O
any	O
more	O
till	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
.	O
She	O
added	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday-night	O
2	O
Men	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
whole	O
Names	O
was	O
Thomas	B-pers
English	I-pers
,	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
where	O
the	O
Woman	O
lay	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
Corps	O
;	O
that	O
Thomas	O
English	O
went	O
away	O
and	O
came	O
no	O
more	O
till	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Coffin	O
set	O
below	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
Thomas	O
English	O
brought	O
down	O
a	O
dead	O
Woman	O
quite	O
naked	O
as	O
ever	O
she	O
was	O
born	O
:	O
that	O
she	O
looked	O
in	O
the	O
Coffin	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Woman	O
lying	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Child	O
laid	O
in	O
her	O
Arms	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Cart	O
came	O
,	O
amdthe	O
Coffin	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
Cart	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
its	O
being	O
carried	O
to	O
be	O
buried	O
at	O
Eling	O
;	O
that	O
her	O
Mistress	O
would	O
have	O
Thomas	O
English	O
have	O
drove	O
the	O
Cart	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
Mary	O
Ipsley	O
hired	O
her	O
Cart	O
,	O
giving	O
her	O
2	O
s.	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
Corps	O
to	O
Eling	O
;	O
that	O
a	O
Boy	O
drove	O
the	O
Cart	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
by	O
the	O
way	O
the	O
Horse	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
Mary	O
Ipsley	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
:	O
she	O
replied	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
afraid	O
the	O
Coffin	O
would	O
burst	O
open	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
answered	O
her	O
again	O
,	O
suppose	O
it	O
had	O
,	O
what	O
then	O
?	O
she	O
hoped	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
buried	O
the	O
Corps	O
naked	O
:	O
she	O
replied	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
buried	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
white	O
Mantle	O
.	O
She	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Woman	O
who	O
died	O
in	O
a	O
Convulsion-Fit	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
said	O
nothing	O
of	O
a	O
Child	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Tille	O
,	O
the	O
Curate	O
of	O
Eling	O
,	O
deposed	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
Clerk	O
Orders	O
that	O
when	O
any	O
Persons	O
were	O
to	O
be	O
buried	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
know	O
of	O
it	O
before	O
hand	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
Children	O
to	O
be	O
buried	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
invited	O
to	O
ne	O
that	O
Day	O
with	O
the	O
Church	O
Warden	O
of	O
Brentford	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
know	O
when	O
they	O
would	O
be	O
ready	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
there	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
they	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Overseer	O
of	O
Brentford	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
dined	O
there	O
also	O
;	O
that	O
after	O
Dinner	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Eling	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Children	O
being	O
brought	O
there	O
to	O
be	O
buried	O
,	O
he	O
looked	O
behind	O
him	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
Coffin	O
in	O
a	O
Cart	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
asked	O
the	O
Clerk	O
from	O
whence	O
it	O
came	O
:	O
he	O
answered	O
,	O
from	O
Tumble-down	O
Dick	O
's	O
at	O
Brentford	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
asked	O
the	O
Clerk	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Grave	O
ready	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
answered	O
him	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
almost	O
ready	O
;	O
he	O
enquired	O
if	O
the	O
had	O
gone	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
answered	O
No	O
.	O
he	O
then	O
enquired	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
who	O
the	O
Person	O
to	O
be	O
buried	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
answered	O
Wife	O
that	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
the	O
last	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
a	O
very	O
violent	O
Fit	O
,	O
and	O
continued	O
in	O
it	O
till	O
she	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
odd	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
acquianted	O
the	O
Church-warden	O
or	O
Overseen	O
of	O
the	O
Poor	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
The	O
answered	O
she	O
had	O
:	O
he	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
sure	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
fact	O
she	O
had	O
acquainted	O
them	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
when	O
,	O
she	O
replied	O
about	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Hours	O
ago	O
:	O
he	O
asked	O
her	O
again	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
she	O
had	O
,	O
she	O
then	O
snapped	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
I	O
tell	O
you	O
so	O
?	O
That	O
then	O
he	O
answered	O
her	O
it	O
was	O
false	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
for	O
4	O
Hours	O
at	O
the	O
Church-warden	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
was	O
at	O
Dinner	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Overseen	O
was	O
at	O
Dinner	O
with	O
him	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
so	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
heard	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
made	O
him	O
no	O
Answer	O
He	O
then	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
much	O
suspect	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
see	O
the	O
Corps	O
:	O
she	O
replied	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
can	O
you	O
answer	O
that	O
?	O
he	O
made	O
answer	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
whether	O
I	O
can	O
or	O
no	O
,	O
but	O
however	O
I	O
will	O
try	O
for	O
once	O
:	O
With	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
and	O
whispered	O
him	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Ear	O
,	O
she	O
died	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
Distemper	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
all	O
over	O
full	O
of	O
Plague	O
Spots	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
replied	O
,	O
let	O
it	O
be	O
Pox	O
or	O
Plague	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
fear	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
of	O
his	O
Duty	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
God	O
he	O
would	O
see	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
the	O
Truth	O
she	O
has	O
no	O
Shroud	O
on	O
:	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
replied	O
,	O
the	O
more	O
Breast	O
you	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
Tools	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
Coffin	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
what	O
Woman	O
were	O
present	O
to	O
inspect	O
the	O
Corps	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
that	O
the	O
Men	O
would	O
withdraw	O
at	O
a	O
distance	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
himself	O
stood	O
at	O
some	O
distance	O
from	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
observed	O
how	O
Mary	O
Ipsley	O
behaved	O
her	O
self	O
:	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
Coffin	O
was	O
railed	O
at	O
the	O
Head	O
and	O
about	O
half	O
open	O
,	O
she	O
ran	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
put	O
her	O
Hand	O
into	O
the	O
Coffin	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Corps	O
hold	O
about	O
the	O
Head	O
or	O
Neck	O
and	O
shook	O
it	O
:	O
he	O
asked	O
what	O
that	O
was	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
answered	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
purge	O
and	O
ink	O
them	O
all	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
.	O
That	O
after	O
the	O
Women	O
had	O
viewed	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
informed	O
that	O
the	O
Corps	O
was	O
indeed	O
stark	O
Naked	O
,	O
as	O
when	O
born	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
saw	O
Marks	O
of	O
Violence	O
and	O
barbarous	O
Usage	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
also	O
a	O
young	O
Child	O
in	O
the	O
Coffin	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Clerk	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
3	O
Hours	O
before	O
the	O
Corps	O
came	O
,	O
a	O
Woman	O
came	O
from	O
Tumble	O
down	O
Dick	O
's	O
at	O
Brentford	O
,	O
and	O
order	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Grave	O
for	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Pensioner	O
's	O
Wife	O
who	O
had	O
died	O
at	O
her	O
Mistress	O
's	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
her	O
why	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
send	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
Bell	O
ring	O
,	O
the	O
Woman	O
answered	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
made	O
the	O
Grave	O
and	O
the	O
Corps	O
was	O
brought	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Tiller	O
talking	O
with	O
him	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
strange	O
hurry	O
of	O
Mind	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
taken	O
with	O
a	O
Trembling	O
and	O
so	O
strange	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
what	O
is	O
the	O
atter	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
wish	O
this	O
Woman	O
is	O
not	O
murdered	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
have	O
the	O
Coffin	O
opened	O
before	O
I	O
bury	O
her	O
;	O
That	O
when	O
the	O
Minister	O
would	O
have	O
the	O
Coffin	O
opened	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
the	O
Plague	O
and	O
flunk	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
so	O
nasty	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
fit	O
to	O
be	O
seen	O
.	O
The	O
Clerk	O
went	O
on	O
and	O
confirmed	O
what	O
the	O
Minister	O
had	O
before	O
related	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
The	O
she	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Persons	O
desired	O
to	O
view	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
found	O
no	O
Plague	O
Spots	O
as	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
said	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
black	O
Place	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
Lock	O
of	O
Hair	O
all	O
bloody	O
and	O
clotted	O
,	O
by	O
her	O
Ear	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Sco	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Tillet	O
asking	O
Mary	O
Ipsley	O
when	O
the	O
Woman	O
died	O
,	O
she	O
answered	O
,	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
:	O
then	O
he	O
asked	O
her	O
why	O
she	O
buried	O
it	O
so	O
soon	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
replied	O
she	O
died	O
of	O
the	O
Pox	O
and	O
the	O
Plague	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
stank	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
bear	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
:	O
that	O
they	O
afterwards	O
opened	O
the	O
Coffin	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	O
Ipsley	O
thrust	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
as	O
had	O
been	O
before	O
related	O
:	O
that	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Corps	O
naked	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Child	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
Coffin	O
,	O
lying	O
under	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Feet	O
,	O
one	O
side	O
of	O
her	O
Head	O
was	O
bruised	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Hair	O
was	O
matted	O
with	O
Blood	O
,	O
and	O
Blood	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
one	O
Ear	O
and	O
one	O
Nostril	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
received	O
much	O
more	O
Damage	O
than	O
is	O
usual	O
below	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
not	O
ragged	O
but	O
seemed	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
cut	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
an	O
Inch	O
or	O
more	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Spots	O
on	O
the	O
Woman	O
's	O
Body	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
clean	O
Corps	O
from	O
head	O
to	O
foot	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Call	O
over	O
the	O
Face	O
of	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Women	O
pulled	O
it	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Nose	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
flat	O
,	O
even	O
with	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
only	O
two	O
Nostrils	O
did	O
appear	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
also	O
confirmed	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Floyd	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Prestons	O
,	O
a	O
Midwise	O
,	O
deposed	O
the	O
same	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
Women	O
,	O
adding	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Blood	O
stood	O
in	O
the	O
Left	O
Ear	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
ready	O
to	O
run	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
places	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
her	O
Mouth	O
looked	O
as	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
hurt	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
her	O
Shoulder	O
to	O
her	O
Elbow	O
as	O
if	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
hard	O
Gripes	O
,	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
Bruise	O
on	O
the	O
Right	O
side	O
of	O
her	O
Belly	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
such	O
a	O
Vacancy	O
that	O
no	O
Child	O
ever	O
made	O
in	O
a	O
Woman	O
by	O
its	O
Birth	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Call	O
being	O
taken	O
from	O
over	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
Face	O
,	O
the	O
Nose	O
was	O
flat	O
,	O
the	O
Nostrils	O
of	O
the	O
Child	O
Bloody	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Blood	O
flew	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
Mouth	O
in	O
a	O
Bladder	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Bruise	O
on	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
Head	O
and	O
the	O
right	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Neck	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
at	O
its	O
full	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
believe	O
that	O
Life	O
of	O
the	O
Woman	O
and	O
Child	O
went	O
out	O
by	O
the	O
common	O
Course	O
of	O
Nature	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Banister	O
confirmed	O
what	O
the	O
other	O
Evidences	O
had	O
said	O
;	O
and	O
deposed	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
Opinion	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
been	O
cut	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
no	O
Woman	O
ever	O
received	O
so	O
much	O
Damage	O
,	O
or	O
could	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Birth	O
of	O
a	O
Child	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
had	O
no	O
Nose	O
only	O
Nostrils	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
as	O
flat	O
as	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Levings	O
,	O
another	O
Midwife	O
,	O
also	O
confirmed	O
what	O
the	O
other	O
Evidences	O
had	O
said	O
;	O
and	O
added	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
belived	O
the	O
Woman	O
was	O
ded	O
dry	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
never	O
purged	O
in	O
the	O
Coffin	O
first	O
nor	O
last	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Round	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
having	O
viewed	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
of	O
opinion	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
barbarously	O
used	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
Mary	O
Ipsley	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
declare	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
and	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
that	O
Barbarity	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
save	O
others	O
and	O
hang	O
her	O
self	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
did	O
believe	O
somebody	O
deserved	O
to	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
made	O
answer	O
,	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
Woman	O
setting	O
at	O
some	O
distance	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
whom	O
she	O
called	O
Nurse	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
what	O
was	O
done	O
she	O
did	O
.	O
The	O
Woman	O
made	O
answer	O
,	O
Ay	O
,	O
Landlady	O
,	O
but	O
you	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
come	O
to	O
no	O
Trouble	O
.	O
That	O
Mary	O
Ipsley	O
replied	O
,	O
Ay	O
,	O
Girl	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
no	O
more	O
shall	O
you	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gilbert	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
desired	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
eight	O
Days	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
buried	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
as	O
has	O
been	O
before	O
testified	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Restum	O
was	O
much	O
delacerated	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
opened	O
the	O
Body	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
a	O
clean	O
found	O
Body	O
.	O
Mary	O
Ipsley	O
pleaded	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
before	O
Christmas-day	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
poor	O
Condition	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
she	O
might	O
lodge	O
there	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
refused	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
,	O
till	O
by	O
the	O
Persuasion	O
of	O
some	O
Men	O
who	O
were	O
drinking	O
there	O
she	O
did	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
London	O
early	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
;	O
that	O
about	O
9	O
a	O
Clock	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
she	O
sent	O
to	O
call	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
answer	O
was	O
made	O
and	O
wondering	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
see	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
Fit	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
got	O
Geneva	O
and	O
robbed	O
her	O
Temples	O
,	O
got	O
Sack	O
and	O
Black	O
Cherry	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Teeth	O
being	O
set	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
it	O
down	O
her	O
Throat	O
;	O
that	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
she	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
little	O
recovered	O
by	O
lying	O
still	O
,	O
but	O
soom	O
after	O
she	O
fell	O
into	O
another	O
Fit	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
continued	O
all	O
Day	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
on	O
Thursday	O
she	O
fell	O
into	O
her	O
Fits	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
continued	O
in	O
and	O
out	O
of	O
them	O
all	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
Friday	O
and	O
Saturday	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
never	O
heard	O
her	O
speak	O
from	O
the	O
Night	O
she	O
came	O
till	O
she	O
died	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
a	O
Woman	O
that	O
came	O
with	O
her	O
from	O
Windsor	O
,	O
and	O
tended	O
her	O
as	O
a	O
Nurse	O
,	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
to	O
see	O
how	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
down	O
in	O
a	O
Fright	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
Labour	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
up	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
both	O
she	O
and	O
the	O
Child	O
were	O
Dead	O
,	O
the	O
Child	O
being	O
born	O
dead	O
.	O
She	O
also	O
called	O
Persons	O
who	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
invalidate	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
her	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
loose	O
Person	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
the	O
Overseen	O
to	O
like	O
she	O
had	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
that	O
was	O
taken	O
ill	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
of	O
Convulsion	O
Fits	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
apply	O
her	O
self	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
Coffin	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
called	O
also	O
a	O
Midwife	O
and	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
who	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
account	O
for	O
the	O
extraordinary	O
Dilaorration	O
,	O
supposing	O
it	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
cut	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
possible	O
to	O
be	O
torn	O
by	O
the	O
strength	O
of	O
the	O
Convulsions	O
(	O
though	O
this	O
was	O
strenously	O
opposed	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
strong	O
Reasons	O
,	O
)	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
had	O
been	O
dead	O
three	O
Days	O
before	O
the	O
Birth	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
that	O
affected	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Rickets	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Mary	O
Ipsley	O
,	O
though	O
strong	O
,	O
being	O
but	O
presumptive	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Veal	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Widgeon	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
Holland	O
and	O
Damask	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
l	O
,	O
Handkerchiefs	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
value	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Shop	O
was	O
broken	O
open	O
the	O
Day	O
above	O
mentioned	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
knew	O
not	O
who	O
did	O
it	O
,	O
till	O
she	O
received	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
one	O
Ash	O
.	O
Ash	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
himself	O
,	O
one	O
Joseph	B-pers
Dud-	I-pers
Me	O
-	O
Daniel	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
were	O
together	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
House	O
at	O
the	O
Hermitage-Bridge	B-place
,	O
and	O
they	O
resolv	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
a	O
Chissel	O
cook	O
cown	O
the	O
Window	O
Shutters	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
handed	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
rest	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
carried	O
them	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
one	O
Richard	B-pers
Pallard	I-pers
to	O
Harro	O
in	O
Whine	O
Chappel	O
for	O
9	O
l.	O
and	O
shared	O
the	O
Money	O
among	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
came	O
to	O
36	O
sie	O
.	O
a	O
piece	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
or	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
knowing	O
the	O
Evidence	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
replied	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
3	O
Years	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
4	O
Burglaries	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
but	O
the	O
very	O
last	O
session	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
(	O
Death	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Hooper	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
17	O
yards	O
of	O
Blue	O
and	O
White	O
Linnen	O
value	O
30	O
s	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
,	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
Deborah	B-pers
Stent	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
knowing	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Shop	O
with	O
one	O
Peg	B-pers
Hardcastle	I-pers
to	O
buy	O
Linnen	O
for	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Linnen	O
.	O
Peg	O
Hardcastle	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
sent	O
,	O
by	O
Deborah	B-pers
Stent	I-pers
on	O
purpose	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
waited	O
near	O
the	O
Shop	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
out	O
they	O
put	O
the	O
Goods	O
into	O
her	O
Lap	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
afterwards	O
carried	O
to	O
Deborah	O
Stent	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
Hooper	O
and	O
Jones	O
received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
and	O
Deborah	O
Stent	O
being	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Old	O
Offender	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
as	O
an	O
Accessary	O
,	O
(	O
Transportation	O
)	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Christopher	I-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
having	O
in	O
her	O
Possession	O
20	O
pieces	O
made	O
of	O
Tin	O
,	O
Copper	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
base	O
Metal	O
in	O
the	O
likeness	O
of	O
the	O
Current	O
Coin	O
of	O
the	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
Counterfeit	O
mark	O
with	O
Grainings	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Katherine	B-pers
Maclear	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
having	O
formerly	O
been	O
concerned	O
in	O
putting	O
off	O
Counterfeit	O
Money	O
,	O
did	O
e	O
to	O
deal	O
with	O
Abigail	B-pers
Newlead	I-pers
,	O
but	O
she	O
being	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
who	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
wanted	O
,	O
telling	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
wanted	O
Counterfeit	O
Money	O
She	O
could	O
supply	O
her	O
,	O
of	O
it	O
were	O
a	O
Cart	O
Load	O
:	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
after	O
that	O
but	O
of	O
her	O
at	O
divers	O
times	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
she	O
paid	O
her	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
l.	O
for	O
,	O
giving	O
her	O
2d	O
per	O
Shilling	O
,	O
and	O
5d	O
per	O
half	O
Crown	O
.	O
That	O
one	O
time	O
she	O
showed	O
her	O
36	O
ba	O
Shillings	O
battered	O
and	O
offered	O
her	O
them	O
for	O
a	O
penny	O
per	O
piece	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
at	O
another	O
time	O
she	O
went	O
and	O
bought	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
came	O
to	O
4	O
Shillings	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
carried	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
Doors	O
and	O
clipped	O
them	O
with	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Scissors	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
made	O
the	O
Grainings	O
by	O
fillsing	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
Edge	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
other	O
Evidences	O
very	O
full	O
and	O
plain	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
High	O
Treason	O
.	O
(	O
to	O
be	O
Burnt	O
)	O
Margaret	B-pers
(	I-pers
the	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Thomas	I-pers
)	I-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Susannah	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
7	O
Guineas	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
Feb.	O
last	O
.	O
Susannah	O
Anderson	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
with	O
a	O
Basket	O
of	O
Pyes	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
they	O
enticed	O
her	O
to	O
play	O
at	O
Cards	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
won	O
Money	O
of	O
them	O
she	O
plaid	O
of	O
Pyes	O
that	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
play	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
took	O
her	O
Basket	O
of	O
Pyes	O
and	O
locked	O
it	O
up	O
from	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
pulling	O
out	O
a	O
Box	O
wherein	O
were	O
7	O
Guineas	O
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
West	I-pers
struck	O
the	O
Box	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Hand	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
pick	O
'd	O
up	O
her	O
Guineas	O
,	O
afterwards	O
beat	O
her	O
and	O
turn	O
'd	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
alledged	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
keeping	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
a	O
Basket	O
of	O
Pyes	O
to	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
some	O
Men	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
very	O
pressing	O
upon	O
them	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Pyes	O
,	O
pleading	O
Povery	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
two	O
Children	O
to	O
maintain	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Money	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
refused	O
:	O
that	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
play	O
a	O
Game	O
at	O
AFours	O
with	O
them	O
for	O
a	O
Shillings	O
worth	O
;	O
that	O
at	O
last	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
did	O
play	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
won	O
a	O
3	O
Shillings	O
worth	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
sat	O
there	O
smoaking	O
and	O
Drinking	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
free	O
with	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Men	O
,	O
and	O
same	O
Lascious	O
actions	O
pass	O
'd	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
afterwards	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
to	O
the	O
Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
back	O
she	O
pretended	O
no	O
miss	O
a	O
Shillings	O
worth	O
of	O
Cheescakes	O
;	O
and	O
bacause	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Shilling	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
better	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
would	O
make	O
it	O
cost	O
her	O
ten	O
;	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
make	O
any	O
mention	O
of	O
having	O
lost	O
7	O
Guineas	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
several	O
Evidences	O
,	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
the	O
Man	O
with	O
whom	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
so	O
free	O
deposed	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
return	O
'd	O
from	O
the	O
Tavern	O
she	O
did	O
in	O
her	O
Rage	O
Ke	O
up	O
a	O
Broom-stick	O
and	O
beat	O
Susannah	O
Anderson	O
for	O
carrying	O
her	O
Husband	O
to	O
a	O
Bawdy-House	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
as	O
much	O
Right	O
to	O
him	O
as	O
she	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
divers	O
credible	O
Performs	O
appeared	O
in	O
behalf	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Katherine	B-pers
Lackey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Linnen	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Stead	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
(	O
Transportation	O
)	O
Margaret	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
val.22	O
s.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Goss	I-pers
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
(	O
Transportation	O
)	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Speed	I-pers
and	O
Rice	B-pers
Speed	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
upon	O
Benjamin	O
Speed	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
,	O
but	O
Price	O
Speed	O
acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
of	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
14	O
s.	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
at	O
her	O
Devotions	O
at	O
the	O
Sicilian	B-place
Ambassador	I-place
's	I-place
Chapel	I-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
picked	O
her	O
Pocket	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
him	O
immediately	O
apprehended	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
(	O
Death	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Hutchins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
val.15	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dry	I-pers
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
met	O
on	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
dropp	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
about	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
produced	O
2	O
Women	O
who	O
deposed	O
he	O
was	O
drinking	O
with	O
them	O
from	O
11	O
in	O
the	O
Forenoon	O
till	O
6	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
house	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
put	O
him	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
drunk	O
.	O
However	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
believing	O
them	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
(	O
Transp	O
.	O
)	O
Ezra	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
in	O
drinking	O
the	O
Pretender	O
's	O
Health	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
King	O
James	O
IIId	O
.	O
The	O
Evidences	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
were	O
3	O
Soldiers	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
being	O
drinking	O
in	O
a	O
Cellar	O
near	O
Charing-Cross	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
who	O
amidst	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Swearing	O
and	O
Cursing	O
,	O
and	O
disrespectful	O
Words	O
of	O
King	O
George	O
,	O
told	O
them	O
he	O
wore	O
better	O
Cloth	O
than	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Soldiers	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
up	O
the	O
Pot	O
said	O
,	O
Here	O
is	O
a	O
Health	O
to	O
King	O
James	O
the	O
IIId	O
.	O
And	O
they	O
finding	O
Fault	O
with	O
his	O
proceedings	O
,	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
fresh	O
Pot	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
in	O
spight	O
of	O
you	O
,	O
Here	O
is	O
a	O
Health	O
to	O
King	O
James	O
the	O
IIId	O
,	O
God	O
bless	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
told	O
him	O
they	O
should	O
be	O
obliged	O
to	O
secure	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
them	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
value	O
them	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
Health	O
to	O
King	O
James	O
the	O
IIId	O
,	O
God	O
bless	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
Fined	O
20	O
Marks	O
and	O
6	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Pardie	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Hartly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hammersmith	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
divers	O
brass	O
Ware	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
was	O
broken	O
open	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
stollen	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
being	O
stopped	O
by	O
the	O
Watch	O
early	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
(	O
Death	O
.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Haynes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Katharine	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Fibb	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
was	O
broken	O
open	O
a	O
Hole	O
being	O
made	O
through	O
the	O
Boards	O
under	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
by	O
the	O
Watch	O
getting	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Hole	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
espying	O
them	O
,	O
sneaked	O
in	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
bundled	O
up	O
ready	O
to	O
carry	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
(	O
Death	O
)	O
Charles	B-pers
Pardie	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
for	O
privately	O
taking,1	O
Pocket,4	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
things	O
from	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Wilkins	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
they	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
knock	O
down	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
pull	O
off	O
her	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Master	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
(	O
Death	O
)	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Ann	B-pers
Pocock	I-pers
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Pocket,5	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
and	O
same	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
Breadstreet	B-place
about	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
she	O
was	O
assaulted	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
pulled	O
off	O
her	O
Pocket	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
immediately	O
seized	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
(	O
Death	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hoster	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Quilt	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Green	I-pers
:	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
(	O
Transportation	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Burridge	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Martha	B-pers
Moor	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Pocket	O
,	O
a	O
Snuff-box	O
val.30	O
s.	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
French-Pistol	O
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
(	O
Death	O
)	O
Edward	B-pers
Potter	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
in	O
stealing	O
Copper	O
,	O
val.5	O
l.	O
from	O
the	O
Freehold	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Galworb	I-pers
,	O
the	O
...	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Copper	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Brewhouse	O
at	O
Enfield	O
and	O
was	O
seized	O
Persons	O
near	B-place
Shoulder	I-place
of	I-place
Mutton	I-place
Fields	I-place
John	B-pers
Walden	I-pers
...	O
John	O
Revel	B-pers
bought	O
them	O
a	O
Bottle-basket	O
at	O
Tower-hill	O
pers	O
:	O
and	O
that	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
went	O
and	O
stole	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
Potter	O
opened	O
the	O
Door	O
with	O
a	O
Chisle	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
stopped	O
at	O
Hackney	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Old	O
Offender	O
:	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
Fined	O
10	O
Marks	O
and	O
3	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
8	O
Guineas,3	O
Moidores	O
,	O
and	O
Silver	O
,	O
together	O
to	O
the	O
sum	O
of	O
20	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Miles	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
Jan.	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Chest	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
at	O
Putney	O
in	O
bed	O
and	O
drunk	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
not	O
above	O
2	O
s.	O
of	O
it	O
left	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
it	O
having	O
been	O
taken	O
from	O
her	O
by	O
two	O
Men	O
that	O
had	O
lain	O
with	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
Barn	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
alledged	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
several	O
times	O
importuned	O
her	O
to	O
lie	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
had	O
left	O
the	O
Chest	O
open	O
and	O
bid	O
her	O
take	O
the	O
Money	O
:	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
believing	O
her	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
(	O
Death	O
)	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Coats	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Coachman	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
as	O
an	O
Accessory	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Portmanteau	O
Trunk	O
full	O
of	O
rich	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
a	O
Watch	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
50	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Drovisin	B-pers
Hubey	I-pers
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
carry	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
Portmanteau	O
into	O
Watling-Street	O
to	O
the	O
Carters	O
about	O
10	O
a-Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
:	O
that	O
the	O
Coachman	O
,	O
supposing	O
he	O
would	O
made	O
him	O
wait	O
,	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
carried	O
him	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
put	O
the	O
Portmanteau	O
into	O
the	O
Coach	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
constraining	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
if	O
he	O
will	O
carry	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
serve	O
him	O
a	O
Trick	O
for	O
it	O
:	O
and	O
accordingly	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
pass	O
'd	O
along	O
,	O
he	O
called	O
to	O
several	O
Coachmen	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
S.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Church-Yard	I-place
he	O
then	O
drove	O
very	O
softly	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
keeping	O
his	O
Hand	O
on	O
the	O
Trunk	O
,	O
till	O
taking	O
it	O
off	O
while	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
pinch	O
of	O
Snuff	O
,	O
in	O
an	O
instant	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
opened	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Trunk	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
jump	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
telling	O
the	O
Coachman	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
pursue	O
the	O
Thieves	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Coachman	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
,	O
jump	O
'd	O
off	O
the	O
Coach-box	O
,	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
pursue	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
calling	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
charg	O
'd	O
them	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
sent	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
after	O
his	O
Footboy	O
that	O
was	O
pursuing	O
them	O
likewise	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
;	O
so	O
the	O
Rogues	O
went	O
clean	O
off	O
with	O
the	O
Booty	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
Innocence	O
of	O
the	O
Design	O
;	O
alledged	O
,	O
he	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
bilk	O
him	O
of	O
his	O
Fair	O
.	O
It	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
plainly	O
proved	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Confederacy	O
with	O
the	O
Thieves	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Court	O
was	O
so	O
incensed	O
at	O
the	O
Baseness	O
of	O
the	O
Action	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
lay	O
an	O
Indictment	O
of	O
another	O
Nature	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cash	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
White	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Cash	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Boyl	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
taking	O
11	O
Guineas	O
,	O
a	O
Pistole	O
,	O
and	O
24	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Tho	O
.	O
Cash	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Hanging-Sword-Alley	B-place
near	I-place
Water-Lane	I-place
,	I-place
Fleet-Street	I-place
,	O
having	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
or	O
Malt	O
,	O
and	O
pulling	O
out	O
his	O
Money	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
Margaret	O
Boyl	O
struck	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
:	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
afterwards	O
Fell	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Leather	O
Breeches	O
cut	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
down	O
the	O
side	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cash	I-pers
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
very	O
drunk	O
,	O
carried	O
him	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Street	O
and	O
laid	O
him	O
there	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
an	O
Oyster	O
Girl	O
near	O
the	O
Temple	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
some	O
Oysters	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
were	O
single	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
:	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
swore	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
Married	O
in	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
marry	O
her	O
:	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
and	O
drank	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
bought	O
a	O
Ring	O
,	O
giving	O
22	O
s.	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
thereto	O
:	O
that	O
he	O
sat	O
there	O
drinking	O
,	O
was	O
drank	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Women	O
take	O
the	O
Money	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
that	O
Boyl	O
and	O
White	O
afterwards	O
gave	O
a	O
Note	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
matter	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
Mary	O
White	O
and	O
Margaret	O
Boyl	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
(	O
Death	O
)	O
and	O
acquitted	O
Tho	O
.	O
Cash	O
.	O
Gent	O
.	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Knapper	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
upon	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
on	O
his	O
Right	O
Breast	O
,	O
near	O
his	O
Right	O
Pap	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
to	O
the	O
29th	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
Manslaughter	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
upon	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
Stabbing	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Holliday	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Deceased	O
having	O
been	O
drinking	O
a	O
Bowl	O
of	O
Punch	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
at	O
10	O
a	O
Clock	O
on	O
Saturday-night	O
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
December	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
rose	O
up	O
he	O
perceived	O
he	O
had	O
drank	O
too	O
freely	O
by	O
his	O
reeling	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
sober	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
thereupon	O
desired	O
the	O
Deceased	O
to	O
take	O
Coach	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
send	O
him	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
three	O
Quarters	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
he	O
heard	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Misfortune	O
:	O
That	O
thereupon	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
vomiting	O
Blood	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
asked	O
how	O
it	O
came	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
Kindness	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
And	O
being	O
asked	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
prosecuted	O
if	O
he	O
died	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
Effect	O
of	O
Malice	O
but	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Friend	O
had	O
mistaken	O
his	O
Kindness	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
back	O
to	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
drew	O
upon	O
him	O
and	O
wounded	O
him	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Knapper	O
's	O
Landlady	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
of	O
Dec.	O
at	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
past	O
10	O
a	O
Clock	O
Mr.	O
Knapper	O
and	O
thePrisoner	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
both	O
come	O
Mr.	O
Knapper	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Pray	O
Sir	O
wash	O
upStairs	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
no	O
Answer	O
,	O
but	O
immediately	O
ran	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
and	O
Mr	O
Knapper	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
Minutes	O
out	O
Mr	O
Knapper	O
came	O
back	O
looking	O
pale	O
and	O
breathed	O
short	O
,	O
having	O
his	O
Hand	O
on	O
his	O
Breast	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
stood	O
with	O
a	O
Ladle	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
expecting	O
their	O
Return	O
;	O
that	O
seeing	O
him	O
come	O
back	O
by	O
himself	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
is	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
coming	O
,	O
or	O
may	O
I	O
shut	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
he	O
replied	O
shut	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
