TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
'S	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminor	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
,	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
being	O
the	O
15th,16th	O
,	O
and	O
17th	O
,	O
of	O
October,1718	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Fifth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
23	O
.	O
Octob-1718	O
.	O
BEfore	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	O
LEWEN	O
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
The	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
Pratt	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Tracy	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Price	I-pers
;	O
The	O
Worshipful	O
John	B-pers
Roby	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
divers	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
Names	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Haward	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
stead	I-pers
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
.	I-pers
James	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
.	O
Giles	B-pers
Hitchman	I-pers
.	I-pers
Lomard	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Samuel	I-pers
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Hug	I-pers
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Wyshare	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Wallis	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
.	O
Jos	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bick	I-pers
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Orbell	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Clement	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Duck	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
Cornhil	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Taster	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Strainer	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Ware-house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Blackham	I-pers
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
finding	O
his	O
Shop	O
broke	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
Drawer	O
had	O
been	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Iron	O
Pin	O
lying	O
by	O
,	O
which	O
could	O
hardly	O
have	O
been	O
found	O
but	O
by	O
some	O
that	O
were	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
Place	O
;	O
that	O
thereupon	O
he	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
searching	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
found	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
that	O
he	O
going	O
by	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Door	O
not	O
fast	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
did	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
ThomasMultus	B-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Colethurst	I-pers
of	O
Newington	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Thomas	B-pers
Philip	I-pers
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
value	O
2	O
s.6	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Spurs	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Gelding	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Matth.ew	B-pers
Lant	I-pers
,	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
September	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
riding	O
near	O
Pancras	O
Wash	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
met	O
by	O
two	O
Men	O
,	O
one	O
on	O
Horseback	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
on	O
Foot	O
,	O
who	O
stop	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
off	O
his	O
Spurs	O
,	O
Boots	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
and	O
afterwards	O
they	O
bid	O
him	O
get	O
off	O
from	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
put	O
on	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
got	O
upon	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
rode	O
away	O
.	O
He	O
could	O
not	O
Swear	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Face	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Coat	O
on	O
his	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Spur	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
of	O
his	O
things	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
By	O
other	O
Evidences	O
it	O
did	O
appear	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
crying	O
our	O
Highway-men	O
,	O
some	O
Persons	O
that	O
happened	O
as	O
to	O
be	O
near	O
,	O
pursued	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
get	O
off	O
,	O
quitted	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
hid	O
himself	O
under	O
some	O
Brambles	O
in	O
a	O
Ditch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Coat	O
on	O
his	O
Back	O
,	O
the	O
Spurs	O
,	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Coat	O
Pocket	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Horse	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Head	O
at	O
Hampstead	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
his	O
Brother	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
so	O
a	O
Fair	O
to	O
sell	O
a	O
Horse	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
some	O
Linnen	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
Road	O
his	O
Brother	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Coat	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
positive	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Christopher	B-pers
Murphy	I-pers
,	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Mr.	O
David	B-pers
Sinclair	I-pers
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Horse	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
set	O
upon	O
between	B-place
Kilburn	I-place
and	I-place
Paddington	I-place
,	O
by	O
two	O
Highway-men	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
his	O
Horse	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
him	O
another	O
Horse	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
claimed	O
afterwards	O
by	O
another	O
Gentleman	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
as	O
was	O
made	O
appear	O
by	O
that	O
other	O
Gentleman	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
would	O
not	O
Swear	O
positively	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
Night	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
;	O
but	O
a	O
Note	O
of	O
40	O
l.	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Coat	O
Pocket	O
when	O
apprehended	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
accounted	O
for	O
,	O
by	O
saying	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Coat	O
of	O
his	O
Brother	O
,	O
who	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
a	O
Highway-man	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
likewise	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
.	O
But	O
as	O
to	O
Murphy	O
he	O
prov	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
Actor	O
in	O
Southwark	O
Fair	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
very	O
time	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Barton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White-Chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bug	I-pers
,	O
of	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.2	O
d.	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Fetton	I-pers
of	O
Norton	B-place
Falgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
value	O
1	O
l.3	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
P	I-pers
..	I-pers
tout	I-pers
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
Convict	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Marrying	O
Joel	B-pers
Lockup	I-pers
,	O
her	O
first	O
Husband	O
John	B-pers
W	I-pers
being	O
alive	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
appearing	O
sufficient	O
to	O
Convict	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hays	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Hays	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
108	O
Yards	O
of	O
Camlet	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sharpless	I-pers
;	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Husband	O
was	O
Journey-man	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
stol'n	O
and	O
same	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
found	O
reposited	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
Convict	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Otway	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
in	O
attempting	O
to	O
break	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Matthew	B-pers
D.d	I-pers
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
Steal	O
,	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Misdemeanour	O
and	O
Sentenc	O
'd	O
to	O
lye	O
in	O
Prison	O
for	O
6	O
Months	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Hill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
of	O
5	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Bagshaw	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
satisfie	O
the	O
Jury	O
he	O
Stole	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Fe.seu	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Gregories	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
20	O
Cane	O
Chairs	O
.	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bushels	I-pers
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
the	O
Chairs	O
at	O
divers	O
times	O
.	O
The	O
Chief	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
who	O
own	O
'd	O
himself	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Stealing	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
hid	O
also	O
run	O
away	O
from	O
his	O
Master	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Master	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
several	O
other	O
Persons	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Codby	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coach	O
Harness	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
July	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
produced	O
Evidence	O
that	O
he	O
fairly	O
bought	O
the	O
Harness	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Gregory	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
18	O
Guineas	O
,	O
a	O
Moidore	O
,	O
and	O
48	O
shillings	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Porter	O
at	O
the	O
Horn	O
Tavern	O
near	O
Doctors	O
Commons	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
Cook	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Hannah	B-pers
Hatley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Quilted	O
Petticoat	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Mosely	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ingelsby	I-pers
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
the	O
Petticoat	O
was	O
bought	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
Drunk	O
;	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
improbable	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Shanon	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
George	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
James	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
.	O
and	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
George	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Wig	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
James	O
Martin	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
walking	O
through	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Park	I-place
,	O
near	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Canal	O
over	O
against	O
the	O
Horse	O
Guards	O
,	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
a	O
Clock	O
on	O
the	O
Night	O
aforesaid	O
;	O
two	O
Soldiers	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Soldier	O
jostled	O
him	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
them	O
what	O
's	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
ca	O
n't	O
you	O
see	O
your	O
way	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Elizabeth	O
George	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
'Sh	O
-	O
d	O
do	O
you	O
assau't	O
my	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
without	O
any	O
more	O
words	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Shannon	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
cut	O
him	O
cross	O
the	O
Forehead	O
;	O
by	O
which	O
blow	O
he	O
was	O
lay	O
'd	O
open	O
to	O
the	O
Skull	O
and	O
tell	O
to	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
the	O
Soldier	O
there	O
cutting	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
another	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
Wrist	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
on	O
the	O
Hand	O
;	O
which	O
had	O
in	O
all	O
probability	O
cut	O
off	O
one	O
or	O
more	O
of	O
his	O
Fingers	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
Edge	O
of	O
the	O
Sword	O
struck	O
upon	O
a	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
with	O
that	O
violence	O
that	O
the	O
Sword	O
broke	O
in	O
half	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
cut	O
out	O
the	O
great	O
Diamond	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
lost	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
all	O
probability	O
Murther	O
'd	O
had	O
not	O
Major	O
for	O
her	O
immediately	O
come	O
to	O
his	O
Assistance	O
,	O
and	O
Captain	O
Beseaux	O
,	O
who	O
apprehended	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
;	O
but	O
his	O
Hat	O
was	O
lost	O
.	O
Captain	O
Beseaux	O
confirm	O
'd	O
what	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
said	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
going	O
along	O
with	O
Captain	O
Martin	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
near	O
to	O
him	O
when	O
the	O
Assault	O
was	O
given	O
,	O
turning	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
Soldier	O
cutting	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
said	O
what	O
are	O
you	O
doing	O
but	O
received	O
to	O
Answer	O
but	O
a	O
Cut	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
his	O
Mouth	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
therupon	O
calling	O
to	O
the	O
Centry	O
,	O
a	O
Soldier	O
came	O
to	O
their	O
Assistance	O
,	O
and	O
Major	O
Forster	O
coming	O
up	O
,	O
they	O
seized	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
but	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Soldiers	O
got	O
away	O
.	O
Major	O
Forster	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
the	O
Park	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
and	O
making	O
up	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
there	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
draw	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
cutting	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
his	O
Sword	O
break	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
lay	O
'd	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
breaking	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
all	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
were	O
taken	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
Soldier	O
escaped	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
Dark	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
his	O
Accoutrements	O
.	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
Tils-Yard	O
Duty	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Soldier	O
that	O
came	O
to	O
their	O
Assistance	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
hearing	O
an	O
Out-cry	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Gentlemens	O
Assistance	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
carried	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
and	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
into	O
the	O
Guard	O
Room	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
Mr.	O
Martins	O
Wig	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
assaulting	O
in	O
washing	O
his	O
Wounds	O
with	O
Brandy	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
George	O
took	O
the	O
Wig	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
opening	O
the	O
Guard	O
Room	O
Door	O
.	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
persued	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
had	O
nothing	O
material	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
that	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Hat	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
of	O
that	O
Robbery	O
;	O
but	O
Elizabeth	O
George	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
Wig	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Shannon	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
for	O
an	O
Assault	O
upon	O
Mr.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
which	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
that	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
Sentenc	O
'd	O
to	O
lye	O
in	O
Prison	O
12	O
Months	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Colealias	I-pers
William	I-pers
Cranfield	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bottolph	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Slade	I-pers
upon	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Pocket	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
17	O
s.6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
from	O
Iron	O
Gate	O
,	O
at	O
Tower-hill	B-place
over	I-place
,	I-place
against	I-place
the	I-place
Victualling	I-place
Office	I-place
,	O
she	O
having	O
a	O
Child	O
in	O
her	O
Arms	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
throw	O
the	O
Child	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Arms	O
over	O
her	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
she	O
being	O
very	O
much	O
affrighted	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
interim	O
of	O
her	O
Fright	O
he	O
pulled	O
off	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
running	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
some	O
Persons	O
coming	O
immediately	O
to	O
her	O
Assistance	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
his	O
Masters	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
the	O
Woman	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
to	O
her	O
Assistance	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
did	O
some	O
other	O
Persons	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
himself	O
Surrounded	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
escape	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
down	O
the	O
Pocket	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
for	O
a	O
Bitch	O
,	O
there	O
's	O
your	O
Pocket	O
,	O
what	O
would	O
you	O
have	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
other	O
Evidences	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
that	O
knew	O
him	O
,	O
having	O
taken	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
like	O
occasion	O
about	O
two	O
Years	O
before	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
having	O
the	O
Pocket	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
hearing	O
a	O
cry	O
of	O
Murther	O
,	O
ran	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
was	O
seiz	O
d.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
.	O
Roger	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
7	O
pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Arthur	B-pers
Emmerson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
this	O
present	O
October	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
came	O
a	O
Person	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Shop	O
,	O
telling	O
his	O
Servant	O
that	O
he	O
must	O
bring	O
half	O
a	O
doz	O
n	O
pair	O
of	O
Black	O
Silk	O
Stockings	O
to	O
one	O
Captain	O
Smith	O
in	O
Norfolk-Street	O
,	O
accordingly	O
the	O
Servant	O
put	O
up	O
7	O
Pair	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
who	O
conducted	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
open	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
but	O
you	O
have	O
brought	O
no	O
White	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
him	O
left	O
the	O
Stockings	O
,	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
gone	O
back	O
to	O
fetch	O
some	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
scrupling	O
to	O
do	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
leave	O
them	O
at	O
an	O
Apothecaries	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
home	O
to	O
fetch	O
the	O
white	O
Stockings	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
comes	O
to	O
the	O
Apothecary	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
careful	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
laid	O
safe	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
might	O
take	O
no	O
hurt	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
shew	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
catch	O
'd	O
them	O
up	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
but	O
the	O
Apothecary	O
's	O
Man	O
pursuing	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Stockings	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
alledge	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
carry	O
after	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Servant	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
not	O
being	O
credited	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Bolanson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
her	O
Male	O
Bastard	O
Child	O
,	O
by	O
throwing	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
suspected	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
deliver	O
'd	O
of	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
was	O
search	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
Midwife	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
Vault	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
directed	O
.	O
But	O
nothing	O
could	O
be	O
seen	O
on	O
it	O
whether	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
hurt	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
nor	O
whether	O
it	O
came	O
at	O
its	O
fulltime	O
,	O
it	O
having	O
lay'n	O
there	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
Weeks	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
pleaded	O
that	O
she	O
having	O
been	O
very	O
much	O
affrighted	O
at	O
the	O
extraordinary	O
Thunder	O
and	O
Lightning	O
,	O
fell	O
very	O
Ill	O
of	O
a	O
Feaver	O
and	O
Measles	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
Fright	O
and	O
Illness	O
she	O
did	O
believe	O
occasion	O
'd	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
the	O
Child	O
within	O
her	O
;	O
for	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
feel	O
it	O
stir	O
for	O
some	O
considerable	O
time	O
before	O
its	O
Birth	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
6	O
Weeks	O
before	O
her	O
time	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
Still-born	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
her	O
Illness	O
;	O
she	O
brought	O
Evidences	O
to	O
prove	O
her	O
Illness	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
made	O
Provision	O
for	O
the	O
Child	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wiggans	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pocket	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
a	O
Common-Prayer	O
Book	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
d.	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
11	O
Pence	O
in	O
Half-pence	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Great	B-place
Queen-street	I-place
,	O
on	O
Sunday	O
about	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
was	O
pull	O
'd	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
pursued	O
and	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Johns	I-pers
and	I-pers
Sarah	I-pers
his	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Kensington	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
rather	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
than	O
a	O
Robbery	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Steps	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
8	O
l.	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Henry	B-pers
Wiseman	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
two	O
others	O
did	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
by	O
taking	O
down	O
the	O
Glass	O
over	O
the	O
Shop-Door	O
and	O
reaching	O
out	O
the	O
Goods	O
with	O
a	O
Hook	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
a	O
Stick	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Kendal	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Chambers	O
of	O
Elias	B-pers
Meridith	I-pers
the	O
18th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
and	O
a	O
Pocket-book	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
wherein	O
was	O
a	O
Note	O
of	O
75	O
l.	O
payable	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Chambers	O
had	O
been	O
broken	O
open	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
stolen	O
and	O
the	O
Note	O
advertised	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
News	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
about	O
a	O
Month	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
discovered	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
Pocket-book	O
and	O
Note	O
,	O
by	O
Sarah	O
Dean	O
,	O
shewing	O
it	O
before	O
one	O
who	O
carried	O
word	O
to	O
Messieurs	O
Mead	O
and	O
Brightland	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
given	O
the	O
Note	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Cashier	O
went	O
to	O
demand	O
it	O
,	O
offering	O
half	O
a	O
Guineas	O
Reward	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
it	O
without	O
paying	O
four	O
Guineas	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
Demand	O
but	O
afterwards	O
they	O
came	O
down	O
to	O
40	O
s.	O
Sarah	O
Dean	O
was	O
a	O
Dumb	O
Woman	O
,	O
who	O
signified	O
by	O
Signs	O
that	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
Pocket	O
book	O
and	O
Note	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
;	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
King	I-pers
affirmed	O
she	O
was	O
by	O
her	O
when	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
and	O
several	O
Evidences	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
shewed	O
it	O
very	O
publickly	O
presently	O
after	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
intimate	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
it	O
cry	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
Cryer	O
:	O
Several	O
appeared	O
who	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
for	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Creature	O
,	O
whereupon	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Giles	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Awdley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Asser	I-pers
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
him	O
of	O
a	O
Purse	O
and	O
ten	O
Guineas	O
,	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Awdley	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
Walking	O
with	O
one	O
David	O
Seal	O
near	O
White	O
Chapel	O
Church	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Will	O
.	O
Awdley	O
who	O
is	O
his	O
Brother	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
pulling	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Shave	O
took	O
him	O
aside	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
place	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
it	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Man	O
lay	O
dead	O
in	O
a	O
Dit	O
.	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
murther	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
Bitch	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
no	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
knew	O
it	O
:	O
that	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Woman	O
having	O
first	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
stand	O
true	O
,	O
then	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
Woman	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
Yes	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Friend	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
,	O
and	O
searching	O
about	O
found	O
the	O
Deceased	O
lying	O
with	O
his	O
Head	O
back	O
,	O
his	O
Mouth	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Legs	O
drawn	O
up	O
:	O
That	O
than	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
discovered	O
it	O
to	O
some	O
Persons	O
at	O
Make-End	O
:	O
Whereupon	O
the	O
Body	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Pockets	O
being	O
Searched	O
,	O
a	O
Pocket-book	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
by	O
some	O
Notes	O
in	O
which	O
they	O
found	O
his	O
Name	O
was	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Asser	I-pers
:	O
he	O
then	O
left	O
Direction	O
's	O
in	O
Writing	O
where	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Friend	O
might	O
be	O
found	O
if	O
need	O
should	O
be	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
sent	O
for	O
produced	O
his	O
Brother	O
Will	O
.	O
Awadley	O
to	O
give	O
a	O
farther	O
Account	O
to	O
the	O
ury	O
.	O
Oliver	B-pers
Fen	I-pers
posed	O
that	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
William	B-pers
Awdley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
one	O
Polemony	O
and	O
Ralph	B-pers
Emmery	I-pers
(	O
the	O
two	O
last	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
having	O
been	O
drinking	O
all	O
the	O
Forenoon	O
,	O
went	O
into	O
Sale-Petre-Bank	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
been	O
up	O
all	O
Night	O
before	O
a	O
pilfering	O
and	O
drinking	O
,	O
were	O
sleepy	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
into	O
the	O
Fields	O
to	O
step	O
where	O
they	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Sarah	O
Brown	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
them	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
with	O
two	O
Rings	O
on	O
his	O
Finger	O
that	O
was	O
asleep	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Ditch	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
sitting	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
no	O
notice	O
of	O
her	O
:	O
that	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
Polemony	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
pulled	O
off	O
his	O
two	O
Rings	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
pull	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
Will	O
.	O
Awdley	O
took	O
up	O
two	O
large	O
pieces	O
of	O
Brick	O
and	O
threw	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
hit	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
on	O
the	O
Side	O
;	O
that	O
Sarah	O
Brown	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
a	O
Green	O
Purse	O
and	O
Eight	O
or	O
Ten	O
Guineas	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
Ralph	O
Emmery	O
took	O
a	O
Pocket-Book	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
Pound	O
of	O
Coffee	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
put	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
saying	O
they	O
were	O
quere	O
:	O
that	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Salt-Petre-Bank	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
Polcrony	O
gave	O
him	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Rings	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
left	O
with	O
a	O
Person	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
:	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
afterwards	O
and	O
drank	O
all	O
together	O
at	O
a	O
House	O
at	O
Salt-Petre	O
Bank	O
and	O
Sarah	O
Brown	O
made	O
an	O
Excuse	O
out	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Necessary	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
eloped	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
the	O
Money	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
share	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Other	O
Evidences	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Coroner	O
and	O
Jury	O
Sat	O
upon	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
that	O
William	B-pers
Awdley	I-pers
being	O
produced	O
by	O
the	O
means	O
of	O
his	O
Brother	O
,	O
did	O
there	O
upon	O
Examination	O
own	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
thrown	O
two	O
Brick-bats	O
at	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
hit	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
.	O
The	O
Surgeon	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
several	O
Bruises	O
and	O
Contusions	O
about	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
as	O
tho	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
beaten	O
very	O
much	O
and	O
tho	O
'	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
external	O
Wound	O
,	O
yet	O
opening	O
his	O
Head	O
near	O
the	O
Temporal	O
Muscles	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
coagulated	O
Blood	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
believe	O
that	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
both	O
don	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
Awdley	O
pleaded	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
indeed	O
drinking	O
that	O
Forenoon	O
with	O
Oliver	O
Fen	O
,	O
and	O
Palcrony	O
,	O
and	O
Ralph	O
Emmery	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
Ralph	O
Emmery	O
layd	O
down	O
to	O
sleep	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
Field	O
,	O
but	O
Oliver	O
Fen	O
and	O
Polcreny	O
would	O
go	O
farther	O
toward	O
Stepney	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
that	O
Oliver	O
Fen	O
and	O
Polcrony	O
had	O
m	O
rare	O
blow	O
(	O
as	O
they	O
term	O
'd	O
it	O
)	O
of	O
a	O
Hat	O
and	O
two	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Ale-house	O
at	O
Salt-Petre-Bank	O
,	O
to	O
demand	O
his	O
own	O
Hat	O
,	O
Supposing	O
they	O
had	O
stollen	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
it	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
asleep	O
.	O
Sarah	O
Brown	O
produced	O
Persons	O
who	O
indeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
prove	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
their	O
Houses	O
at	O
Salt-Peter-Bank	O
that	O
Day	O
,	O
from	O
11	O
in	O
the	O
Forenoon	O
till	O
1	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
;	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
satisfaction	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
and	O
Oliver	O
Fen	O
telling	O
the	O
Court	O
that	O
the	O
Husband	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
Evidences	O
was	O
at	O
that	O
very	O
Sessions	O
indicted	O
for	O
pulling	O
off	O
a	O
Pocket	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
upon	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
,	O
of	O
both	O
Robbery	O
and	O
Murther	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.10	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Humphreys	I-pers
the	O
25th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
for	O
stealing	O
divers	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Jordon	I-pers
the	O
13th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
facts	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
upon	O
each	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pauls	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
30	O
Silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
.	O
value	O
45	O
s.	O
and	O
8	O
Neckcloths	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
November	O
1716	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
Edward	B-pers
Ash	I-pers
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
Ralph	B-pers
Emmery	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
called	O
Bandy-legg	O
'd	O
Doctor	O
;	O
broke	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
for	O
26	O
s.	O
to	O
one	O
Bradbury	O
in	O
Rosemary-Lane	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
corroborating	O
Evidence	O
to	O
confirm	O
what	O
Edward	B-pers
Ash	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Barnet	B-pers
Egan	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michaels	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
brass	O
Tops	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Coach	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Mead	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
:	O
The	O
fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
be	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
grey	O
Mare	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
indicted	O
2d	O
time	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
black	O
Mare	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Cony	I-pers
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
September	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
,	O
and	O
received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Leverson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pack	O
of	O
Cards	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
1st	O
.	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
sufficient	O
proof	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Johns	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Pound	O
of	O
Candles	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
of	O
small	O
value	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wase	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
proof	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Maynard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Pot	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hambley	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
body	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
counterfeiting	O
the	O
current	O
Coyn	O
of	O
the	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
and	O
making	O
20	O
pieces	O
in	O
the	O
Likeness	O
and	O
of	O
Shillings	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Masden	I-pers
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Mrs.	O
Reynolds	O
and	O
Sherwin	O
sent	O
her	O
out	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
Block	O
Tin	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Crucible	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
mistaking	O
the	O
name	O
,	O
and	O
asking	O
for	O
a	O
Crucifix	O
,	O
the	O
People	O
laugh	O
'd	O
at	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
a	O
Crucible	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
buy	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
Pound	O
of	O
Block	O
Tin	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
3	O
d.	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
fault	O
with	O
for	O
giving	O
no	O
more	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
always	O
gave	O
16	O
pence	O
per	O
pound	O
for	O
what	O
they	O
used	O
;	O
that	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
Supt	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
work	O
,	O
melted	O
the	O
Metal	O
in	O
a	O
Fire-Shovel	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
blow	O
'd	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
made	O
the	O
Mold	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
12	O
s.	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
Shilling	O
that	O
was	O
plain	O
enough	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
sent	O
her	O
about	O
to	O
Several	O
places	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
plain	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
a	O
Riding-hood	O
for	O
that	O
purpose	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
would	O
teach	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
small	O
matter	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
cast	O
one	O
Shilling	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
had	O
so	O
done	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
now	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
enough	O
to	O
be	O
burnt	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
discover	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
then	O
design	O
to	O
make	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
came	O
to	O
20	O
l.	O
and	O
then	O
leave	O
off	O
;	O
but	O
her	O
Heart	O
fail	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
and	O
discover	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Room	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
Wooden	O
Mold	O
and	O
some	O
Black	O
Tin	O
,	O
and	O
asking	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
when	O
he	O
did	O
coyn	O
for	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
for	O
his	O
fancy	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
same	O
of	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
asking	O
him	O
concerning	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
never	O
made	O
but	O
one	O
Shilling	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
Wooden	O
Mold	O
did	O
belong	O
to	O
a	O
Brother	O
that	O
was	O
lately	O
dead	O
and	O
called	O
his	O
Mother	O
who	O
did	O
affirm	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
to	O
cast	O
Chuckers	O
in	O
.	O
That	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Block	O
Tin	O
it	O
was	O
what	O
he	O
used	O
in	O
his	O
Business	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
using	O
the	O
Guiney	O
Trade	O
.	O
That	O
as	O
to	O
Martha	B-pers
Masdon	I-pers
,	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
ill	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
accused	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
spite	O
,	O
because	O
they	O
had	O
borrow	O
'd	O
some	O
Money	O
and	O
jointly	O
given	O
a	O
Note	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
her	O
Name	O
scratcht	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Note	O
,	O
which	O
because	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
get	O
done	O
,	O
she	O
threatned	O
to	O
be	O
revenged	O
on	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
Evidencs	O
to	O
prove	O
several	O
of	O
these	O
Circumstances	O
and	O
also	O
called	O
several	O
Persons	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Oldfield	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Oley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Fulham	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Plumridge	I-pers
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
value	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Plumridge	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
broken	O
through	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Window	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
four	O
of	O
them	O
who	O
did	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
two	O
Men	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
Bedside	O
with	O
Pistols	O
,	O
threatning	O
to	O
shoot	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
discover	O
where	O
her	O
Father	O
's	O
Money	O
lay	O
;	O
broke	O
open	O
several	O
Locks	O
in	O
her	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
what	O
they	O
pleased	O
;	O
she	O
telling	O
them	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
of	O
any	O
Money	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
to	O
Search	O
in	O
other	O
Rooms	O
,	O
threatning	O
her	O
that	O
if	O
they	O
found	O
any	O
Money	O
they	O
would	O
certainly	O
kill	O
her	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Maid	O
's	O
Chamber	O
and	O
broke	O
several	O
Locks	O
there	O
,	O
took	O
what	O
they	O
pleas	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
threatned	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
made	O
any	O
Noise	O
they	O
would	O
murther	O
her	O
.	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
her	O
Father	O
's	O
Room	O
,	O
an	O
ancient	O
Man	O
of	O
Fourscore	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
and	O
threatned	O
him	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
discover	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
fired	O
a	O
Pistol	O
at	O
him	O
which	O
discharged	O
a	O
Buffer	O
through	O
a	O
Flannel	O
which	O
was	O
wrapp	O
'd	O
round	O
her	O
Father	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
though	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
through	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
yet	O
it	O
hurt	O
his	O
Forehead	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
some	O
Blood	O
:	O
that	O
then	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
came	O
into	O
her	O
Chamber	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
Pocket	O
which	O
hung	O
by	O
the	O
Bed	O
side	O
,	O
wherein	O
was	O
about	O
19	O
s.	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
:	O
that	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
about	O
two	O
Hours	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
carrying	O
with	O
them	O
what	O
they	O
thought	O
fit	O
:	O
But	O
she	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
Fright	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
positively	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Connor	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
two	O
Women	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
Patrick	B-pers
White	I-pers
and	O
Matthew	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
used	O
to	O
come	O
,	O
and	O
owing	O
her	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
urging	O
them	O
to	O
pay	O
her	O
,	O
they	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
patient	O
telling	O
her	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
old	O
Man	O
lived	O
at	O
Hammersmith	O
where	O
was	O
only	O
his	O
Daughter	O
and	O
the	O
Maid	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
go	O
thither	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
soon	O
pay	O
her	O
,	O
saying	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
or	O
two	O
to	O
meet	O
them	O
:	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
reply	O
'd	O
then	O
perhaps	O
they	O
'd	O
be	O
taken	O
and	O
hang	O
'd	O
:	O
That	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
about	O
ten	O
a-Clock	O
,	O
a	O
Sack	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
by	O
the	O
other	O
Men	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
full	O
of	O
divers	O
sorts	O
of	O
Goods	O
,	O
several	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
saw	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
and	O
a	O
Cup	O
which	O
was	O
given	O
her	O
to	O
sell	O
to	O
pay	O
her	O
her	O
Debt	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
sell	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Spoons	O
were	O
marked	O
with	O
the	O
first	O
Letters	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Name	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
got	O
from	O
the	O
Goldsmith	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
as	O
was	O
the	O
Sack	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
things	O
:	O
That	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
present	O
)	O
she	O
heard	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
say	O
,	O
how	O
hardy	O
the	O
old	O
Dog	O
was	O
that	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
where	O
his	O
Money	O
lay	O
,	O
though	O
we	O
shot	O
at	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
not	O
knowing	O
where	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
goes	O
to	O
Covent-Garden	O
Marker	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
enquiry	O
found	O
out	O
where	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
liv	O
'd	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
notice	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Evidences	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Grenadier	O
was	O
then	O
upon	O
Guard	O
at	O
the	O
very	O
time	O
that	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
satisfying	O
the	O
Jury	O
they	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
The	O
bringing	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
Conners	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
being	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
also	O
by	O
another	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
s	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
two	O
Shillings	O
from	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
One	O
Gibbs	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
driving	O
a	O
Load	O
of	O
Straw	O
over	O
Hounslow-heath	B-place
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Man	O
riding	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
they	O
espy	O
'd	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
Persons	O
,	O
they	O
rode	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
and	O
stopped	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Man	O
one	O
Berrisford	O
held	O
out	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
they	O
took	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
rode	O
after	O
two	O
other	O
Men	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
held	O
out	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
what	O
he	O
took	O
from	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
afterwards	O
stopped	O
another	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
out	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
riding	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
Berrisford	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
but	O
4	O
Six-pences	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
one	O
to	O
say	O
nothing	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
inform	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
one	O
Berrisford	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
some	O
Persons	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
a	O
Horse	O
and	O
pursued	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
follow	O
'd	O
them	O
several	O
Miles	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
apprehended	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
Berrisford	O
took	O
to	O
Kingston	O
Road	O
and	O
got	O
off	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
Examination	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
wherein	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
one	O
Berrisford	O
a	O
Butcher	O
in	O
Hedge-lane	O
had	O
several	O
times	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
get	O
some	O
Money	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
that	O
Night	O
at	O
the	O
Hand-in-Hand	O
at	O
Kingston	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
at	O
Redding	O
,	O
on	O
Monday	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Races	O
;	O
then	O
coming	O
towards	O
London	O
,	O
Berrisford	O
did	O
take	O
4	O
s.6	O
d.	O
from	O
a	O
Person	O
on	O
the	O
Road	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evi-	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
any	O
from	O
any	O
Body	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Moor	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Muslin	O
Aprons	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.10	O
d.1	O
Muslin	O
Window	O
Curtain	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
from	O
Mary	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
agreed	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
teach	O
her	O
to	O
Clear	O
Stearch	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
not	O
coming	O
according	O
as	O
she	O
expected	O
;	O
leaving	O
some	O
business	O
in	O
Fenchurch-street	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Lodging	O
near	B-place
Mark-lane	I-place
,	O
and	O
having	O
some	O
very	O
rich	O
Muslin	O
Aprons	O
and	O
Curtains	O
in	O
a	O
Band-box	O
,	O
open	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
shew	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
having	O
view	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
help	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
double	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
folding	O
up	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Curtains	O
at	O
the	O
further	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
put	O
her	O
Hand	O
into	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
Box	O
to	O
put	O
in	O
the	O
Window	O
Curtains	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
Duskish	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
thinking	O
the	O
Box	O
was	O
lighter	O
than	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
,	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
the	O
Aprons	O
,	O
who	O
reply	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
Bottom	O
of	O
the	O
Box	O
;	O
she	O
believing	O
her	O
,	O
ty	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
a	O
Milliners	O
,	O
and	O
opening	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
two	O
Aprons	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
Curtains	O
were	O
missing	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
went	O
next	O
Morning	O
to	O
demand	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
view	O
'd	O
the	O
Aprons	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
as	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
Sworn	O
but	O
said	O
she	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
Box	O
her	O
Self	O
.	O
Some	O
Persons	O
appear	O
'd	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
under	O
the	O
left	O
Pap	O
.	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languish	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
10th	O
and	O
then	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
deposed	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Mr.	O
William	B-pers
Rutton	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
's	O
Brother	O
,	O
Col.	O
Burslow	B-pers
,	O
Capt	O
.	O
Fletcher	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Heath	O
and	O
himself	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
Drinking	O
together	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
Friendly	O
manner	O
at	O
the	O
Red-lion-Tavern	O
in	O
Richmond	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
engag	O
'd	O
in	O
Conversation	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
mov	O
'd	O
by	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Company	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
proper	O
to	O
break	O
up	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
it	O
grew	O
late	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Heath	O
and	O
himself	O
being	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Istle	O
worth	O
,	O
't	O
was	O
thought	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
difficult	O
to	O
get	O
passage	O
over	O
the	O
Water	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Deceased	O
reply	O
'd	O
he	O
could	O
do	O
well-enough	O
as	O
to	O
that	O
,	O
for	O
being	O
known	O
to	O
the	O
Ferry-man	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
easily	O
procure	O
a	O
passage	O
.	O
They	O
staid	O
till	O
past	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
then	O
going	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Ferry	O
,	O
the	O
Ferry-man	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
told	O
his	O
Name	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Ferry-man	O
made	O
them	O
wait	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
;	O
that	O
upon	O
saying	O
a	O
Shilling	O
they	O
went	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
landed	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
Friendly	O
manner	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
walking	O
to	O
Istleworth	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Path	O
near	O
the	O
River	O
side	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
passing	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
discoursing	O
concerning	O
their	O
Passage	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
said	O
that	O
a	O
Shilling	O
was	O
little	O
enough	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Heath	O
reply	O
'd	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
,	O
provided	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
done	O
readily	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
obliged	O
to	O
wait	O
so	O
long	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
upon	O
this	O
took	O
occasion	O
to	O
grow	O
Warm	O
,	O
and	O
Angry	O
,	O
and	O
clapt	O
his	O
Hand	O
to	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
Witness	O
)	O
holding	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
left	O
Arm	O
prevented	O
him	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
attempted	O
it	O
several	O
times	O
;	O
but	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
perceive	O
Mr.	O
Heath	O
attempts	O
to	O
draw	O
,	O
or	O
meddle	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
at	O
last	O
growing	O
so	O
unruly	O
and	O
resolure	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
well	O
hold	O
him	O
he	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
by	O
that	O
time	O
come	O
near	O
the	O
Houses	O
,	O
walked	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
not	O
gone	O
but	O
a	O
small	O
Distance	O
,	O
before	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Clashing	O
of	O
Swords	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
immediately	O
turned	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Deceased	O
,	O
found	O
them	O
about	O
20	O
Yards	O
distant	O
from	O
the	O
Foot	O
Path	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
fallen	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Heath	O
helping	O
him	O
up	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
hearing	O
some	O
Men	O
in	O
a	O
Boat	O
,	O
they	O
called	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
gotten	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Boat	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Coffee	O
House	O
at	O
Istleworth	O
,	O
whither	O
he	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Heath	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Watermen	O
walked	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
Bed	O
,	O
they	O
laid	O
him	O
upon	O
the	O
Watermen	O
's	O
Tilts	O
,	O
and	O
Cushions	O
before	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
Fire	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
being	O
immediately	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
took	O
care	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Heath	O
,	O
Tom	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
thou	O
hast	O
Kill	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
freely	O
forgive	O
thee	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Health	O
reply	O
'd	O
he	O
hoped	O
not	O
.	O
He	O
likewise	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
had	O
always	O
been	O
an	O
intire	O
Friendship	O
between	O
Mr.	O
Heath	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
and	O
an	O
,	O
intimate	O
familiarity	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
the	O
least	O
misunderstanding	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
of	O
,	O
nor	O
no	O
just	O
Provocation	O
given	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Heath	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
this	O
unhappy	O
Accident	O
.	O
Bryan	B-pers
Cabe	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Partner	O
rose	O
about	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
that	O
Night	O
to	O
go	O
a	O
Fishing	O
,	O
(	O
they	O
being	O
Fishermen	O
)	O
and	O
that	O
being	O
in	O
their	O
Boat	O
,	O
they	O
heard	O
some	O
Gentlemen	O
discoursing	O
about	O
the	O
Ferry	O
and	O
a	O
Shiiling	O
,	O
they	O
thinking	O
they	O
might	O
want	O
to	O
go	O
over	O
the	O
Water	O
,	O
made	O
towards	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
come	O
near	O
the	O
Bank	O
,	O
they	O
heard	O
the	O
Clashing	O
of	O
Swords	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
called	O
out	O
what	O
are	O
you	O
doing	O
there	O
,	O
Killing	O
one	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
answer	O
'd	O
we	O
hope	O
not	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
heard	O
a	O
Person	O
Groan	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
called	O
to	O
them	O
to	O
come	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
wounded	O
Gentlemen	O
into	O
their	O
Boat	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Coffee-House	O
at	O
Istleworth	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
made	O
answer	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
come	O
provided	O
they	O
would	O
lay	O
by	O
their	O
Swords	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
perhaps	O
if	O
we	O
take	O
the	O
wounded	O
Gentleman	O
into	O
the	O
Boat	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
go	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
shall	O
have	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
;	O
But	O
they	O
replying	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
Mr.	O
Heath	O
have	O
gone	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
refused	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Wounded	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
afraid	O
he	O
should	O
take	O
Cold	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
walk	O
and	O
meet	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
Coffee-House	O
;	O
that	O
thereupon	O
his	O
Mate	O
walk	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
himself	O
Rowed	O
the	O
Deceased	O
to	O
Istleworth	O
;	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
mortally	O
wounded	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
freely	O
forgave	O
him	O
that	O
did	O
it	O
.	O
That	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
Istleworth	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Heath	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Rutton	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
carried	O
the	O
Deceased	O
to	O
the	O
Coffee-House	O
,	O
where	O
Heath	O
expressed	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Concern	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
Care	O
and	O
Tenderness	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
tending	O
on	O
him	O
,	O
frequently	O
asking	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
what	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
easy	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
nothing	O
,	O
perswaded	O
him	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Rutton	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Bed	O
.	O
Bonas	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
the	O
other	O
Fisherman	O
,	O
confirmed	O
what	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
had	O
said	O
,	O
adding	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
required	O
them	O
to	O
lay	O
by	O
their	O
Swords	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Rutton	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Sword	O
off	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
sticking	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Ground	O
broke	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Heath	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Coffee-House	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
attempted	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
done	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
pleased	O
,	O
but	O
sent	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
careful	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
refused	O
to	O
let	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
meddle	O
with	O
his	O
Wounds	O
till	O
he	O
had	O
dressed	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
often	O
looking	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
carefully	O
observing	O
whether	O
he	O
spit	O
any	O
Blood	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Packs	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
called	O
by	O
the	O
last	O
Evidence	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Coffee-House	O
,	O
just	O
as	O
the	O
Clock	O
struck	O
one	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Deceased	O
not	O
being	O
then	O
brought	O
from	O
the	O
Boat	O
,	O
he	O
walk	O
'd	O
toward	O
the	O
Water-side	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
bringing	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
procure	O
a	O
Bed	O
,	O
laid	O
him	O
on	O
some	O
Chairs	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
on	O
some	O
Tilts	O
and	O
Cushions	O
before	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
and	O
dress	O
'd	O
his	O
Wound	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
then	O
dare	O
to	O
Probe	O
and	O
Dilate	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Heath	O
shew	O
'd	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
concern	O
for	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
much	O
Affection	O
and	O
Tenderness	O
towards	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
was	O
Wounded	O
in	O
both	O
Arms	O
,	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
dress	O
'd	O
till	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
dress	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
having	O
done	O
,	O
did	O
afterwards	O
dress	O
Mr.	O
Heath	O
of	O
two	O
Wounds	O
,	O
one	O
quite	O
through	O
his	O
left	O
Arm	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
under	O
his	O
right	O
Arm	O
near	O
the	O
Arm-Pir	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Heath	O
sent	O
to	O
Richmond	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Brother	O
,	O
who	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
said	O
to	O
his	O
Brother	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
God	O
Sam	O
,	O
how	O
came	O
this	O
Misfortune	O
?	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
but	O
several	O
times	O
desired	O
his	O
Brother	O
if	O
he	O
dy	O
'd	O
not	O
to	O
Prosecute	O
.	O
He	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
having	O
gotten	O
him	O
into	O
Bed	O
,	O
he	O
search	O
'd	O
his	O
Wound	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
had	O
penecrated	O
the	O
Abdoman	O
;	O
and	O
thereupon	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
apprehended	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
Mortal	O
.	O
His	O
Brother	O
sent	O
for	O
another	O
Surgeon	O
;	O
and	O
all	O
proper	O
means	O
was	O
used	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
dy	O
'd	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Heath	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
exprest	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
a	O
great	O
concern	O
for	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
said	O
that	O
his	O
Death	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
Affiction	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
long	O
acquaintance	O
and	O
intimacy	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
ferv	O
'd	O
him	O
upon	O
all	O
Occasions	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
never	O
had	O
been	O
any	O
Difference	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
till	O
this	O
Fatal	O
time	O
;	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
gave	O
this	O
Relation	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
Deceased	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Rutton	O
,	O
and	O
himself	O
,	O
returning	O
from	O
Richmond	O
to	O
Istleworth	O
,	O
they	O
met	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Brother	O
,	O
Col.	O
Barston	B-pers
,	O
and	O
Capt	O
.	O
Flescher	O
,	O
(	O
who	O
were	O
just	O
come	O
from	O
London	O
)	O
and	O
went	O
back	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
Richmond	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Red-Lion-Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
stay	O
'd	O
there	O
longer	O
than	O
they	O
intended	O
;	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Rutton	O
several	O
times	O
express	O
'd	O
some	O
concern	O
about	O
getting	O
over	O
the	O
Ferry	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
often	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
need	O
not	O
trouble	O
himself	O
about	O
that	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Ferryman	O
knew	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
carry	O
him	O
over	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Tavern	O
Boy	O
lighted	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Water-side	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
long	O
before	O
the	O
Ferry-man	O
would	O
answer	O
and	O
consent	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
over	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
named	O
his	O
Name	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
know	O
him	O
;	O
at	O
length	O
with	O
much	O
entreaty	O
,	O
he	O
suffer	O
'd	O
his	O
Boy	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
over	O
for	O
a	O
Shilling	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
seemed	O
displeased	O
at	O
the	O
Ferry-man	O
's	O
want	O
of	O
respect	O
towards	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
Landed	O
,	O
and	O
walking	O
toward	O
Istleworth	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Rutton	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
glad	O
they	O
had	O
gotten	O
over	O
the	O
Ferry	O
,	O
altho	O
'	O
they	O
had	O
so	O
much	O
trouble	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
himself	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
Ay	O
,	O
so	O
was	O
he	O
,	O
but	O
those	O
Ferry-men	O
were	O
surly	O
Fellows	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
no	O
body	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
of	O
Night	O
without	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
grew	O
Angry	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
Fellow	O
deserv	O
'd	O
a	O
Shilling	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
so	O
he	O
did	O
and	O
more	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
made	O
them	O
wait	O
so	O
long	O
on	O
the	O
Shore	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
Bargain	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Foolish	O
thing	O
to	O
Dispute	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
was	O
Angry	O
,	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
draw	O
his	O
Sword	O
several	O
times	O
;	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Ruttan	O
prevented	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
walk	O
'd	O
on	O
,	O
he	O
following	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Rutton	O
at	O
about	O
the	O
distance	O
of	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Yards	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
explain	O
'd	O
what	O
had	O
been	O
said	O
,	O
as	O
not	O
intending	O
any	O
Offence	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Anger	O
encreasing	O
after	O
Mr.	O
Ruttan	O
left	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
he	O
hoped	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
of	O
another	O
Mind	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
Slept	O
.	O
He	O
reply	O
'd	O
no	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
say	O
I	O
am	O
Drunk	O
you	O
lye	O
;	O
and	O
immediately	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
pressing	O
hard	O
upon	O
Mr.	O
Heath	O
,	O
and	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
close	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
received	O
his	O
Wound	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
himself	O
received	O
a	O
Wounds	O
from	O
the	O
Deceased,1	O
of	O
them	O
quite	O
through	O
his	O
left	O
Arm	O
;	O
and	O
had	O
no	O
way	O
to	O
save	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
drawing	O
his	O
Sword	O
to	O
defend	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
who	O
appeared	O
to	O
speak	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
Behaviour	O
and	O
Temper	O
.	O
Those	O
who	O
were	O
called	O
,	O
being	O
well	O
known	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
Peaceable	O
,	O
inoffensive	O
Gentleman	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
upon	O
hearing	O
that	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
brought	O
in	O
their	O
Verdict	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
-	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
in	O
attempting	O
to	O
break	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Furn	I-pers
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
Steal	O
.	O
The	O
fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
Sentenced	O
to	O
be	O
Imprisoned	O
for	O
6	O
Months	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
divers	O
Goods	O
,	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gumley	I-pers
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
Stollen	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
-	O
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
pieces	O
of	O
Plate	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
and	O
6	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Holebrook	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Joel	B-pers
Lobb	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
abroad	O
,	O
her	O
Chamber	O
was	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
Stollen	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
being	O
informed	O
that	O
a	O
Person	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
come	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
whose	O
Person	O
being	O
described	O
,	O
the	O
description	O
answered	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Crossfield	I-pers
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Lobb	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
come	O
down	O
the	O
Stairs	O
with	O
some	O
things	O
within	O
the	O
Bosom	O
of	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
verily	O
believe	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
Lobb	O
having	O
known	O
him	O
before	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
used	O
formerly	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
produced	O
several	O
Evidences	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
an	O
account	O
from	O
time	O
to	O
time	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
very	O
probable	O
that	O
he	O
committed	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
upon	O
hearing	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
,	O
of	O
Chelsea	B-place
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Jenkinson	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Inch	O
and	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
Four	O
Inches	O
,	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
deposed	O
as	O
follows	O
:	O
Mary	B-pers
Plat	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
Mr.	O
T	O
-	O
came	O
home	O
about	O
7	O
a	O
Clock	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
Support	O
with	O
the	O
Family	O
about	O
8	O
read	O
Prayers	O
in	O
the	O
Family	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
Nine	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
about	O
Ten	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
did	O
she	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Family	O
,	O
leaving	O
the	O
Footman	O
below	O
Stairs	O
,	O
who	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchin	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Hours	O
after	O
the	O
Footman	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
knocking	O
at	O
her	O
Chamber-Door	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
a	O
Candle	O
;	O
accordingly	O
she	O
arose	O
,	O
struck	O
a	O
Light	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Candle	O
asking	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
wanted	O
it	O
for	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
answered	O
,	O
for	O
Mr.	O
T	O
-	O
and	O
he	O
to	O
look	O
about	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
apprehensive	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
heard	O
Thieves	O
about	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
she	O
therefore	O
having	O
given	O
him	O
the	O
Candle	O
,	O
shut	O
her	O
Chamber-Door	O
last	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
being	O
afraid	O
,	O
the	O
House	O
having	O
been	O
attempted	O
to	O
be	O
broken	O
open	O
once	O
or	O
twice	O
before	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
the	O
Footman	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
for	O
the	O
Security	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
heard	O
as	O
he	O
thought	O
,	O
somebody	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
trample	O
on	O
the	O
Gravel	O
Walk	O
in	O
the	O
Garden	O
,	O
just	O
under	O
the	O
Window	O
where	O
he	O
lay	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
listning	O
diligently	O
for	O
above	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
confirmed	O
in	O
his	O
Suspicion	O
;	O
be	O
having	O
been	O
ordered	O
by	O
his	O
Mistress	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
that	O
Nature	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
and	O
acquaint	O
Mr.	O
T	O
-	O
,	O
accordingly	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
there	O
were	O
Thieves	O
about	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
that	O
Mr.	O
T	O
-	O
thereupon	O
asked	O
him	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
answered	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
;	O
who	O
thereupon	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Maid	O
and	O
get	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
T	O
-	O
Mose	O
,	O
put	O
on	O
his	O
Night	O
Gown	O
and	O
Slippers	O
,	O
taking	O
his	O
Sword	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
saying	O
to	O
Mr.	O
T	O
-	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
in	O
my	O
Hand	O
for	O
a	O
Defence	O
,	O
he	O
bid	O
him	O
get	O
a	O
Club	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
Pistols	O
in	O
Mr.	O
T	O
-	O
's	O
Chamber	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
not	O
Charged	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
looked	O
about	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
no	O
body	O
got	O
in	O
,	O
they	O
opened	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
standing	O
about	O
20	O
Yards	O
from	O
that	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Garden	O
,	O
who	O
seeing	O
Mr.	O
T	O
-	O
come	O
out	O
,	O
made	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
T	O
-	O
thinking	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Thief	O
that	O
had	O
attempted	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
and	O
Pistol	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
stand	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
least	O
any	O
Person	O
should	O
slip	O
into	O
the	O
s	O
;	O
but	O
Mr.	O
T	O
-	O
having	O
followed	O
the	O
Deceased	O
out	O
of	O
Sight	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
returning	O
in	O
the	O
space	O
of	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
Minutes	O
,	O
he	O
seeing	O
no	O
body	O
about	O
,	O
venturd	O
Mr	O
.	O
T	O
-	O
.	O
I	O
searing	O
some	O
hurt	O
might	O
have	O
befallen	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
,	O
met	O
Mr.	O
T	O
-	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
coming	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
saying	O
he	O
was	O
Wounded	O
;	O
Mr.	O
T	O
-	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
Wounded	O
him	O
,	O
or	O
done	O
him	O
any	O
hurt	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Sony	O
and	O
that	O
Mr.	O
T	O
-	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
assist	O
him	O
in	O
carrying	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
hard	O
by	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
they	O
went	O
,	O
Mr.	O
T	O
-	O
telling	O
him	O
he	O
attempted	O
to	O
wrest	O
the	O
Pistol	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
no	O
reply	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
charging	O
him	O
with	O
an	O
attempt	O
to	O
break	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
no	O
Thief	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
it	O
,	O
what	O
a	O
Fool	O
was	O
I	O
.	O
And	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
sudden	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
;	O
but	O
by	O
the	O
Assistance	O
of	O
another	O
Person	O
that	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
they	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
,	O
Mr.	O
T	O
-	O
sent	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
and	O
let	O
him	O
Blood	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
bled	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
a	O
Drop	O
or	O
two	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
found	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Wound	O
in	O
his	O
Breast	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Westerburn	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
had	O
occasion	O
to	O
be	O
out	O
late	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
coming	O
a	O
long	O
after	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
Road	O
groaning	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Deceased	O
made	O
him	O
no	O
answer	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
T-not	O
being	O
far	O
off	O
,	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
some	O
care	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Whereupon	O
they	O
carry	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
who	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
Bleed	O
him	O
as	O
before	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
they	O
got	O
him	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
dress	O
'd	O
his	O
Wound	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
be	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Speech	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
disorder	O
'd	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
Cursed	O
and	O
Swore	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
what	O
a	O
Fool	O
am	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
dye	O
this	O
Night	O
;	O
told	O
them	O
where	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
dyed	O
about	O
5	O
a	O
Clock	O
that	O
Morning	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Footman	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
Mr.	O
T	O
-	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
come	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
gotten	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
he	O
dress	O
'd	O
his	O
Wound	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
his	O
left	O
Pap	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
Speak	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
desired	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
Spoke	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
People	O
would	O
come	O
and	O
tell	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
again	O
and	O
apply	O
proper	O
means	O
to	O
help	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
next	O
news	O
he	O
heard	O
he	O
was	O
Dead	O
.	O
The	O
Witnesses	O
all	O
agreed	O
that	O
Mr.	O
T	O
-	O
shew	O
'd	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
concern	O
and	O
care	O
for	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
welfare	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
sensible	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Robber	O
as	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
.	O
Mr.	O
T	O
-	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
gave	O
the	O
same	O
account	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
given	O
by	O
the	O
Evidences	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
adding	O
that	O
he	O
seeing	O
the	O
Deceased	O
run	O
away	O
upon	O
seeing	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
was	O
fully	O
persuded	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
whom	O
the	O
Footman	O
had	O
heard	O
about	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
thereupon	O
taking	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
Robber	O
,	O
he	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
following	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
a	O
Street	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
seemed	O
to	O
turn	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
might	O
easily	O
have	O
escaped	O
,	O
he	O
turned	O
suddenly	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
caution	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
keep	O
off	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
he	O
suspected	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Thief	O
,	O
yet	O
he	O
Swore	O
violently	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
clos	O
'd	O
in	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Pistol	O
,	O
and	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
wrest	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Scuffle	O
some	O
way	O
received	O
the	O
Wound	O
,	O
by	O
pressing	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
design	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
or	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
knowing	O
he	O
was	O
Wounded	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
divers	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
Distinction	O
and	O
Reputation	O
to	O
his	O
Character	O
,	O
who	O
all	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
Civil	O
,	O
inoffensive	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
never	O
inclining	O
to	O
Quarrels	O
or	O
Passion	O
;	O
but	O
of	O
such	O
Affability	O
as	O
rendred	O
his	O
Conversation	O
desirable	O
,	O
both	O
by	O
Superiours	O
and	O
Inferiours	O
,	O
And	O
the	O
Reverend	O
Doctor	O
King	B-pers
,	O
Minister	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
,	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
Young	O
Gentleman	O
very	O
exemplary	O
for	O
Sobriety	O
,	O
coolness	O
of	O
Temper	O
,	O
Courtesy	O
and	O
Piety	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
upon	O
bearing	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
brought	O
in	O
their	O
Verdict	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgement	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death,9	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Multus	I-pers
alias	O
Colethurst	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
alias	O
William	B-pers
Cranfield	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Awdley	I-pers
,	O
Roger	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wiggan	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported,9	O
.	O
B	O
-	O
S	O
-	O
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Steps	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Barton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Oldfield	I-pers
,	O
Alice	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
alias	O
Adams	O
,	O
Barnet	B-pers
Egan	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
George	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand,2	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
,	O
S	O
-	O
T	O
-	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,6	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Otway	I-pers
,6	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Shannon	I-pers
,12	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
pleaded	O
her	O
Belly	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
being	O
impannel	O
'd	O
,	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
not	O
with	O
quick	O
Child	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
The	O
First	O
and	O
Second	O
volumes	O
of	O
Remarkable	O
Tryals	O
,	O
Behaviour	O
and	O
Dying	O
Speeches	O
,	O
of	O
notorious	O
Malefactors	O
,	O
having	O
met	O
with	O
so	O
kind	O
a	O
Reception	O
by	O
the	O
Publick	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
carry	O
off	O
the	O
First	O
Impression	O
:	O
There	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
Press	O
and	O
will	O
speadily	O
be	O
Publish	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Third	O
and	O
Fourth	O
Volumes	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
continuation	O
of	O
them	O
down	O
to	O
this	O
present	O
Year,1718	O
.	O
Which	O
will	O
contain	O
as	O
follows	O
.	O
THE	O
Adventures	O
Tryals	O
Behaviour	O
and	O
Dying	O
Speeches	O
of	O
the	O
German	O
Princess	O
,	O
Jack-fall	O
the	O
Chimney	O
Sweeper	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Low	I-pers
,	O
Stephen	B-pers
Bance	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Montisano	I-pers
,	O
Deborah	B-pers
Charchill	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Iorrot	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Maw	I-pers
,	O
Andrew	B-pers
Baynes	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Weymouth	I-pers
,	O
Kit	B-pers
Dickson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
,	O
Tony	B-pers
Gery	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Lullom	I-pers
,	O
Rodery	B-pers
Andery	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Awdery	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Awdery	I-pers
and	O
Mary	O
Awdery	O
3-	O
Macknammar	O
and	O
-	O
Douaghu	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
other	O
Notorions	O
Offenders	O
,	O
pick	O
Pockets	O
and	O
House-Breachers	O
;	O
Richard	B-pers
Royston	I-pers
the	O
Rich	O
Beggar	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Helloway	I-pers
,	O
Patrick	B-pers
Harlay	I-pers
,	O
Andrew	B-pers
Harpet	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Goodmen	I-pers
and	O
Heavy	O
Powel	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
other	O
Remarkable	O
Highway-	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Chessey	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
for	O
Robbing	O
the	O
Mail	O
;	O
James	B-pers
Nallar	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Calcon	I-pers
,	O
Web	O
Rawllor	O
,	O
Gabriel	B-pers
Half	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Rawlins	I-pers
,	O
for	O
the	O
Mathew	O
of	O
Hamson	O
in	O
the	O
Farthing	O
Pye	O
Field	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Bowen	I-pers
for	O
the	O
Marthes	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Barna	I-pers
for	O
the	O
Marther	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Edgebrook	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Ratcliff-High-Way	O
and	O
cutting	O
ber	O
in	O
Pieces	O
;	O
Alice	O
Hall	O
for	O
Poisoning	O
Parish	O
Children	O
,	O
for	O
Killing	O
Sir	O
Cholmley	O
Dearsag	O
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Cronch	I-pers
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
at	O
Shipperton	O
,	O
Grace	B-pers
Trip	I-pers
for	O
Murdering	O
Madam	O
Bhoodel	O
,	O
the	O
Lord	O
Turrington	O
's	O
House-Keeper	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
for	O
Poisoning	O
her	O
Mistress	O
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
for	O
cutting	O
the	O
Throat	O
of	O
a	O
Day	O
of	O
Six	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Holloway	I-pers
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Howaden	I-pers
,	O
for	O
Killing	O
Mr.	O
Spurling	O
,	O
the	O
Turnkey	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
Colonel	O
Hamilton	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Duel	O
between	O
Dake	O
Hamilton	O
and	O
Lord	O
Mohan	O
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Goslin	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
Watermen	O
for	O
Murdering	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
their	O
Boat	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Keel	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Lowther	I-pers
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Keepers	O
of	O
Clerkenwell	O
Bridewel	O
,	O
Joyce	B-pers
Hodges	I-pers
,	O
for	O
Murdering	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
Henry	O
nket	O
,	O
for	O
cutting	O
his	O
Friends	O
'	O
Throat	O
,	O
at	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Visit	O
,	O
Richard	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Field	I-pers
,	O
for	O
Murdering	O
the	O
Pipe-makers	O
Wife	O
at	O
Oxbridge	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Parkhurst	O
for	O
killing	O
Count	O
Pleura	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Staples	I-pers
for	O
Shooting	O
his	O
Wives	O
Gallant	O
,	O
William	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Thurland	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Madam	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Cocterel	I-pers
,	O
for	O
Killing	O
Esq	O
;	O
Carpenter	O
's	O
Mas	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Tempkins	I-pers
,	O
for	O
Murdering	O
his	O
Fellow	O
Servant	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Gristich	I-pers
,	O
for	O
cutting	O
off	O
his	O
Fellow	O
Servants	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
Barying	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
Danghill	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Sweethones	I-pers
,	O
for	O
a	O
Murther	O
and	O
Robery	O
at	O
Aston	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Mounsiours	I-pers
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Hemingaul	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
for	O
Murdering	O
her	O
Sister-in-Law	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Jastley	I-pers
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murthers	O
of	O
a	O
Woman	O
and	O
her	O
Child	O
at	O
Branford	O
,	O
the	O
Marquess	O
de	O
Paleotti	O
,	O
for	O
Killing	O
his	O
Man	O
Nicolo	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Remarkable	O
Marthers	O
.	O
Captain	O
Smith	O
,	O
Captain	O
Oobreel	B-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Peacock	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Tipping	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
&	O
c.	O
for	O
Pyracy	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ruffel	I-pers
Hugh	B-pers
Leeson	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Blandford	I-pers
,	O
&	O
c.	O
for	O
Rapes	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Dianaree	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Purchase	I-pers
,	O
for	O
pulling	O
down	O
Dr.	O
Burges	O
's	O
Mr.	O
Bradbury	O
's	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Meeting-Houses	O
;	O
Sir	O
Mark	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Squib	I-pers
,	O
Hugh	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Reading	I-pers
and	O
Dermot	O
for	O
Mubocking	O
,	O
Cotton	O
and	O
Warren	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
Riot	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Casey	I-pers
,	O
for	O
a	O
Riot	O
and	O
Murder	O
,	O
Pye	O
,	O
Harvey	O
,	O
Stringer	O
,	O
Tyler	O
and	O
Canon	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
Riot	O
;	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bean	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Purchase	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Love	I-pers
,	O
Richard	O
price	O
and	O
Nsth	O
,	O
for	O
pulling	O
down	O
the	O
Mug-House	O
,	O
in	O
Salisbury-Court	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Beaves	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Eldridge	I-pers
,	O
Hester	B-pers
Stibs	I-pers
and	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Hornby	I-pers
,	O
for	O
a	O
Riot	O
in	O
C-lebrating	O
Tho	O
:	O
Beans	O
Burial	O
;	O
Robert	B-pers
Read	I-pers
,	O
for	O
Shooting	O
Daniel	B-pers
Vanghan	I-pers
,	O
Captain	O
of	O
the	O
Mob	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Boacher	I-pers
,	O
&	O
c.	O
for	O
Sodony	O
,	O
Town	O
the	O
Tallow-Chandier	O
,	O
for	O
defranding	O
his	O
Creditors	O
,	O
William	O
alias	O
Humburg	O
Skelson	O
Beanmore	O
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jacobs	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Morris	O
,	O
for	O
forging	O
Betten	O
Testimonial	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
procure	O
Ordination	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Panton	I-pers
for	O
Filling	O
Gistness	O
.	O
Evidence	O
Poller	O
for	O
Cheating	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Panton	I-pers
,	O
Car	O
and	O
Lewis	B-pers
Barbanjano	I-pers
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Gold	O
Changers	O
.	O
Two	O
Gypses	O
for	O
Seducing	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
Robber	O
Master	O
.	O
Lewis	B-pers
Amand	I-pers
de	O
la	O
Cour	O
.	O
John	O
Bournoiz	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Colethurst	I-pers
,	O
Henry	O
Whitehead	O
a	O
Cleargyman	O
,	O
for	O
Reditional	O
and	O
Treasonable	O
Words	O
,	O
Jasper	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
;	O
for	O
tearing	O
the	O
Register	O
of	O
St.	O
Andrew	O
Holbown	O
.	O
Two	O
Grave	O
Diggers	O
for	O
Digging	O
up	O
and	O
Selling	O
the	O
Dead	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Sullivan	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Whitty	I-pers
and	O
Felix	B-pers
O	I-pers
Hara	I-pers
,	O
for	O
Listing	O
Mos	O
for	O
the	O
Prectender	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Francia	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Shepward	I-pers
,	O
Ec	O
.	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
Lawerence	O
Homes	O
,	O
George	B-pers
Hint	I-pers
,	O
for	O
Writing	O
Treasonable	O
Libets	O
,	O
Isage	O
Dustan	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	O
for	O
Publishing	O
the	O
Shift	O
Shifted	O
,	O
Etc	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Dalton	I-pers
a	O
Sw	O
and	O
many	O
other	O
Remarkable	O
Tryals	O
,	O
too	O
many	O
to	O
be	O
Jefested	O
hent	O
.	O
A	O
Water	O
that	O
perfectly	O
the	O
Itch	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
I	O
in	O
a	O
time	O
without	O
secondary	O
of	O
purging	O
or	O
the	O
Dangerous	O
life	O
of	O
Murcury	O
,	O
Price	O
1	O
s.6	O
d.	O
Prepared	O
and	O
Sold	O
only	O
by	O
A.	O
Dawning	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
and	O
Bell	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Dark-love	O
in	O
West-Smithfield	O
.	O
Where	O
also	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
,	O
the	O
true	O
Spirits	O
of	O
Scory-	O
;	O
Parging	O
and	O
;	O
and	O
Spirits	O
of	O
Ground-lay	O
at	O
1	O
s.	O
each	O
Bottla	O
.	O
Likewise	O
,	O
a	O
Remedy	O
for	O
the	O
Tooth-	O
,	O
the	O
most	O
for	O
their	O
use	O
of	O
any	O
yet	O
known	O
,	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
To	O
prevent	O
and	O
care	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
in	O
the	O
Gums	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
preserve	O
and	O
fasten	O
loose	O
Teeth	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
And	O
also	O
a	O
most	O
successful	O
Plai	O
to	O
prevent	O
in	O
Vinmen	O
,	O
which	O
has	O
help	O
'd	O
beyond	O
exploitation	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
hope	O
of	O
Relief	O
Price	O
5	O
s.	O
for	O
the	O
Clint	O
of	O
the	O
Publick	O
.	O
WHereas	O
several	O
Gentlewomen	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
that	O
Sex	O
,	O
in	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
have	O
contrasted	O
an	O
Evil	O
Habit	O
of	O
Body	O
,	O
wherein	O
the	O
Humours	O
,	O
at	O
Sorit	O
dispos	O
'd	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Whole	O
,	O
come	O
at	O
length	O
to	O
be	O
lodged	O
in	O
one	O
Part	O
or	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
times	O
,	O
for	O
too	O
long	O
to	O
be	O
here	O
mentioned	O
,	O
are	O
thrown	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
occasionally	O
a	O
dangerous	O
in	O
that	O
Part	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
at	O
as	O
Money	O
.	O
Some	O
BOOKS	O
Printed	O
for	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
Edmund	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
and	O
Crown	O
in	O
Lombard	O
Street	O
,	O
near	O
Stock	O
,	O
Market	O
.	O
AESOP	O
's	O
Fables	O
,	O
with	O
Morals	O
and	O
Restriction	O
,	O
as	O
improv	O
'd	O
by	O
Sir	O
Roger	B-pers
L'Estrange	I-pers
,	O
done	O
into	O
Variety	O
of	O
English	O
Verie	O
.	O
Illustrated	O
with	O
Cuts	O
curiously	O
engrav	O
'd	O
on	O
Copper	O
Plates	O
.	O
The	O
Second	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
2	O
s.6	O
d.	O
The	O
London	O
,	O
New	O
Method	O
and	O
Art	O
of	O
Teaching	O
Children	O
to	O
Spell	O
and	O
Read	O
;	O
so	O
as	O
they	O
may	O
,	O
without	O
the	O
Help	O
of	O
any	O
other	O
Books	O
,	O
read	O
the	O
Bible	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
twelve	O
Months	O
Note	O
,	O
This	O
Way	O
of	O
Teaching	O
is	O
approved	O
by	O
most	O
school	O
Masters	O
as	O
the	O
best	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
6	O
d.	O
with	O
great	O
Allowance	O
to	O
those	O
who	O
sell	O
or	O
give	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
Note	O
,	O
There	O
are	O
some	O
printed	O
on	O
Fine	O
Paper	O
,	O
bound	O
up	O
with	O
Cuts	O
.	O
pt.8	O
d.	O
M.	O
Jordsine	O
's	O
Duodecimal	O
Arithmeick	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
most	O
Cocise	O
and	O
Exact	O
Method	O
extant	O
.	O
In	O
Three	O
Books	O
.	O
Contains	O
,	O
Notation	O
,	O
Addition	O
,	O
Subtraction	O
,	O
Multiplication	O
,	O
Division	O
,	O
Reduction	O
,	O
Extraction	O
of	O
the	O
Square	O
and	O
Cube	O
Root	O
,	O
Rule	O
of	O
Proportion	O
Direct	O
and	O
Reverse	O
,	O
Dmedecimall	O
y	O
performed	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
Practically	O
applied	O
to	O
the	O
measuring	O
of	O
all	O
sorts	O
or	O
Superficies	O
,	O
and	O
Solids	O
,	O
as	O
Board	O
,	O
Glass	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Timber	O
,	O
Stone	O
,	O
scott	O
Guaging	O
of	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
Brewers	O
Tuns	O
and	O
Casks	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
and	O
with	O
more	O
Ease	O
and	O
Expedition	O
,	O
than	O
by	O
Velgar	O
or	O
Decimal	O
Arithmetick	O
.	O
Very	O
Useful	O
for	O
all	O
sorts	O
o	O
'	O
Men	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
Gentlemen	O
as	O
others	O
,	O
but	O
especially	O
for	O
Merchants	O
,	O
Writing	O
Masters	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
Measuring	O
Artificers	O
.	O
And	O
all	O
the	O
Rules	O
made	O
Plan	O
,	O
and	O
Easie	O
for	O
the	O
meanest	O
Capacity.800	O
.	O
Price	O
Bound	O
2	O
s.6	O
d.	O
The	O
Benefit	O
of	O
Early	O
Piety	O
recommended	O
in	O
all	O
Young	O
Persons	O
,	O
and	O
particularly	O
to	O
those	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
La	O
By	O
W.	O
Smythies	O
,	O
late	O
Morning	O
Lecturer	O
of	O
St.	O
Michael	O
to	O
Cornhil	O
,	O
London	O
.	O
The	O
Third	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
Daily	O
Self-Examinant	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
An	O
earnest	O
Persuasive	O
to	O
the	O
Duty	O
of	O
Daily	O
Self-Examination	O
;	O
with	O
Devout	O
Prayers	O
,	O
Meditations	O
,	O
Directions	O
and	O
Ejaculations	O
for	O
an	O
Holy	O
Life	O
and	O
Happy	O
Death	O
,	O
By	O
R.	O
Warren	O
,	O
D.D.6th	O
Edit	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
Communicant	O
's	O
constant	O
Exercise	O
.	O
In	O
Three	O
Parts	O
Containing	O
.	O
I	O
Am	O
earnest	O
xhocation	O
to	O
the	O
Communication	O
:	O
With	O
proper	O
Devotions	O
Before	O
,	O
At	O
,	O
and	O
After	O
Receivias	O
II	O
.	O
His	O
Duty	O
of	O
Consideration	O
,	O
Resolution	O
,	O
and	O
actual	O
Amendment	O
after	O
Receiving	O
the	O
Blessed	O
Sacrament	O
.	O
III	O
.	O
The	O
continual	O
Pleasure	O
of	O
a	O
Religious	O
Life	O
.	O
And	O
Devout	O
Prayers	O
fukable	O
to	O
each	O
important	O
Subject	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
last	O
Parts	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
bound	O
up	O
together	O
or	O
regly	O
.	O
A	O
Devout	O
Christians	O
Preparative	O
to	O
Death	O
.	O
Written	O
by	O
Krafmns	O
,	O
now	O
reader	O
'd	O
into	O
English	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
are	O
added	O
,	O
Meditations	O
,	O
Prayers	O
and	O
Directions	O
for	O
Sick	O
and	O
Dying	O
Persons	O
.	O
Recommended	O
as	O
proper	O
to	O
be	O
given	O
as	O
Funerals	O
.	O
The	O
Sixth	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
6	O
d.	O
or	O
two	O
Guineas	O
per	O
Hundred	O
to	O
those	O
who	O
give	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
These	O
Three	O
by	O
Robert	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
,	O
D.	O
D.	O
Rector	O
of	O
Chairman	O
in	O
Kent	O
.	O
The	O
Daily	O
Companion	O
,	O
with	O
Christian	O
Supports	O
under	O
the	O
Troubles	O
of	O
this	O
World	O
,	O
to	O
comfort	O
and	O
succour	O
all	O
those	O
who	O
in	O
this	O
Transitory	O
Life	O
are	O
in	O
Trouble	O
,	O
Sorrow	O
,	O
Need	O
,	O
Sickness	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
other	O
Adventy	O
.	O
Upto	O
which	O
are	O
added	O
,	O
Prayers	O
and	O
Meditations	O
,	O
suitable	O
for	O
all	O
Persons	O
afficted	O
in	O
Mind	O
,	O
Body	O
or	O
Estate	O
.	O
The	O
Fourth	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
6	O
d.	O
or	O
two	O
Guineas	O
per	O
Hundred	O
to	O
those	O
that	O
give	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
Orders	O
,	O
By-Laws	O
,	O
and	O
Ordinances	O
for	O
the	O
good	O
Government	O
and	O
Regulating	O
of	O
the	O
Persons	O
Licensed	O
to	O
Keep	O
and	O
Drive	O
Hackoey-Coaches	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
Renters	O
and	O
Drivers	O
.	O
Made	O
,	O
Publish	O
'd	O
and	O
Declar	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Commissioners	O
;	O
and	O
Allowed	O
and	O
Approved	O
by	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chancellor	O
and	O
Judges	O
as	O
the	O
Law	O
directs	O
.	O
Price	O
3	O
d.	O
The	O
following	O
Books	O
are	O
given	O
Gratis	O
.	O
1st	O
,	O
THE	O
Practical	O
Scheme	O
of	O
the	O
Secret	O
Disease	O
and	O
Broken	O
Constitutions	O
,	O
by	O
Fast	O
Living	O
,	O
Former	O
ill	O
Cures	O
,	O
Salivations	O
and	O
Mercury	O
-2ly	O
.	O
The	O
New	O
System	O
of	O
the	O
GOUT	O
and	O
Rhenmatison	O
,	O
drawn	O
from	O
Reason	O
,	O
Amtomical	O
Observations	O
and	O
Experience.-3ly	O
,	O
A	O
Rational	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Chase	O
,	O
Nature	O
,	O
and	O
Cure	O
of	O
WEAKNESSES	O
usually	O
attending	O
Persons	O
after	O
Former	O
,	O
Cures	O
,	O
Over-	O
,	O
Self-abuses	O
,	O
Hard	O
,	O
miscarrages	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Where	O
in	O
is	O
given	O
a	O
full	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
burrid	O
Nature	O
,	O
and	O
most	O
measurable	O
Consequences	O
of	O
Self	O
.	O
A	O
houses	O
in	O
particular	O
.	O
These	O
Books	O
(	O
all	O
New	O
Edition	O
)	O
are	O
given	O
Gratis	O
Up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
ANODYNE	O
.	O
NECK-LACE	O
,	O
without	O
Temple	O
Bar	O
.	O
At	O
Mr.	O
Cowpers	O
Toyshop	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Charles	O
Court	O
by	O
ford-Market	O
in	O
the	O
Stand	O
,	O
And	O
And	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Gurraway	O
's	O
,	O
Shop	O
at	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms	O
at	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange-Gate	O
next	O
Cornhill	O
.	O
