TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
,	O
ON	O
Friday	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
30th	O
and	O
31st	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
1718	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Fourth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
LEWEN	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
King	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Mountagus	I-pers
;	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Deputy	O
-	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
Names	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Nathall	I-pers
John	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
Daniel	B-pers
Robertson	I-pers
John	B-pers
Barket	I-pers
William	B-pers
Noy	I-pers
William	B-pers
Meakins	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Archer	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Loader	I-pers
John	B-pers
Banker	I-pers
John	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Bruce	B-pers
Randal	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Partridge	I-pers
Hecter	B-pers
Mackenzie	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Whitting	I-pers
Percival	B-pers
Ludgate	I-pers
John	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
Benjamin	B-pers
Forster	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
John	B-pers
Walkingham	I-pers
David	B-pers
Fysield	I-pers
James	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Frances	B-pers
Jacobs	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Christ	B-place
Church	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
26	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Gum	O
Elamy	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Antrim	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Shop	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
buying	O
some	O
Coco-Nuts	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Gum	O
Elamy	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
suspecting	O
she	O
had	O
stollen	O
it	O
,	O
remembring	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
such	O
Gum	O
lie	O
in	O
his	O
Neighbour	O
a	O
Druggist	O
's	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
sending	O
to	O
enquire	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
came	O
and	O
owned	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
pleading	O
she	O
used	O
to	O
deal	O
in	O
such	O
things	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
finding	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
Handkerchief	O
among	O
some	O
Chocolate	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
brought	O
it	O
from	O
home	O
.	O
This	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
for	O
7	O
Years	O
.	O
Hugh	B-pers
Alford	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
Ludgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Ann	B-pers
May	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Pocket	O
,	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
Thread	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
d.	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
passing	O
under	O
Ludgate	O
at	O
about	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
met	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Jostle	O
,	O
pull	O
'd	O
of	O
her	O
Pocket	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
pursuing	O
him	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
him	O
till	O
the	O
Watch	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
Assistance	O
upon	O
her	O
calling	O
out	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
another	O
Evidence	O
:	O
Yet	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
for	O
7	O
Years	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Wade	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bartholomew	I-place
the	I-place
Great	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
poor	O
Woman	O
,	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
to	O
assist	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servants	O
in	O
washing	O
Dishes	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
the	O
Time	O
of	O
the	O
Passover	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
take	O
the	O
Spoon	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
owned	O
upon	O
her	O
being	O
apprehended	O
:	O
But	O
yet	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
for	O
7	O
Years	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Whittle	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Serjeant	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
FleetStreet	O
he	O
felt	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Hand	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
out	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
and	O
thrust	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
Breeches	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
pursued	O
him	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
seized	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
great	O
Complaint	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
barbarously	O
used	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
,	O
made	O
all	O
over	O
of	O
a	O
gore	O
Blood	O
,	O
and	O
bled	O
at	O
least	O
near	O
a	O
Pint	O
and	O
half	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
indeed	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
but	O
not	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
be	O
in	O
pursuing	O
him	O
,	O
his	O
Sword	O
got	O
between	O
his	O
Legs	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
the	O
start	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
calling	O
out	O
to	O
stop	O
him	O
,	O
some	O
body	O
did	O
knock	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
J.	O
H.	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
seized	O
him	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
him	O
ill	O
,	O
for	O
pursuing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
his	O
causing	O
a	O
Riot	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
now	O
prosecuting	O
the	O
said	O
Constable	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
for	O
7	O
Years	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Capstock	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
6	O
Pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Edge	I-pers
,	O
and	O
13	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
32	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Fosset	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Wall	I-pers
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
employed	O
to	O
assist	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
Dye-house	O
for	O
two	O
Days	O
,	O
stole	O
the	O
Stockings	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
(	O
Death	O
.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Cutler	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Hillenden	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Linnen	O
Headclothes	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
having	O
washed	O
the	O
Linnen	O
hung	O
it	O
to	O
dry	O
on	O
a	O
Hedge	O
,	O
and	O
missing	O
it	O
was	O
inform	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
seen	O
lurking	O
near	O
the	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
taxing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
them	O
he	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
from	O
a	O
Hedge	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
bid	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
for	O
7	O
Years	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lawler	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
Carcass	O
of	O
a	O
Lamb	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kotum	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Lamb	O
hanging	O
at	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
was	O
carried	O
away	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
pursued	O
was	O
apprehended	O
with	O
the	O
Lamb	O
under	O
her	O
Arm	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
disorder	O
'd	O
in	O
her	O
Head	O
and	O
crazy	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
nor	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
owned	O
indeed	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
drunk	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
Disorder	O
did	O
not	O
excuse	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
for	O
7	O
Years	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ryley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pocket	O
,	O
9	O
Keys	O
,	O
18	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Hilliard	I-pers
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
having	O
been	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
was	O
set	O
down	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
Charles-Court	B-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Strand	I-place
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
standing	O
there	O
and	O
seeing	O
her	O
pay	O
the	O
Coachman	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
great	O
Violence	O
pulled	O
it	O
off	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
pursuing	O
him	O
and	O
crying	O
out	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
seized	O
before	O
he	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
sight	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Pocket	O
was	O
conveyed	O
away	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
two	O
Men	O
that	O
immediately	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
pulled	O
off	O
her	O
Pocket	O
ran	O
to	O
him	O
as	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
run	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
both	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
also	O
a	O
Note	O
produced	O
by	O
the	O
Constable	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
thrown	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Round-house-Window	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
secured	O
there	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Acquaintance	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Constable	O
seized	O
him	O
immediately	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
:	O
This	O
Note	O
contained	O
a	O
Confirmation	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
swearing	O
positively	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
pulled	O
off	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
(	O
Death	O
.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Shipley	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
reach	O
his	O
Hand	O
over	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Window	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
Shoes	O
off	O
from	O
a	O
Shelf	O
and	O
go	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
pursued	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Shoes	O
in	O
his	O
Bosom	O
.	O
Notwithstanding	O
he	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Shoes	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
for	O
7	O
Years	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
and	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
value	O
35	O
s.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
Unkle	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
very	O
kind	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
being	O
Apprentice	O
grew	O
disorderly	O
and	O
absented	O
himself	O
from	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
to	O
his	O
Unkle	O
took	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
or	O
carrying	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
at	O
his	O
Apprehension	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
alledg	O
'd	O
they	O
were	O
given	O
him	O
by	O
his	O
Aunt	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
not	O
proving	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transported	O
for	O
7	O
Years	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Lang	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Pitts	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Adderson	I-pers
,	O
for	O
an	O
Assault	O
upon	O
John	B-pers
Forrel	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
and	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
been	O
ill	O
used	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Associates	O
,	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
and	O
beat	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Handkerchief	O
were	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
both	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Comrades	O
were	O
Persons	O
of	O
no	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
also	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
Drink	O
and	O
very	O
quarrelsom	O
:	O
But	O
it	O
not	O
being	O
sufficiently	O
proved	O
that	O
the	O
Assault	O
was	O
made	O
with	O
a	O
felonious	O
Intent	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Washington	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Parcels	O
of	O
Silks	O
and	O
Calicoes	O
,	O
value	O
55	O
l.	O
from	O
George	B-pers
Dondswell	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Journey-man	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
taken	O
divers	O
Opportunities	O
of	O
taking	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
small	O
Parcels	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
carried	O
them	O
out	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
at	O
fourteen	O
different	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
twice	O
as	O
many	O
different	O
Tittles	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Pawn-brokers	O
suspecting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
inform	O
'd	O
the	O
Master	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
whole	O
;	O
gave	O
his	O
Master	O
a	O
Catalogue	O
of	O
each	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Goods	O
pawn	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
several	O
places	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
found	O
and	O
had	O
according	O
to	O
his	O
Direction	O
,	O
which	O
Goods	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
with	O
a	O
Felonious	O
Intent	O
,	O
to	O
wrong	O
his	O
Master	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
in	O
Debt	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
pressed	O
by	O
his	O
Creditors	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Expectation	O
he	O
had	O
from	O
his	O
Friends	O
depending	O
upon	O
his	O
being	O
in	O
Business	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
Money	O
to	O
come	O
up	O
from	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
delayed	O
some	O
Month	O
;	O
longer	O
than	O
he	O
expected	O
,	O
did	O
make	O
bold	O
to	O
pawn	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Goods	O
,	O
with	O
Intent	O
when	O
he	O
received	O
his	O
Money	O
to	O
have	O
redeemed	O
them	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
carried	O
them	O
again	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Shop	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
indeed	O
call	O
several	O
Persons	O
he	O
had	O
formerly	O
served	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
;	O
and	O
some	O
that	O
did	O
confirm	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
of	O
Money	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
receive	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
delayed	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
at	O
last	O
come	O
,	O
but	O
just	O
before	O
his	O
Apprehension	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
his	O
Allegations	O
did	O
appear	O
probable	O
.	O
But	O
these	O
Excuses	O
not	O
being	O
allowable	O
in	O
such	O
Cases	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Devereux	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
Linnen	O
,	O
value	O
35	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
Benson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
stollen	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
seen	O
by	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
under	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Arm	O
and	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
pursued	O
and	O
taken	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
Essex	O
Man	O
of	O
War	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
them	O
a	O
Pressing	O
,	O
but	O
staying	O
behind	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
after	O
them	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
being	O
very	O
drunk	O
.	O
In	O
answer	O
to	O
this	O
the	O
Constable	O
deposed	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
first	O
apprehended	O
he	O
appear	O
'd	O
very	O
sober	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
carrying	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
he	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
very	O
drunk	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
scarce	O
hold	O
him	O
up	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
sober	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
scarce	O
keep	O
him	O
from	O
running	O
away	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Henrietta	B-pers
Brady	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Pancrass	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
Yard	O
of	O
Muslin	O
and	O
Edging	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Evan	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
the	O
12th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
employed	O
to	O
tend	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Child	O
,	O
stole	O
the	O
things	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
She	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
sufficient	O
Proof	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Cutler	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Canvas	O
Bag	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
28	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
18	O
l.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Roff	I-pers
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
the	O
Son	O
of	O
an	O
intimate	O
Acquaintance	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
from	O
his	O
Infancy	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
about	O
11	O
a-Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Forenoon	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
made	O
him	O
welcome	O
,	O
fetching	O
a	O
Full	O
Pot	O
of	O
Drink	O
and	O
putting	O
some	O
Brandy	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
fetch	O
'd	O
more	O
Drink	O
into	O
which	O
he	O
put	O
more	O
Brandy	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
drank	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lay	O
down	O
on	O
his	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
thought	O
slept	O
;	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
he	O
lighted	O
a	O
Pipe	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
for	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Staid	O
till	O
about	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
he	O
look	O
'd	O
for	O
his	O
Flask	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
look	O
'd	O
for	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
put	O
in	O
a	O
Nook	O
in	O
the	O
Chimney-Corner	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
gone	O
too	O
:	O
that	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
no	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
there	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
put	O
a	O
Crown	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
brought	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Darrel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Queenhithe	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
9	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Spurs	O
,	O
value	O
35	O
s.	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Augustin	B-pers
Meadows	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
black	O
Hood	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Wakeford	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Augustin	B-pers
Meadows	I-pers
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
lesing	O
Goods	O
at	O
divers	O
times	O
,	O
suspected	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
taxing	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
acknowledged	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
of	O
them	O
he	O
found	O
accordingly	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
lent	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Money	O
upon	O
the	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
and	O
brought	O
a	O
written	O
Order	O
for	O
the	O
selling	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
saying	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
Master	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Foreign	O
Ambassador	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
owing	O
her	O
40	O
s.	O
for	O
Wages	O
,	O
order	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Surplusage	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
they	O
were	O
sold	O
for	O
,	O
more	O
than	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
pawn	O
'd	O
for	O
,	O
for	O
her	O
Wages	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
pleaded	O
,	O
her	O
Master	O
had	O
absconded	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Mistress	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
pawn	O
for	O
her	O
Use	O
;	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
not	O
willing	O
her	O
Master	O
should	O
know	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Upon	O
hearing	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Warman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Stuff	O
Curtains	O
and	O
a	O
Curtain-Rod	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Roger	B-pers
Ewbank	I-pers
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
kept	O
the	O
Sun-Tavern	B-place
in	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
seen	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servants	O
lurking	O
about	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
Entry	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
watch	O
'd	O
,	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
a	O
Room	O
below	O
Stairs	O
,	O
cut	O
of	O
which	O
Company	O
was	O
just	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
followed	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
had	O
taken	O
down	O
the	O
Curtains	O
and	O
Rod	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
Servant	O
went	O
in	O
threw	O
them	O
down	O
behind	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
alledged	O
he	O
only	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
inquire	O
for	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Day	I-pers
,	O
and	O
was	O
no	O
further	O
than	O
the	O
Entry	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Kin	O
g	O
's	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
otherwise	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
for	O
7	O
Years	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Burnet	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bow	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Callicoe	O
Pocket	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
d.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Thimble	O
gilt	O
with	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
14	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
in	O
Bow	O
Church-Yard	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
followed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Coachman	O
jumping	O
off	O
his	O
Coach-Box	O
apprehended	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Pocket	O
was	O
not	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
Coachman	O
who	O
apprehended	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
cautious	O
of	O
swearing	O
positively	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
took	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
dark	O
;	O
but	O
said	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
person	O
she	O
did	O
verily	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
a	O
Cry	O
of	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
ran	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
was	O
apprehended	O
by	O
the	O
Coachman	O
.	O
This	O
pretence	O
and	O
the	O
Gentlewoman	O
's	O
Cautiousness	O
availed	O
him	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Ferryman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Camblet	O
Pocket	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
3	O
Handkerchiefs	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
Snuff-box	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
7	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Lydia	B-pers
Ashley	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
passing	O
along	O
Ludgate-Hill	B-place
about	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
her	O
Pocket	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
before	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
her	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
turned	O
back	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
give	O
the	O
second	O
pull	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
the	O
Pocket	O
came	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
thereupon	O
he	O
pursued	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
crying	O
out	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ran	O
along	O
crying	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
cryed	O
out	O
;	O
stop	O
him	O
who	O
cryes	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
seized	O
by	O
another	O
person	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
his	O
Door	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Baily	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
the	O
Out-cry	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
towards	O
Ludgate-Hill	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
running	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
Thief	O
was	O
a	O
Man	O
that	O
ran	O
before	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
not	O
believing	O
him	O
,	O
held	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Pocket	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
at	O
some	O
small	O
distance	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
for	O
7	O
Years	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
,	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
Company	O
of	O
People	O
standing	O
together	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
pass	O
'd	O
along	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
was	O
pick	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
who	O
did	O
it	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
,	O
a	O
Lad	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Hand	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
ran	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
seized	O
him	O
,	O
taxing	O
him	O
with	O
stealing	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
saying	O
keep	O
it	O
,	O
keep	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
held	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
of	O
an	O
Errand	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
lie	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
only	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
for	O
giving	O
it	O
the	O
right	O
Owner	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Gerrard	B-pers
Pell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminister	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Brass	O
Cocks	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Court	I-pers
the	O
22d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Necessary	O
House	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
another	O
Pint	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
an	O
Excuse	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
pass	O
'd	O
by	O
him	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
your	O
Humble	O
Servant	O
;	O
he	O
saying	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
kindly	O
Welcome	O
,	O
not	O
knowing	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
.	O
The	O
Servant	O
deposed	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
adding	O
that	O
he	O
going	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
to	O
draw	O
some	O
Sider	O
,	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
Stairs	O
different	O
from	O
what	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
asking	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
pretended	O
he	O
had	O
mistaken	O
his	O
way	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
saw	O
the	O
Cock	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
But	O
of	O
Stout	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Cask	O
of	O
Sider	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Liquors	O
running	O
about	O
the	O
Cellar	O
;	O
however	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
off	O
for	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
by	O
accident	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
he	O
ever	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
his	O
Life	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
contrary	O
being	O
sufficiently	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
for	O
7	O
Years	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Gibbons	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Doulton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Enfield	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Cows	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Pepper	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Cow	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Pigot	I-pers
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
One	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
live	O
at	O
Enfield	O
not	O
long	O
before	O
,	O
having	O
taken	O
a	O
Cottage	O
of	O
45	O
s.	O
per	O
Annum	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
no	O
Land	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
was	O
observed	O
to	O
have	O
Cattle	O
which	O
were	O
fed	O
upon	O
Enfield-Chase	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Ann	B-pers
Pigot	I-pers
lost	O
a	O
Cow	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
drive	O
from	O
the	O
Chase	O
and	O
own	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
.	O
General	O
Pepper	O
's	O
Servant	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
hearing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
suspected	O
,	O
and	O
knowing	O
that	O
the	O
General	O
had	O
lost	O
two	O
Cows	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
among	O
his	O
Cattle	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
about	O
6	O
Months	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
since	O
lost	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Cattle	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
two	O
Cows	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Marks	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
cut	O
or	O
filed	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
Horns	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
Beasts	O
to	O
be	O
General	O
Pepper	O
's	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Cows	O
were	O
all	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
them	O
ever	O
since	O
Bartholo-tide	O
last	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
Welsh-Fair	O
at	O
Clerkenwell	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
he	O
brought	O
an	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
he	O
bought	O
two	O
such	O
Beasts	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
which	O
very	O
near	O
or	O
altogether	O
answered	O
the	O
Description	O
:	O
He	O
produced	O
several	O
Persons	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
and	O
industrious	O
Man	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
keep	O
Cows	O
,	O
succle	O
Calves	O
,	O
sell	O
Milk	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
for	O
a	O
Living	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
before	O
he	O
removed	O
to	O
Enfield	O
lived	O
very	O
honestly	O
at	O
Kentish-Town	O
,	O
but	O
meeting	O
with	O
Misfortunes	O
,	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
leave	O
that	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Doulton	O
:	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
always	O
behav	O
'd	O
himself	O
very	O
honestly	O
and	O
industriously	O
.	O
Upon	O
hearing	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Groves	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sorrel	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Nathanael	B-pers
Dod	I-pers
,	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
Horse	O
upon	O
Enfield-Chase	B-place
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sold	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Person	O
who	O
bought	O
the	O
Horse	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sold	O
him	O
a	O
Horse	O
for	O
3	O
l.10	O
s.	O
and	O
engaged	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
were	O
own	O
'd	O
within	O
a	O
Twelve	O
Month	O
and	O
a	O
Day	O
he	O
would	O
return	O
his	O
Money	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
bought	O
the	O
Horse	O
above	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
own	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Keeper	O
of	O
the	O
Lodge-House	O
in	O
Enfield-Chase	O
belonging	O
to	O
General	O
Pepper	O
and	O
finding	O
a	O
stray	O
Horse	O
upon	O
the	O
Chase	O
he	O
enquir	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
owner	O
but	O
could	O
hear	O
of	O
none	O
,	O
although	O
he	O
had	O
rid	O
him	O
from	O
Town	O
to	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
Fair	O
to	O
Fair	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
inform	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Country	O
People	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
(	O
as	O
he	O
understood	O
them	O
)	O
sell	O
the	O
House	O
in	O
a	O
Twelve	O
Month	O
and	O
a	O
Day	O
the	O
buyer	O
and	O
he	O
meeting	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
both	O
in	O
drink	O
struck	O
the	O
Bargin	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Intent	O
at	O
all	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
but	O
mistaking	O
the	O
matter	O
of	O
keeping	O
him	O
a	O
Twelve	O
Month	O
and	O
a	O
Day	O
and	O
then	O
selling	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
understood	O
he	O
might	O
sell	O
him	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
within	O
a	O
Twelve	O
Month	O
and	O
a	O
Days	O
.	O
Some	O
Persons	O
from	O
General	O
Pepper	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
Honest	O
Man	O
,	O
who	O
having	O
behav	O
'd	O
himself	O
for	O
16	O
Years	O
very	O
well	O
in	O
the	O
Army	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
grown	O
in	O
Years	O
had	O
been	O
put	O
into	O
that	O
Employment	O
by	O
the	O
General	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
rather	O
the	O
Effects	O
of	O
Ignorance	O
and	O
Liquor	O
than	O
a	O
Felonious	O
intent	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Pierpoint	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Shippy	I-pers
,	O
(	O
three	O
boys	O
)	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
as	O
Principals	O
,	O
and	O
Rebeccah	B-pers
White	I-pers
as	O
Accessary	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
three	O
former	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
Dimety	O
,	O
Shalloon	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
value	O
3l	O
.	O
10s	O
.	O
May	O
the	O
12th	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Glass	O
over	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
taken	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
person	O
put	O
in	O
who	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Shop-door	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
off	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
called	O
by	O
some	O
Neighbours	O
found	O
his	O
Shop-door	O
open	O
about	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
and	O
had	O
Intimation	O
given	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
some	O
Idle	O
Boys	O
living	O
about	O
Barbacin	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-House	O
,	O
and	O
informing	O
them	O
of	O
his	O
House	O
being	O
broken	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
,	O
one	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
,	O
desiring	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Candle	O
for	O
a	O
Half-penny	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
his	O
Mother	O
was	O
taken	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
wanted	O
a	O
Light	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
assist	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
this	O
Boy	O
being	O
known	O
by	O
the	O
Watch	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Boy	O
of	O
an	O
ill	O
Character	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
no	O
Notice	O
,	O
but	O
dogging	O
him	O
home	O
,	O
rush	O
'd	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
on	O
a	O
sudden	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Boy	O
's	O
Mother	O
,	O
Rebeccah	O
White	O
,	O
up	O
and	O
dress	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
standing	O
by	O
the	O
Table	O
;	O
on	O
which	O
there	O
lay	O
several	O
parcels	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutors	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
were	O
afterwards	O
found	O
brush	O
'd	O
off	O
the	O
Table	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
That	O
thereupon	O
they	O
apprehended	O
Rebeccah	O
White	O
the	O
Mother	O
,	O
and	O
John	O
White	O
the	O
Son	O
,	O
who	O
at	O
first	O
was	O
obstinate	O
,	O
but	O
after	O
some	O
time	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Accomplices	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
the	O
prisoners	O
above	O
mentioned	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
apprehended	O
.	O
John	O
White	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
himself	O
and	O
the	O
three	O
other	O
Boys	O
were	O
drinking	O
together	O
at	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
Smith-field	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
there	O
while	O
Twelve	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
they	O
all	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutors	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
John	B-pers
Pierpoint	I-pers
lifted	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
down	O
the	O
Glass	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
who	O
hid	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
Shop	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
all	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
Home	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
not	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
their	O
parcel	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
threw	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
fetched	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
designing	O
in	O
about	O
an	O
Hour	O
to	O
have	O
gone	O
to	O
meet	O
them	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
have	O
shared	O
the	O
Goods	O
among	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Boy	O
laboured	O
to	O
clear	O
his	O
Mother	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
Bed	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
let	O
in	O
by	O
a	O
little	O
Brother	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Boys	O
all	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
each	O
;	O
but	O
acquited	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
All	O
three	O
Transported	O
for	O
7	O
Years	O
.	O
And	O
by	O
finding	O
it	O
only	O
Larceney	O
,	O
Rebeccah	O
White	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coach	O
Seat	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
Lady	O
Ursula	B-pers
Shaftoe	I-pers
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Coach	O
Seat	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
another	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
pursued	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Man	O
to	O
avoid	O
being	O
apprehended	O
threw	O
down	O
the	O
Seat	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
However	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
positive	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
for	O
7	O
Years	O
.	O
Grace	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
so	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
purse	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
19	O
d.	O
Pence	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Moreton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
going	O
out	O
about	O
Twelve	O
a	O
Clock	O
a	O
Saturday-night	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
penny	O
worth	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
standing	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
called	O
him	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
entertaining	O
him	O
with	O
some	O
strange	O
sort	O
of	O
Discourse	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Purse	O
and	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
missing	O
it	O
,	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
following	O
her	O
for	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
length	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
charged	O
them	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
did	O
them	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
so	O
they	O
bore	O
one	O
another	O
Company	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
positive	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
her	O
throw	O
away	O
the	O
purse	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
for	O
7	O
Years	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pinner	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
3	O
Necks	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Linnen	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
body	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Wrapper	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
and	O
3	O
Clouts	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Tapley	I-pers
,	O
the	O
same	O
8th	O
of	O
May	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
body	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
also	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
7	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Tallow	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Sack	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Skinner	I-pers
;	O
but	O
no	O
body	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
likewise	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Bucklberry	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
for	O
7	O
Years	O
.	O
Ruth	B-pers
Dalton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
12	O
l.	O
from	O
Joseph	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
Box	O
in	O
his	O
Room	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
he	O
missed	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
she	O
must	O
have	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
her	O
Tryal	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Evidences	O
appeared	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
since	O
that	O
tim	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
oblig	O
'd	O
to	O
relieve	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
signs	O
of	O
her	O
having	O
Money	O
appearing	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
believe	O
she	O
had	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Harabin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
marrying	O
Mary	B-pers
Dukes	I-pers
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
former	O
Wife	O
being	O
alive	O
;	O
the	O
Marriages	O
being	O
both	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Wives	O
both	O
alive	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
accordingly	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Wade	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Hingle	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Finchly	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Seabrook	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
2	O
Keys	O
and	O
15	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
at	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
riding	O
over	O
Finchly-Common	B-place
between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
met	O
by	O
three	O
Men	O
on	O
foot	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
catch	O
'd	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Horse	O
's	O
Bridle	O
,	O
pull	O
'd	O
him	O
off	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
said	O
him	O
upon	O
his	O
Back	O
and	O
risted	O
him	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
they	O
wanted	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
swearing	O
and	O
cursing	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
violent	O
Manner	O
;	O
and	O
taking	O
his	O
Money	O
our	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
they	O
swore	O
one	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
Gold	O
amongst	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
aware	O
of	O
false	O
Pockets	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
unbutton	O
'd	O
his	O
Breeches	O
and	O
searched	O
his	O
Phob	O
;	O
they	O
also	O
took	O
away	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
begg	O
'd	O
of	O
them	O
not	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
make	O
him	O
go	O
home	O
bare-headed	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
threw	O
down	O
his	O
Hat	O
in	O
the	O
Road	O
and	O
left	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
got	O
up	O
upon	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
desired	O
them	O
not	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
they	O
told	O
him	O
they	O
would	O
leave	O
him	O
at	O
a	O
Place	O
two	O
Mile	O
off	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
all	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
followed	O
them	O
,	O
desiring	O
them	O
not	O
to	O
carry	O
his	O
Horse	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
swore	O
terribly	O
at	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
came	O
a	O
foot	O
further	O
they	O
would	O
shoot	O
him	O
through	O
the	O
Head	O
:	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
forbear	O
following	O
them	O
.	O
So	O
they	O
rode	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Finchly	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
met	O
with	O
a	O
Butcher	O
and	O
a	O
Farmer	O
who	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
at	O
Horrow	O
the	O
Hill	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
the	O
Men	O
.	O
Being	O
asked	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
to	O
charge	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
;	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Brother	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Hingle	I-pers
being	O
apprehended	O
for	O
another	O
Robbery	O
and	O
sent	O
to	O
New	O
Prison	O
,	O
sent	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
there	O
confest	O
to	O
him	O
that	O
himself	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
apprehended	O
and	O
committed	O
upon	O
his	O
Information	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
said	O
Hingle	O
had	O
since	O
made	O
his	O
Escape	O
out	O
of	O
New	O
Prison	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
since	O
been	O
retaken	O
.	O
He	O
also	O
produced	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Keys	O
in	O
Court	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
which	O
Key	O
was	O
bought	O
of	O
Henry	O
Hingle	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
both	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
Henry	O
Hingle	O
alledg	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Keys	O
in	O
the	O
Road	O
near	O
Highgate	O
;	O
so	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
sufficient	O
Proof	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
But	O
are	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
down	O
to	O
Hertford	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
be	O
Try	O
'd	O
for	O
another	O
Fact	O
,	O
where	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
will	O
in	O
all	O
probability	O
be	O
found	O
against	O
them	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Pearse	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Books	O
,	O
Linnen	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
Charles	B-pers
Stamper	I-pers
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
served	O
one	O
Counsellor	O
Hawks	O
;	O
but	O
was	O
turn	O
'd	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Day	O
he	O
lying	O
asleeping	O
upon	O
the	O
Grass	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
falling	O
into	O
some	O
Discourse	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
enquired	O
concerning	O
his	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
asking	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
single	O
Man	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
Yes	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
asked	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
live	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
something	O
to	O
buy	O
her	O
some	O
Clothes	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
they	O
concerted	O
measures	O
to	O
rob	O
Mr.	O
Hawk	O
's	O
Chambers	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
got	O
in	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
out	O
three	O
Books	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
things	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
she	O
brought	O
the	O
Soldier	O
,	O
William	O
Pearse	O
,	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
all	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Chambers	O
and	O
gave	O
out	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
carried	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Crispin	O
and	O
Crispana	O
in	O
Partridge-Lane	O
,	O
some	O
they	O
sold	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
they	O
carried	O
to	O
pawn	O
.	O
Other	O
Evidences	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Mary	O
Jones	O
had	O
been	O
seen	O
lurking	O
about	O
the	O
Chambers	O
some	O
Nights	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
turn	O
'd	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
did	O
neither	O
of	O
them	O
deny	O
their	O
being	O
at	O
the	O
Chambers	O
,	O
and	O
receiving	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Stamper	I-pers
,	O
but	O
they	O
pleaded	O
they	O
thought	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
told	O
them	O
they	O
were	O
left	O
him	O
by	O
an	O
Unkle	O
's	O
of	O
his	O
that	O
was	O
dead	O
:	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
believing	O
them	O
,	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
for	O
7	O
Years	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
9	O
Yards	O
of	O
Muslin	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Demayd	I-pers
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
under	O
pretence	O
to	O
buy	O
Muslin	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
followed	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
them	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
the	O
Muslin	O
was	O
given	O
her	O
to	O
carry	O
by	O
a	O
Woman	O
that	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Things	O
in	O
her	O
Apron	O
more	O
than	O
she	O
could	O
well	O
carry	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
who	O
the	O
Woman	O
was	O
.	O
Thereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
for	O
7	O
Years	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Lye	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Wheatly	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
body	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Packison	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Pound	O
of	O
Thread	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Lace-maker	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
to	O
work	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
known	O
to	O
take	O
some	O
Thread	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Matter	O
not	O
plainly	O
appearing	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
steal	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolph	I-place
's	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Preston	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
her	O
Shop	O
was	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
the	O
Shutter	O
being	O
taken	O
down	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
whom	O
she	O
knew	O
not	O
.	O
To	O
bring	O
it	O
home	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
a	O
Baker	O
's	O
Man	O
,	O
who	O
lived	O
over	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
at	O
work	O
,	O
about	O
One	O
a	O
Clock	O
he	O
sat	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Cellar-stairs	O
waiting	O
on	O
his	O
Work	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
sat	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
crashing	O
of	O
some	O
Wood	O
,	O
and	O
listening	O
he	O
heard	O
it	O
again	O
;	O
then	O
sospecting	O
some	O
such	O
Matter	O
,	O
he	O
unbolted	O
the	O
Cellar-door	O
of	O
a	O
sudden	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
two	O
Men	O
at	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
jump	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
which	O
of	O
them	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
they	O
both	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
pursuing	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
Perfom	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
Seaman	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Barslour	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Billingsgate	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
Boat	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
his	O
Ship	O
;	O
but	O
had	O
no	O
body	O
to	O
confirm	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
not	O
to	O
give	O
any	O
Account	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
They	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
,	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
William	I-pers
Hayes	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
20	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Counterfeit	O
Money	O
of	O
Katherine	B-pers
Kook	I-pers
,	O
at	O
a	O
lower	O
Rate	O
than	O
it	O
did	O
import	O
,	O
contrary	O
to	O
the	O
Statute	O
in	O
that	O
Case	O
provided	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
body	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
4	O
Richard	B-pers
Capstock	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Ryley	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Washington	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Harabin	I-pers
,	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
,	O
20.	O
Frances	B-pers
Jacob	I-pers
,	O
Hugh	B-pers
Alford	I-pers
,	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Wade	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Whittle	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Cutler	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lawler	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Warman	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Berryman	I-pers
,	O
Gerrard	B-pers
Pell	I-pers
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Pierpoint	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Shippy	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Grace	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
pearse	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
Next	O
Week	O
will	O
be	O
Publish	O
'd	O
in	O
Two	O
Nest	O
Pocket	O
Volumes	O
,	O
A	O
Compleat	O
Collection	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
most	O
remarlcable	O
Tryals	O
that	O
ahve	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
Session-House	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
baily	O
for	O
more	O
than	O
Forty	O
Years	O
last	O
past	O
for	O
Murthers	O
High	O
way	O
Robbing	O
,	O
Pytacy	O
,	O
House-breaking	O
,	O
Foot-padding	O
,	O
Rapes	O
,	O
Sodomy	O
,	O
Bestialiey	O
,	O
Polygamy	O
,	O
Fortune-stealing	O
,	O
Trepaming	O
,	O
Kidnapping	O
,	O
Shop-Lifting	O
,	O
Perjury	O
,	O
Counterseiting	O
the	O
Coin	O
,	O
Exchequer	O
Bills	O
,	O
Bank-Notes	O
,	O
Stamps	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Collected	O
from	O
the	O
Originals	O
,	O
Books	O
of	O
Tryal	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
papers	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Paul	B-pers
Lorrain	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Wykes	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Alen	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
,	O
the	O
several	O
Ordinaries	O
of	O
Newgate	O
.	O
Even	O
from	O
the	O
very	O
first	O
printing	O
of	O
them	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
present	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
other	O
Anthentick	O
narratives	O
.	O
And	O
particularly	O
the	O
lie	O
Tryals	O
,	O
Behaviour	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
,	O
of	O
Count	O
Coxingsmark	O
,	O
Capt	O
.	O
Vratz	O
.	O
Lieutenant	O
Tiers	B-pers
,	O
and	O
Boroski	O
the	O
Palender	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Marther	O
of	O
Esquise	O
Thomas	O
;	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sivage	I-pers
;	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Maid	O
;	O
Hannah	B-pers
Blay	I-pers
,	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Fact	O
;	O
Rojer	O
Congden	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Marther	O
of	O
Madam	O
Getting	O
,	O
her	O
Child	O
and	O
Maid	O
;	O
Margaret	B-pers
Marvel	I-pers
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Madam	O
Pullen	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Jenifer	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Madam	O
La	O
Grand	O
,	O
the	O
Frenchman	O
in	O
Spittle-Fields	O
;	O
Cyrus	B-pers
Simon	I-pers
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
his	O
Father-in-Law	O
;	O
James	B-pers
Selby	I-pers
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Bartlet	I-pers
;	O
Peter	B-pers
Dramatti	I-pers
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
his	O
wife	O
;	O
Edward	B-pers
Aadley	I-pers
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Madam	O
Bullevams	O
;	O
Harman	B-pers
Strodtman	I-pers
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Wolters	I-pers
his	O
Fellow-Prentice	O
;	O
Gerard	B-pers
Dramekins	I-pers
,	O
Micheal	O
Ven	O
Berg	O
,	O
and	O
Katherine	B-pers
Van	I-pers
Berg	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Dutch	O
People	O
in	O
East-Smithfield	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Norrice	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Foulks	O
,	O
a	O
Clergyman	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
his	O
Bastard-Child	O
;	O
The	O
Butcher	O
of	O
Glaseter	O
for	O
Killing	O
Mr.	O
Cooper	O
the	O
Constable	O
in	O
May-Fair	O
;	O
Roger	O
L	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Loyd	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Morgridge	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Kettle-Drummer	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Capt	O
.	O
Caps	O
of	O
the	O
Guards	O
;	O
Maynard	O
,	O
Bevins	O
and	O
Arsh	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Sutton	O
the	O
Vctuater	O
;	O
William	B-pers
Eress	I-pers
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
his	O
Wife	O
:	O
and	O
many	O
other	O
remarkable	O
Murthers	O
.	O
Of	O
Highway-Men	O
,	O
the	O
Tryals	O
,	O
Confessions	O
,	O
and	O
Dying-Speeches	O
fo	O
Clande	O
dx	O
Val	O
,	O
Old	O
Mob	O
,	O
the	O
Golden	O
Farmer	O
,	O
Capt	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Whitney	I-pers
.	O
Abrahim	O
Sticey	O
,	O
Capt	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Tool	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Benford	I-pers
(	O
a	O
Blind	O
Man	O
)	O
and	O
Willliam	O
James	O
(	O
a	O
Lame	O
Man	O
)	O
for	O
Robbing	O
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
more	O
notoriuos	O
Highway-Men	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
Pyracy	O
,	O
the	O
Tryal	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
of	O
Capt	O
.	O
Kid	O
and	O
his	O
Crew	O
,	O
Capt	O
.	O
Culliford	O
and	O
his	O
Crew	O
,	O
Capt	O
.	O
Guittar	O
and	O
70	O
of	O
his	O
Crew	O
,	O
Capt	O
.	O
Brens	O
,	O
Capt	O
.	O
Boyce	O
,	O
Capt	O
.	O
Lawrence	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
Capt	O
.	O
Snapes	O
and	O
Acres	O
for	O
insuring	O
and	O
borning	O
the	O
Ship	O
Cloudsley	O
Gally	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Salisbury	I-pers
a	O
Celergman	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
for	O
Conterfeiting	O
the	O
Stamps	O
on	O
Paper	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
Samuel	B-pers
Oldersbaw	I-pers
,	O
&	O
c.	O
for	O
Counterfeiting	O
Exchequer	O
Bills	O
.	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Blackham	I-pers
,	O
for	O
Coining	O
Dutch	O
Shillings	O
Fouler	O
,	O
Scalan	O
,	O
Goff	O
,	O
and	O
Moor	O
,	O
for	O
Robbing	O
the	O
Goldsmith	O
in	O
Bosmel	O
Cours	O
,	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
Mrs.	O
VVbarson	O
.	O
Hasgon	O
Swendsen	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
Mrs	O
Rawlings	O
.	O
Handsom	O
Fielding	O
,	O
for	O
marrying	O
the	O
Dutchess	O
of	O
Cleveland	O
.	O
Capt	O
.	O
Rigbey	O
,	O
fur	O
sodomy	O
.	O
Vanghan	O
and	O
Davis	O
,	O
for	O
fallty	O
swearing	O
Sodomy	O
on	O
several	O
Perforns	O
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Popish	O
Priest	O
,	O
for	O
absolting	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Rich	I-pers
of	O
her	O
s.	O
Margaret	B-pers
VVilkinson	I-pers
,	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
for	O
turning	O
Roman-Catholick	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Marchand	I-pers
,	O
for	O
Trepanning	O
Mr.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Pites	I-pers
,	O
a	O
french	O
Refugee	O
,	O
into	O
the	O
Hands	O
of	O
Publish	O
'd	O
Priest	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
send	O
in	O
to	O
the	O
Inquisition	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
for	O
a	O
Rape	O
;	O
Henry	B-pers
Simpkins	I-pers
,	O
&	O
c	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Stickland	I-pers
alias	O
Butler	O
,	O
for	O
forging	O
a	O
Bond	O
for	O
37000	O
l.	O
on	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Cleyton	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
for	O
Kidnapping	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lartin	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Contriver	O
fo	O
the	O
Sham-Plot	O
,	O
Charg	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
Bishop	O
of	O
rachester	O
,	O
Earts	O
of	O
Marlborough	O
and	O
Salisbury	O
:	O
And	O
many	O
more	O
notorious	O
Criminals	O
of	O
all	O
Kinds	O
,	O
too	O
many	O
to	O
be	O
inserted	O
here	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
Phillips	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
J.	O
Brotherton	O
and	O
W.	O
Meadows	O
at	O
the	O
Black	O
Bull	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
,	O
and	O
J.	O
Roberts	O
in	O
Warwick-Lane	O
.	O
Price	O
Five	O
Shillings	O
the	O
Two	O
Vo	O
.	O
Some	O
BOOKS	O
Printed	O
for	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
rd	O
Parker	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
and	O
Crown	O
in	O
Leonard	O
Street	O
,	O
near	O
Stocks	O
Market	O
SCP	O
,	O
with	O
and	O
Refl	O
;	O
ect	O
on	O
,	O
as	O
improv	O
'd	O
by	O
Sa	O
Roger	O
l'Erange	O
,	O
done	O
into	O
V	O
of	O
English	O
ver	O
with	O
C	O
t	O
out	O
on	O
Copper	O
Plates	O
.	O
The	O
Second	O
Edition	O
.	O
bound	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
London	O
New	O
Method	O
and	O
Art	O
or	O
Teaching	O
Children	O
to	O
Spell	O
and	O
Read	O
;	O
so	O
as	O
they	O
may	O
,	O
without	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
any	O
other	O
Books	O
,	O
read	O
the	O
Bible	O
Je	O
ch	O
Twelve	O
Months	O
Note	O
,	O
This	O
Way	O
of	O
Teaching	O
is	O
approved	O
by	O
mull	O
School	O
Masters	O
as	O
the	O
best	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
6	O
d.	O
With	O
great	O
Allowance	O
to	O
those	O
who	O
sell	O
or	O
give	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
Note	O
,	O
There	O
are	O
some	O
printed	O
on	O
Fine	O
Paper	O
,	O
bound	O
up	O
with	O
Cuts	O
.	O
pt	O
.	O
8	O
d.	O
For	O
the	O
Compleating	O
of	O
Palmody	O
.	O
The	O
Dev	O
Singer	O
's	O
Guide	O
;	O
Containing	O
all	O
the	O
Common	O
Tunes	O
now	O
in	O
Use	O
,	O
with	O
Select	O
portions	O
of	O
the	O
Psalms	O
,	O
adapted	O
to	O
each	O
Tune	O
,	O
and	O
Rules	O
for	O
singing	O
Treble	O
and	O
Bass	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
prefix	O
'd	O
,	O
Directions	O
for	O
Parish	O
Clerks	O
in	O
the	O
Choice	O
of	O
proper	O
Plates	O
on	O
most	O
Occasions	O
.	O
Recommended	O
by	O
the	O
best	O
Singing	O
Masters	O
.	O
The	O
second	O
Edition	O
,	O
Price	O
bound	O
1	O
s.	O
The	O
Benefit	O
of	O
Early	O
Piety	O
,	O
recommended	O
to	O
off	O
Yound	O
Persons	O
,	O
and	O
particularly	O
to	O
those	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
.	O
By	O
W.	O
Smitbles	O
,	O
late	O
morning	O
Lecturer	O
of	O
St.	O
Michael	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
,	O
London	O
.	O
The	O
Third	O
Edition	O
,	O
Price	O
bound	O
6	O
d.	O
Mr.	O
Jordaine	O
's	O
Duodecimal	O
Arithmetick	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
must	O
Concise	O
and	O
Exact	O
Method	O
extant	O
.	O
In	O
Three	O
Books	O
,	O
Containing	O
Notation	O
,	O
Addition	O
,	O
Subtraction	O
,	O
Moltiplication	O
,	O
Divition	O
,	O
Reduction	O
Extraction	O
of	O
the	O
Square	O
and	O
Cube	O
Root	O
,	O
Rule	O
of	O
Proportion	O
Direct	O
and	O
Reverse	O
,	O
Deodecimally	O
performed	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
Practically	O
applied	O
in	O
the	O
measuring	O
of	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
Supesficies	O
,	O
and	O
Solids	O
,	O
as	O
Board	O
,	O
Glass	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Timber	O
,	O
Stone	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Gnaging	O
of	O
all	O
sorts	O
at	O
Brewers	O
Tons	O
and	O
Casks	O
.	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
that	O
with	O
more	O
Ease	O
and	O
Expedition	O
,	O
than	O
by	O
Valgar	O
or	O
Decimal	O
Arithmetick	O
.	O
Very	O
Usesul	O
for	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
Men	O
,	O
at	O
well	O
Gentlemen	O
as	O
others	O
,	O
but	O
especially	O
for	O
Machanes	O
,	O
Existing	O
Masters	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
Measuring	O
Artificers	O
.	O
And	O
all	O
the	O
Rules	O
made	O
Plain	O
,	O
and	O
Easie	O
for	O
the	O
meanest	O
Capacity	O
.	O
Price	O
Sound	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
Daily	O
Self-Examinant	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
An	O
earnest	O
Persuasive	O
to	O
the	O
Duty	O
of	O
Daily	O
Self-Examination	O
;	O
with	O
Devent	O
Prayers	O
,	O
Meditations	O
,	O
Directions	O
and	O
Ejaculations	O
for	O
an	O
Holy	O
Life	O
and	O
Happy	O
Death	O
.	O
By	O
R.	O
Warren	O
,	O
D.	O
D.	O
6th	O
Edit	O
,	O
Price	O
bound	O
6	O
l.	O
The	O
Communicands	O
constant	O
Exercise	O
.	O
In	O
Three	O
Parts	O
Containing	O
.	O
I	O
.	O
An	O
earnest	O
Exhortation	O
to	O
the	O
Communion	O
:	O
With	O
proper	O
Devotions	O
Before	O
,	O
At	O
,	O
and	O
After	O
Receiving	O
.	O
II	O
.	O
His	O
Duty	O
of	O
Consideration	O
,	O
Resolution	O
,	O
and	O
actual	O
Amendment	O
after	O
Receiving	O
the	O
Blessed	O
sacrament	O
.	O
III	O
.	O
The	O
conttinual	O
Pleasure	O
fo	O
a	O
Religious	O
Life	O
.	O
And	O
Devout	O
Prayers	O
suitable	O
to	O
each	O
important	O
Subject	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
last	O
Parts	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
bound	O
up	O
together	O
or	O
singly	O
.	O
A	O
Devout	O
Christians	O
Preparative	O
to	O
Death	O
.	O
Written	O
by	O
Erasmans	O
,	O
now	O
render	O
'd	O
into	O
English	O
,	O
To	O
which	O
are	O
added	O
,	O
Meditations	O
,	O
Prayers	O
and	O
Directions	O
for	O
Sick	O
and	O
Dying	O
Persons	O
.	O
Recommended	O
as	O
proper	O
to	O
be	O
given	O
as	O
Funerals	O
.	O
The	O
Sixth	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
6	O
d.	O
or	O
two	O
Gaineas	O
per	O
Hundred	O
to	O
those	O
who	O
give	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
These	O
Thres	O
by	O
Robert	O
Warren	O
,	O
D.D	O
.	O
Rector	O
of	O
Charlton	O
in	O
Kent	O
.	O
The	O
Daily	O
Companion	O
,	O
with	O
Christian	O
Supports	O
under	O
the	O
Troubles	O
of	O
this	O
Worid	O
,	O
to	O
comfort	O
and	O
succour	O
all	O
those	O
who	O
In	O
this	O
Transitory	O
Life	O
are	O
in	O
Trouble	O
,	O
Sorrow	O
,	O
Need	O
,	O
Sickness	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
other	O
Adversity	O
.	O
Unto	O
which	O
are	O
added	O
,	O
Prayers	O
and	O
Meditations	O
,	O
suitable	O
for	O
all	O
Persons	O
afflicted	O
in	O
Mind	O
,	O
Body	O
or	O
flate	O
.	O
The	O
Fourth	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
6	O
d.	O
or	O
two	O
Guineas	O
per	O
Hundred	O
to	O
those	O
that	O
give	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
Arithmetick	O
made	O
easie	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
New	O
Method	O
now	O
taught	O
and	O
practis	O
'd	O
in	O
London	O
.	O
Wherein	O
the	O
Rules	O
of	O
that	O
necessary	O
Art	O
are	O
briefly	O
explain	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
illustrated	O
with	O
Such	O
Similiar	O
Examples	O
as	O
may	O
suit	O
the	O
meanest	O
Capacity	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
desire	O
to	O
learn	O
it	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
a	O
Succinct	O
Treatise	O
of	O
Decimal	O
Fractions	O
,	O
with	O
Compleat	O
Tables	O
,	O
Rules	O
,	O
and	O
Examples	O
demonstrating	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
like	O
ot	O
extant	O
in	O
any	O
other	O
Treatise	O
of	O
this	O
Nature	O
.	O
The	O
Fourth	O
Editor	O
.	O
By	O
John	B-pers
Copeland	I-pers
,	O
Writing-Master	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
1	O
s.	O
Orders	O
.	O
By	O
Laws	O
,	O
and	O
Ordinances	O
for	O
the	O
good	O
Government	O
and	O
Regulating	O
of	O
the	O
Persons	O
Licensed	O
to	O
Keep	O
and	O
Drive	O
Hackoey-Coaches	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
Renters	O
and	O
Drivers	O
.	O
Made	O
,	O
Publish	O
'd	O
and	O
Declar	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Commissioners	O
;	O
and	O
Allowed	O
and	O
Approved	O
by	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chancellor	O
and	O
Judges	O
as	O
the	O
Law	O
direct	O
.	O
Price	O
3	O
d.	O
B.	O
LILBURN	O
,	O
that	O
formerly	O
lived	O
on	O
Ludgate-hill	O
next	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms	O
Tavern	O
,	O
near	O
Fleet-bridge	O
;	O
and	O
for	O
seven	O
Years	O
past	O
,	O
int	O
he	O
Great	O
Old	O
Baily	O
,	O
now	O
lives	O
at	O
the	O
Turner	O
's	O
without	O
Newgate	O
;	O
who	O
has	O
made	O
and	O
sold	O
between	O
Thirty	O
and	O
Forty	O
Years	O
,	O
The	O
Water	O
for	O
taking	O
away	O
the	O
Freckles	O
,	O
Panples	O
,	O
Worms	O
,	O
Morphew	O
,	O
and	O
Red	O
Marks	O
of	O
the	O
Small	O
Pox	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
;	O
the	O
Price	O
of	O
the	O
Half	O
Pint	O
Five	O
Shilling	O
,	O
Sealed	O
with	O
the	O
Three	O
Water-Budgets	O
and	O
B	O
L	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
Seal	O
.	O
Pray	O
notice	O
,	O
the	O
has	O
taken	O
the	O
Sale	O
of	O
the	O
Water	O
from	O
all	O
in	O
and	O
near	O
London	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
had	O
now	O
only	O
of	O
her	O
self	O
;	O
and	O
never	O
off	O
the	O
receipt	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
some	O
that	O
for	O
her	O
in	O
depth	O
pretended	O
;	O
for	O
no	O
other	O
Receipt	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
she	O
makes	O
,	O
or	O
in	O
much	O
as	O
per	O
them	O
into	O
Manuscript	O
.	O
She	O
likewise	O
sells	O
her	O
Antiscorbutick	O
,	O
Hasterick	O
,	O
and	O
Head	O
,	O
being	O
good	O
for	O
C	O
,	O
King	O
's	O
Evil	O
,	O
Gout	O
and	O
Rhem	O
,	O
Drop	O
,	O
ga	O
,	O
Sursuits	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Price	O
Two	O
Shillings	O
the	O
Box	O
.	O
The	O
r	O
for	O
the	O
Collick	O
and	O
Gripes	O
,	O
good	O
for	O
ages	O
,	O
Consumptions	O
,	O
or	O
Coughs	O
,	O
Colds	O
,	O
Stone	O
or	O
Gravel	O
,	O
Vomiting	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
Cul	O
,	O
Price	O
One	O
Shilling	O
the	O
Viet	O
,	O
or	O
Five	O
Shillings	O
the	O
Half-pine	O
.	O
The	O
Ointment	O
for	O
Bruises	O
,	O
Aches	O
,	O
Strains	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
du	O
Swellings	O
,	O
One	O
Shilling	O
the	O
Pot	O
.	O
The	O
Ointment	O
for	O
sore	O
Nipples	O
,	O
the	O
Piles	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
Hair	O
grow	O
,	O
One	O
shilling	O
the	O
Pot	O
.	O
The	O
Girdle	O
for	O
the	O
Itch	O
,	O
Bighteen	O
Pence	O
.	O
These	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
Preparations	O
,	O
both	O
for	O
Ornament	O
,	O
Eating	O
and	O
Curing	O
most	O
Distempers	O
,	O
help	O
for	O
inward	O
Bruies	O
and	O
Hurts	O
on	O
the	O
Breast	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
have	O
of	O
B.	O
Lilburn	O
.	O
All	O
Melancholy	O
,	O
Hysterical	O
and	O
Hypecondriack	O
Distempers	O
,	O
Which	O
variously	O
affect	O
the	O
Mind	O
,	O
with	O
strange	O
Fears	O
and	O
di	O
Apprehentions	O
;	O
Fainting	O
and	O
Sinkings	O
of	O
the	O
Spirit	O
,	O
grant	O
Hurries	O
,	O
Refl	O
and	O
Disquirements	O
(	O
N	O
understood	O
and	O
seldom	O
cured	O
by	O
any	O
common	O
means	O
)	O
also	O
Pains	O
and	O
Giddiness	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
;	O
Risings	O
to	O
the	O
Throats	O
,	O
Sick	O
Fits	O
,	O
Tremblings	O
,	O
Oppressions	O
of	O
the	O
Heart	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
other	O
Distempers	O
caused	O
by	O
Vapours	O
;	O
are	O
succesfully	O
cured	O
(	O
with	O
God	O
's	O
Blessing	O
)	O
by	O
a	O
Physician	O
well	O
experienced	O
therein	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
So	O
Succesor	O
to	O
a	O
late	O
eminent	O
Physician	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
of	O
more	O
than	O
30	O
Years	O
successful	O
Practice	O
in	O
those	O
Deplorable	O
Cases	O
,	O
he	O
also	O
Cu	O
all	O
kind	O
of	O
Fits	O
,	O
the	O
strange	O
and	O
violent	O
(	O
it	O
curable	O
)	O
which	O
he	O
will	O
justly	O
inform	O
you	O
;	O
living	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
1.	O
in	O
Burt-street	O
in	O
St.	O
Katherines	O
near	O
the	O
Tower	O
,	O
London	O
:	O
where	O
those	O
that	O
have	O
occason	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
remote	O
,	O
may	O
direct	O
their	O
Letters	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
shall	O
be	O
speedily	O
answered	O
,	O
or	O
attended	O
on	O
if	O
desired	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Good	O
of	O
the	O
Publick	O
.	O
WHereas	O
several	O
Gentlewomen	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
that	O
Sex	O
,	O
in	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
have	O
contracted	O
an	O
Evil	O
Habit	O
of	O
Body	O
,	O
wherein	O
the	O
vicious	O
Humours	O
,	O
at	O
first	O
dispers	O
'd	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Whole	O
,	O
come	O
at	O
length	O
to	O
be	O
lodged	O
in	O
one	O
Part	O
or	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
times	O
,	O
for	O
Causes	O
too	O
long	O
to	O
be	O
here	O
mentioned	O
,	O
are	O
thrown	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Womb	O
,	O
occasioning	O
a	O
dangerous	O
Weakness	O
in	O
that	O
Part	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
neglected	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
turns	O
Cancerous	O
,	O
and	O
often	O
proves	O
Fatal	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
to	O
acquaint	O
all	O
such	O
as	O
may	O
have	O
occasion	O
,	O
that	O
speedy	O
Relief	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
had	O
from	O
a	O
Sworn	O
and	O
experienc	O
'd	O
Midwife	O
,	O
dwelling	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Arm	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
the	O
Tin-Shop	O
near	O
Exeter	O
Change	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
who	O
perform	O
'd	O
a	O
wonderful	O
Cure	O
upon	O
a	O
Lay	O
at	O
the	O
Bark	O
,	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
given	O
over	O
by	O
the	O
Physicians	O
,	O
and	O
since	O
has	O
Cured	O
several	O
Gentlewomen	O
and	O
others	O
in	O
the	O
City	O
and	O
Suburbs	O
of	O
London	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
put	O
my	O
self	O
in	O
publick	O
Print	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
satisfy	O
the	O
Afflicted	O
where	O
they	O
may	O
have	O
present	O
Ease	O
and	O
Relief	O
,	O
if	O
not	O
,	O
no	O
Money	O
.	O
FRom	O
a	O
Distemper	O
of	O
sixteen	O
Years	O
standing	O
the	O
Refult	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
Scabs	O
and	O
Nodes	O
in	O
my	O
Body	O
,	O
as	O
big	O
as	O
Nut	O
;	O
Blotches	O
and	O
Sores	O
from	O
Head	O
to	O
Foot	O
;	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
legs	O
,	O
large	O
enough	O
to	O
lay	O
an	O
Egg-in	O
;	O
my	O
Body	O
so	O
weak	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Hesh	O
so	O
rotten	O
,	O
that	O
upon	O
my	O
stretching	O
its	O
it	O
would	O
rend	O
a	O
funder	O
as	O
tho	O
'	O
cut	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
.	O
I	O
willian	O
Forbush	O
,	O
Cap	O
maker	O
over	O
against	O
Queen	O
Elizabeth	O
's	O
Head	O
in	O
Church-lane	O
near	O
Whitechappel	O
,	O
an	O
now	O
reliev	O
'd	O
and	O
made	O
whose	O
by	O
God	O
Almighty	O
's	O
Blessing	O
on	O
the	O
Specifick	O
Remedy	O
and	O
Elixir	O
,	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Practical	O
Scheme	O
for	O
Brokes	O
Constitutions	O
,	O
gives	O
Grates	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Anodyne	O
.	O
NECKLACE	O
without	O
Temple	O
Par	O
.	O
The	O
Amazement	O
of	O
all	O
my	O
Friends	O
at	O
my	O
Cure	O
when	O
declared	O
Incurable	O
by	O
many	O
Physicians	O
,	O
will	O
,	O
no	O
doubt	O
,	O
raise	O
the	O
Curiousity	O
of	O
several	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
I	O
shall	O
,	O
with	O
incredible	O
Pleasure	O
,	O
declare	O
the	O
Fact	O
more	O
at	O
large	O
,	O
with	O
many	O
surprizing	O
Particulars	O
.	O
April	O
1718.	O
William	B-pers
Forbeth	I-pers
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
PHILLIPS	O
;	O
by	O
M.	O
Jenour	O
against	O
St.	O
Sepulchres	O
Back	O
Gate	O
in	O
Gilt	O
Spur	O
Street	O
near	O
Newgate	O
;	O
and	O
Sold	O
by	O
J.	O
Roberts	O
near	O
the	O
Oxford-Arms	O
in	O
Warnick	O
Lane	O
.	O
1718	O
.	O
Where	O
Advertisements	O
are	O
taken	O
in	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
d	O
.	O
)	O
