TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
,	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
and	O
Thursday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
9th	O
and	O
10th	O
of	O
July,1718	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Fourth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign.18	O
.	O
July.1718	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
LEWEN	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	B-pers
Bary	I-pers
;	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Powis	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Blancoe	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
Names	O
were	O
as	O
followth	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
Benjamin	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
John	B-pers
Boyce	I-pers
John	B-pers
Yerberry	I-pers
Christopher	B-pers
Cheesbrook	I-pers
John	B-pers
Cromwell	I-pers
Walter	B-pers
Boddington	I-pers
John	B-pers
Sutron	I-pers
John	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
Joshua	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
Nathanael	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cutbert	I-pers
William	B-pers
Cleeve	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Thompkins	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Hull	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Ayliff	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Charley	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Ingram	I-pers
William	B-pers
Thame	I-pers
William	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
William	B-pers
Gass	I-pers
William	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Fell	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
James	B-pers
Quinn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Woolwich	I-place
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bowen	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
Side	O
of	O
his	O
Belly	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
and	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
four	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Wound	O
he	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
20th	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
at	O
the	O
Fleece-Tavern	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
the	O
17	O
of	O
April	O
about	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
a-Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
Mr.Bowen	O
being	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
espying	O
him	O
,	O
called	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Wine	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Quinn	O
was	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
;	O
that	O
as	O
they	O
drank	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
and	O
Quinn	O
put	O
pretty	O
Smartly	O
upon	O
one	O
another	O
with	O
wirty	O
s	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
up	O
talk	O
of	O
their	O
Performances	O
in	O
Acting	O
,	O
whereupon	O
Mr.	O
Quinn	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Occasion	O
to	O
value	O
himself	O
so	O
much	O
on	O
that	O
score	O
,	O
since	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
,	O
who	O
bad	O
but	O
seldom	O
Acted	O
it	O
,	O
did	O
Act	O
the	O
part	O
of	O
Jacamo	O
in	O
the	O
Libertine	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
be	O
who	O
had	O
Acted	O
it	O
often	O
.	O
That	O
from	O
this	O
Discourse	O
they	O
fell	O
into	O
Discourse	O
about	O
their	O
Honesty	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
giving	O
himself	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
as	O
honest	O
a	O
Man	O
as	O
any	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Quinn	O
reply	O
'd	O
by	O
asking	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
if	O
he	O
should	O
tell	O
the	O
Story	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
no	O
Matter	O
;	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
said	O
he	O
might	O
tell	O
it	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
,	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Quinn	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
still	O
persisting	O
to	O
abide	O
by	O
the	O
assertion	O
of	O
his	O
Honesty	O
,	O
they	O
proceeded	O
so	O
far	O
as	O
to	O
lay	O
Wagers	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
Money	O
was	O
laid	O
down	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Quinn	O
Charg	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
with	O
sometimes	O
drinking	O
Healths	O
to	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Ormond	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
other	O
times	O
refusing	O
it	O
.	O
Asking	O
Mr.	O
Martin	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
the	O
Decision	O
of	O
the	O
Wager	O
was	O
left	O
,	O
How	O
could	O
be	O
he	O
as	O
honest	O
a	O
Man	O
as	O
any	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
who	O
Acted	O
upon	O
two	O
different	O
Principles	O
?	O
That	O
thereupon	O
Mr.	O
Martin	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
insisted	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
being	O
as	O
Honest	O
a	O
Man	O
as	O
any	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
needs	O
give	O
it	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
this	O
Discourse	O
was	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
carry	O
'd	O
on	O
with	O
a	O
jocular	O
Air	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
this	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
rose	O
up	O
,	O
flung	O
down	O
some	O
Money	O
for	O
the	O
Rockoning	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
bear	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
must	O
be	O
gone	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
go	O
away	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
perceive	O
in	O
him	O
any	O
Signs	O
of	O
a	O
Resentment	O
that	O
should	O
procure	O
so	O
fatal	O
a	O
Consequence	O
.	O
That	O
after	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
had	O
been	O
gone	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
there	O
came	O
a	O
Porter	O
to	O
the	O
Fleece-Tavern	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Quinn	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
Company	O
;	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Quinn	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
Porter	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Porter	O
having	O
Whisper	O
'd	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Ear	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
been	O
gone	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Quinn	O
came	O
back	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
where	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
lodg	O
'd	O
,	O
desiring	O
that	O
they	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Pope's-head-Tavern	B-place
and	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Dispute	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
he	O
had	O
wounded	O
him	O
Mortally	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Quinn	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Day	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
then	O
in	O
Company	O
,	O
went	O
immediately	O
to	O
the	O
Pope's-Head-Tavern	O
and	O
enquired	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Quinn	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Porter	O
of	O
the	O
Tavern	O
said	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
them	O
,	O
not	O
would	O
own	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
that	O
setting	O
down	O
to	O
drink	O
in	O
an	O
open	O
Room	O
next	O
the	O
Passage	O
they	O
saw	O
a	O
Chair	O
brought	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
asking	O
whether	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
wounded	O
there	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
answered	O
so	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Gentleman	O
there	O
wounded	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
Chair	O
was	O
for	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
that	O
was	O
something	O
disordered	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
came	O
down	O
Stairs	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Chair	O
but	O
the	O
fight	O
being	O
intercepted	O
by	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
go	O
in	O
,	O
but	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
to	O
the	O
Man	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
wounded	O
in	O
your	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
is	O
done	O
very	O
fairly	O
,	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
has	O
done	O
it	O
fairly	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Day	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
with	O
some	O
Gentlemen	O
at	O
the	O
Fleece-Tavern	O
was	O
going	O
Home	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Tavern	O
Yard	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
hipp	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
setting	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
by	O
himself	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Wine	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
refus	O
'd	O
,	O
not	O
having	O
dined	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
going	O
home	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
about	O
4	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
the	O
Family	O
had	O
din	O
'd	O
.	O
whereupon	O
he	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Fleece	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
found	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Quinn	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Martin	O
together	O
.	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Quinn	O
,	O
were	O
talking	O
together	O
in	O
a	O
Jocular	O
manner	O
about	O
their	O
Performances	O
in	O
Acting	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
reflected	O
on	O
Mr.	O
Quinn	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
acted	O
Tamerlane	O
in	O
a	O
loose	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
manner	O
;	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Quinn	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
had	O
no	O
great	O
occasion	O
to	O
value	O
himself	O
for	O
his	O
Performance	O
,	O
in	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
acted	O
it	O
but	O
seldom	O
,	O
acted	O
the	O
part	O
of	O
Jacamo	O
in	O
the	O
Libertine	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
he	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
acted	O
it	O
often	O
.	O
That	O
from	O
this	O
discourse	O
,	O
by	O
what	O
Transition	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
,	O
they	O
fell	O
into	O
discourse	O
about	O
Honesty	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
giving	O
himself	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
as	O
honest	O
a	O
Man	O
as	O
any	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
Mr.	O
Quinn	O
told	O
a	O
Story	O
,	O
That	O
having	O
been	O
out	O
one	O
Night	O
pretty	O
late	O
and	O
going	O
Home	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
in	O
a	O
Court	O
a	O
hot	O
Contention	O
between	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
which	O
Gentleman	O
he	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
,	O
who	O
in	O
very	O
high	O
terms	O
was	O
demanding	O
the	O
return	O
of	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
was	O
unwilling	O
to	O
part	O
with	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
swearing	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
offered	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
back	O
a	O
Shilling	O
of	O
the	O
Half	O
Crown	O
but	O
he	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
it	O
all	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
offered	O
him	O
18	O
Pence	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
insisting	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
Ungentleman	O
like	O
,	O
to	O
insist	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
her	O
Body	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
still	O
insisting	O
she	O
offered	O
a	O
Shillings	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
swearing	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
it	O
all	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
all	O
back	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
story	O
being	O
told	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
insisted	O
still	O
on	O
his	O
Honesty	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
not	O
ing	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
as	O
Honest	O
a	O
Man	O
as	O
any	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
lay	O
a	O
Wager	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Quinn	O
would	O
have	O
evaded	O
;	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
urging	O
it	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Quinn	O
said	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
lay	O
I	O
will	O
lay	O
you	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
laid	O
down	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Martin	O
was	O
to	O
decide	O
the	O
Controversy	O
.	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Quinn	O
then	O
related	O
some	O
Pastages	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
's	O
drinking	O
the	O
Healths	O
of	O
Persons	O
obnoxious	O
to	O
the	O
Government	O
,	O
and	O
such	O
like	O
matters	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Martin	O
said	O
,	O
If	O
I	O
must	O
give	O
my	O
Opinion	O
as	O
to	O
your	O
being	O
as	O
Honest	O
a	O
Man	O
as	O
any	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
,	O
or	O
in	O
England	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
give	O
it	O
against	O
you	O
.	O
That	O
soon	O
after	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
in	O
a	O
hasty	O
fort	O
of	O
a	O
manner	O
rose	O
up	O
and	O
threw	O
down	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
stay	O
in	O
the	O
Company	O
any	O
longer	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
But	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
perceive	O
any	O
such	O
high	O
Resentments	O
and	O
Anger	O
in	O
him	O
as	O
to	O
apprehend	O
any	O
such	O
fatal	O
Consequence	O
;	O
the	O
mutual	O
Freedoms	O
that	O
were	O
taken	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
seeming	O
to	O
rise	O
no	O
higher	O
than	O
to	O
cause	O
the	O
common	O
Ruffles	O
of	O
Human	O
Nature	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
such	O
as	O
he	O
would	O
call	O
Mr.	O
Quinn	O
to	O
an	O
account	O
for	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
having	O
been	O
gone	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
or	O
less	O
,	O
a	O
Porter	O
came	O
and	O
enquir	O
'd	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Quinn	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Porter	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
knew	O
not	O
it	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
had	O
sent	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hours	O
time	O
Mr.	O
Quinn	O
came	O
back	O
and	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
had	O
sent	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Pope's-head-Tavern	O
,	O
had	O
taken	O
Occasion	O
to	O
quarrel	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
had	O
obliged	O
him	O
to	O
fight	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
so	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
believed	O
he	O
had	O
hurt	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
us	O
to	O
go	O
see	O
if	O
it	O
were	O
mortal	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
immediately	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Pope's-head-Tavern	O
,	O
as	O
has	O
been	O
before	O
related	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
People	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
deny	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
's	O
being	O
there	O
;	O
but	O
seeing	O
a	O
Chair	O
brought	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
heard	O
his	O
voice	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Chair	O
,	O
saying	O
to	O
the	O
Landlord	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
wounded	O
in	O
your	O
House	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
has	O
done	O
it	O
fairly	O
,	O
If	O
I	O
die	O
I	O
forgive	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
I	O
live	O
I	O
will	O
be	O
revenged	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Tho	B-pers
Antrum	I-pers
the	O
Porter	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
standing	O
by	O
Tom's-Coffee-house	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
called	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Fleece-Tavern	O
and	O
ask	O
for	O
Mr.-	O
and	O
seeming	O
to	O
have	O
forgot	O
the	O
Name	O
,	O
swore	O
as	O
tho	O
'	O
in	O
a	O
fret	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
then	O
calling	O
him	O
again	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
and	O
ask	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Martin	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
Mr.	O
Quinn	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Company	O
to	O
tell	O
him	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Quinn	O
came	O
immediately	O
out	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
then	O
walked	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
score	O
Doors-lower	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Quinn	O
coming	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
they	O
,	O
went	O
both	O
together	O
into	O
the	O
Swan-Tavern	O
,	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
gave	O
him	O
nothing	O
for	O
his	O
pains	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Treesa	I-pers
,	O
Drawn	O
at	O
the	O
Shan-Tavern	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
about	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
April	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Quinn	O
came	O
in	O
together	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
Room	O
,	O
he	O
show	O
'd	O
them	O
a	O
Room	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
going	O
up	O
first	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
Room	O
having	O
been	O
new	O
painted	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
objected	O
against	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
smelling	O
of	O
Paint	O
,	O
he	O
then	O
show	O
'd	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
Great	O
Room	O
,	O
which	O
because	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
Gentlemen	O
drinking	O
at	O
one	O
end	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
said	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
,	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
about	O
shaking	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
seeming	O
angry	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
went	O
down	O
Stairs	O
and	O
so	O
away	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Griffin	B-pers
Bowen	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
about	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
a	O
Person	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
desiring	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
his	O
Father	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
wounded	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
his	O
Father	O
in	O
Bed	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
asked	O
him	O
several	O
times	O
how	O
it	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
who	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
him	O
:	O
But	O
at	O
last	O
,	O
with	O
much	O
Urgency	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Quinn	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
Is	O
it	O
that	O
Man	O
!	O
she	O
worst	O
of	O
all	O
Mankind	O
?	O
how	O
came	O
you	O
into	O
his	O
Company	O
?	O
If	O
you	O
get	O
over	O
it	O
,	O
is	O
will	O
be	O
a	O
Reflection	O
upon	O
your	O
Family	O
-	O
That	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
apprehensive	O
that	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
mortal	O
;	O
but	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
about	O
Twelve	O
or	O
One	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
some	O
Symptoms	O
of	O
Death	O
appearing	O
,	O
as	O
his	O
Nails	O
turning	O
black	O
,	O
the	O
Doctor	O
being	O
present	O
told	O
his	O
Father	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
him	O
think	O
of	O
another	O
World	O
,	O
in	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
Yard	O
from	O
Death	O
:	O
Whereupon	O
he	O
again	O
urged	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
Adying	O
Man	O
,	O
to	O
tell	O
him	O
how	O
the	O
Accident	O
came	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
met	O
Mr.	O
Quinn	O
at	O
the	O
Fleece-Tavern	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
always	O
abusive	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
given	O
him	O
provoking	O
Language	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
him	O
out	O
to	O
desire	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
give	O
himself	O
that	O
Freedom	O
of	O
Speech	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
Quinn	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Swan	O
and	O
afterwards	O
to	O
the	O
Pope	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
where	O
with	O
a	O
Volley	O
of	O
Oaths	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
abusive	O
Language	O
,	O
barricado	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
with	O
two	O
Chairs	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
given	O
him	O
such	O
foul	O
Language	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
bear	O
,	O
their	O
Swords	O
were	O
drawn	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
catching	O
Mr.	O
Quinn	O
by	O
the	O
Sword-Arm	O
he	O
wrested	O
himself	O
from	O
him	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
that	O
Wound	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Sewel	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
being	O
present	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
or	O
an	O
Hour	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
's	O
Death	O
,	O
heard	O
him	O
,	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
how	O
it	O
came	O
,	O
say	O
,	O
very	O
unfairly	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
barbarously	O
murthered	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Essex	O
Walter	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
for	O
near	O
two	O
Years	O
standing	O
a	O
Misunderstanding	O
between	O
Mr.	O
Quinn	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
apprehended	O
was	O
occasion	O
'd	O
as	O
follows	O
.	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Quinn	O
at	O
his	O
first	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
Play-house	O
behaved	O
himself	O
with	O
much	O
Civility	O
and	O
good	O
Manners	O
,	O
but	O
soon	O
after	O
broke	O
out	O
into	O
quite	O
the	O
reverse	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
taking	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
advise	O
him	O
to	O
another	O
manner	O
of	O
Behaviour	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
a	O
Difference	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
since	O
that	O
time	O
Mr.	O
Quinn	O
had	O
shewn	O
an	O
Animosity	O
against	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
vile	O
Fellow	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
not	O
fit	O
to	O
live	O
;	O
used	O
to	O
call	O
him	O
Turn-coat	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
sometimes	O
ask	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
drink	O
the	O
Doke	O
of	O
Ormond	O
's	O
Health	O
in	O
his	O
Heart	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
saying	O
he	O
ought	O
to	O
be	O
used	O
like	O
a	O
Dog	O
,	O
and	O
deserved	O
to	O
be	O
stuck	O
.	O
That	O
this	O
had	O
continued	O
for	O
two	O
Winters	O
,	O
till	O
Mr.	O
Quinn	O
left	O
the	O
Company	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Lincolns-Inn	O
Fields	O
Play-house	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
further	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
Mr.	O
Quinn	O
was	O
fitting	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
behind	O
the	O
Scenes	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
passed	O
through	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Quinn	O
seeing	O
him	O
said	O
,	O
here	O
comes	O
that	O
rascally	O
,	O
Whiggish	O
,	O
Tory	O
Fellow	O
,	O
Bowen	O
,	O
who	O
deserves	O
to	O
be	O
stuck	O
;	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
went	O
on	O
,	O
not	O
seeming	O
to	O
take	O
any	O
notice	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Mounsey	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
Thursday	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
April	O
he	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Horn-Tavern	O
in	O
Fleetstreet	O
to	O
dress	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
then	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
small	O
.	O
Wound	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
in	O
his	O
Belly	O
about	O
four	O
Inches	O
below	O
the	O
Navel	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
dress	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
another	O
Patient	O
left	O
him	O
,	O
not	O
then	O
apprehending	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
mortal	O
;	O
but	O
afterwards	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
being	O
dead	O
,	O
he	O
opened	O
him	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Wound	O
had	O
gone	O
several	O
Inches	O
into	O
the	O
Cavity	O
of	O
his	O
Belly	O
,	O
slanting	O
a	O
little	O
toward	O
the	O
Left	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
touch	O
'd	O
a	O
Gut	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
persuaded	O
that	O
Wound	O
was	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Quinn	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
having	O
accidentally	O
met	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
at	O
the	O
Fleece-Tavern	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
,	O
they	O
drank	O
together	O
in	O
the	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
Conversation	O
that	O
has	O
been	O
before	O
related	O
;	O
that	O
thereupon	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
leaving	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Company	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Martin	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Day	O
;	O
that	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
a	O
Porter	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Gloves	O
,	O
his	O
Sword	O
being	O
then	O
by	O
his	O
Side	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Porter	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
about	O
six	O
Doors	O
below	O
the	O
Fleece	O
he	O
found	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
had	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
to	O
spare	O
,	O
he	O
thought	O
it	O
were	O
better	O
to	O
spend	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Company	O
of	O
those	O
Gentlemen	O
they	O
had	O
before	O
been	O
in	O
adding	O
likewise	O
that	O
he	O
coming	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Porter	O
had	O
not	O
paid	O
his	O
Reckoning	O
:	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
refus	O
'd	O
so	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Swan	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
asking	O
for	O
a	O
Room	O
follow	O
'd	O
the	O
Drawer	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
himself	O
follow	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Room	O
having	O
been	O
new	O
painted	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
the	O
Drawer	O
show	O
'd	O
them	O
the	O
Great	O
Room	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
some	O
Gentlemen	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
said	O
it	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
;	O
the	O
Drawer	O
offered	O
to	O
draw	O
a	O
Curtain	O
to	O
part	O
the	O
Companies	O
,	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
saying	O
it	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
,	O
went	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
he	O
following	O
him	O
.	O
Then	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Pope's-Head	O
,	O
he	O
expecting	O
to	O
meet	O
some	O
Gentlemen	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
put	O
off	O
some	O
Tickets	O
of	O
a	O
Benefit	O
Play	O
of	O
his	O
that	O
was	O
coming	O
on	O
.	O
So	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Pope's-Head	O
,	O
where	O
being	O
shown	O
a	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
for	O
a	O
Print	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
they	O
sat	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
desired	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
to	O
tell	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
desiring	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
short	O
,	O
in	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
his	O
Company	O
without	O
paying	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
having	O
drank	O
each	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
he	O
perceiving	O
a	O
Distortion	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
's	O
Countenance	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
rose	O
and	O
barricado	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
with	O
two	O
Chairs	O
,	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
injured	O
him	O
past	O
verbal	O
Reparation	O
,	O
and	O
nothing	O
but	O
fighting	O
him	O
should	O
make	O
him	O
amends	O
.	O
That	O
thereupon	O
he	O
argued	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
disswade	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
bid	O
him	O
not	O
trifle	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
then	O
desired	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
again	O
to	O
defer	O
his	O
Resentment	O
and	O
sleep	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
come	O
into	O
Temper	O
by	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
meet	O
him	O
and	O
ask	O
his	O
Pardon	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Company	O
that	O
be	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
injured	O
him	O
in	O
;	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
bid	O
him	O
again	O
not	O
trifle	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
injur	O
'd	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
resolv	O
'd	O
never	O
to	O
survive	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
now	O
do	O
himself	O
Justice	O
;	O
and	O
drawing	O
his	O
Sword	O
in	O
a	O
violent	O
Passion	O
,	O
swore	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
draw	O
he	O
would	O
run	O
him	O
through	O
:	O
Upon	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
oblig	O
'd	O
to	O
draw	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Consequence	O
has	O
been	O
before	O
related	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
having	O
given	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
the	O
Wound	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
kissed	O
him	O
,	O
bid	O
him	O
take	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
and	O
go	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Fleece	O
,	O
and	O
send	O
Mr.	O
Martin	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
afterwards	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
Escape	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
be	O
died	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Father	O
to	O
his	O
Children	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
then	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Evidences	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
as	O
follows	O
.	O
Besides	O
the	O
Porter	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
as	O
before	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
sent	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Fleece-Tavern	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Quinn	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Drawer	O
at	O
the	O
Swan	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
as	O
before	O
as	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
's	O
disliking	O
the	O
Rooms	O
.	O
And	O
Benji	B-pers
Wicks	I-pers
,	O
Drawer	O
at	O
the	O
Pope	O
's	O
head-Tavern	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
came	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Room	O
:	O
that	O
he	O
show	O
'd	O
him	O
one	O
;	O
that	O
having	O
carried	O
in	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
fill	O
'd	O
a	O
Glass	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
set	O
it	O
down	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
any	O
Encounter	O
,	O
or	O
heard	O
any	O
Noise	O
,	O
till	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
rang	O
the	O
Bell	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
Mr.	O
Quinn	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Fleece-Tavern	O
and	O
call	O
Mr.	O
Martin	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
,	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Martin	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
bid	O
him	O
call	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
but	O
recalling	O
him	O
again	O
bid	O
him	O
fetch	O
a	O
Chair	O
,	O
leaning	O
his	O
Head	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
;	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
Chair	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
his	O
going	O
in	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
what	O
Mr.	O
Quinn	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
very	O
honourably	O
and	O
justly	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
heartily	O
forgave	O
Mr.	O
Quinn	O
live	O
or	O
die	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Meakins	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Master	O
of	O
the	O
Pope's-head-Tavern	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
engaged	O
with	O
the	O
Parish	O
Officers	O
then	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
till	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
had	O
gotten	O
a	O
Chair	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Chair	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
desired	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
wounded	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
found	O
;	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
added	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
you	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
,	O
If	O
I	O
die	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
done	O
me	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
fair	O
Play	O
;	O
I	O
freely	O
forgive	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
Drawer	O
at	O
the	O
Horn-Tavern	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
came	O
about	O
7	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
to	O
their	O
House	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
:	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Steward	O
's	O
Coffee-House	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
to	O
the	O
Horn-Tavern	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
wounded	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
fetch	O
him	O
Mr.	O
Mounsey	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
who	O
dress	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
another	O
Patient	O
,	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
,	O
Who	O
had	O
wounded	O
him	O
?	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Quinn	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
several	O
times	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
fairly	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
freely	O
forgave	O
him	O
.	O
Prudence	B-pers
Inwell	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
came	O
to	O
Steward	O
's	O
Coffee-House	O
in	O
Fleetstreet	O
,	O
supported	O
by	O
the	O
Drawer	O
of	O
the	O
Horn-Tavern	O
;	O
he	O
seem	O
'd	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
land	O
out	O
of	O
Order	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Drawer	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
wounded	O
:	O
She	O
asked	O
him	O
who	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
who	O
did	O
it	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
very	O
fairly	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
freely	O
forgave	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
put	O
a	O
Question	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
how	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
had	O
used	O
to	O
behave	O
himself	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
;	O
she	O
answered	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
used	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
often	O
out	O
of	O
Humour	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
oftentimes	O
been	O
very	O
disturbing	O
to	O
the	O
Company	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Gadsdon	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Coffee-house	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
wounded	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
that	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
,	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
fairly	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
freely	O
forgave	O
him	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
seeing	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
come	O
into	O
Steward	O
's	O
Coffee-house	O
in	O
Disorder	O
,	O
did	O
think	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
said	O
,	O
here	O
comes	O
Bowen	O
in	O
his	O
old	O
Pickle	O
;	O
but	O
afterwards	O
understood	O
he	O
was	O
wounded	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
fairly	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
freely	O
forgave	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Cheret	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Wilks	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
was	O
killed	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Quinn	O
had	O
killed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
had	O
sent	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
much	O
care	O
for	O
going	O
,	O
as	O
Mr.	O
Quinn	O
had	O
quitted	O
their	O
House	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
as	O
an	O
Evidence	O
to	O
any	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
World	O
might	O
imagine	O
he	O
show	O
'd	O
something	O
of	O
Spleen	O
:	O
but	O
however	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
in	O
those	O
Circumstances	O
having	O
sent	O
for	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
desired	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Wilks	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Play	O
to	O
be	O
acted	O
for	O
his	O
Benefit	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
died	O
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
Children	O
might	O
have	O
the	O
Benefit	O
.	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Quinn	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
very	O
ill	O
Language	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
bear	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
oblig	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
draw	O
his	O
Sword	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
receiv	O
'd	O
that	O
Wound	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
Mrs.	O
Bowen	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
prosecuting	O
Mr.	O
Quinn	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Cheret	O
also	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Quinn	O
had	O
often	O
had	O
Disputes	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
used	O
to	O
be	O
jangling	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
Whereas	O
Mr.	O
Weller	O
has	O
given	O
me	O
a	O
very	O
ill	O
Character	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
produce	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
one	O
Reason	O
for	O
that	O
Character	O
,	O
calling	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Reason	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
he	O
had	O
heard	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Weller	O
say	O
,	O
That	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
be	O
would	O
be	O
an	O
Instrument	O
of	O
hanging	O
Mr.	O
Quinn	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
quarrel	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
then	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
though	O
he	O
was	O
unwilling	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
's	O
past	O
Life	O
upon	O
the	O
Stage	O
,	O
yet	O
it	O
being	O
necessary	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Defence	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
Leave	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
to	O
call	O
Mr.	O
Francis	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
quarrelsome	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
several	O
times	O
attempted	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
once	O
particularly	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
sitting	O
at	O
his	O
Father	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
passed	O
by	O
him	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
civilly	O
answered	O
;	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
passed	O
on	O
,	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
Coffee-house	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
back	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
still	O
sitting	O
there	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
Provocation	O
,	O
called	O
him	O
Rascal	O
,	O
and	O
Son	O
of	O
a	O
Whore	O
,	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
cut	O
him	O
over	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
rising	O
and	O
retreating	O
backward	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
he	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
fall	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
made	O
two	O
Passes	O
at	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
but	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
miss	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
putting	O
it	O
by	O
with	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
body	O
coming	O
by	O
and	O
taking	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
shortning	O
his	O
Sword	O
to	O
have	O
stabbed	O
him	O
as	O
he	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
prevented	O
by	O
Persons	O
running	O
to	O
his	O
Assistance	O
.	O
That	O
thereupon	O
he	O
advised	O
with	O
Sir	O
Peter	B-pers
King	I-pers
in	O
order	O
to	O
prosecute	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
but	O
by	O
the	O
Mediation	O
of	O
some	O
Great	O
Men	O
on	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
's	O
Account	O
did	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
afterwards	O
did	O
attack	O
him	O
in	O
Salisbury-Court	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Sword	O
;	O
but	O
People	O
coming	O
to	O
his	O
Assistance	O
prevented	O
him	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
Arrested	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
afterwards	O
broke	O
into	O
his	O
Chamber	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
were	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
demanding	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
met	O
him	O
about	O
three	O
Days	O
before	O
he	O
received	O
this	O
Wound	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Quinn	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
needs	O
drink	O
a	O
Pint	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Ship-Tavern	O
near	O
Temple-Bar	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Lee	O
,	O
you	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
Difference	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
desire	O
you	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
older	O
Man	O
than	O
you	O
,	O
shall	O
probably	O
die	O
before	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
desire	O
you	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
my	O
Burial	O
,	O
which	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
promised	O
him	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
then	O
no	O
Apprehension	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
so	O
soon	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Allpress	I-pers
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
first	O
Assault	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
upon	O
Mr.	O
Lee	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
seeing	O
him	O
push	O
at	O
him	O
as	O
he	O
lay	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
pulling	O
him	O
back	O
prevented	O
him	O
from	O
stabbing	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
was	O
always	O
very	O
fractious	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
Sugar-Loaf	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
Fleetstreet	O
,	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
drawn	O
,	O
swearing	O
and	O
making	O
a	O
great	O
Disturbance	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Man	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
he	O
knew	O
he	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
no	O
Drink	O
,	O
having	O
several	O
times	O
forbad	O
him	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
made	O
a	O
Difference	O
between	O
him	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
thereupon	O
persuaded	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
and	O
not	O
be	O
further	O
troublesome	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
Passion	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
swearing	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
d	O
-	O
m	O
his	O
Bl	O
-	O
d	O
,	O
you	O
prevented	O
me	O
in	O
my	O
Business	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
do	O
yours	O
for	O
you	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
afterwards	O
meeting	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Bowen	O
reply	O
'd	O
It	O
is	O
my	O
Temper	O
,	O
I	O
means	O
no	O
burt	O
,	O
you	O
're	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Fellow	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
then	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Persons	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Theophilus	B-pers
Keen	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
Mr.	O
Quinn	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
always	O
found	O
him	O
rather	O
inclinable	O
to	O
make	O
up	O
than	O
promote	O
Quarrels	O
,	O
and	O
rather	O
take	O
those	O
Things	O
others	O
call	O
'd	O
Affronts	O
,	O
than	O
quarrelsomely	O
resent	O
them	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
confirmed	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Bullock	O
.	O
Mr.	O
King	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Hawks	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Moreton	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
then	O
added	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
done	O
nothing	O
but	O
what	O
I	O
was	O
compelled	O
to	O
do	O
;	O
had	O
I	O
not	O
opposed	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
's	O
Violence	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
have	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
Self-Murther	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
upon	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Swithin	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Pearse	I-pers
;	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
put	O
up	O
a	O
Sash	O
Window	O
and	O
steal	O
the	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
off	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
pursuing	O
him	O
immediately	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan'sin	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Snuff	O
Box	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
3	O
s.6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
another	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
House	O
in	O
White-Friers	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
several	O
Women	O
in	O
company	O
,	O
having	O
drank	O
a	O
Pot	O
or	O
2	O
of	O
Drink	O
and	O
a	O
or	O
3	O
Drams	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
demanded	O
23	O
s.	O
which	O
they	O
refusing	O
to	O
pay	O
,	O
they	O
lock	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
swore	O
at	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
violent	O
manner	O
,	O
run	O
at	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
bot	O
Poker	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Fray	O
his	O
Snuff	O
Box	O
and	O
Money	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
that	O
the	O
Snuff	O
Box	O
was	O
given	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Women	O
whom	O
he	O
brought	O
in	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Wade	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
93	O
yds	O
of	O
Lace	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Pomfret	I-pers
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
desiring	O
him	O
to	O
send	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Lace	O
to	O
one	O
Counsellor	O
Cook	O
's	O
Lady	O
.	O
The	O
Maid	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
sent	O
with	O
the	O
Lace	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
going	O
with	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
Temple	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bid	O
her	O
give	O
her	O
the	O
Lace	O
to	O
show	O
the	O
Lady	O
,	O
and	O
come	O
again	O
at	O
3	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
She	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
Second	O
time	O
for	O
stealing	O
13	O
yards	O
of	O
Mecklin	O
Lace	O
value	O
3	O
l.5	O
s	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Katherine	B-pers
Spathum	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
the	O
2d	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Reign	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
being	O
within	O
the	O
Act	O
of	O
Parliament	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Plintoff	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
her	O
Male	O
Bastard	O
Infant	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Humphreys	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
acknowledge	O
her	O
self	O
to	O
be	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
3	O
Months	O
gone	O
;	O
that	O
about	O
the	O
time	O
aforesaid	O
she	O
complain	O
'd	O
she	O
was	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
suspecting	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
deliver	O
'd	O
taxed	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
denyed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
whereas	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
suspected	O
she	O
had	O
put	O
it	O
,	O
into	O
the	O
Vault	O
;	O
telling	O
her	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
more	O
a	O
Child	O
in	O
the	O
Vault	O
than	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Other	O
Evidences	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
purpose	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
Matter	O
lay	O
undiscovered	O
till	O
the	O
2d	O
Day	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
being	O
emptying	O
,	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
second	O
Bucket	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Skull	O
broke	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
suppos	O
'd	O
was	O
done	O
by	O
the	O
Bucket	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Beecham	O
,	O
a	O
Midwife	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
she	O
could	O
see	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
belt	O
of	O
her	O
Judgment	O
the	O
Child	O
did	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
its	O
full	O
Time	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
wasted	O
by	O
lying	O
so	O
long	O
in	O
the	O
Vault	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
say	O
nothing	O
to	O
its	O
having	O
been	O
born	O
alive	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
Upon	O
its	O
being	O
taken	O
up	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
confess	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
her	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
;	O
but	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
born	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Miscarriage	O
,	O
she	O
having	O
come	O
before	O
her	O
Time	O
.	O
It	O
did	O
appear	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
owned	O
her	O
being	O
with	O
Child	O
;	O
and	O
had	O
provided	O
some	O
Linnen	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
she	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Vault	O
being	O
poor	O
and	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
bear	O
the	O
expence	O
of	O
burying	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Rushatch	I-pers
the	O
6th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Masters	O
Shop	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
and	O
stole	O
a	O
pair	O
,	O
putting	O
them	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
which	O
upon	O
taxing	O
him	O
with	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Counter	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
the	O
Stockings	O
were	O
fallen	O
down	O
.	O
which	O
he	O
stooping	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
the	O
Lad	O
mistook	O
,	O
supposing	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
However	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Free	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Deal	O
Boards	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Eddin	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Barnet	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Ram	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Charleton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
his	O
Ram	O
was	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Head	O
and	O
Skin	O
found	O
buried	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
the	O
Mutton	O
hid	O
between	O
the	O
Tyling	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ryton	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Katherine	B-pers
Speed	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
13	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Marmaduke	B-pers
Bromley	I-pers
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broken	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Pewter	O
stole	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
sold	O
Pewter	O
that	O
Day	O
in	O
a	O
suspitious	O
manner	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ryton	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
own	O
Pewter	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
prov	O
'd	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Procesutor	O
's	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Abnett	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Jame	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
In	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Ray	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
July	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
being	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
(	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Source	O
)	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
the	O
Coat	O
was	O
carrying	O
it	O
off	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
being	O
pursued	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
only	O
a	O
trifling	O
Defence	O
to	O
make	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.10	O
d	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
80	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
fit	O
for	O
Transportation	O
,	O
was	O
burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Issac	B-pers
Tyser	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
half	O
for	O
bringing	O
of	O
Grains	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
.	O
Some	O
Circumstances	O
made	O
the	O
Presumption	O
very	O
strong	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
coming	O
up	O
to	O
a	O
full	O
proof	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
He	O
was	O
again	O
indicted	O
with	O
Katherine	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Batten	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Day	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
19	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
likewise	O
several	O
Circumstances	O
that	O
gave	O
sufficient	O
ground	O
for	O
a	O
strong	O
suspicion	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
amounting	O
to	O
a	O
legal	O
Proof	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Brand	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Wellington	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	O
Leonard	O
Shoreditch	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Spurs	O
value	O
30	O
s	O
in	O
the	O
Stable	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Pratt	I-pers
the	O
19th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
and	O
also	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Window-Curtains	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
The	O
Goods	O
or	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Pratt	O
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
Brand	O
had	O
been	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
taken	O
had	O
confest	O
the	O
Facts	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
denyed	O
them	O
on	O
his	O
Tryal	O
.	O
The	O
Facts	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
the	O
jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
.	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Tyser	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
value	O
3	O
l.10	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3rd	O
of	O
July	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutors	O
Servant	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Watch	O
lying	O
on	O
a	O
Table	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
while	O
she	O
turned	O
her	O
back	O
to	O
do	O
some	O
Business	O
she	O
was	O
about	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
followed	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
cry	O
'd	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
pursued	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
pursued	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
into	O
an	O
Inn-Yard	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
dropp	O
'd	O
the	O
Watch	O
behind	O
a	O
Gate	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
the	O
Fact	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
(	O
Death	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bellamy	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
High-way	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
Wig	O
value	O
20	O
s	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Guinea	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
cross	O
Privy	B-place
Garden	I-place
about	O
a	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
asking	O
him	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
drink	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
refusing	O
,	O
she	O
snatched	O
of	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
slapping	O
her	O
Hand	O
into	O
his	O
,	O
took	O
away	O
a	O
Guinea	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
following	O
her	O
she	O
drop	O
'd	O
the	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Soldier	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
Assistance	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
drawn	O
,	O
hectering	O
him	O
,	O
demanding	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
do	O
to	O
middle	O
with	O
his	O
Wife	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
alleged	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
lain	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
because	O
the	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
his	O
Will	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
be	O
called	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Men	O
with	O
drawn	O
Swords	O
.	O
She	O
denyed	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
but	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Long	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
the	O
3rd	O
of	O
July	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
he	O
being	O
at	O
St.	O
Anns	O
Church	O
,	O
laid	O
his	O
Hat	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
Paw	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
got	O
it	O
on	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
thrusting	O
his	O
own	O
into	O
his	O
Bosom	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Hat	O
on	O
the	O
Church-Steps	O
.	O
But	O
this	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Masters	I-pers
of	O
Hackney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cummins	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
being	O
at	O
Hackney-Church	B-place
his	O
Pocket	O
was	O
pickt	O
of	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
be	O
found	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appeared	O
otherwise	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
her	O
Female	O
Bastard	O
Infant	O
,	O
and	O
throwing	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
the	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Rew	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Necessary	O
House	O
about	O
10	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
with	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
chanc	O
'd	O
to	O
call	O
her	O
Eye	O
into	O
the	O
Vault	O
,	O
and	O
espy	O
'd	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
in	O
to	O
her	O
Husband	O
in	O
a	O
Surprize	O
told	O
him	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
;	O
who	O
not	O
having	O
any	O
body	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
then	O
suspect	O
of	O
fact	O
a	O
matter	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
give	O
credit	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
convinc	O
'd	O
by	O
seeing	O
with	O
his	O
own	O
Eyes	O
;	O
but	O
neither	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
the	O
least	O
thought	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
and	O
his	O
Lady	O
in	O
the	O
Neighborhood	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Row	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
having	O
seen	O
what	O
his	O
Wife	O
had	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Justice	O
of	O
Peace	O
and	O
inform	O
'd	O
him	O
of	O
what	O
had	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
who	O
sent	O
his	O
Clerk	O
,	O
who	O
with	O
an	O
Officer	O
saw	O
the	O
Child	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
knowing	O
whence	O
it	O
should	O
come	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
a	O
Woman	O
whom	O
upon	O
Examination	O
he	O
found	O
was	O
suspected	O
wrongfully	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Night	O
a	O
Man	O
who	O
used	O
his	O
House	O
coming	O
,	O
in	O
took	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
perceive	O
an	O
Uneasiness	O
in	O
his	O
Countenance	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
's	O
him	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
about	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
being	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Vault	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
acknowledging	O
,	O
the	O
Person	O
advised	O
him	O
to	O
he	O
easy	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
know	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Morrow	O
.	O
He	O
thereupon	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
why	O
them	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
?	O
he	O
made	O
no	O
direct	O
Answer	O
,	O
but	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
again	O
if	O
a	O
Woman-body	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
early	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
:	O
he	O
then	O
recollected	O
himself	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
bringing	O
home	O
a	O
Candle	O
she	O
had	O
borrow	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
laying	O
it	O
down	O
had	O
past	O
hastily	O
through	O
the	O
House	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
upon	O
her	O
coming	O
back	O
he	O
perceiving	O
her	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
who	O
to	O
'd	O
him	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
a	O
Sister	O
in	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
for	O
it	O
to	O
do	O
her	O
Work	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
remembering	O
this	O
,	O
began	O
to	O
conclude	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
put	O
the	O
Child	O
in	O
the	O
Vault	O
:	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
then	O
late	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Family	O
gone	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
he	O
concluded	O
to	O
omit	O
the	O
further	O
inquiry	O
into	O
the	O
matter	O
till	O
Morning	O
;	O
but	O
going	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
could	O
not	O
left	O
,	O
but	O
getting	O
up	O
walk	O
'd	O
about	O
the	O
Chamber	O
till	O
Day-light	O
,	O
then	O
about	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Mabent	O
Door	O
till	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
desired	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
taxing	O
her	O
with	O
offering	O
him	O
the	O
Abuse	O
,	O
she	O
at	O
first	O
Stiffly	O
deny	O
'd	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
acknowledged	O
it	O
.	O
Frances	B-pers
Amberry	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Mid	O
wife	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
according	O
to	O
her	O
Judgment	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
at	O
its	O
full	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
born	O
alive	O
,	O
because	O
its	O
Hands	O
were	O
open	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
believed	O
it	O
dy	O
'd	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
Help	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
perceive	O
any	O
Marks	O
of	O
Violence	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
another	O
Midwife	O
,	O
confirm	O
'd	O
what	O
the	O
other	O
had	O
deposed	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
her	O
Tryal	O
acknowledged	O
the	O
Child	O
to	O
be	O
hers	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Vault	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
deluded	O
by	O
a	O
fellow	O
servant	O
at	O
another	O
Place	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
promised	O
her	O
Marriage	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
put	O
her	O
off	O
from	O
time	O
to	O
time	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
born	O
dead	O
,	O
she	O
having	O
received	O
Harm	O
by	O
two	O
Falls	O
not	O
long	O
before	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
six	O
Weeks	O
before	O
her	O
time	O
,	O
had	O
made	O
provision	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
had	O
spoke	O
to	O
a	O
Person	O
to	O
get	O
her	O
a	O
Lodging	O
to	O
Lie-inn	O
in	O
three	O
Days	O
before	O
,	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
Mistress	O
Warning	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
Lie-inn	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
she	O
expected	O
,	O
did	O
try	O
out	O
for	O
Help	O
,	O
but	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
Garret	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Master	O
and	O
Lady	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
Floor	O
,	O
the	O
was	O
not	O
heard	O
;	O
that	O
after	O
her	O
Delivery	O
she	O
lay	O
two	O
Hours	O
in	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
the	O
Child	O
to	O
stir	O
or	O
cry	O
.	O
She	O
brought	O
an	O
Evidence	O
was	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
three	O
Days	O
before	O
this	O
Accident	O
the	O
had	O
spoken	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
procure	O
her	O
a	O
Lodging	O
,	O
telling	O
her	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
Child	O
:	O
she	O
brought	O
others	O
to	O
prove	O
,	O
that	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Prisoner	O
she	O
gave	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
her	O
Trunk	O
to	O
two	O
Women	O
who	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
Mistress	O
's	O
and	O
found	O
Childbed-Linnen	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
presence	O
of	O
her	O
Mistress	O
and	O
others	O
:	O
she	O
produced	O
three	O
others	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
asked	O
them	O
to	O
help	O
her	O
to	O
Childbed	O
Linnen	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
so	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
that	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Linnen	O
which	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
;	O
she	O
produc	O
'd	O
others	O
who	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
distance	O
of	O
her	O
Lodging	O
from	O
that	O
of	O
her	O
Master	O
and	O
Mistress	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
Mistress	O
did	O
remember	O
some	O
Tokens	O
of	O
her	O
having	O
had	O
a	O
Fall	O
.	O
Upon	O
Consideration	O
of	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Bedder	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Boots	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Unwin	I-pers
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Boots	O
hung	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Stoke-hole	O
of	O
a	O
Brewhouse	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
here	O
with	O
a	O
Cart	O
to	O
fetch	O
away	O
the	O
Grains	O
stole	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
lock	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
his	O
Box	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
However	O
the	O
Prisner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
given	O
him	O
to	O
lay	O
up	O
by	O
his	O
Fellow-servant	O
.	O
But	O
this	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Dillon	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
val.2	O
s.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Goodson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
26	O
pound	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Ashurst	I-pers
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisner	O
was	O
Coachman	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
Sugar-baker	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Sugar	O
was	O
hid	O
under	O
the	O
Manger	O
in	O
the	O
Stable	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
that	O
one	O
Lump	O
was	O
given	O
him	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Men	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
the	O
rest	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
proving	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
Mary	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
's	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transport	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rowley	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
in	O
having	O
Goods	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
Stolen	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Proof	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Percival	B-pers
Hutchinson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Mr	O
Peter	B-pers
Anthony	I-pers
Motteux	I-pers
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
indicted	O
also	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
for	O
stealing	O
8	O
Guineas	O
from	O
the	O
Said	O
Mrs.	O
Motteux	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Susan	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Bedding	O
,	O
val.24s	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Seed	I-pers
;	O
Feb.17	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
Lodgers	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
off	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
,	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
.	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
80	O
Handkerchiefs	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
from	O
Samuel	B-pers
Beck	I-pers
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
;	O
he	O
having	O
sold	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
the	O
Handkerechiefs	O
,	O
and	O
stopp	O
'd	O
them	O
for	O
Non	O
Payment	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
therefore	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
value	O
1	O
s,6	O
d.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Ursula	B-pers
Parks	I-pers
the	O
18th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
which	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Gilbert	B-pers
Sharp	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
12	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
the	O
1	O
st	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Lodger	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Room	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
gone	O
,	O
white	O
he	O
was	O
abroad	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
strong	O
enough	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
27	O
Guineas	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
his	O
Lodger	O
,	O
broke	O
open	O
his	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Room	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
parcel	O
of	O
Pick-lock-keys	O
and	O
other	O
such-like	O
instruments	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
This	O
Fact	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Dillon	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Young	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Wearing	O
Apparel	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Good	O
were	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
upon	O
Dillon	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Young	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Dillon	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
11	O
Shillings	O
,	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
proved	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cave	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Field	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
8	O
s.6	O
d	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Sampson	B-pers
Barret	I-pers
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
through	O
Drury	B-place
Lane	I-place
at	O
about	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
Women	O
kind	O
standing	O
together	O
,	O
who	O
divided	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
Lane	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
through	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
by	O
his	O
Side	O
talking	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
:	O
He	O
Immidiately	O
seized	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
dropped	O
1	O
s.6	O
d.	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
7	O
s.	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Stocking	O
in	O
the	O
Round-house	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
she	O
received	O
8	O
s.6	O
d.	O
for	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
as	O
Pocket	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
her	O
Stocking	O
for	O
Security	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
believing	O
her	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
(	O
Death	O
)	O
Robert	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolph	I-place
's	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
in	O
speaking	O
Seditious	O
and	O
Treasonable	O
Words	O
against	O
the	O
King	B-pers
and	I-pers
Government	I-pers
the	O
16th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Ryland	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
Minories	B-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
passed	O
along	O
,	O
crying	O
,	O
King	O
James	O
for	O
ever	O
,	O
who	O
dare	O
oppose	O
him	O
?	O
Capt	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Smart	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
passed	O
along	O
the	O
Minories	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
King	O
James	O
the	O
Third	O
,	O
King	O
James	O
the	O
Third	O
for	O
ever	O
,	O
who	O
dare	O
oppose	O
him	O
?	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
all	O
his	O
Foes	O
:	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
replied	O
,	O
I	O
dare	O
oppose	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
laying	O
hold	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
asking	O
him	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
ever	O
taken	O
the	O
Abjuration-Oath	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
never	O
had	O
,	O
nor	O
ever	O
would	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
and	O
Place	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
King	O
James	O
the	O
Third	O
for	O
ever	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
-	O
all	O
his	O
Foes	O
,	O
who	O
dare	O
oppose	O
King	O
James	O
the	O
Third	O
?	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
allow	O
'd	O
they	O
believ	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
to	O
that	O
degree	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
it	O
believ	O
'd	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
receiv	O
'd	O
sentence	O
to	O
stand	O
once	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
,	O
to	O
pay	O
20	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
suffer	O
6	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
Bridget	B-pers
Noland	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
of	O
2	O
Guineas	O
and	O
7	O
s.6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Fleetstreet	O
about	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
a	O
Company	O
of	O
Men	O
and	O
women	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
into	O
the	O
Crowd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Sleeve	O
,	O
another	O
being	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
that	O
some	O
Fellow	O
followed	O
her	O
and	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
rid	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
desiring	O
him	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
home	O
to	O
her	O
Lodgings	O
;	O
which	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
were	O
hard	O
by	O
;	O
he	O
accordingly	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
White-Fryers	B-place
,	O
taking	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
civil	O
Women	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
they	O
would	O
needs	O
have	O
him	O
drink	O
some	O
Wine	O
or	O
a	O
Dram	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Cherry-Brandy	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
full	O
Glasses	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
him	O
suspect	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
drink	O
above	O
half	O
his	O
Glass	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
had	O
drank	O
a	O
Dram	O
or	O
two	O
round	O
,	O
they	O
pulled	O
up	O
their	O
Coats	O
about	O
their	O
Wast	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
now	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
what	O
they	O
had	O
,	O
they	O
must	O
see	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
to	O
unbuttoning	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
pickt	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
demanded	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
threatning	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
it	O
him	O
;	O
in	O
Return	O
of	O
which	O
,	O
a	O
Woman	O
in	O
a	O
Furbelow-Scarf	O
fell	O
a	O
swearing	O
and	O
damming	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
swore	O
if	O
he	O
made	O
any	O
Noise	O
there	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
knock	O
out	O
his	O
Brains	O
.	O
So	O
the	O
Landlord	O
came	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
she	O
charg	O
'd	O
the	O
Constable	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
both	O
were	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
Women	O
in	O
the	O
Furbelow-Scarf	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
with	O
her	O
with	O
his	O
Breeches	O
unbutton	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
not	O
lie	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
saying	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Pox	O
,	O
but	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Shilling	O
to	O
fetch	O
Rods	O
to	O
Slogg	O
him	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
pay	O
his	O
Reckoning	O
it	O
was	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
Money	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
while	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Cryer	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Clogs	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Noble	I-pers
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
under	O
pretence	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Clogs	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Katherine	B-pers
Rosse	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Susannah	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Collot	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
in	O
defrauding	O
John	B-pers
Akerman	I-pers
of	O
4	O
s	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
Shop	O
desiring	O
him	O
to	O
change	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
objected	O
,	O
as	O
not	O
having	O
Silver	O
enough	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
12	O
s.	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
haste	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
a	O
Portmantean	O
that	O
was	O
brought	O
:	O
He	O
having	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
threw	O
down	O
7	O
s	O
6	O
d.	O
into	O
the	O
Drawer	O
,	O
saying	O
it	O
was	O
no	O
matter	O
,	O
and	O
goes	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
4	O
s	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
Find	O
20	O
s.	O
Mary	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
or	O
Ann	B-pers
Bickam	I-pers
,	O
by	O
Strangling	O
her	O
with	O
a	O
Leather	O
Strap	O
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
July	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
;	O
at	O
which	O
the	O
Court	O
being	O
something	O
surprized	O
,	O
would	O
have	O
permitted	O
her	O
to	O
withdraw	O
her	O
Plea	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
still	O
persisted	O
to	O
plead	O
Guilty	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
then	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
well	O
to	O
consider	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
Murther	O
was	O
laid	O
to	O
her	O
Charge	O
,	O
which	O
perhaps	O
if	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
,	O
might	O
not	O
be	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
she	O
must	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
:	O
To	O
which	O
she	O
replied	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
confess	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
nothing	O
but	O
the	O
Truth	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
perceiving	O
that	O
nothing	O
had	O
but	O
to	O
alter	O
her	O
Plea	O
doubted	O
whether	O
she	O
were	O
compis	O
mentis	O
order	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
set	O
by	O
till	O
the	O
Alter	O
she	O
being	O
called	O
up	O
was	O
Arraign	O
'd	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
Guilty	O
,	O
saying	O
she	O
did	O
do	O
it	O
:	O
and	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
Court	O
why	O
she	O
did	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
Revenge	O
the	O
Father	O
of	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
he	O
been	O
there	O
she	O
had	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
she	O
desired	O
no	O
other	O
than	O
to	O
die	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
Blood	O
required	O
Blood	O
.	O
Being	O
afterwards	O
called	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
to	O
receive	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
to	O
say	O
why	O
sentence	O
should	O
not	O
pass	O
upon	O
her	O
according	O
to	O
Law	O
?	O
she	O
made	O
Answer	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
The	O
Person	O
whom	O
she	O
murder	O
'd	O
was	O
a	O
Girl	O
of	O
about	O
3	O
Years	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
old	O
,	O
the	O
Daughter	O
of	O
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
that	O
either	O
is	O
,	O
or	O
is	O
reputed	O
her	O
Mother	O
's	O
Husband	O
by	O
a	O
former	O
Wife	O
.	O
The	O
Provocation	O
was	O
,	O
his	O
taking	O
away	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Tobacco-box	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
set	O
a	O
great	O
Value	O
upon	O
for	O
the	O
sake	O
of	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
;	O
at	O
his	O
taking	O
away	O
of	O
which	O
,	O
she	O
threatned	O
Revenge	O
either	O
upon	O
him	O
or	O
his	O
;	O
and	O
accordingly	O
be	O
bing	O
gone	O
to	O
the	O
Guard	O
,	O
took	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Leather	O
Garters	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
,	O
strangled	O
the	O
Child	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
acquainted	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
with	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
:	O
yet	O
there	O
is	O
not	O
in	O
her	O
the	O
least	O
appearance	O
of	O
Lunacy	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jacob	B-pers
Wykes	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Rape	O
committed	O
on	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
,	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Michael	I-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
of	O
27	O
years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
Jacob	O
Wykes	O
did	O
against	O
her	O
Will	O
ravish	O
and	O
Carnally	O
know	O
her	O
the	O
said	O
Ann	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
and	O
that	O
John	O
Johnson	O
was	O
present	O
Aiding	O
and	O
Assisting	O
.	O
Ann	O
Cooper	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
day	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
desired	O
by	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Shamber	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Jacob	O
Wykes	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	B-place
Tavern	I-place
in	I-place
Drury-lane	I-place
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
one	O
Capt	O
.	O
Hacket	O
,	O
to	O
desire	O
him	O
to	O
send	O
to	O
Guineas	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Shamber	O
,	O
she	O
accordingly	O
went	O
about	O
7	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Wykes	O
's	O
House	O
(	O
who	O
she	O
said	O
had	O
kept	O
a	O
Bawdy	O
House	O
in	O
the	O
Hundreds	O
of	O
Drury	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
asked	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
how	O
she	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Bawdy-house	O
,	O
replied	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
occasion	O
enough	O
to	O
know	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
Sorrow	O
)	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
thither	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
but	O
Wykes	O
the	O
Master	O
,	O
Johnson	O
for	O
the	O
Drawer	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Porter	O
,	O
whom	O
she	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
send	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Italian	O
Coffee-house	O
for	O
Capt	O
.	O
Hacket	O
;	O
that	O
Wykes	O
asked	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
a	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
her	O
into	O
a	O
back	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Drawer	O
brought	O
her	O
half	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
in	O
came	O
Mr.	O
Wykes	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
Madam	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
sent	O
for	O
Captain	O
Hacket	O
,	O
and	O
takes	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
wine	O
and	O
drinks	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
double	O
locks	O
it	O
,	O
comes	O
to	O
her	O
and	O
says	O
,	O
Madam	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
-	O
mn	O
my	O
Soul	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
,	O
lie	O
with	O
you	O
:	O
To	O
which	O
she	O
replied	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
to	O
struggling	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
striving	O
and	O
crying	O
and	O
till	O
she	O
was	O
dead	O
almost	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
still	O
resisting	O
and	O
crying	O
out	O
he	O
hit	O
her	O
several	O
Blows	O
an	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
stopp	O
'd	O
her	O
Month	O
,	O
held	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Throat	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
at	O
last	O
recovering	O
herself	O
upon	O
her	O
Knees	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
quite	O
spent	O
with	O
striving	O
and	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
be	O
slung	O
her	O
cross	O
a	O
low	O
Table	O
and	O
did	O
lie	O
with	O
her	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
Drawer	O
,	O
Johnson	O
,	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
holding	O
the	O
Door	O
on	O
the	O
out-side	O
.	O
That	O
having	O
done	O
,	O
the	O
Drawer	O
opened	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
call	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
mn	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
Bitch	O
,	O
not	O
he	O
;	O
if	O
you	O
make	O
such	O
a	O
Noise	O
I	O
'll	O
kill	O
You	O
.	O
But	O
he	O
afterwards	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
his	O
Knees	O
begg	O
'd	O
her	O
Pardon	O
,	O
telling	O
her	O
his	O
Master	O
hired	O
him	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
That	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
crying	O
with	O
her	O
Clothes	O
tore	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Mob	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
way	O
to	O
Exeter-street	O
,	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Cater	O
,	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
how	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
used	O
:	O
but	O
he	O
refused	O
to	O
go	O
without	O
a	O
Warrant	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Cater	O
had	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
meet	O
him	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
To	O
prove	O
this	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Evidences	O
folllowing	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Cater	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
come	O
to	O
him	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Day	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
that	O
the	O
Man	O
at	O
the	O
Globe-Tavern	O
had	O
lyen	O
with	O
her	O
whether	O
she	O
would	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
be	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
safe	O
to	O
go	O
without	O
a	O
Warrant	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Thursday	O
following	O
Mr.	O
Wykes	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
struck	O
her	O
twice	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
denied	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
either	O
lyen	O
with	O
her	O
or	O
struck	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
her	O
any	O
Harm	O
he	O
would	O
ask	O
her	O
Pardon	O
,	O
saying	O
indeed	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
10	O
s.	O
for	O
tearing	O
her	O
Smock	O
.	O
Hugh	B-pers
Reason	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
Cater	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
abused	O
by	O
Wykes	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
lie	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
force	O
her	O
Body	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
struggled	O
with	O
her	O
and	O
bruised	O
her	O
Arm	O
:	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Neal	I-pers
,	O
Clerk	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
came	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
a	O
Clock	O
for	O
a	O
Warrant	O
,	O
soubbing	O
and	O
crying	O
so	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
speak	O
,	O
and	O
tell	O
him	O
what	O
she	O
came	O
about	O
;	O
she	O
gave	O
an	O
Information	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
lie	O
with	O
her	O
upon	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
and	O
-	O
in	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
more	O
,	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
Information	O
.	O
That	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
her	O
Clothes	O
were	O
much	O
rumpled	O
her	O
Arms	O
bruised	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
was	O
hurt	O
in	O
other	O
Parts	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
inquire	O
into	O
.	O
He	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
inform	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
gone	O
from	O
his	O
House	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
not	O
taken	O
till	O
5	O
Days	O
after	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Gamble	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
Home	O
her	O
Gown	O
was	O
torn	O
,	O
all	O
the	O
Sleeve	O
off	O
,	O
her	O
Apron	O
and	O
her	O
Smock	O
torn	O
,	O
her	O
Arms	O
Black	O
and	O
Blue	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
used	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
as	O
has	O
been	O
before	O
declared	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
threatned	O
that	O
if	O
the	O
did	O
make	O
a	O
Noise	O
he	O
would	O
murther	O
her	O
.	O
He	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
as	O
to	O
her	O
Character	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
lodg	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
five	O
Months	O
,	O
had	O
always	O
behaved	O
her	O
self	O
very	O
modestly	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
never	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
that	O
had	O
she	O
been	O
otherwise	O
she	O
should	O
never	O
have	O
come	O
into	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
one	O
who	O
always	O
kept	O
,	O
very	O
good	O
Hours	O
,	O
had	O
no	O
Company	O
resorted	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
worked	O
very	O
industriously	O
at	O
her	O
Needle	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
inform	O
'd	O
,	O
had	O
a	O
Husband	O
at	O
Sea	O
,	O
who	O
sent	O
her	O
sometimes	O
10	O
,	O
sometimes	O
30	O
l.	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Clarks	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Week	O
following	O
when	O
she	O
saw	O
her	O
,	O
her	O
Arms	O
had	O
several	O
Marks	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
said	O
came	O
by	O
her	O
being	O
so	O
misused	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
the	O
same	O
was	O
confirmed	O
by	O
one	O
Ann	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
indeed	O
the	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
about	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
requir	O
'd	O
for	O
Capt	O
.	O
Harket	O
,	O
be	O
seat	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
Room	O
about	O
five	O
Foot	O
from	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
open	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
in	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
that	O
Company	O
calling	O
,	O
above	O
stairs	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
having	O
drank	O
one	O
Half-Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
paid	O
for	O
two	O
Half-pint	O
,	O
went	O
away	O
without	O
making	O
any	O
Noise	O
.	O
The	O
Porter	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Entry	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
she	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Mistress	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Bar	O
or	O
Bar	O
Room	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
then	O
called	O
Persons	O
to	O
her	O
Character	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Jerrings	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Common	O
Woman	O
,	O
that	O
made	O
it	O
her	O
Business	O
(	O
as	O
they	O
call	O
it	O
)	O
to	O
Trap	O
People	O
,	O
by	O
pretending	O
to	O
be	O
with	O
Child	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
be	O
Ravish	O
d	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Woman	O
that	O
he	O
thought	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
so	O
notorious	O
a	O
Woman	O
upon	O
the	O
Face	O
of	O
the	O
whole	O
Earth	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
indicted	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Butler	O
,	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
the	O
Fleet	O
,	O
on	O
such	O
an	O
Occasion	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
produc	O
'd	O
no	O
less	O
than	O
37	O
Evidences	O
against	O
her	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
arrested	O
a	O
Person	O
for	O
a	O
Bastard	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
offering	O
her	O
2	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
she	O
swore	O
'd	O
-	O
him	O
,	O
had	O
it	O
not	O
been	O
for	O
him	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
got	O
100	O
l	O
,	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Singleton	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
by	O
relation	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
ruin	O
'd	O
half	O
a	O
hundred	O
Families	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
employed	O
him	O
and	O
his	O
Partner	O
to	O
arrest	O
a	O
Man	O
for	O
a	O
Bastard	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
his	O
Partner	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
his	O
Hand	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
middle	O
Finger	O
of	O
his	O
Right	O
Hand	O
to	O
her	O
Body	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Officers	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
oldest	O
Bite	O
and	O
oldest	O
Whore	O
we	O
have	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
ruin	O
'd	O
several	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
them	O
run	O
away	O
from	O
their	O
Families	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
,	O
another	O
Officer	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
Common	O
Woman	O
of	O
the	O
Town	O
for	O
some	O
Years	O
,	O
has	O
been	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Work	O
House	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Short	I-pers
,	O
another	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
by	O
such	O
Sratagems	O
got	O
a	O
Note	O
of	O
a	O
Silversmith	O
of	O
his	O
Acquaintance	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
Warrant	O
for	O
her	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
deliver	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
In	O
answer	O
to	O
this	O
,	O
she	O
affed	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
as	O
Innocent	O
of	O
all	O
as	O
an	O
Angel	O
in	O
Heaven	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
both	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
,	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cousens	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
60	O
Pound	O
of	O
Tea	O
,	O
value	O
60	O
l.	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broken	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Tea	O
stolen	O
,	O
a	O
Door	O
that	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Cellar	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
was	O
broken	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Till	O
where	O
his	O
Money	O
used	O
to	O
be	O
was	O
broken	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
not	O
answering	O
Expectation	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Money	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Warehouse-Door	O
was	O
forced	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Tea	O
stollen	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Shop-Door	O
,	O
the	O
Door	O
being	O
left	O
open	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
by	O
the	O
Wch	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
hearing	O
of	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Tea	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
old	O
,	O
upon	O
Enquiry	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
;	O
and	O
suspecting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
apprehended	O
,	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
in	O
the	O
Day-time	O
.	O
Conceal	O
'd	O
himself	O
till	O
late	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
then	O
broke	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Cellar	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
thence	O
into	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
(	O
Death	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Receiving	O
(	O
Knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stollen	O
)	O
17	O
yards	O
of	O
Linnen	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Hooper	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
convicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
it	O
last	O
April	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
Thomas	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Persons	O
beforemention	O
'd	O
having	O
stollen	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
Information	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
by	O
Andrew	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
,	O
but	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
:	O
But	O
Hooper	O
and	O
Jones	O
being	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
one	O
Margaret	B-pers
Hardcastle	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
pawned	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
in	O
Plumbtree	O
,	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
but	O
Margaret	B-pers
Hardcastle	I-pers
having	O
by	O
the	O
Management	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
as	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
)	O
been	O
gotten	O
out	O
of	O
Clerkenwell	O
Prison	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
disappointed	O
of	O
his	O
Evidence	O
;	O
so	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
Proof	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death,5	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Tyser	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cave	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand,2	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Quinn	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Abnett	I-pers
To	O
be	O
Transported,19	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
Katherine	B-pers
Roffe	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Wade	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
William	I-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Wellington	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Free	I-pers
,	O
Benjamim	B-pers
Brand	I-pers
,	O
Bridget	B-pers
Noland	I-pers
,	O
Susan	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Long	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Masters	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
,	O
Philip	B-pers
Goodson	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Dillon	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Cryer	I-pers
,	O
to	O
be	O
Whipp	O
'd	O
.	O
Roberst	O
Harrison	O
,	O
Fin	O
'd	O
20	O
Marks,6	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Collet	I-pers
,	O
Fin	O
'd	O
20	O
s.	O
Letter	O
Published	O
on	O
two	O
Neat	O
Pocket	O
Volumes	O
A	O
Compleat	O
Collection	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
most	O
remarkable	O
Tryals	O
that	O
have	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
Sessions-House	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Baily	O
more	O
than	O
forty	O
Years	O
last	O
past	O
;	O
for	O
Murthers	O
High	O
Way	O
Robbing	O
Pyracy	O
House-king	O
Foot-padding	O
Rape	O
Sodomy	O
By	O
Polygamy	O
Fortune-stealing	O
Trepanning	O
Kidnapping	O
Shop-Litting	O
Perjury	O
Countericiting	O
the	O
Coin	O
,	O
Exchequer-Bills	O
,	O
Bank-Notes	O
,	O
Stamps	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Collected	O
from	O
the	O
Originals	O
,	O
Books	O
of	O
Tryal	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Papers	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Paul	B-pers
Lorrain	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Wykes	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Allen	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
,	O
the	O
several	O
Orries	O
of	O
Newgate	O
.	O
Even	O
from	O
the	O
very	O
first	O
Print	O
ing	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
present-Time	O
;	O
and	O
from	O
other	O
Authentick	O
Narratives	O
.	O
And	O
particulary	O
these	O
Tryals	O
,	O
Behaviour	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
,	O
following	O
,	O
Of	O
Count	O
Coningsmark	O
,	O
Capt	O
.	O
Vratz	O
,	O
Lieutenant	O
Stern	B-pers
,	O
and	O
Boroski	O
the	O
Polander	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
squite	O
Thynne	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sivage	I-pers
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Maid	O
;	O
Kannab	O
Blay	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Fact	O
;	O
Roger	B-pers
Congden	I-pers
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Madam	O
Gettings	O
,	O
her	O
Child	O
and	O
Maid	O
;	O
Margaret	B-pers
Martel	I-pers
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Madam	O
Pullen	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Jowster	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Madam	O
La	O
Grand	O
,	O
the	O
Frenchwomen	O
in	O
Spittle-Fields	O
;	O
Cyrus	B-pers
Simon	I-pers
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
his	O
Father-in-Law	O
;	O
James	B-pers
Solby	I-pers
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Bartlet	I-pers
;	O
Pater	O
Dramanti	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
his	O
Wife	O
;	O
Edmund	B-pers
Andley	I-pers
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Madam	O
Bullevant	O
;	O
Harman	B-pers
Strodtman	I-pers
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Wolters	I-pers
his	O
Fellow-Prentice	O
;	O
Gerad	O
Dromelius	O
,	O
Micheal	O
Van	B-pers
Berg	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Katherine	B-pers
Van	I-pers
Berg	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Dutch	O
People	O
in	O
East-Smithfield	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Norrice	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Foulks	O
,	O
a	O
Clergyman	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
his	O
Bastard-Child	O
;	O
The	O
Butcher	O
of	O
Glacester	O
for	O
killing	O
Mr.	O
Cooper	O
the	O
Constable	O
in	O
May-Fair	O
;	O
Roger	B-pers
Lowen	I-pers
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Loyd	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Margridge	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Kettle-Drumer	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Capt	O
.	O
Cape	O
of	O
the	O
Guards	O
;	O
Maynard	O
,	O
Bevins	O
and	O
Marsh	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Stocton	O
the	O
Victualler	O
;	O
William	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
his	O
Wife	O
;	O
and	O
many	O
other	O
remarkable	O
Murthers	O
.	O
Of	O
Highway-men	O
,	O
the	O
Tryals	O
,	O
Confessions	O
,	O
and	O
Dying	O
Speeches	O
of	O
Clande	O
du	O
Val	O
,	O
Old	O
Mob	O
,	O
the	O
Golden	O
Farmer	O
,	O
Capt	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Whiteney	I-pers
,	O
Abraham	B-pers
Statey	I-pers
,	O
Capt	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Tool	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Benford	I-pers
(	O
a	O
Blind	O
Man	O
)	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
(	O
a	O
Lame	O
Man	O
)	O
for	O
Robbing	O
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
more	O
notorions	O
Highway-Men	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
Pyracy	O
,	O
the	O
Tryal	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
of	O
Capt	O
.	O
Kid	O
and	O
his	O
Crew	O
.	O
Capt	O
.	O
Culiford	O
his	O
Crew	O
,	O
Capt	O
.	O
Guittar	O
and	O
70	O
of	O
his	O
Crew	O
,	O
Capt	O
.	O
Brent	O
,	O
Capt	O
.	O
Boyce	O
,	O
Capt	O
.	O
Lawrence	O
&	O
c.	O
for	O
a	O
Clergyman	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
for	O
Counterfeiting	O
the	O
Stamps	O
on	O
Paper	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
for	O
Counterfeiting	O
Exchequer	O
Bills	O
.	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Blackham	I-pers
,	O
for	O
Coining	O
Dutch	O
Skillings	O
Fouler	O
,	O
Stanlan	O
,	O
and	O
Goff	O
.	O
and	O
Moor	O
,	O
or	O
Robbing	O
the	O
Goldsmiths	O
in	O
Boswel	O
Court	O
,	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
Mr.	O
VVharton	O
,	O
Hargen	O
Swend	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
Mrs	O
Ramlings	O
.	O
Hand	O
on	O
Fielding	O
,	O
for	O
marrying	O
the	O
Dutche	O
's	O
of	O
Cleveland	O
.	O
Capt	O
.	O
Rigbey	O
,	O
for	O
Sodoms	O
.	O
Vangbam	O
and	O
Davis	O
,	O
for	O
fallty	O
swearing	O
Sodomy	O
on	O
several	O
Persons	O
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
,	O
Popish	O
Priest	O
,	O
for	O
absuling	O
Eilzabeth	O
Rich	O
of	O
her	O
Sins	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
,	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
for	O
turning	O
Roman-Catholick	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Marchant	I-pers
,	O
for	O
Pre	O
Mr.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Pitot	I-pers
,	O
a	O
French	O
Refugee	O
,	O
into	O
the	O
Hands	O
of	O
Popish	O
Priests	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
send	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Inquisition	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
for	O
a	O
Rape	O
;	O
Henry	B-pers
Simpkins	I-pers
&	O
c	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Strickland	I-pers
alias	O
Butler	O
,	O
for	O
forging	O
a	O
Bond	O
for	O
27000	O
l.	O
on	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Clayton	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
for	O
Kidnapping	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Larkin	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Contriver	O
of	O
the	O
Sham-Plot	O
,	O
charg	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
Bishop	O
of	O
Rochester	O
,	O
Earls	O
of	O
Marlborough	O
and	O
Salisbury	O
:	O
And	O
many	O
more	O
notorious	O
Criminals	O
of	O
all	O
Kinds	O
,	O
too	O
many	O
to	O
be	O
inserted	O
here	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
Phillips	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
J.	O
Brotherton	O
and	O
W.	O
Meadows	O
at	O
the	O
Black	O
Hull	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
,	O
and	O
J.	O
Roberts	O
in	O
Warwick-Lane	O
.	O
Price	O
Five	O
Shillings	O
the	O
Two	O
Volumes	O
bound	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Good	O
of	O
the	O
Publick	O
.	O
WHereas	O
several	O
Gentlewomen	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
that	O
Sex	O
,	O
in	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
have	O
contracted	O
an	O
Evil	O
Habit	O
of	O
Body	O
,	O
wherein	O
the	O
vicious	O
Humours	O
,	O
at	O
first	O
dispers	O
'd	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Whole	O
,	O
come	O
at	O
length	O
to	O
be	O
lodged	O
in	O
one	O
part	O
or	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
times	O
,	O
for	O
Causes	O
too	O
long	O
to	O
be	O
here	O
mentioned	O
,	O
are	O
thrown	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Womb	O
,	O
occasioning	O
a	O
dangerous	O
Weakness	O
in	O
that	O
part	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
neglected	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
turns	O
Cancerous	O
;	O
and	O
often	O
proves	O
Fatal	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
to	O
acquiant	O
all	O
such	O
as	O
may	O
have	O
occasion	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
speedy	O
Relief	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
had	O
from	O
a	O
Sworn	O
and	O
Experienc	O
'd	O
Midwife	O
,	O
dwelling	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Arms	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
the	O
Tin-Shop	O
near	O
Exeter	O
Change	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
who	O
perform	O
'd	O
a	O
wonderful	O
Cure	O
upon	O
a	O
Lady	O
at	O
the	O
Back	O
,	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
given	O
over	O
by	O
the	O
Physicians	O
,	O
and	O
since	O
has	O
Cured	O
several	O
Gentlewomen	O
and	O
others	O
in	O
the	O
City	O
and	O
Suburbs	O
of	O
London	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
put	O
my	O
self	O
in	O
publick	O
Print	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
satisfy	O
the	O
Afflicted	O
where	O
they	O
may	O
have	O
present	O
Ease	O
and	O
Relief	O
,	O
if	O
not	O
,	O
no	O
Money	O
.	O
Some	O
BOOKs	O
printed	O
for	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
Edmund	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
as	O
the	O
Bible	O
and	O
Crown	O
in	O
Lombard	O
Street	O
,	O
near	O
Stocks	O
Market	O
.	O
AE	O
P'Fables	O
,	O
with	O
Morals	O
and	O
Reflections	O
,	O
as	O
improv	O
'd	O
by	O
Sir	O
Roger	O
l'Estrange	O
,	O
done	O
into	O
Variety	O
of	O
English	O
Vene	O
.	O
Illustrated	O
with	O
C'ts	O
curiously	O
engrav	O
'd	O
on	O
Copper	O
Plates	O
.	O
The	O
Second	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
2	O
s.6	O
d.	O
The	O
London	O
New	O
Method	O
and	O
Art	O
of	O
Teaching	O
Children	O
to	O
Spell	O
and	O
Read	O
;	O
so	O
as	O
they	O
may	O
,	O
without	O
the	O
Help	O
of	O
any	O
other	O
Books	O
,	O
read	O
the	O
Bible	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
twelve	O
Months	O
.	O
Note	O
,	O
This	O
Way	O
of	O
Teaching	O
is	O
approved	O
by	O
most	O
School	O
Masters	O
as	O
the	O
best	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
6	O
d.	O
with	O
great	O
Allowance	O
to	O
those	O
who	O
sell	O
or	O
give	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
Note	O
,	O
There	O
are	O
some	O
priated	O
on	O
Fine	O
Paper	O
,	O
bound	O
up	O
with	O
Cuts	O
pt.8	O
d	O
Mr.	O
Jordaine	O
Duodecimal	O
Arithmetick	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
most	O
Concise	O
and	O
Exact	O
Method	O
extant	O
.	O
In	O
Three	O
Books	O
.	O
Containing	O
Notation	O
,	O
Addition	O
,	O
Subtraction	O
,	O
Multiplication	O
,	O
Division	O
,	O
Reduct	O
on	O
,	O
Extraction	O
of	O
the	O
Square	O
and	O
Cube	O
Roots	O
,	O
Rule	O
of	O
Proportion	O
Direct	O
and	O
Reverse	O
,	O
Duodecimally	O
performed	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
Practically	O
applied	O
to	O
the	O
measuring	O
of	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
surperficies	O
,	O
and	O
Solids	O
,	O
as	O
Board	O
,	O
Glass	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Timber	O
,	O
Stone	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
Guaging	O
of	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
Brewers	O
Tuns	O
and	O
Carks	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
and	O
that	O
with	O
more	O
Ease	O
and	O
Expedition	O
,	O
than	O
by	O
Vulgar	O
or	O
Decimal	O
Arithematick	O
.	O
Very	O
Useful	O
for	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
Men	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
Gentlemen	O
as	O
others	O
,	O
but	O
especially	O
for	O
Merchants	O
,	O
Writing	O
Matters	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
Measuring	O
Artificers	O
.	O
And	O
all	O
the	O
Rules	O
made	O
Plain	O
,	O
and	O
Easie	O
for	O
the	O
meanest	O
Capacity.8	O
vo	O
.	O
Price	O
Bound	O
2	O
s.6	O
d.	O
The	O
Benefit	O
of	O
Early	O
Piety	O
,	O
recommended	O
to	O
all	O
Young	O
Persons	O
,	O
and	O
particularly	O
to	O
those	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
.	O
By	O
W.	O
Smythies	O
,	O
late	O
Morning	O
Lecturer	O
of	O
St.	O
Michael	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
,	O
London	O
.	O
The	O
Third	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
6	O
d	O
:	O
The	O
Pen	O
's	O
Dexterly	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
The	O
Ingentons	O
and	O
useful	O
Art	O
of	O
Writing	O
Short-Hand	O
.	O
Containing	O
Twenty	O
Copper-plates	O
(	O
curioully	O
engrav	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Author	O
's	O
Life-time	O
for	O
the	O
Use	O
of	O
his	O
Scholars	O
)	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Letters	O
,	O
Characters	O
and	O
Contractious	O
used	O
therein	O
.	O
With	O
Rules	O
and	O
Directions	O
explaining	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
the	O
meanest	O
Capacity	O
.	O
Whereonto	O
are	O
added	O
Law-terms	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
Discourses	O
,	O
as	O
on	O
War	O
,	O
Trade	O
,	O
Birds	O
,	O
Beasts	O
,	O
Fruits	O
,	O
Vermin	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Approv	O
'd	O
by	O
both	O
Universities	O
,	O
Practis	O
'd	O
to	O
Hononrable	O
Persons	O
,	O
Eminent	O
Lawyers	O
and	O
Gentlemen	O
:	O
and	O
is	O
of	O
all	O
Use	O
for	O
Travellers	O
,	O
Historian	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
By	O
Jeremish	O
Rich	O
.	O
The	O
Sixth	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
A	O
Compleat	O
Collection	O
of	O
Curts	O
of	O
the	O
Old	O
and	O
New	O
Testament	O
,	O
well	O
Design	O
'd	O
and	O
Engraved	O
;	O
Diverting	O
and	O
Useful	O
(	O
for	O
Young	O
Persons	O
especially	O
)	O
in	O
helping	O
them	O
to	O
Attain	O
to	O
the	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
the	O
Historical	O
and	O
most	O
Remarkable	O
Passages	O
therein	O
.	O
Maximum	O
in	O
Mixing	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
Mr	O
Jeremish	O
Rich	O
's	O
Pens	O
Dexterty	O
compleated	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
plainest	O
and	O
easiest	O
Method	O
of	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
are	O
added	O
,	O
line	O
er	O
of	O
the	O
Law	O
compleat	O
in	O
Characters	O
at	O
length	O
,	O
being	O
of	O
great	O
use	O
to	O
all	O
Lawyers	O
and	O
others	O
who	O
take	O
Tryals	O
at	O
large	O
in	O
Courts	O
.	O
Never	O
done	O
till	O
now	O
.	O
By	O
