TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
,	O
ON	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
being	O
the	O
15th,16th,17th	O
,	O
and	O
19th	O
of	O
January	O
1718	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Sixth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
EDWARD	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	B-pers
Bary	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Tracy	B-pers
Mr	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Ridby	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Depu	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
Names	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
Lur	O
Ch	O
Thicker	O
ddy	O
Withers	O
.	O
Bury	O
Dewhurst	O
.	O
Smith	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
Edward	O
Samuel	B-pers
Chases	I-pers
Diston	O
Richard	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
John	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Gouge	I-pers
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wootton	I-pers
John	B-pers
Isabbel	I-pers
John	B-pers
Marley	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Milter	I-pers
Abraham	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
John	B-pers
Moody	I-pers
of	O
Alhallows	B-place
Lombard-street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
Wastcoat	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pocket-Book	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Gibbons	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
going	O
to	O
Lodge	O
at	O
the	O
Cross	B-place
Keys	I-place
Inn	I-place
in	O
street	O
,	O
being	O
in	O
Bed	O
and	O
asleep	O
;	O
about	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
was	O
wakened	O
by	O
,	O
a	O
noise	O
of	O
his	O
Chamber	O
Door	O
on	O
the	O
inside	O
,	O
and	O
feeling	O
his	O
Clothes	O
found	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
calling	O
to	O
the	O
Servants	O
,	O
and	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
a	O
Pain	O
of	O
Glass	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Window	O
in	O
his	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
suspecting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
to	O
lodge	O
there	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
,	O
they	O
searched	O
his	O
Room	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Clothes	O
upon	O
some	O
Leads	O
put	O
out	O
at	O
back	O
Window	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Pocket-Book	O
hid	O
behind	O
the	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
remarkable	O
piece	O
of	O
old	O
Silver	O
belonging	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Pocket	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
confirmed	O
by	O
the	O
Servants	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Read	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Gibbons	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Motts	I-pers
.	O
;	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Orms	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
;	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
lodg	O
'd	O
some	O
small	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
House	O
,	O
took	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
founds	O
by	O
her	O
direction	O
.	O
The	O
fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Bush	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Clarkenwel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
divers	O
Carpenters	O
Tools	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
left	O
in	O
an	O
empty	O
House	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
stollen	O
were	O
found	O
;	O
the	O
Coat	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Tools	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
he	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
Man	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
Tools	O
and	O
had	O
bought	O
the	O
Coat	O
of	O
him	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Clarkenwel	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Camblet	O
Cloak	O
of	O
a	O
riding	O
Hood	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Baid	I-pers
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
;	O
it	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
the	O
Cloak	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
it	O
was	O
given	O
her	O
to	O
hold	O
by	O
another	O
Woman	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
Barrel	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Tittonser	I-pers
the	O
9th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
was	O
Twelve	O
Month	O
's	O
it	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Pistol	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
stollen	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
pawned	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
he	O
receiv	O
'd	O
it	O
from	O
one	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
pawned	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
not	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
stollen	O
.	O
His	O
defence	O
appearing	O
probable	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Whitaker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Gun-barrels	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
value	O
35	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Tittonser	I-pers
the	O
29th	O
of	O
Nov	O
.	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
not	O
Evidence	O
sufficient	O
to	O
affect	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cinnamon	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Mason	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
Back	I-place
Church	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
Chain	O
and	O
Seal	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
l.10	O
s.9	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
value	O
9	O
l.	O
s	O
2	O
Perriwigs	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Gold	O
Buddes	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Sword	O
value	O
5	O
l	O
and	O
16	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
December	O
;	O
This	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
appearingly	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
weak	O
and	O
helpless	O
Condition	O
's	O
as	O
if	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
walk	O
,	O
nor	O
help	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
a	O
Rug	O
hanging	O
over	O
his	O
Shoulders	O
,	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
Salivation	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Tongue	O
so	O
swelled	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
speak	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
arraigned	O
,	O
supported	O
himself	O
upon	O
,	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
a	O
considerable	O
time	O
would	O
not	O
by	O
any	O
means	O
plead	O
to	O
his	O
Indictment	O
the	O
threatned	O
with	O
the	O
Profs	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
Court	O
ordering	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
to	O
be	O
called	O
,	O
who	O
examining	O
his	O
Mouth	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
more	O
obstinacy	O
that	O
inability	O
,	O
which	O
when	O
deposed	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
presently	O
cured	O
of	O
his	O
dumbness	O
,	O
and	O
pleading	O
to	O
his	O
Indictment	O
took	O
his	O
Tryal	O
:	O
By	O
the	O
Evidence	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
opportunity	O
to	O
steal	O
Which	O
,	O
Money	O
&	O
c.	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Masters	O
Breeches	O
as	O
they	O
hung	O
upon	O
a	O
Chair	O
in	O
the	O
Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
with	O
him	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
search	O
after	O
him	O
was	O
taken	O
at	O
the	O
King	O
Georges	O
Head	O
Tavern	O
near	O
Temple	O
Bar	O
,	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
Gaming	O
,	O
where	O
being	O
apprehended	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Sword	O
wound	O
to	O
the	O
Constable	O
twice	O
,	O
one	O
Wound	O
going	O
quite	O
through	O
his	O
thigh	O
and	O
wounding	O
also	O
another	O
Person	O
that	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
apprehend	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
get	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
pursued	O
by	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
and	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
;	O
the	O
Watch	O
Buckles	O
,	O
Sword	O
&	O
c.	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
him	O
and	O
25	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
has	O
had	O
lent	O
his	O
Master	O
Mr.	O
Richard	O
Newman	O
60	O
l.	O
but	O
that	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
prove	O
so	O
great	O
an	O
improbability	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
for	O
robbing	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Burroughs	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Watch	O
value	O
40	O
s.4	O
Rings	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
s.6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
;	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
being	O
with	O
another	O
Person	O
in	O
a	O
Chaise	O
on	O
Hounsloe	B-place
Heath	I-place
,	O
between	O
and	O
6	O
a	O
Clock	O
the	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Person	O
,	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
presenting	O
a	O
Pistol	O
and	O
demanding	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
Rings	O
,	O
Watch	O
&	O
c.	O
threatened	O
to	O
shoot	O
them	O
through	O
the	O
Head	O
if	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
deliver	O
them	O
presently	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Rings	O
and	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Watch	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
positive	O
which	O
took	O
that	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
confirmed	O
by	O
the	O
other	O
Person	O
in	O
the	O
Chaise	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
positive	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
however	O
he	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
yet	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Hutton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
5	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Silver	O
and	O
Gold	O
Waste	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Will	B-pers
Basson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
He	O
was	O
Journeyman	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spinner	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
discovered	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Lodging	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Holyday	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
81.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wardman	I-pers
the	O
25th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
some	O
others	O
were	O
a	O
drinking	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
much	O
in	O
drink	O
they	O
refused	O
to	O
set	O
him	O
have	O
any	O
more	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
the	O
boy	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
bidding	O
him	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
setting	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
after	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
suspect	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
long	O
known	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
have	O
intrusted	O
him	O
with	O
10	O
times	O
the	O
value	O
;	O
still	O
some	O
small	O
time	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
heard	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Wife	O
was	O
making	O
great	O
Lamentation	O
her	O
Husband	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
by	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Tankard	O
and	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
Jonathan	O
Wild	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
forenoon	O
the	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
much	O
in	O
drink	O
,	O
brought	O
the	O
Tankard	O
to	O
,	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
Apron	O
to	O
pawn	O
or	O
sell	O
,	O
having	O
with	O
,	O
him	O
his	O
little	O
Boy	O
,	O
that	O
thereupon	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
whose	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
He	O
then	O
reply	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
no	O
Pawn-broker	O
,	O
why	O
did	O
he	O
bring	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
answered	O
he	O
was	O
directed	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
answered	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
worth	O
3	O
l.	O
He	O
then	O
reply	O
'd	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
provided	O
he	O
could	O
make	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Title	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
him	O
Satisfaction	O
that	O
his	O
Wife	O
should	O
not	O
come	O
and	O
break	O
his	O
Window	O
's	O
she	O
buying	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
buy	O
it	O
;	O
by	O
this	O
discourse	O
while	O
she	O
got	O
an	O
Officer	O
to	O
seize	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
had	O
it	O
given	O
him	O
by	O
2	O
Men	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
who	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
know	O
Jonathan	O
Wild	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
fetch	O
3	O
l.	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
same	O
token	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
him	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
be	O
with	O
him	O
again	O
at	O
3	O
a	O
Clock	O
.	O
But	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
prove	O
this	O
tho	O
'	O
indeed	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Person	O
who	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
for	O
Industry	O
and	O
Honesty	O
from	O
his	O
very	O
Childhood	O
the	O
perfect	O
time	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Aldermanbury	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Goodman	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
Sept	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
clean	O
the	O
Window	O
took	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
upon	O
search	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Trunk	O
.	O
The	O
fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Amy	B-pers
Furnace	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolph	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
were	O
indicted	O
privately	O
stealing	O
printed	O
Linnen	O
value	O
48	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
the	O
5th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
January	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Shop	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
buying	O
a	O
Shift	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
wanted	O
to	O
see	O
Linnen	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
perceived	O
one	O
slily	O
to	O
draw	O
away	O
the	O
Linnen	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
it	O
fall	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
conceal	O
of	O
The	O
fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
each	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Leppingworth	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Christ-church	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
part	O
of	O
Silver	O
Snuffers	O
Value	O
10s	O
.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
January	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Simon	B-pers
Jarvis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Allhallows	B-place
Bread-street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
wearing	O
Appeal	O
still	O
3	O
l.10	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Biggs	I-pers
the	O
30th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
pack	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
be	O
carried	O
to	O
a	O
Coach	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
carry	O
and	O
went	O
quite	O
off	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
him	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Welden	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Washer	I-pers
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
steal	O
his	O
Goods	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
January	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
a	O
being	O
a	O
Barber	O
at	O
Lincoln-Inn	O
did	O
use	O
to	O
shave	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
knowing	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
,	O
did	O
get	O
over	O
a	O
high	O
Wall	O
and	O
was	O
breaking	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
heard	O
by	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
some	O
contigous	O
Chambers	O
she	O
fired	O
a	O
Pistol	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
which	O
would	O
ed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Leg	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
wound	O
he	O
being	O
rendered	O
uncapable	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
escape	O
was	O
apprehended	O
:	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
Proof	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
any	O
Entry	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Francis	B-pers
Retthor	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High	O
way	O
and	O
king	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
value	O
8	O
l.10	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
about	O
2	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
the	O
day	O
aforesaid	O
was	O
set	O
upon	O
by	O
Men	O
on	O
Horseback	O
,	O
in	O
Monmouth-Street	B-place
,	O
who	O
presenting	O
at	O
Pistol	O
demanded	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
afterwards	O
it	O
being	O
carried	O
to	O
a	O
Watch-maker	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
he	O
received	O
Intelligence	O
,	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
robbed	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
September	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
one	O
Edward	B-pers
Baily	I-pers
,	O
he	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
pawn	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
so	O
for	O
6	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
order	O
of	O
Edward	O
Baily	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
mended	O
:	O
having	O
lent	O
Edward	O
Baily	O
Guinea	O
more	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
that	O
appeared	O
favourable	O
on	O
his	O
Side	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Hackney	B-place
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Lamb	I-pers
and	O
stealing	O
divers	O
rich	O
Furniture	O
,	O
Plate	O
&	O
c.	O
to	O
a	O
very	O
considerable	O
value	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
was	O
broken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
Stollen	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Plate	O
was	O
carried	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
sold	O
for	O
13	O
l.	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Areber	O
,	O
Goldsmith	O
;	O
who	O
having	O
notice	O
given	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
stopped	O
them	O
with	O
another	O
parcel	O
of	O
Plate	O
the	O
next	O
day.-	O
pleaded	O
she	O
had	O
received	O
the	O
Plate	O
to	O
sell	O
form	O
one	O
Esther	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
and	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
its	O
stollen	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
sent	O
and	O
Endeavoured	O
to	O
apprehend	O
this	O
Watson	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
absconded	O
.	O
Several	O
Persons	O
appeared	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
thereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
Mother	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
Daughter	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Hanwell	B-place
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
House	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bransgrove	I-pers
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
20	O
of	O
Burdet	O
value	O
tax	O
50	O
s.	O
a	O
Gold	O
R	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Alice	B-pers
Bransgrove	I-pers
the	O
7th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Bransgrove	I-pers
deposed	O
and	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
and	O
invited	O
her	O
abd	O
being	O
House	O
saying	O
she	O
must	O
go	O
to	O
such	O
staid	O
about	O
stay	O
while	O
she	O
came	O
this	O
made	O
another	O
found	O
her	O
House	O
broken	O
gone	O
other	O
evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
Parisoner	O
she	O
dogg	O
'd	O
next	O
Day	O
from	O
Brantsfordto	O
Monmouth-street	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
offering	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
Mary	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
evidence	O
against	O
Senior	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
of	O
Chiswick	B-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assualting	O
upon	O
the	O
Highway	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
Value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
Guinea	O
the	O
,	O
of	O
Dream	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
day	O
Sunday	O
,	O
he	O
beoing	O
at	O
Friends	O
House	O
as	O
had	O
dressed	O
himself	O
with	O
a	O
design	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
about	O
a	O
Clock	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
but	O
dinner	O
toward	O
Strand	O
on	O
the	O
Grain	O
near	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Scory	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
saw	O
so	O
habited	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
for	O
Gentlemans	O
on	O
a	O
Strawberry	O
colour	O
'd	O
horse	O
,	O
very	O
able	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Holster	O
Saddle	O
and	O
2	O
Pistols	O
,	O
that	O
dirty	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
into	O
a	O
foot	O
path	O
in	O
and	O
having	O
gone	O
over	O
2	O
Fields	O
come	O
out	O
in	O
where	O
he	O
there	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
who	O
mending	O
his	O
stirr	O
up	O
;	O
that	O
having	O
,	O
gone	O
a	O
before	O
him	O
he	O
heard	O
him	O
coming	O
,	O
after	O
him	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
by	O
the	O
found	O
he	O
took	O
enquiry	O
to	O
Strand	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
halted	O
to	O
inform	O
him	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
the	O
drew	O
a	O
pistol	O
and	O
cock	O
and	O
presenting	O
it	O
bid	O
him	O
deliver	O
;	O
He	O
not	O
think	O
in	O
earnest	O
or	O
could	O
be	O
so	O
impudent	O
at	O
time	O
a	O
Day	O
and	O
in	O
that	O
place	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
be	O
was	O
but	O
and	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
man	O
.	O
and	O
so	O
expostulating	O
with	O
him	O
as	O
tho	O
'	O
in	O
jest	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
answered	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
:	O
D	O
-	O
i	O
-	O
m	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
deliver	O
your	O
Money	O
&	O
c.	O
or	O
I	O
'll	O
the	O
Head	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
seeing	O
no	O
on	O
to	O
his	O
assistance	O
,	O
he	O
pretending	O
to	O
feel	O
.	O
privately	O
,	O
put	O
the	O
Chain	O
and	O
Seal	O
into	O
his	O
Breeches	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
not	O
see	O
:	O
demanded	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
which	O
he	O
threatned	O
shoot	O
him	O
.	O
If	O
he	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
will	O
you	O
shoot	O
me	O
because	O
of	O
Which	O
?	O
so	O
putting	O
the	O
contrary	O
hand	O
to	O
his	O
pulled	O
out	O
the	O
purse	O
,	O
and	O
Guinea	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
,	O
and	O
rode	O
off	O
,	O
he	O
by	O
that	O
means	O
sav	O
'd	O
and	O
other	O
valuables	O
he	O
had	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
he	O
offering	O
a	O
reward	O
of	O
five	O
Guineas	O
had	O
word	O
,	O
brought	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Evidences	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Pistols	O
did	O
hire	O
the	O
such	O
a	O
Saddle	O
of	O
them	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
to	O
Stains	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
very	O
dirty	O
saying	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
behind	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
mad	O
for	O
his	O
Hire	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
both	O
to	O
Man	O
and	O
Horse	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
not	O
to	O
make	O
an	O
answerable	O
defence	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
32	O
Guineas	O
a	O
half	O
Guinea	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Moidores	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
,	O
of	O
Lyon	B-pers
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Guillam	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
Instant	O
January	O
,	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
Prosecutor	O
went	O
and	O
lodged	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Guillam	O
House	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
lodged	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
,	O
that	O
lying	O
both	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Bed	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
Money	O
into	O
his	O
Breeches	O
laying	O
them	O
under	O
his	O
Pillow	O
and	O
Bol	O
under	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
so	O
secure	O
as	O
he	O
thought	O
they	O
could	O
taken	O
thence	O
with	O
it	O
about	O
3	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
being	O
awaked	O
by	O
the	O
unlocking	O
Chamber	O
Door	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
surprized	O
felt	O
for	O
his	O
Breeches	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
Pillow	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
his	O
Bedfellow	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
his	O
Landlord	O
,	O
enquiring	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
was	O
told	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
pretending	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
so	O
early	O
to	O
help	O
a	O
certain	O
Person	O
to	O
work	O
,	O
that	O
upon	O
this	O
he	O
put	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
News	O
offering	O
5	O
Guineas	O
as	O
a	O
Reward	O
;	O
and	O
by	O
that	O
means	O
heard	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
also	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
his	O
Landlord	O
that	O
he	O
brought	O
but	O
3	O
s.6	O
d.	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
first	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
being	O
gone	O
she	O
supported	O
:	O
him	O
with	O
victuals	O
,	O
designing	O
to	O
help-him	O
to	O
a	O
place	O
of	O
Labouring	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
so	O
poot-that	O
he	O
have	O
had	O
penny	O
;	O
to	O
have	O
his	O
beard	O
shaved	O
.	O
Thomas	O
kancliff	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
(	O
a	O
Stranger	O
to	O
him	O
)	O
calling	O
for	O
Drink	O
and	O
seeing	O
his	O
watch	O
offered	O
him	O
4	O
Guineas	O
for	O
it	O
but	O
he	O
not	O
caring	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
carried-him	O
to	O
his	O
Watchmakers	O
,	O
where	O
be	O
bought	O
one	O
for	O
4	O
l.8	O
s.	O
be	O
like	O
wise	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
assist	O
him	O
in	O
buying	O
suit	O
of	O
Clothes	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
had	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
and	O
who	O
very	O
full	O
of	O
Money	O
and	O
had	O
25	O
Guineas	O
lost	O
at	O
this	O
apprehension	O
.	O
He	O
having	O
nothing	O
material	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
and	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stanwell	B-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
9	O
Yards	O
of	O
China	O
Stuff	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s	O
:	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
North	I-pers
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
as	O
12	O
Months	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
sent	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
Waggon	O
to	O
be	O
carryed	O
to	O
Basingstoke	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
took	O
Passage	O
in	O
the	O
Waggon	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
being	O
there	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
cut	O
a	O
Pack	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
sewed	O
it	O
up	O
again	O
and	O
being	O
come	O
near	B-place
Stains	I-place
got	O
out	O
,	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
walk	O
to	O
call	O
:	O
on	O
somebody	O
at	O
Eggham	O
and	O
would	O
there	O
be	O
taken	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
quite	O
away	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Jackson	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
cut	O
the	O
Pack	O
,	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
sewed	O
it	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
travelled	O
all	O
night	O
long	O
,	O
up	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
piece	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sunk	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
pawned	O
for	O
three	O
Pound	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
however	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Matth.ew	B-pers
Whitten	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
of	O
6	O
pieces	O
of	O
Ghenting	O
Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
pieces	O
of	O
Linnen	O
.	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
jump	O
off	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
stall	O
with	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Linnen	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
dropp	O
'd	O
the	O
Linnen	O
and	O
he	O
crying	O
out	O
stop	O
Thief	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
however	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Reynods	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
goods	O
value	O
29	O
s	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Cornwallis	I-pers
,	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
found	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
reposited	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
they	O
were	O
given	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Daughter	O
,	O
and	O
produced	O
evidences	O
to	O
confirm	O
it	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Norton	B-place
Falgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Callico	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Leatherhead	I-pers
the	O
13	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Masters	O
House	O
had	O
been	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Goods	O
stollen	O
April	O
,	O
last	O
was	O
12	O
Months	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Gown	O
among	O
the	O
rest	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Shop	O
to	O
buy	O
Goods	O
with	O
the	O
Gown	O
on	O
her	O
back	O
which	O
she	O
knowing	O
challenged	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
she	O
,	O
bought	O
the	O
Gown	O
at	O
a	O
Brokers	O
in	O
Halbourn	O
several	O
appearing	O
to	O
her	O
reputation	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Biggs	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
the	O
17th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
:	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Wigg	O
was	O
delivered	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
Boy	O
that	O
he	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Barben	O
had	O
several	O
others	O
sent	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Boy	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
several	O
times	O
put	O
him	O
upon	O
the	O
project	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Wigg	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
having	O
received	O
,	O
the	O
Wigg	O
ask	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
into	O
fetch	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Wigg	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Box	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
instructed	O
him	O
to	O
tell	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Servant	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
put	O
a	O
trick	O
upon	O
him	O
in	O
giving	O
him	O
the	O
Box	O
Guinea	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
so	O
many	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
that	O
gave	O
her	O
such	O
a	O
Character	O
as	O
induced	O
the	O
Jury	O
to	O
aquit	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
surprizing	O
so	O
little	O
a	O
Villian	O
should	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
forge	O
such	O
a	O
Caluinay	O
against	O
an	O
innocent	O
Woman	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
scarlet	O
Coach	O
Seats	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Gilbert	B-pers
Sheldon	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
January	O
;	O
it	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Coach	O
was	O
going	O
slowly	O
into	O
little	B-place
Ormond-yard	I-place
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
were	O
seen	O
about	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
one	O
on	O
the	O
one	O
side	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
Person	O
threw	O
out	O
the	O
Seats	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
who	O
told	O
them	O
up	O
and	O
was	O
running	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
feen	O
was	O
pursued	O
and	O
taken	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
fact	O
;	O
and	O
pleaded	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Ticket	O
Porter	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
only	O
shew	O
'd	O
his	O
Ticket	O
in	O
Court	O
but	O
brought	O
one	O
who	O
also	O
confirmed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
ply	O
'd	O
in	O
Fish-street	O
,	O
but	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
said	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
greatest	O
stealing	O
of	O
Coach	O
Seats	O
in	O
England	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
quest	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
a	O
full	O
Month	O
on	O
that	O
account	O
the	O
fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Buckley	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Connor	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
value	O
18	O
s	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Gundy	I-pers
,	O
the	O
2nd	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
January	O
.	O
They	O
Prosecutors	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
.	O
under	O
presence	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Ring	O
and	O
that	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
weighing	O
a	O
Ring	O
Conney	O
took	O
a	O
Ring	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Box	O
and	O
laid	O
down	O
a	O
brass	O
Ring	O
in	O
the	O
place	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
scale	O
with	O
the	O
priced	O
of	O
the	O
Ring	O
he	O
weigh	O
'd	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
but	O
he	O
immediately	O
perceiving	O
the	O
Cheat	O
stept	O
after	O
them	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
back	O
where	O
Conner	O
fell	O
a	O
Grughing	O
and	O
the	O
Ring	O
fell	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Mouth	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
;	O
the	O
fact	O
being	O
plain	O
against	O
Connor	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
not	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
that	O
Buckley	O
was	O
privy	O
to	O
the	O
fact	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Tho	B-pers
Goodram	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Dickson	I-pers
and	O
Katherine	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
the	O
2	O
former	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
9	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
latter	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
Tankard	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stollen	O
.	O
This	O
Prosecution	O
deposed	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
and	O
the	O
Plate	O
stollen	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
suspected	O
Garden	O
because	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
was	O
that	O
Night	O
absent	O
from	O
his	O
Master	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
having	O
found	O
him	O
he	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
and	O
that	O
Dickson	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
Johnathan	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
hearing	O
that	O
KatherineBrown	O
was	O
apprehended	O
for	O
receiving	O
stollen	O
Goods	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
confessed	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
discover	O
several	O
Robbers	O
,	O
and	O
directed	O
him	O
to	O
find	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
that	O
going	O
to	O
Dickson	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
Goodram	O
was	O
a	O
filly	O
Dog	O
to	O
confess	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
got	O
40	O
Spankers	O
;	O
that	O
Katherine	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
owned	O
she	O
knew	O
the	O
Plate	O
to	O
be	O
stollen	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
carry	O
the	O
Tankard	O
to	O
Esther	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
that	O
she	O
gave	O
her	O
8	O
l.15	O
s.	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
three	O
Pound	O
and	O
kept	O
the	O
rest	O
her	O
self	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
all	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
Transporation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gulliford	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Bennet	I-place
Panls	I-place
wharf	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Sticks	O
of	O
Timber	O
value	O
35	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mesheures	O
Bugby	B-pers
and	O
Atkinson	B-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
December	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Vane	I-pers
and	I-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
his	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	O
his	O
Wife	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Guineas	O
a	O
Ring	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
things	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
the	O
24th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
left	O
her	O
Trunk	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
came	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
them	O
the	O
Trunk	O
was	O
indeeed	O
lock	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
then	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
several	O
appearing	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
the	O
1st	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
January	O
,	O
The	O
Evidences	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
driving	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
Deceased	O
and	O
John	O
S	O
his	O
Mate	O
driving	O
a	O
Dray	O
in	O
Chancery-Lane	B-place
behind	O
Whitell	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
in	O
Deceased	O
against	O
the	O
fore	O
Plank	O
of	O
the	O
Dray	O
with	O
that	O
Violence	O
that	O
he	O
died	O
presently	O
after	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
produced	O
several	O
Evidence	O
that	O
he	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
prevent	O
it	O
by	O
giving	O
all	O
the	O
way	O
he	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
done	O
carelesly	O
on	O
his	O
part	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
of	O
St	B-place
Peters	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Calves	O
Skins	O
Value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
d.	O
of	O
several	O
Persons	O
.	O
the	O
5	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Skins	O
were	O
stollen	O
out	O
of	O
Leaden-hill	B-place
market	I-place
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Hony-lane-market	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Abraham	B-pers
Darison	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Butolph	I-place
Bishopgate	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
10	O
Galons	O
of	O
Strong	O
Beer	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
and	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
May	I-pers
the	O
10th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
was	O
12	O
Months	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Hakshaw	O
and	O
the	O
Evidences	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
were	O
fellow	O
several	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Drink	O
was	O
stollen	O
and	O
sold	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
but	O
the	O
proof	O
depending	O
intirely	O
upon	O
the	O
Evidences	O
of	O
the	O
Accompliced	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gibbons	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
York	I-pers
and	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
value	O
45	O
s.	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broken	O
open	O
and	O
the	O
goods	O
stollen	O
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
himself	O
did	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
a	O
like	O
Crime	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
for	O
Transportation	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
felonly	O
only	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
of	O
Alhallows	B-place
in	O
the	O
wall	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
value	O
39	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kesles	I-pers
the	O
24th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Packer	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Pecket	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Prior	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Vickers	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pancras	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assualting	O
George	B-pers
Noyer	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Pistols	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Holster-Cloth	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Spurs	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Gelding	O
val.30	O
l.	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
Sept	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Floyer	O
deposed	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
comming	O
from	O
Hamstead	B-place
about	O
7	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
before	O
3	O
Men	O
shook	O
a	O
Man	O
off	O
of	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
upon	O
he	O
pulled	O
the	O
Pistol	O
and	O
made	O
towards	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
made	O
toward	O
him	O
still	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Horse	O
Bridle	O
and	O
pulled	O
his	O
Pistol	O
to	O
the	O
Ground	O
that	O
he	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
discharge	O
his	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Pan	O
,	O
thereupon	O
he	O
struck	O
Prime	O
his	O
Pistol	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
on	O
his	O
hind	O
Legs	O
got	O
him	O
off	O
;	O
but	O
He	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
off	O
his	O
Horse	O
by	O
a	O
Quarter	O
Staff	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
himself	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
whereupon	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
you	O
surrender	O
or	O
I	O
'll	O
shoot	O
you	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Head	O
he	O
gave	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
a	O
Prick	O
or	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Belley	O
;	O
but	O
sayin	O
himself	O
overpowered	O
,	O
no	O
made	O
his	O
Escape	O
to	O
all	O
those	O
not	O
far	O
off	O
,	O
where	O
was	O
in	O
Old	O
Man	O
and	O
a	O
Boy	O
,	O
and	O
acquainted	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
his	O
Horse	O
;	O
and	O
another	O
got	O
upon	O
the	O
other	O
Man	O
Horse	O
;	O
the	O
old	O
Man	O
and	O
Boy	O
took	O
Pitch	O
Forks	O
came	O
out	O
and	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
had	O
mounted	O
his	O
Horse	O
rode	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
fired	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
took	O
off	O
the	O
Point	O
of	O
his	O
Sword	O
and	O
the	O
Bullet	O
flew	O
over	O
the	O
but	O
was	O
so	O
near	O
him	O
that	O
the	O
Force	O
of	O
the	O
Power	O
him	O
down	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
burnt	O
he	O
was	O
forc	O
'd	O
Surgeon	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
possible	O
to	O
out	O
the	O
Power	O
and	O
dress	O
him	O
.	O
But	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
positively	O
to	O
and	O
of	O
their	O
Faces	O
Mr.	O
Floyer	O
produced	O
his	O
Pistols	O
in	O
Court	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
among	O
the	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
apprehended	O
at	O
the	O
one	O
.	O
The	O
Tavern	O
Price	O
upon	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
struck	O
him	O
over	O
the	O
Head	O
they	O
them	O
you	O
I	O
you	O
to	O
and	O
knock	O
now	O
then	O
they	O
roobb	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
himself	O
came	O
up	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.Floyer	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Blow	O
another	O
of	O
and	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
his	O
Breast	O
;	O
that	O
Prior	O
got	O
upon	O
Mr.	O
Floyer	O
's	O
Horse	O
and	O
rode	O
after	O
Mr.	O
Floyer	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
hav	O
like	O
him	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
Pistol	O
go	O
off	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
afterwards	O
the	O
Turn	O
Pike	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
several	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
not	O
take	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
Mr.	O
Floyers	O
Horse	O
and	O
Pistol	O
Cloth	O
in	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
and	O
hollowing	O
to	O
he	O
answering	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	O
A	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
indeed	O
was	O
not	O
with	O
them	O
in	O
this	O
but	O
that	O
Vickars	O
and	O
Prior	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
Gentleman	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
and	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Gentleman	O
Broke	O
Parquort	O
's	O
Head	O
and	O
cut	O
him	O
over	O
with	O
his	O
Pistol	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Prior	O
mounted	O
his	O
signing	O
to	O
stop	O
him	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
the	O
House	O
near	O
Fig.-Lane	O
.	O
The	O
fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
all	O
guilty	O
.	O
were	O
all	O
Three	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Strange	B-pers
upon	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Purse	O
value	O
6	O
d.14	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half,8	O
l.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
August	O
Strange	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Hackney	B-place
Farington-lane	I-place
near	O
Hornsey,3	O
Men	O
came	O
armed	O
with	O
Guns	O
,	O
Pistols	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Swearing	O
and	O
very	O
violent	O
manner	O
,	O
and	O
Parquort	O
held	O
a	O
Vickers	O
took	O
his	O
Money	O
and	O
the	O
also	O
his	O
Buckles	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shoes	O
,	O
on	O
his	O
Finger	O
demanded	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
off	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
Prior	O
said	O
I	O
'll	O
have	O
it	O
off	O
or	O
I	O
'll	O
cut	O
off	O
your	O
Finger	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Prior	O
in	O
the	O
he	O
owned	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
lost	O
was	O
in	O
pawn	O
by	O
him	O
which	O
he	O
Thomas	O
confirmed	O
what	O
Mr	O
.	O
Spin	O
also	O
several	O
other	O
Circumstances	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
were	O
all	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
face	O
(	O
as	O
he	O
hears	O
)	O
gone	O
to	O
Sea.The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
found	O
Indictment	O
like	O
wise	O
.	O
Vickers	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Squire	B-pers
on	O
the	O
High-Way	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Watch	O
value	O
6	O
l.2	O
Seals	O
,	O
a	O
Chain	O
Lanser-Cafe	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Mr.	O
Squire	O
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
Lord	O
Sunderland	O
to	O
the	O
Lord	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
November	O
before	O
5	O
a	O
Clock	O
the	O
one	O
thro	O
'	O
theTurn	O
Pike	O
the	O
upon	O
by	O
3	O
Men	O
on	O
Foot	O
,	O
Pistols	O
under	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
Messenger	O
and	O
was	O
upon	O
his	O
bass	O
;	O
but	O
instead	O
of	O
that	O
shoot	O
him	O
dead	O
;	O
and	O
mak	O
carried	O
into	O
a	O
Field	O
;	O
and	O
hid	O
but	O
his	O
Letter	O
,	O
pulled	O
off	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
several	O
times	O
for	O
killing	O
him	O
but	O
neither	O
to	O
kill	O
him	O
not	O
rob	O
him	O
Messenger	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
exposed	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
he	O
might	O
do	O
them	O
they	O
still	O
snatching	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
opening	O
his	O
him	O
if	O
they	O
durst	O
but	O
tho	O
'	O
they	O
still	O
He	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
Vickers	O
by	O
his	O
Voice	O
,	O
he	O
in	O
Court	O
which	O
were	O
ta	O
in	O
a	O
Trunk	O
and	O
Portmanteau	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
full	O
Blunderbusses	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
and	O
Prior	O
gave	O
his	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Vickers	O
had	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
Watch	O
.	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
horp	O
.	O
The	O
Facts	O
being	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
round	O
guilty	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
Willoughby	B-pers
Strickland	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
harbouring	O
the	O
Persons	O
aforesaid	O
and	O
recieved	O
afore	O
mentioned	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
By	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Squires	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
gave	O
him	O
an	O
account	O
that	O
served	O
Gold	O
which	O
he	O
lost	O
,	O
naming	O
them	O
,	O
were	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
the	O
Proof	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
con	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Coleburn	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Snuff-Box	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Witeron	I-pers
Esq	O
.	O
the	O
26	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
having	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Coach	O
near	B-place
the	I-place
King	I-place
's	I-place
Bagnio	I-place
,	O
he	O
going	O
along	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Crowd	O
of	O
People	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
perceived	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
a	O
Man	O
to	O
Jostle	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
followed	O
her	O
and	O
struck	O
her	O
with	O
his	O
Cane	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
turned	O
to	O
strike	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Box	O
dropped	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Bosom	O
and	O
fell	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
and	O
broke	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
thereupon	O
repeated	O
his	O
Blows	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Fellows	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
infused	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
Murther	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Mob	O
arose	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Constable	O
being	O
sent	O
for	O
they	O
were	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
she	O
having	O
been	O
abroad	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
struck	O
her	O
and	O
abused	O
her	O
at	O
a	O
very	O
greatrate	O
without	O
any	O
manner	O
of	O
Provocations	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
then	O
Charge	O
her	O
with	O
having	O
taken	O
any	O
thing	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
nor	O
till	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
charged	O
a	O
Constable	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
abusing	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
for	O
this	O
she	O
called	O
several	O
Evidences	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Evidence	O
was	O
one	O
who	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Sweet-Heart	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
having	O
been	O
abroad	O
that	O
Day	O
were	O
going	O
home	O
about	O
10	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
a	O
Riding-Hood	O
on	O
;	O
and	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Arm	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
rained	O
pretty	O
fast	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Bagnio	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
struck	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
why	O
he	O
struck	O
the	O
Woman	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
struck	O
her	O
several	O
other	O
Blows	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
took	O
away	O
his	O
Cane	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
Walter	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Bagnio	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
retiring	O
into	O
the	O
Bagnio	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
to	O
apprehend	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sitting	O
on	O
the	O
out	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
at	O
liberty	O
to	O
have	O
gone	O
where	O
she	O
would	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
on	O
the	O
Inn	O
side	O
and	O
the	O
door	O
shut	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
going	O
in	O
and	O
Charging	O
the	O
Constable	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
he	O
attempted	O
to	O
strike	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
the	O
Constable	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
lay	O
anything	O
to	O
her	O
Charge	O
,	O
till	O
after	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
Round-Houses	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
several	O
Evidences	O
,	O
some	O
as	O
to	O
one	O
Circumstance	O
and	O
some	O
to	O
another	O
.	O
Another	O
evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
w	O
as	O
at	O
the	O
Round-House	O
,	O
sitting	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
much	O
in	O
drink	O
,	O
let	O
it	O
fall	O
upon	O
the	O
Fonder	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
broke	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
himself	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
pieces	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
produced	O
her	O
Mistress	O
and	O
several	O
Persons	O
of	O
Reputation	O
and	O
Fashion	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
an	O
extraordinary	O
Character	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Floyd	I-pers
of	O
St	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Quine	I-pers
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Linne	I-pers
of	O
St	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Julias	B-pers
Bagley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Plate	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
40	O
l.	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
July	O
1717	O
.	O
Williams	O
Matthews	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
with	O
himself	O
,	O
one	O
David	O
and	O
one	O
Alsey	O
,	O
not	O
taken	O
did	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
the	O
Plate	O
for	O
30	O
l.	O
to	O
one	O
Harding	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Williams	O
Ward	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
10	O
l.	O
Tea	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
April	O
1717	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Mathews	I-pers
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
himself	O
did	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
likewise	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Cane	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
8	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Padwick	I-pers
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
she	O
pickt	O
her	O
Pocket	O
as	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
Market	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Periwig	O
value	O
29s	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
;	O
but	O
no	O
body	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Vincent	B-pers
Strange	I-pers
and	O
Stene	B-pers
Theberton	I-pers
of	O
Fulham	B-place
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twelve	O
pound	O
of	O
Pork	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
How	I-pers
the	O
15	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Wiseman	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Frances	B-pers
Parkinson	I-pers
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
3	O
l.10	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
and	O
pulled	O
off	O
her	O
pocket	O
,	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White	I-place
Chappel	I-place
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Rowley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
2	O
Ducks	O
and	O
a	O
Drake,2	O
Aprons	O
&	O
c.	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
in	O
stealing	O
a	O
Copper	O
value	O
30	O
l.	O
fixt	O
to	O
the	O
Free-Hold	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
Rowley	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
Indictment	O
being	O
proved	O
by	O
their	O
own	O
Confession	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dampney	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
in	O
Counterfeiting	O
the	O
Currant	O
Coyn	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
Robert	B-pers
Foot	I-pers
,	O
convicted	O
in	O
September	O
last	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Offence	O
,	O
(	O
but	O
who	O
afterwards	O
died	O
in	O
Newgate	O
)	O
being	O
apprehended	O
in	O
putting	O
off	O
a	O
counterfeit	O
Guinea	O
,	O
did	O
confess	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
made	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
himself	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
Searching	O
Robert	B-pers
Font	I-pers
's	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
there	O
found	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Flasks	O
,	O
and	O
Crucibles	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
three	O
Crown	O
pieces	O
and	O
11	O
half	O
Crown	O
pieces	O
which	O
were	O
counterfeit	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
being	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
a	O
counterfeit	O
Crown	O
Piece	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
examined	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
board	O
own	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
Coyn	O
that	O
Guinea	O
Foot	O
was	O
apprehended	O
in	O
putting	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
other	O
;	O
and	O
also	O
about	O
15	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
which	O
confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
in	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
Suspicion	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
strengthned	O
,	O
in	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
deposed	O
that	O
upon	O
the	O
said	O
Guinea	O
's	O
being	O
show	O
'd	O
him	O
he	O
pretended	O
to	O
affirm	O
there	O
was	O
in	O
that	O
Guinea	O
Gold	O
to	O
the	O
Quantity	O
of	O
9	O
or	O
12	O
s.	O
To	O
these	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
answered	O
that	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
being	O
in	O
Robert	O
Foot	O
's	O
Lodging	O
it	O
was	O
because	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
;	O
that	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Flasks	O
,	O
Crucibles.	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
there	O
found	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
by	O
Trade	O
a	O
Silver	O
Smith	O
;	O
that	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Counterfeit	O
Money	O
there	O
found	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
owning	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
pleaded	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Drink	O
and	O
under	O
Terrour	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Crown	O
piece	O
taken	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Piece	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
several	O
Months	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
given	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
kept	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
Pocket-Piece	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
some	O
Persons	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
He	O
called	O
also	O
divers	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews-Holbourn	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
receiving	O
200	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Malt	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Sweetapple	I-pers
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stollen	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
to	O
be	O
Sweepings	O
and	O
not	O
Malt	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
deemed	O
a	O
Perquisite	O
of	O
the	O
Millers	O
and	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
stollen	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
a	O
fair	O
Character	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Humphreys	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Freeman	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Faiths	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
17	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Barron	I-pers
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
his	O
Wife	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Council	O
opened	O
the	O
Cause	O
,	O
setting	O
forth	O
that	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Stevens	O
coming	O
to	O
lodge	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
reporting	O
frequently	O
,	O
let	O
himself	O
into	O
the	O
Acquaintance	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Barron	O
,	O
who	O
by	O
the	O
persuasion	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Mrs.	O
Stevens	O
was	O
prevailed	O
upon	O
to	O
lend	O
him	O
3	O
l.	O
or	O
thereabouts	O
,	O
unknown	O
to	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
the	O
Payment	O
of	O
which	O
He	O
,	O
having	O
deferred	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
she	O
grew	O
uneasie	O
for	O
fear	O
her	O
Husband	O
should	O
call	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
did	O
frequently	O
dun	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
who	O
at	O
last	O
told	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
meet	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	B-place
Cock	I-place
in	I-place
Amen	I-place
Corner	I-place
he	O
would	O
pay	O
her	O
the	O
3	O
l.	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
goes	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
meeting	O
her	O
there	O
,	O
would	O
treat	O
her	O
with	O
a	O
Pot	O
or	O
two	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
during	O
which	O
time	O
,	O
she	O
putting	O
her	O
Hand	O
into	O
her	O
Pocket	O
to	O
pull	O
out	O
her	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
pulled	O
out	O
along	O
with	O
it	O
a	O
Purse	O
and	O
17	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
which	O
her	O
Husband	O
(	O
being	O
a	O
Dealer	O
in	O
Cattle	O
)	O
had	O
,	O
left	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
at	O
which	O
she	O
being	O
surprized	O
,	O
thinking	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
it	O
at	O
Home	O
,	O
was	O
desirous	O
to	O
go	O
Home	O
and	O
carry	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
put	O
it	O
again	O
into	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
put	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
she	O
grew	O
uneasie	O
several	O
times	O
demanding	O
her	O
Money	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
amused	O
her	O
,	O
telling	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
easie	O
,	O
ho	O
hoped	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
he	O
designed	O
to	O
keep	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
at	O
length	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
3	O
l.	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
should	O
go	O
Home	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
in	O
Fish-Street	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
there	O
give	O
her	O
her	O
Money	O
again	O
and	O
pay	O
the	O
3	O
l.	O
also	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
consenting	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
carrying	O
her	O
into	O
a	O
private	O
Room	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
all	O
the	O
Persons	O
in	O
that	O
House	O
were	O
his	O
Friends	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
if	O
she	O
called	O
out	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
worse	O
for	O
her	O
and	O
afterwards	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
Rope	O
,	O
telling	O
her	O
that	O
if	O
she	O
discovered	O
what	O
had	O
past	O
between	O
them	O
that	O
should	O
be	O
her	O
Fate	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
under	O
great	O
Terror	O
did	O
not	O
dare	O
to	O
call	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
kept	O
there	O
confin	O
'd	O
for	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Days	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
carried	O
her	O
abroad	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
to	O
Fleet	O
Ditch	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
sending	O
for	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
who	O
brought	O
a	O
Book	O
pretending	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Parson	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
another	O
Man	O
as	O
a	O
Clerk	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
must	O
marry	O
him	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
why	O
you	O
know	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
Husband	O
already	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
no	O
matter	O
for	O
that	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
that	O
should	O
be	O
her	O
Fare	O
shewing	O
her	O
the	O
Rope	O
:	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
under	O
a	O
great	O
Fright	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
Words	O
repeated	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
carry	O
's	O
her	O
back	O
to	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
be	O
married	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
kept	O
her	O
two	O
Days	O
,	O
The	O
Court	O
having	O
heard	O
the	O
Cause	O
,	O
thus	O
far	O
opened	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
fit	O
to	O
proceed	O
any	O
further	O
on	O
the	O
Tryal	O
so	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Sheldon	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Myres	I-pers
of	O
St	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
and	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
and	O
Chain	O
val.13	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
the	O
12th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Latter	O
for	O
receiving	O
it	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stollen	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
Edward	O
Sheldon	O
being	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
stole	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
found	O
,	O
him	O
,	O
upon	O
examination	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
pawn	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
a	O
Reckoning	O
he	O
had	O
run	O
on	O
Score	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
thereupon	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisners	O
House	O
and	O
demanded	O
the	O
Watch	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
refused	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
it	O
unless	O
he	O
paid	O
him	O
10	O
l.	O
This	O
was	O
also	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
another	O
Evidence	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
that	O
Edward	O
Sheldon	O
having	O
been	O
formerly	O
his	O
Fooy	O
came	O
to	O
drink	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
wanting	O
Money	O
to	O
pay	O
his	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
he	O
lent	O
him	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
20	O
s.	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
deny	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
demanded	O
10	O
l.	O
for	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
alledged	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Sheldon	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
Watch	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
divers	O
Persons	O
of	O
Credit	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
an	O
extraordinary	O
Character	O
.	O
Edward	O
Sheldon	O
pleaded	O
that	O
he	O
put	O
the	O
Watch	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
his	O
Malter	O
being	O
from	O
Home	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
it	O
might	O
have	O
some	O
harm	O
come	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
out	O
fell	O
into	O
Company	O
and	O
getting	O
in	O
Liquor	O
did	O
pawn	O
the	O
Watch	O
;	O
but	O
did	O
intend	O
to	O
restore	O
it	O
again	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
;	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
they	O
,	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Gent	O
.	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Loxton	I-pers
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
Mortal	O
wound	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
side	O
of	O
his	O
Body	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
first	O
and	O
second	O
Rib	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
breath	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
12	O
Inches	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
immediately	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
on	O
the	O
Coroners	O
.	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
a	O
3d	O
time	O
on	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
Stabbing	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Baberton	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Vernassel	I-pers
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Seeds	O
well	O
's	O
House	O
at	O
the	B-place
Bagnio	I-place
in	I-place
Silver-Street	I-place
together	O
with	O
a	O
Woman	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
bringing	O
with	O
him	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Champain	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Samuel	O
Loxton	O
the	O
deceased	O
waited	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
and	O
lay	O
still	O
about	O
2	O
a	O
Clock	O
and	O
then	O
knocking	O
,	O
the	O
deceased	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
coming	O
down	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
demanded	O
a	O
Bath	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
then	O
Cupping	O
a	O
great	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
almost	O
done	O
and	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
one	O
gotten	O
ready	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
possible	O
,	O
that	O
Loxton	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
Damned	O
him	O
and	O
Cursed	O
him	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
one	O
that	O
very	O
Moment	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
threatned	O
and	O
attempted	O
to	O
kill	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
still	O
keeping	O
a	O
knocking	O
,	O
he	O
begg	O
'd	O
leave	O
of	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
he	O
was	O
Cupping	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
deceased	O
being	O
afraid	O
to	O
go	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
a	O
Bath	O
presently	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
set	O
the	O
Cock	O
a	O
fighting	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
ready	O
in	O
the	O
8th	O
part	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
G	O
-	O
D	O
-	O
m	O
,	O
you	O
Sirrah	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
have	O
it	O
thin-Moment	O
,	O
and	O
getting	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Bed	O
made	O
8	O
or	O
10	O
Passes	O
which	O
he	O
avoided	O
by	O
holding	O
the	O
Door	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
it	O
.	O
too	O
;	O
then	O
hearing	O
him	O
either	O
see	O
his	O
Sword	O
fall	O
or	O
throw	O
it	O
down	O
he	O
ventured	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
again	O
to	O
pacifie	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
after	O
him	O
and	O
flung	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
of	O
his	O
Ribs	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Mistress	O
this	O
enquired	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
her	O
Maid	O
fent	O
her	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
expoltulats	O
with	O
him	O
why	O
he	O
would	O
kill	O
her	O
Servants	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
D	O
-	O
m	O
,	O
you	O
for	O
a	O
Bitch	O
it	O
should	O
come	O
at	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
stick	O
you	O
first	O
;	O
that	O
Master	O
Mr.	O
Seedwell	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Seedwell	O
Mrs.	O
Seedwell	O
,	O
and	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
deceafed	O
went	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
all	O
together	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Seedwell	O
went	O
that	O
the	O
deceafed	O
went	O
in	O
next	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
fol	O
Loxton	O
with	O
a	O
Candle	O
in	O
a	O
low	O
brass	O
Candlestick	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Seedwell	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
just	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Seedwell	O
stood	O
by	O
the	O
the	O
deceased	O
at	O
the	O
Beds	O
feet	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
behind	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Seedwell	O
at	O
the	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
any	O
of	O
Weapon	O
,	O
Sword	O
Stick	O
,	O
Cane	O
or	O
anything	O
Candle	O
and	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
Mr.	O
Seedwell	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
For	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
What	O
is	O
What	O
have	O
my	O
Servants	O
home	O
?	O
If	O
they	O
have	O
I	O
will	O
punish	O
them	O
before	O
your	O
Face	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
accomodation	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
you	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
I	O
will	O
provide	O
,	O
you	O
either	O
Coach	O
or	O
Chair	O
to	O
go	O
,	O
you	O
please	O
,	O
and	O
nothing	O
for	O
what	O
you	O
have	O
had	O
,	O
of	O
you	O
not	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
disturbance	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
seve	O
of	O
consideration	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
do	O
me	O
a	O
:	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
still	O
very	O
outragi	O
without	O
any	O
other	O
provocation	O
immediately	O
start	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
out	O
a	O
Sword	O
which	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
,	O
the	O
Woman	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
,	O
himself	O
up	O
griping	O
the	O
Sword	O
made	O
2	O
at	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
stagger	O
'd	O
a	O
little	O
wards	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
never	O
speaking	O
one	O
but	O
died	O
immediately	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
With	O
a	O
Pinch	O
of	O
Snuff	O
betwixt	O
the	O
Thumb	O
for	O
his	O
Right	O
Hand	O
as	O
he	O
lay	O
dead	O
on	O
the	O
Mr.	O
Seedwell	O
said	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
manner	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
the	O
Evidence	O
had	O
deposed	O
;	O
adding	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
with	O
him	O
why	O
he	O
should	O
kill	O
his	O
Servants	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
D	O
-	O
m	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
kill	O
you	O
all	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
had	O
considerable	O
struggling	O
with	O
him	O
before	O
they	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
have	O
killed	O
them	O
that	O
the	O
Woman	O
lay	O
still	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
or	O
do	O
any	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
generality	O
of	O
what	O
had	O
before	O
deposed	O
,	O
adding	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
sent	O
up	O
she	O
bid	O
her	O
give	O
her	O
and	O
her	O
Masters	O
Ser	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
tell	O
him	O
they	O
would	O
both	O
wait	O
upon	O
themselves	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Maid	O
came	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
spoke	O
of	O
her	O
Husbands	O
going	O
up	O
,	O
the	O
reply	O
'd	O
Madam	O
,	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
says	O
he	O
will	O
my	O
Masters	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
killed	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
endeavouring	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
it	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
to	O
wound	O
any	O
that	O
should	O
happen	O
to	O
be	O
him	O
Surgeon	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
sent	O
for	O
found	O
quite	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
searching	O
found	O
2	O
Wounds	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Breast	O
slanting	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
Inches	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
but	O
another	O
betwixt	O
1st	O
and	O
2d	O
Rib	O
that	O
the	O
Body	O
and	O
Lungs.4	O
Fingers	O
deep	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
verily	O
believe	O
was	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
pleaded	O
,	O
than	O
being	O
to	O
of	O
Town	O
and	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
he	O
lay	O
at	O
the	O
Bagnio	O
to	O
prevent	O
the	O
trouble	O
,	O
getting	O
out	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
might	O
occasion	O
the	O
Family	O
that	O
about	O
2	O
Clock	O
desired	O
a	O
Bath	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Water	O
coming	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
other	O
times	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
none	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
and	O
locked	O
him	O
in	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
above	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
they	O
all	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
Bath	O
but	O
he	O
turned	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
Street	O
that	O
Moment	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
refusing	O
to	O
go	O
they	O
all	O
surrounded	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
laid	O
Hands	O
I	O
on	O
him	O
,	O
store	O
his	O
Ship	O
and	O
deceased	O
gave	O
him	O
several	O
blows	O
,	O
which	O
brinsed	O
him	O
very	O
much	O
on	O
his	O
Side	O
Arm	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Knuckles	O
,	O
that	O
be	O
thereupon	O
thinking	O
mischief	O
was	O
designed	O
him	O
,	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
to	O
defend	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
repeating	O
his	O
blows	O
,	O
and	O
unfortunately	O
falling	O
or	O
stooping	O
toward	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
this	O
unfortunate	O
Accident	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
a	O
Man	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
difference	O
with	O
before	O
.	O
In	O
proof	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
called	O
the	O
following	O
Evidences	O
.	O
S	O
-	O
W	O
-	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
being	O
at	O
the	O
place	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
Two	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
knock	O
'd	O
and	O
wou	O
'd	O
have	O
a	O
Bath	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Waiter	O
made	O
.	O
Answer	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
the	O
Bath	O
and	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
till	O
5	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
would	O
call	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saying	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
one	O
presently	O
,	O
the	O
Waiter	O
reply	O
'd	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
D	O
-	O
m	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
Rascal	O
he	O
neither	O
could	O
nor	O
should	O
have	O
any	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
reply	O
'd	O
that	O
Gentlemen	O
were	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
abused	O
,	O
that	O
upon	O
this	O
he	O
arose	O
and	O
pushed	O
the	O
Waiter	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
,	O
who	O
lock	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
after	O
him	O
and	O
lock	O
'd	O
them	O
in	O
that	O
them	O
knock	O
'd	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
threat'ned	O
to	O
turn	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Man	O
at	O
the	O
Bedsfeet	O
struck	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
she	O
heard	O
an	O
out	O
cry	O
of	O
Murder	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
afraid	O
they	O
should	O
both	O
be	O
Murdered	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
rise	O
up	O
in	O
his	O
Bed	O
and	O
Men	O
holding	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
deceased	O
lay	O
dead	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
dark	O
colour	O
'd	O
Cane	O
hanging	O
on	O
his	O
Wrist	O
by	O
a	O
black	O
String	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
knew	O
of	O
no	O
Sword	O
in	O
the	O
Bed	O
.	O
nor	O
saw	O
any	O
Wound	O
given	O
.	O
E	O
-	O
R	O
-	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
lodging	O
that	O
Night	O
at	O
the	O
Bagnio	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
the	O
disturbance	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Room	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
deceased	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
Floor	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Cane	O
lying	O
by	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Faggor-stick	O
upon	O
the	O
Stairs	O
hard	O
by	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
which	O
last	O
Circumstance	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Faggor-stick	O
was	O
also	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
another	O
Evidence	O
.	O
The	O
Walker	O
who	O
succeeded	O
the	O
deceased	O
as	O
Waiter	O
at	O
the	O
Bagnio	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
that	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Bagnio	O
and	O
enquired	O
into	O
the	O
circumstances	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
being	O
Shew	O
'd	O
the	O
Room	O
in	O
which	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
examined	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
Wainscot	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
perceive	O
any	O
Marks	O
of	O
the	O
8	O
or	O
10	O
Passes	O
made	O
against	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
as	O
had	O
been	O
deposed	O
by	O
.	O
The	O
Barberton	O
alias	O
Vernassel	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
discoursing	O
with	O
Baberton	O
about	O
the	O
breaking	O
of	O
his	O
Ribbs	O
,	O
seeing	O
him	O
stript	O
,	O
saw	O
no	O
mark	O
or	O
appearance	O
of	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
and	O
that	O
Baberton	O
when	O
he	O
asked	O
him	O
why	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
apply	O
something	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
broke	O
but	O
bruis	O
'd	O
.	O
And	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
besides	O
an	O
ill	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
be	O
abusive	O
to	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
wounded	O
not	O
long	O
before	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
could	O
not	O
deny	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
several	O
Evidences	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
his	O
Shirt	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
torn	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
confirmed	O
by	O
the	O
Constable	O
and	O
Watchman	O
that	O
apprehended	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
:	O
He	O
also	O
called	O
the	O
Constable	O
and	O
Watchman	O
and	O
Several	O
other	O
Evidences	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
see	O
a	O
bruise	O
on	O
his	O
Arm	O
and	O
also	O
a	O
hurt	O
upon	O
his	O
Knuckles	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
bloody	O
.	O
He	O
likewise	O
called	O
several	O
Persons	O
of	O
Credit	O
and	O
Worth	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
and	O
peaceable	O
demeanour	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
He	O
also	O
observed	O
that	O
little	O
credit	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
given	O
to	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
Baberton	O
alias	O
Vernassel	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
swore	O
that	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
of	O
his	O
Ribs	O
were	O
broke	O
,	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
sworn	O
By	O
another	O
Evidence	O
that	O
he	O
himself	O
owned	O
his	O
Ribs	O
were	O
not	O
broken	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
bruised	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
owned	O
in	O
Court	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
had	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
any	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
on	O
that	O
account	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
accordingly	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
receiving	O
of	O
which	O
,	O
being	O
asked	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
why	O
Judgement	O
should	O
not	O
pass	O
upon	O
him	O
according	O
to	O
Law	O
he	O
spoke	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
I	O
submit	O
my	O
self	O
to	O
your	O
Lordship	O
and	O
this	O
Honourable	O
Bench	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
beg	O
only	O
your	O
honourable	O
Favour	O
and	O
Regard	O
that	O
as	O
she	O
Witness	O
's	O
for	O
me	O
swore	O
positively	O
to	O
my	O
being	O
assaulted	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Jury	O
(	O
to	O
my	O
,	O
great	O
Misfortune	O
)	O
were	O
not	O
pleased	O
to	O
give	O
Credit	O
to	O
the	O
family	O
your	O
Lordship	O
will	O
make	O
the	O
most	O
favourable	O
Interpretation	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
But	O
above	O
all	O
I	O
desire	O
your	O
Lordship	O
's	O
notice	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
many	O
manifest	O
Contradiction	O
,	O
in	O
Vernassell	O
's	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
may	O
say	O
Impossibilities	O
in	O
other	O
of	O
their	O
Witnesses	O
.	O
Besides	O
her	O
denying	O
on	O
my	O
Tryal	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
double	O
lock	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
swore	O
he	O
did	O
before	O
the	O
Coroner	O
,	O
makes	O
me	O
with	O
reason	O
believe	O
my	O
Life	O
has	O
been	O
maliciously	O
sought	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
call	O
God	O
to	O
Witness	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
offer	O
the	O
least	O
Violence	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
till	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
struck	O
and	O
ill	O
used	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
submit	O
my	O
self	O
to	O
your	O
Lordship	O
,	O
and	O
hope	O
your	O
will	O
make	O
such	O
favorable	O
Report	O
to	O
his	O
Majesty	O
as	O
may	O
not	O
obstruct	O
,	O
but	O
leave	O
room	O
to	O
apply	O
to	O
his	O
Wisdom	O
for	O
Mercy	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgement	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
15.	O
John	B-pers
Moody	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Reed	I-pers
alias	O
Morris	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Thorn	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cinnamon	I-pers
alias	O
Mason	O
,	O
Matthew	O
,	O
Whitten	O
Francis	O
Parquet	O
alias	O
Parket	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Prior	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Vickars	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Linne	I-pers
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Wiseman	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported,18	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Bush	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Holyday	I-pers
,	O
Willium	O
Phillips	O
,	O
Anny	O
Furnace	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
,	O
Simon	B-pers
Jaron	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Halmes	I-pers
;	O
Katherine	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gibbons	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
,	O
William	O
Conner	O
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Floyd	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Butcher	I-pers
alias	O
Cone	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Goodram	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Dickson	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
Coristopher	B-pers
Hutton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Faxford	I-pers
convicted	O
last	O
Sessions	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
,	O
W	O
-	O
F	O
-	O
,	O
and	O
Aaran	O
Wileox	O
,	O
which	O
last	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
Transported	O
last	O
Sessions	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Reed	I-pers
,	O
pleaded	O
their	O
,	O
Bellies	O
:	O
And	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
being	O
impannell	O
'd	O
,	O
found	O
Mary	O
Reed	O
with	O
Quick	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
Margarets	O
Smith	O
not	O
.	O
A	O
D	O
V	O
E	O
R	O
T	O
I	O
S	O
E	O
M	O
E	O
N	O
T	O
For	O
the	O
Good	O
of	O
the	O
Publick	O
WHereas	O
several	O
Gentleman	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
that	O
Sex	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Kingdom	O
here	O
contracted	O
an	O
Evil	O
Habit	O
of	O
Body	O
,	O
wherein	O
the	O
victual	O
Humours	O
,	O
at	O
first	O
dispers	O
'd	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Whole	O
,	O
come	O
at	O
length	O
to	O
be	O
lodged	O
in	O
one	O
Part	O
or	O
another	O
;	O
and	O
many	O
times	O
,	O
for	O
Causes	O
too	O
long	O
to	O
be	O
here	O
mentioned	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Womb	O
,	O
ocassioning	O
a	O
dangerous	O
Weakness	O
in	O
that	O
Part	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
neglected	O
at	O
last	O
turns	O
Cancerous	O
and	O
often	O
proves	O
Fatal	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
to	O
acquaint	O
all	O
such	O
as	O
may	O
have	O
occasion	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
speedy	O
Relief	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
had	O
from	O
a	O
Sworn	O
and	O
Experienc	O
'd	O
Midwife	O
,	O
dwelling	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Arms	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
the	O
Tin-Shop	O
near	O
Exeter	O
Change	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
who	O
perform	O
'd	O
a	O
wonderful	O
Cure	O
upon	O
a	O
Lady	O
at	O
the	O
Bath	O
,	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
given	O
over	O
by	O
the	O
Physicians	O
,	O
and	O
since	O
has	O
Cured	O
several	O
Gentlewomen	O
and	O
others	O
in	O
the	O
City	O
and	O
Suburbs	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
put	O
my	O
self	O
in	O
publick	O
Print	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
satisfy	O
the	O
Afflicted	O
where	O
they	O
may	O
have	O
present	O
Ease	O
and	O
Relief	O
if	O
not	O
,	O
no	O
Money	O
.	O
All	O
Melancholy	O
,	O
Hysterioal	O
and	O
Hypocondriack	O
Distempers	O
,	O
WHich	O
variously	O
affect	O
the	O
Mind	O
,	O
with	O
strange	O
Fears	O
and	O
disnal	O
Apprehensions	O
;	O
Faintings	O
and	O
Sinkings	O
of	O
the	O
Spirits	O
,	O
great	O
Hurries	O
,	O
Restlesness	O
and	O
Disquietment	O
(	O
little	O
understand	O
and	O
seldom	O
cured	O
by	O
any	O
common	O
means	O
)	O
also	O
Pains	O
Giddiness	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
;	O
Risings	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Throat	O
,	O
Sick	O
Fits	O
,	O
Treatings	O
,	O
Oppressions	O
of	O
the	O
Heart	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
other	O
Disorder	O
caused	O
by	O
Vapours	O
;	O
are	O
sucessfully	O
(	O
with	O
God	O
's	O
Blessing	O
)	O
by	O
a	O
Physician	O
well-experienced	O
there	O
,	O
(	O
who	O
is	O
Son	O
and	O
sucessor	O
to	O
a	O
late	O
eminent	O
Physician	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
of	O
more	O
than	O
10	O
Years	O
successful	O
Practice	O
in	O
those	O
Deplorable	O
Cases	O
)	O
be	O
a	O
so	O
all	O
kind	O
of	O
Fits	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
strange	O
and	O
violent	O
(	O
if	O
curable	O
)	O
which	O
he	O
will	O
justily	O
inform	O
you	O
;	O
living	O
at	O
No	O
1.	O
in	O
Burt-Street	O
in	O
St.	O
Katherines	O
near	O
the	O
Tower	O
,	O
London	O
:	O
where	O
those	O
that	O
have	O
occasion	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
remote	O
,	O
direct	O
their	O
Letters	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
shall	O
be	O
speedily	O
answered	O
be	O
attended	O
on	O
if	O
desired	O
.	O
Some	O
B	O
O	O
O	O
K	O
S	O
printed	O
for	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
Edmund	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
and	O
Crown	O
its	O
Lombard	O
Street	O
,	O
near	O
Stocks-Market	O
.	O
THE	O
London	O
New	O
Method	O
and	O
Art	O
of	O
Teaching	O
Children	O
to	O
Spell	O
and	O
Read	O
so	O
as	O
they	O
may	O
,	O
without	O
the	O
Help	O
of	O
any	O
other	O
Books	O
,	O
read	O
the	O
Bible	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
twelve	O
Months	O
,	O
Note	O
,	O
This	O
Way	O
of	O
Teaching	O
is	O
approved	O
by	O
most	O
School	O
Masters	O
as	O
the	O
best	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
6	O
d.	O
with	O
great	O
Allowance	O
to	O
those	O
who	O
sell	O
or	O
give	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
Note	O
,	O
There	O
are	O
some	O
printed	O
on	O
Fine	O
Paper	O
,	O
bound	O
up	O
with	O
Cuts	O
.	O
pr.8	O
d.	O
M.	O
Jordaine	O
's	O
Duodecimal	O
:	O
Arithmetick	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
multiplication	O
cite	O
and	O
Exact	O
Method	O
extant	O
.	O
In	O
Three	O
Books	O
.	O
Containing	O
Notation	O
,	O
Addition	O
,	O
Subtraction	O
,	O
Multiplication	O
,	O
Division	O
,	O
Reduction	O
,	O
Extraction	O
of	O
the	O
Square	O
and	O
Cube	O
Roots	O
,	O
Rule	O
of	O
Proportion	O
,	O
Direct	O
and	O
Reverse	O
,	O
Duodecimally	O
performed	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
Practically	O
applied	O
to	O
the	O
measuring	O
of	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
Superficies	O
,	O
and	O
Solids	O
,	O
as	O
Board	O
,	O
Glass	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Timber	O
,	O
Stone	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
Gauging	O
of	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
Brewers	O
Tuns	O
and	O
Casks	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
and	O
that	O
with	O
more	O
Ease	O
and	O
Expedition	O
,	O
that	O
by	O
Vulgar	O
or	O
Decimal	O
Arithmetick	O
:	O
Very	O
useful	O
for	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
Men	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
Gentlemen	O
as	O
others	O
,	O
but	O
especially	O
for	O
Machines	O
,	O
Writing	O
Masters	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
Measuring	O
Artificers	O
And	O
all	O
the	O
Rules	O
made	O
Plain	O
,	O
and	O
Easie	O
for	O
the	O
meauest	O
Capacity	O
.	O
The	O
Second	O
Edition	O
8	O
vo	O
Price	O
Bound	O
8	O
s.6	O
d.	O
Asop	O
's	O
Fahles	O
,	O
with	O
Morals	O
and	O
Reflection	O
,	O
as	O
improv	O
'd	O
by	O
Sir	O
Roger	O
L'Estrange	O
,	O
done	O
into	O
Variety	O
of	O
English	O
Verse	O
Illustrated	O
with	O
Cuts	O
curiouly	O
engray	O
'd	O
on	O
Copper	O
Plates	O
.	O
Very	O
useful	O
to	O
Divert	O
and	O
Instruct	O
Young	O
Gentlemen	O
and	O
Ladies	O
in	O
the	O
Conc	O
of	O
Human	O
Life	O
.	O
The	O
second	O
Editions	O
Price	O
bound	O
2	O
s.6	O
d.	O
The	O
Benefit	O
of	O
Early	O
Piety	O
,	O
recommended	O
to	O
all	O
Young	O
Persons	O
.	O
By	O
W	O
Smythies	O
,	O
late	O
Morning	O
Lectures	O
of	O
St.	O
Michael	O
in	O
Cornhil	O
,	O
London	O
.	O
The	O
Third	O
Edition	O
Price	O
bound	O
6	O
d	O
;	O
For	O
the	O
Compleating	O
of	O
Psalmody	O
.	O
The	O
Devout	O
Singer	O
's	O
Guide	O
;	O
containing	O
all	O
the	O
Common	O
Tunes	O
now	O
in	O
life	O
,	O
with	O
select	O
;	O
portions	O
of	O
the	O
psalms	O
adapted	O
to	O
each	O
Tones	O
and	O
Rules	O
for	O
singing	O
Treble	O
and	O
,	O
Bass	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
A	O
Table	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
psalms	O
and	O
Hymns	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Version	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Hopkins	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Siernbold	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
New	O
Version	O
of	O
Dr.	O
Brady	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Tate	O
;	O
adapted	O
to	O
the	O
Tastes	O
;	O
and	O
Directions	O
for	O
parish	O
Clerks	O
in	O
the	O
Choice	O
of	O
proper	O
psalms	O
on	O
most	O
Occasions	O
.	O
Recommended	O
by	O
the	O
best	O
Singing	O
Masters	O
.	O
The	O
Third	O
Edition	O
;	O
8	O
ve	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
1	O
s.	O
Maximum	O
in	O
Minima	O
:	O
Or	O
!	O
Mr.	O
Jeremish	O
Rich	O
's	O
Pens	O
Dexterity	O
compleated	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
plainest	O
and	O
earliest	O
Method	O
of	O
writing	O
SHORT-HAND	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
are	O
added	O
.	O
The	O
Terms	O
of	O
the	O
Law	O
compleat	O
in	O
Characters	O
at	O
length	O
,	O
being	O
of	O
great	O
use	O
to	O
all	O
Lawyers	O
and	O
others	O
who	O
take	O
Tryals	O
at	O
large	O
,	O
in	O
Courts	O
.	O
Never	O
done	O
till	O
now	O
.	O
By	O
Samuel	B-pers
Botley	I-pers
,	O
The	O
whole	O
curiously	O
engrav	O
'd	O
on	O
Thirty	O
Copper	O
Plates	O
.	O
Pr.6	O
d.	O
Arithmetick	O
made	O
easie	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
New	O
Method	O
how	O
taught	O
and	O
practis	O
'd	O
in	O
London	O
.	O
Wherein	O
the	O
Rules	O
of	O
that	O
necessary	O
Art	O
are	O
briefly	O
explain	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
with	O
such	O
familiar	O
,	O
Examples	O
as	O
may	O
suit	O
the	O
meanest	O
Capacity	O
.	O
If	O
they	O
desire	O
to	O
learn	O
it	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
a	O
inct	O
.	O
Treatise	O
of	O
Decimal	O
Fractions	O
,	O
with	O
Compleat	O
Tables	O
,	O
Rules	O
,	O
and	O
Examples	O
demonstrating	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
blue	O
not	O
extant	O
in	O
any	O
other	O
Treatise	O
of	O
this	O
Nature	O
.	O
The	O
Fourth	O
Editions	O
.	O
By	O
John	B-pers
Copeland	I-pers
,	O
Writing-Master	O
Price	O
bound	O
1	O
s.	O
A	O
Guide	O
to	O
English	O
Juries	O
:	O
Setting	O
forth	O
their	O
quity	O
Power	O
and	O
Duty	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Common-Law	O
and	O
Statues	O
.	O
With	O
a	O
Table	O
.	O
By	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
Quality	O
.	O
Also	O
a	O
Letter	O
to	O
Author	O
upon	O
the	O
same	O
Subject	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
Orders	O
.	O
By	O
Laws	O
,	O
and	O
Ordinances	O
for	O
the	O
good	O
Government	O
and	O
Regulating	O
:	O
of	O
the	O
persons	O
Licensed	O
to	O
Keep	O
and	O
Drive	O
Hackney-Coaches	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
Reuters	O
and	O
Drivers	O
.	O
Made	O
,	O
Publish	O
'd	O
and	O
,	O
Declar	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Commissioners	O
and	O
Allowed	O
and	O
Approved	O
by	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chancellor	O
and	O
Judges	O
at	O
the	O
Law	O
directs	O
.	O
Price	O
3	O
d.	O
The	O
following	O
Books	O
are	O
given	O
Graths	O
.	O
1st	O
.	O
THE	O
Practical	O
Scheme	O
of	O
the	O
Secret	O
Disease	O
and	O
Brokes	O
Constitutions	O
,	O
by	O
Fast	O
Living	O
,	O
Former	O
its	O
Cures	O
,	O
Salivations	O
and	O
Mercury	O
-2ly	O
,	O
The	O
New	O
System	O
of	O
the	O
GOUR	O
and	O
Rheumatism	O
,	O
drawn	O
from	O
Reasons	O
,	O
Autnomical	O
Observations	O
and	O
Experience	O
,	O
-3ly	O
,	O
A	O
Rational	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Cause	O
,	O
Nature	O
,	O
and	O
Cure	O
of	O
WEAKNESSES	O
usually	O
attending	O
Persons	O
,	O
after	O
former	O
Cures	O
,	O
Over-strainings	O
Self-Abuses	O
,	O
Hard	O
Labours	O
,	O
Miscarriages	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Wherein	O
is	O
given	O
a	O
full	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
horrid	O
Nature	O
,	O
and	O
most	O
miserable	O
Consequently	O
of	O
Self-Abuses	O
in	O
particular	O
.	O
These	O
Books	O
(	O
all	O
New	O
Editions	O
)	O
are	O
given	O
Gratis	O
Up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
ANODYNE	O
.	O
NECK	O
-	O
LACE	O
,	O
without	O
Temple	O
Bar	O
At	O
Mr.	O
Gowpers	O
Toyshop	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Charles	O
Court	O
by	O
Hungerford-Market	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
And	O
And	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Garraway	O
's	O
Shop	O
at	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms	O
at	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange-Gate	O
next	O
Cornhill	O
.	O
LONDON	O
,	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
Phillips	O
;	O
by	O
M.	O
against	O
St.	O
Sepulchres	O
Buck-Gate	O
in	O
Gilt-Spur-Street	O
near	O
Newgate	O
;	O
and	O
Sold	O
by	O
J.	O
Roberts	O
in	O
Warwick-Lane	O
1718	O
.	O
Where	O
Advertisements	O
are	O
taken	O
in	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
3	O
d	O
.	O
)	O
