TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
,	O
ON	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
and	O
Monday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
4th	O
,	O
5th	O
,	O
and	O
7th	O
,	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
,	O
1719	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Sixth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
GEORGE	B-pers
THOROLD	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
and	O
Baronet	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
The	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
King	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Ayres	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Page	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
Names	O
were	O
as	O
followth	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Claris	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Freerson	I-pers
,	O
Barnard	B-pers
Sower	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Reed	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Yardley	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Drinkwell	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Goodchild	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Wools	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Highmore	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Wardel	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Boswell	I-pers
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Goudge	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wootten	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Eddy	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Prator	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Goddard	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Clements	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
John	B-pers
Layfield	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Undershaft	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Waterman	I-pers
,	O
1	O
pound	O
of	O
Sperma	O
Ceti	O
,	O
3	O
pound	O
of	O
Jesuits	O
Bark	O
,	O
1	O
pound	O
of	O
Opium	O
,	O
1	O
pound	O
of	O
Rheubarb	O
and	O
3	O
pound	O
of	O
Spanish	O
South	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Porter	O
,	O
who	O
having	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
upon	O
his	O
Return	O
mist	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
two	O
Persons	O
who	O
appeared	O
against	O
him	O
in	O
Court	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
contact	O
the	O
Fact	O
when	O
taken	O
up	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
which	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
acknowledged	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
at	O
three	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
14	O
Silver	O
Buttons	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Whaley	I-pers
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
at	O
the	O
Bull-Inn	B-place
in	I-place
White	I-place
Chappel	I-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
by	O
there	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
where	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Box	O
of	O
Clothes	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Buttons	O
,	O
off	O
a	O
Coat	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
going	O
for	O
his	O
Coat	O
mist	O
his	O
Buttons	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
suspected	O
because	O
he	O
absented	O
himself	O
from	O
the	O
Inn	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
otherwise	O
have	O
been	O
,	O
being	O
known	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
search	O
being	O
made	O
after	O
him	O
they	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
confest	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
and	O
sold'em	O
for	O
14	O
s.	O
his	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
on	O
his	O
Tryal	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Hinchman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Faiths	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rhodes	I-pers
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
going	O
into	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Church	I-place
Yard	I-place
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
another	O
Person	O
,	O
who	O
carry	O
'd	O
it	O
off	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
called	O
none	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
positive	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Marshal	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
six	O
Camblet	O
Curtains	O
,	O
3	O
Vallains	O
,	O
2	O
Pillowbears	O
and	O
a	O
Crape	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
let	O
a	O
Lodging	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
them	O
have	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
a	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
,	O
all	O
but	O
one	O
Drawer	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
reserv	O
'd	O
to	O
her	O
self	O
;	O
that	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Drawer	O
for	O
her	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
them	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
further	O
mist	O
her	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Pillowbears	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
Bed	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
charg	O
'd	O
Mary	O
Pain	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
her	O
other	O
Goods	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Pillowbears	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
should	O
have	O
then	O
again	O
that	O
Night	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
got	O
a	O
search	O
Warrant	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
two	O
Brokers	O
where	O
Pain	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
at	O
one	O
Pawnbrokers	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
her	O
Goods	O
at	O
another	O
.	O
Two	O
other	O
Evidences	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Pain	O
pleaded	O
that	O
she	O
and	O
Challenged	O
Pain	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
confirmed	O
her	O
owning	O
them	O
as	O
before	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Pain	O
pleaded	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
necessicated	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
pawned	O
them	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
being	O
them	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Drawer	O
was	O
not	O
lockt	O
but	O
open	O
;	O
that	O
Elizabeth	O
Marshal	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
that	O
the	O
Drawer	O
was	O
lockt	O
;	O
and	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
Marshal	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Mary	O
Pain	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Quiet	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Hill	I-place
at	I-place
Billinsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
pound	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hide	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
a	O
Hogshead	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
was	O
broke	O
at	O
Bottolph	B-place
Wharf	I-place
,	O
and	O
16	O
pound	O
weight	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
watch	O
'd	O
on	O
she	O
Key	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
3	O
pound	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
between	O
1	O
and	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
just	O
come	O
from	O
France	O
with	O
Prunes	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Master	O
of	O
the	O
Ship	O
order	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
keep	O
on	O
Board	O
;	O
But	O
the	O
Ship	O
lying	O
by	O
the	O
Key	O
he	O
ventur	O
'd	O
on	O
Shore	O
to	O
see	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
feeling	O
something	O
soft	O
under	O
his	O
Feet	O
,	O
tooking	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
which	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
3	O
pound	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
either	O
broke	O
the	O
Hogshead	O
or	O
took	O
the	O
Tobacco	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Duke	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Alphage	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Whitten	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Bruise	O
on	O
his	O
Left	O
Leg	O
with	O
the	O
off	O
Wheel	O
of	O
a	O
Dray	O
,	O
loaded	O
with	O
Barrels	O
of	O
Drink	O
fix	O
'd	O
to	O
two	O
Horses	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languish	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
22d	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
some	O
others	O
to	O
play	O
an	O
Engine	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
keep	O
it	O
in	O
Repair	O
and	O
fit	O
for	O
Service	O
in	O
Case	O
a	O
Fire	O
should	O
happen	O
;	O
and	O
carrying	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Handles	O
of	O
the	O
Pump	O
on	O
his	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
turned	O
short	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Church	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Dray	O
going	O
by	O
at	O
the	O
sametime	O
,	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
it	O
toucht	O
either	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Horses	O
or	O
the	O
Dray	O
,	O
which	O
threw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Horses	O
being	O
Young	O
,	O
started	O
and	O
ran	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
all	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
to	O
keep	O
the	O
Dray	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
far	O
turn	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
only	O
went	O
over	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Leg	O
,	O
whereas	O
if	O
it	O
had	O
gone	O
directly	O
on	O
,	O
it	O
must	O
have	O
gone	O
over	O
the	O
upper	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
Body	O
.	O
The	O
Surgeon	O
deposed	O
his	O
Heel	O
was	O
torn	O
almost	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Leg	O
bruised	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
died	O
of	O
his	O
Wounds	O
:	O
but	O
it	O
fully	O
appearing	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drove	O
softly	O
till	O
the	O
Horse	O
started	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
did	O
all	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
to	O
prevent	O
the	O
Misfortune	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Armor	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Armstrong	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
her	O
Female	O
Bastard	O
Child	O
,	O
by	O
throwing	O
her	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
she	O
received	O
a	O
mortal	O
Bruise	O
on	O
the	O
Left	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
deliver	O
'd	O
of	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Scull	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
Crackt	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
acknowledged	O
her	O
being	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
gone	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
to	O
her	O
Fathers	O
to	O
Lye	O
in	O
.	O
The	O
Indictment	O
being	O
laid	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
her	O
Bastard	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
fully	O
appearing	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Married	O
Woman	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Osborn	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Wallis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Canvas	O
Bag	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
ten	O
Guineas	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Nathanael	B-pers
Macascree	I-pers
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
and	O
Wallis	O
calling	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Nicholson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Peter	I-place
's	I-place
Poor	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
her	O
Male	O
Bastard	O
Child	O
by	O
wrapping	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Cloth	O
and	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
Trunk	O
whereby	O
he	O
was	O
suffocated	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
Nov	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
deliver	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
took	O
a	O
Lodging	O
at	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Linegar	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Days	O
her	O
Landlady	O
smelt	O
an	O
unusual	O
Stink	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
come	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Trunk	O
,	O
whereupon	O
she	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
and	O
had	O
it	O
open	O
'd	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Child	O
ty	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Cloth	O
by	O
the	O
four	O
Corners	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
believ	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
full	O
grown	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Cloth	O
was	O
unty	O
'd	O
its	O
Limbs	O
fell	O
at	O
their	O
Length	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
very	O
Limber	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
Still-Born	O
;	O
and	O
called	O
the	O
following	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
having	O
made	O
Provision	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Her	O
first	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sent	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
Labour	O
;	O
and	O
bid	O
her	O
take	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
her	O
Trunk	O
to	O
fetch	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
Linnen	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
return	O
'd	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
born	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
turning	O
up	O
the	O
bed	O
clothes	O
perceived	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
wrong	O
Birth	O
,	O
and	O
still	O
Born	O
.	O
Another	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
about	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
before	O
,	O
owned	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
had	O
made	O
some	O
Preparation	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
make	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
a	O
Lodging	O
(	O
being	O
then	O
at	O
Service	O
)	O
and	O
desired	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
come	O
to	O
her	O
Labour	O
when	O
sent	O
for	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
over	O
before	O
she	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
her	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
still	O
born	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
Linnen	O
:	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
complained	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
well	O
all	O
Day	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
her	O
Sister	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
her	O
Sister	O
came	O
,	O
this	O
Evidence	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
and	O
Saw	O
Linnen	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
.	O
There	O
appeared	O
no	O
Marks	O
of	O
Violence	O
upon	O
the	O
Child	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Brett	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Gregory	I-place
's	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Cloak	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
about	O
6	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
in	O
Huggin-Lane	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
confest	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
accordingly	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
acknowledged	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Finley	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
in	I-place
Lothbury	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
four	O
Printed	O
Books	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Mercer	I-pers
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
two	O
Volumes	O
of	O
Tatlers	O
and	O
a	O
Book	O
of	O
Novels	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
third	O
Volume	O
of	O
Tatlers	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Browne	O
's	O
without	O
Temple-Bar	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
two	O
Volumes	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
them	O
that	O
they	O
would	O
soon	O
catch	O
the	O
Thief	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
just	O
lost	O
the	O
third	O
Volume	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
concluded	O
that	O
would	O
be	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
two	O
first	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
accordingly	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
secur	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Books	O
were	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
be	O
bought	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
Moor-fields	O
,	O
but	O
produc	O
'd	O
none	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Goodchild	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Christ	B-place
Church	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
4	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
2	O
Huckaback	O
Tablecloths	O
and	O
a	O
Child	O
's	O
Shift	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Bretland	I-pers
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
work	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
with	O
a	O
Lodger	O
(	O
a	O
Quilter	O
,	O
)	O
and	O
being	O
suspected	O
was	O
forwarn	O
'd	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
that	O
now	O
coming	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
clogs	O
,	O
mov	O
'd	O
a	O
parcel	O
wet	O
Linnen	O
from	O
the	O
Dresler	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
into	O
the	O
Passage	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
higher	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
left	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
being	O
mist	O
she	O
was	O
follow	O
'd	O
and	O
taken	O
,	O
with	O
two	O
wet	O
Shirts	O
in	O
her	O
Apron	O
,	O
own	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Price	I-pers
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Ashby	I-pers
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
going	O
down	O
Fleet-street	B-place
with	O
a	O
Friend	O
Arm	O
in	O
Arm	O
,	O
he	O
felt	O
a	O
Hand	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
turn	O
'd	O
back	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
within	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
Yard	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
body	O
else	O
near	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Riding-Hoods	O
,	O
a	O
Furbelow	O
Scarf	O
and	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Clayton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
December	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
about	O
7	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
a	O
Funeral	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
and	O
as	O
they	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
the	O
Coach	B-place
and	I-place
Horses	I-place
in	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
to	O
refresh	O
themselves	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
behind	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
mist	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
as	O
were	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
others	O
who	O
were	O
drinking	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
;	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Fee-Lane	O
with	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
secur	O
'd	O
him	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
before	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Withers	I-pers
;	O
that	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
Restitution	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
prosecute	O
him	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Clayton	O
confirmed	O
their	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
being	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Loss	O
of	O
their	O
Goods	O
.	O
Another	O
deposed	O
that	O
while	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
others	O
were	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
waiting	O
to	O
go	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
toss	O
something	O
White	O
over	O
the	O
Wall	O
of	O
his	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Maid	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
owned	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
Tom	O
the	O
Kidnapper	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
Jun	O
.	O
of	O
Isleworth	B-place
in	O
the	O
Country	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Paul	B-pers
Jodderel	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
4	O
large	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
4	O
Silver	O
Tea-Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
China	O
Milk-pot	O
,	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
a	O
Cane	O
,	O
Perriwig	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
It	O
fully	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
and	O
his	O
Goods	O
stole	O
,	O
and	O
great	O
reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
fix	O
it	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Michael	O
Wells	O
Junior	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
Tabatha	B-pers
Marshal	I-pers
,	O
did	O
imbezel	O
and	O
convert	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
use	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
Wastcoat	O
and	O
Breeches	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
hired	O
Servant	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
Year	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
a	O
way	O
with	O
the	O
Livery	O
without	O
her	O
consent	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
at	O
Branford	O
,	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
sold	O
the	O
Coat	O
in	O
Monmouth-street	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
Judging	O
this	O
Inbezlement	O
of	O
his	O
Livery	O
to	O
be	O
within	O
the	O
Statute	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
also	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Hafted	O
Knife	O
and	O
Fork	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Cornelius	B-pers
a	I-pers
Tilburgh	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Knife	O
and	O
Fork	O
off	O
the	O
Dresser	O
from	O
among	O
others	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
a	O
Man	O
persuaded	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
bring	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Isleworth	B-place
in	O
the	O
Country	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Varney	I-pers
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
about	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
a	O
Bed-Quilt	O
,	O
a	O
Chints	O
Gown	O
,	O
2	O
pieces	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
a	O
Muslin	O
Apron	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Porringer	O
,	O
4	O
Silver	O
Tea	O
Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
Purse	O
of	O
Mother	O
of	O
Pearl	O
Compters	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
fully	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Porringer	O
and	O
Spoons	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Gown	O
and	O
Quilt	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Constable	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Micklewright	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
are	O
considerate	O
Men	O
,	O
and	O
will	O
not	O
take	O
away	O
my	O
Life	O
,	O
if	O
not	O
for	O
my	O
saks	O
,	O
yet	O
for	O
my	O
Wife	O
and	O
Childrens	O
:	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
them	O
20	O
Guineas	O
to	O
stifle	O
the	O
matter	O
:	O
The	O
Goods	O
taken	O
upon	O
him	O
were	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
and	O
Swore	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servants	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
and	O
sold	O
Old	O
Clothes	O
about	O
the	O
Streets	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
a	O
Man	O
a	O
Coat	O
for	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Head	O
in	O
Cross-Street	O
Covent-Garden	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
another	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
said	O
his	O
Wife	O
was	O
dead	O
and	O
he	O
must	O
dispose	O
of	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Effects	O
to	O
raise	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
him	O
the	O
Gown	O
and	O
Quilt	O
for	O
4	O
l.	O
than	O
shewed	O
him	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
bought	O
that	O
also	O
at	O
5	O
s.	O
1	O
d.	O
an	O
Ounce	O
;	O
he	O
called	O
one	O
Ann	B-pers
Clerks	I-pers
and	O
3	O
others	O
who	O
all	O
pretended	O
not	O
to	O
know	O
him	O
but	O
to	O
be	O
there	O
accidentally	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
.	O
But	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
produce	O
the	O
Man	O
be	O
sold	O
the	O
Coat	O
to	O
,	O
nor	O
he	O
who	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Goods	O
off	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Trippuck	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bone	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
together	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Constable	I-pers
,	O
(	O
already	O
Executed	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
)	O
did	O
Assault	O
Giles	B-pers
Blackman	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Bodily	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
Three	O
Pence	O
Half-Penny	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
about	O
7	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
that	O
against	O
Constable	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
that	O
Constable	O
rode	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
within	B-place
10	I-place
Yards	I-place
of	I-place
Tyburn	I-place
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
who	O
ty	O
'd	O
his	O
Hands	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
let	O
down	O
his	O
Breeches	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
Money	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
sure	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
having	O
seen	O
him	O
before	O
in	O
the	O
Marshalsea	O
,	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Hope	I-pers
whom	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
there	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Parish	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
before	O
they	O
met	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Sack	O
of	O
Hair	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
not	O
so	O
positive	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
one	O
staid	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
fetcht	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
bound	O
him	O
by	O
this	O
Evidence	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
apprehended	O
them	O
,	O
Constable	O
fired	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
aware	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
better	O
provided	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
should	O
have	O
cost	O
them	O
dearer	O
.	O
Another	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
lent	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
House	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Twitenham	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
home	O
with	O
it	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
sent	O
it	O
home	O
next	O
Night	O
by	O
a	O
Boy	O
,	O
hard	O
rid	O
,	O
and	O
without	O
Money	O
for	O
the	O
Hire	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
dined	O
that	O
Day	O
at	O
a	O
House	O
by	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
Pound	O
on	O
a	O
Shoulder	O
of	O
Veal	O
,	O
and	O
Staid	O
there	O
till	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
the	O
Woman	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
Dorathy	B-pers
Percival	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
to	O
borrow	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Husband	O
not	O
being	O
at	O
Home	O
he	O
waited	O
there	O
for	O
his	O
coming	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Shoulder	O
of	O
Veal	O
for	O
dinner	O
,	O
and	O
invited	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
dine	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
there	O
till	O
10	O
or	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
and	O
out	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
nor	O
go	O
further	O
than	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
being	O
askt	O
how	O
long	O
he	O
might	O
stay	O
at	O
most	O
to	O
her	O
best	O
remembrance	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
about	O
Half	O
an	O
Hour	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
also	O
observed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
apprehended	O
for	O
this	O
Robbery	O
but	O
for	O
the	O
Hire	O
of	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
nothing	O
was	O
found	O
on	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
some	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
one	O
who	O
deposed	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
20	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
heard	O
him	O
declare	O
how	O
glad	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
to	O
lead	O
an	O
honest	O
happy	O
Life	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
to	O
receive	O
Sentence	O
,	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
say	O
why	O
it	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
pronounced	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
hoped	O
the	O
Court	O
would	O
consider	O
the	O
Punishment	O
he	O
had	O
already	O
undergone	O
by	O
being	O
Shot	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Arm	O
into	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
had	O
already	O
been	O
Excecuted	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Fact	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
in	I-place
White	I-place
Chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Snuff	O
Box	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
went	O
into	O
the	B-place
two	I-place
Brewers	I-place
in	I-place
Brick-Lane	I-place
to	O
stay	O
for	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
three	O
Men	O
coming	O
in	O
to	O
drink	O
were	O
shewed	O
into	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
pulled	O
out	O
her	O
Snuff	O
Box	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
Pinch	O
of	O
Snuff	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
a	O
Pinch	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Men	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
thinking	O
her	O
Husband	O
staid	O
long	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
left	O
her	O
Box	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
;	O
that	O
misting	O
of	O
it	O
she	O
came	O
back	O
and	O
charged	O
the	O
three	O
Men	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
who	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
,	O
nor	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
another	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
carried	O
some	O
pieces	O
of	O
Silver	O
to	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
by	O
the	O
Monument	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
judged	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
pieces	O
of	O
a	O
broken	O
Snuff	O
Box	O
,	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
followed	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
said	O
a	O
Box	O
was	O
lost	O
and	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
some	O
stir	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Pieces	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
but	O
neither	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
nor	O
his	O
Wife	O
wood	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
the	O
Lid	O
was	O
pretty	O
remarkable	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Name	O
graved	O
at	O
Length	O
,	O
very	O
plain	O
to	O
be	O
seen	O
notwithstanding	O
the	O
breaking	O
and	O
battering	O
of	O
the	O
Box	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
another	O
Room	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Carpenter	O
and	O
workt	O
honestly	O
at	O
his	O
Business	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
entrusted	O
considerably	O
and	O
always	O
found	O
honest	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
value	O
5	O
s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Farrel	I-pers
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
at	O
Burlington	B-place
Gardens	I-place
and	O
left	O
his	O
Coat	O
at	O
the	O
work	O
while	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
view	O
another	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
for	O
his	O
Coat	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Friend	O
advised	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Monmouth-Street	O
to	O
buy	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
Mr.	O
Jackson	O
's	O
at	O
the	O
Black-a-moor	O
's	O
Head	O
there	O
,	O
(	O
who	O
had	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
bought	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Coat	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
who	O
shewed	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
some	O
Coats	O
which	O
would	O
not	O
fit	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
notice	O
of	O
his	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
concluded	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
Cloth	O
with	O
the	O
Coat	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
,	O
told	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
could	O
shew	O
him	O
his	O
own	O
Coat	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
fitted	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
swore	O
to	O
by	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
afterwards	O
to	O
tell	O
him	O
another	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
apprehended	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hutchins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Dale	I-pers
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
desired	O
to	O
leave	O
an	O
old	O
Casement	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Wig	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Box	O
on	O
the	O
Casement	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Box	O
and	O
carried	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Casement	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
mist	O
it	O
presently	O
,	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
confest	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
in	O
Middle	O
Row	O
Holbourn	O
for	O
3	O
s.	O
where	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
owned	O
it	O
also	O
on	O
her	O
Tryal	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Raven	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
of	O
Twittenham	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Beck	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
Beck	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hassel	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
Mr.	O
Beck	O
was	O
inform	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
that	O
Lewis	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
Coat	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
sent	O
his	O
Apprentice	O
(	O
Francis	O
Lamb	O
)	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
who	O
overtook	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
his	O
own	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
and	O
a	O
Wastcoat	O
in	O
Raven	O
's	O
Bag	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hassel	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
and	O
owned	O
the	O
other	O
Coat	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
Raven	O
's	O
Bag	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
Mistake	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
Indictment	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
therein	O
laid	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	O
Beck	O
,	O
and	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Francis	O
Lamb	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
them	O
both	O
of	O
that	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
affecting	O
Lewis	O
in	O
the	O
second	O
Indictment	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
of	O
that	O
also	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Raven	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White	I-place
Chappel	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
40	O
Hats	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Lanney	I-pers
of	O
Hornsey	B-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
12	O
Geese	O
and	O
14	O
Ducks	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictiment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Dillon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
Looking-Glass	O
,	O
a	O
Bible	O
,	O
and	O
The	O
Whole	O
Duty	O
of	O
Man	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Ray	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Lodger	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Indictment	O
being	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
William	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Name	O
being	O
Robert	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Berrisford	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
6	O
tame	O
Deer	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
for	O
killing	O
6	O
tame	O
Deer	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Godfrey	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Ashby	I-pers
and	O
Martha	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Stuff	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Oliver	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
and	O
cheapen	O
'd	O
some	O
Yard-wide	O
Stuff	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Godfrey	O
bid	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
so	O
low	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Oliver	O
missing	O
the	O
Goods	O
followed	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Stuff	O
under	O
Arm	O
under	O
her	O
Riding-Hood	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Riding-Hood	O
and	O
the	O
piece	O
dropt	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
Asbby	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
would	O
have	O
made	O
it	O
up	O
for	O
12	O
l.	O
saying	O
he	O
could	O
have	O
so	O
much	O
for	O
a	O
Certificate	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
4	O
l.	O
and	O
if	O
they	O
could	O
have	O
made	O
it	O
up	O
12	O
l.	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
Prosecute	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
4	O
l.	O
was	O
brought	O
him	O
by	O
an	O
unknown	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
open	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
brought	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Justice	O
of	O
Peace	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
should	O
do	O
in	O
the	O
Case	O
.	O
Godfrey	O
's	O
Sister	O
deposed	O
that	O
Ashby	O
told	O
her	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
would	O
take	O
6	O
l.	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
40	O
s.	O
a-piece	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
carried	O
and	O
put	O
into	O
his	O
own	O
Hand	O
without	O
taking	O
any	O
Notice	O
,	O
or	O
saying	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
thinking	O
by	O
that	O
means	O
there	O
could	O
be	O
no	O
further	O
trouble	O
,	O
carried	O
4	O
l.	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
40	O
s.	O
of	O
her	O
own	O
and	O
40	O
s.	O
of	O
Asbuy	O
's	O
(	O
the	O
other	O
40	O
s.	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
by	O
another	O
)	O
but	O
finding	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
deceived	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
had	O
her	O
Money	O
again	O
.	O
Godfrey	O
and	O
Ashby	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
Godfrey	O
and	O
Smith	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Ashby	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Delmee	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harwood	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Witherly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
at	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
former	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Hewet	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
26	O
Yards	O
of	O
Hair	O
and	O
Worsted	O
Stuff	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Lewis	B-pers
Cattinoe	I-pers
;	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
Childbed	O
Linnen	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	O
Hewet	O
;	O
and	O
Mary	O
Witherly	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
staple	O
was	O
forc	O
'd	O
off	O
and	O
26	O
yards	O
off	O
Plush	O
cut	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Loom	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Linnen	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
His	O
Brother	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Leach	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
Delmee	O
,	O
Harwood	O
,	O
and	O
himself	O
coming	O
down	O
Monmouth	B-place
Street	I-place
in	I-place
Spittle	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
no	O
Light	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Street-Door	O
being	O
open	O
,	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
broke	O
the	O
Staple	O
of	O
the	O
Lock	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
Mary	O
Witherly	O
in	O
Southwark	O
to	O
sell	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
and	O
had	O
sold	O
some	O
Goods	O
before	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Hat	O
was	O
found	O
on	O
Harwood	O
's	O
Head	O
and	O
produced	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
Delmee	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
Harwood	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Hat	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
Leacb	O
;	O
and	O
Witherly	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
own	O
House	O
,	O
as	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
but	O
an	O
Inmate	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
charg	O
'd	O
upon	O
Witherly	O
to	O
arise	O
in	O
Surry	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Delmee	O
and	O
Harwood	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
Delmee	O
and	O
Harwood	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Upham	I-pers
,	O
between	O
6	O
and	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
a	O
Hat	O
a	O
Callicoe	O
Quilt	O
,	O
two	O
Coats	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	O
Witherly	O
for	O
receiving	O
them	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Chamber	O
Door	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Harwood	O
pawn	O
'd	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Coats	O
for	O
a	O
Crown	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Lee	O
in	O
Bisbopsgate	O
street	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
and	O
sworn	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
fix	O
the	O
Burglary	O
on	O
him	O
,	O
nor	O
to	O
affect	O
the	O
others	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Harwood	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Delmee	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Witheryl	I-pers
were	O
again	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Blak	O
Callimancoe	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
;	O
And	O
Witherly	O
as	O
Accessory	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Callimancoe	O
which	O
was	O
just	O
come	O
from	O
the	O
Hot-Pressers	O
;	O
that	O
Henry	O
Leach	O
being	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
John	O
Delmee	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
:	O
whereupon	O
he	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
and	O
a	O
Constable	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
search	O
after	O
Delmee	O
and	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Callimancoe	O
over	O
the	O
Bed	O
's	O
Tester	O
;	O
that	O
Witherly	O
had	O
slipt	O
her	O
Gown	O
on	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
and	O
another	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
finding	O
Delmee	O
in	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
's	O
Tester	O
.	O
Henry	O
Leach	O
deposed	O
that	O
Delmee	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
against	O
Witherley	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Delmee	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
But	O
he	O
died	O
in	O
Newgate	O
on	O
Sunday	O
,	O
so	O
could	O
not	O
receive	O
Sentence	O
with	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Black	O
Mare	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Graveny	I-pers
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pursel	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Love	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
on	O
his	O
Right	O
Side	O
near	O
his	O
Pap	O
with	O
a	O
Drawn	O
Sword	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Breadth	O
of	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
three	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Vaughan	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
House	O
(	O
a	O
Punch	O
House	O
in	O
Leicester-Fields	B-place
)	O
with	O
two	O
of	O
his	O
Countrymen	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
some	O
Fine	O
Ale	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
complained	O
the	O
Place	O
was	O
too	O
Hazy	O
and	O
Thick	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
put	O
up	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Sashes	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
going	O
by	O
,	O
said	O
there	O
goes	O
Long	O
Legs	O
,	O
(	O
or	O
Long	O
Shanks	O
)	O
call	O
'd	O
after	O
him	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
complemented	O
the	O
Deceased	O
upon	O
his	O
coming	O
from	O
Ireland	O
,	O
who	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
excused	O
himself	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
of	O
Burgundy	O
;	O
that	O
after	O
some	O
Discourse	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
the	O
Deceased	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
have	O
10	O
l.	O
nay	O
20	O
,	O
30	O
,	O
or	O
40	O
l.	O
of	O
a	O
Laceman	O
,	O
for	O
setting	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
wonder	O
'd	O
that	O
any	O
Man	O
should	O
offer	O
so	O
much	O
Money	O
for	O
him	O
who	O
intended	O
to	O
pay	O
all	O
Men	O
very	O
honestly	O
;	O
and	O
especially	O
that	O
the	O
Laceman	O
should	O
,	O
since	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
not	O
owe	O
him	O
above	O
22	O
l.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
Deceased	O
he	O
would	O
speak	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
his	O
Pipe	O
in	O
his	O
Mouth	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
talk	O
'd	O
together	O
;	O
that	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
after	O
Mr.	O
Mullins	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
Clashing	O
of	O
Swords	O
is	O
that	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
their	O
Swords	O
Drawn	O
,	O
battering	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
led	O
the	O
Deceased	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
wounded	O
,	O
bled	O
at	O
the	O
Nose	O
and	O
Mouth	O
,	O
fell	O
on	O
his	O
Face	O
and	O
died	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Mullins	O
confirmed	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
only	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
whether	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
I	O
'd	O
speak	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
so	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
followed	O
Vaughan	O
out	O
,	O
saw	O
both	O
Swords	O
drawn	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
One	O
Perry	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
pass	O
'd	O
by	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Deceased	O
were	O
talking	O
together	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
and	O
struck	O
the	O
Pipe	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Mouth	O
with	O
his	O
drawn	O
Sword	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
Deceased	O
drew	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Passes	O
received	O
the	O
Wound	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
the	O
first	O
Push	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
till	O
the	O
Deceased	O
drew	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Du	I-pers
Batt	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
him	O
bleeding	O
at	O
the	O
Mouth	O
and	O
Nose	O
space	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
him	O
conclude	O
that	O
some	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
Lungs	O
was	O
cut	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
died	O
immediately	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Brand	O
,	O
the	O
Laceman	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
enquired	O
of	O
another	O
Person	O
if	O
Mr.	O
Love	O
was	O
come	O
from	O
Ireland	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
do	O
him	O
what	O
service	O
he	O
could	O
:	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
did	O
owe	O
him	O
22	O
l.	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
no	O
Reward	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Flanningen	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
call	O
him	O
in	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
spit	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
parry	O
'd	O
with	O
his	O
Hand	O
and	O
retired	O
,	O
then	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
and	O
retired	O
further	O
till	O
his	O
Breech	O
came	O
against	O
a	O
Post	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Pipe	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Hand	O
,	O
not	O
in	O
his	O
Mouth	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Habbs	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
would	O
have	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
refused	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Coat	O
,	O
swore	O
he	O
should	O
go	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
Spit	O
in	O
his	O
Face	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Morton	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
beat	O
down	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
retire	O
till	O
his	O
Breech	O
came	O
against	O
a	O
Post	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hear	I-pers
,	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Hough	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Tieldall	I-pers
deposed	O
they	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
make	O
several	O
Passes	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
retired	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
against	O
the	O
Post	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Hammilton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Felony	O
,	O
in	O
taking	O
to	O
Wife	O
Ann	B-pers
Burdin	I-pers
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
his	O
first	O
Wife	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Downs	I-pers
being	O
then	O
living	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Marriage	O
was	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
gave	O
his	O
Wife	O
in	O
Marriage	O
to	O
him	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
August	O
1714.	O
and	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
confest	O
he	O
was	O
Married	O
to	O
Ann	O
Burdin	O
at	O
the	B-place
Fleet	I-place
,	O
and	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
accordingly	O
for	O
about	O
10	O
Weeks	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
also	O
owned	O
on	O
his	O
Tryal	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
why	O
he	O
Marryed	O
a	O
Second	O
Wite	O
while	O
his	O
first	O
was	O
living	O
,	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
then	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
another	O
Husband	O
:	O
and	O
being	O
told	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
indicted	O
for	O
his	O
Second	O
's	O
Wife	O
having	O
another	O
Husband	O
,	O
but	O
for	O
Marrying	O
her	O
while	O
his	O
first	O
Wife	O
was	O
living	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
whether	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
,	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
him	O
.	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
liv	O
'd	O
together	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Bed	O
,	O
Bolster	O
,	O
pair	O
of	O
Blankets	O
,	O
Quilt	O
,	O
Chairs	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Birdin	I-pers
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
when	O
she	O
had	O
Married	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
went	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
off	O
all	O
his	O
Goods	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
fix	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Charlesworth	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White	I-place
Chapel	I-place
,	O
Victualler	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
7	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
15	O
Black	O
Hoods	O
,	O
70	O
Ells	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
one	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
Home	O
till	O
9	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
found	O
his	O
Windows	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
gone	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
open	O
'd	O
his	O
Door	O
he	O
saw	O
two	O
Persons	O
rush	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Back	O
Door	O
,	O
that	O
Charlesworth	O
was	O
one	O
,	O
who	O
jumpt	O
over	O
the	O
Wall	O
from	O
the	O
Steps	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Garden	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
ran	O
into	O
the	O
Garden	O
and	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
Wall	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
positive	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
him	O
well	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Rightson	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
fasten	O
up	O
his	O
Windows	O
and	O
Door	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
Key	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
that	O
two	O
Men	O
jumpt	O
over	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
above	O
Stairs	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wheatley	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
dined	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
that	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
Dinner	O
went	O
a-board	O
a-ship	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
till	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
Home	O
they	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
put	O
a	O
Writing	O
into	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
Hand	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
to	O
read	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Rag-Fair	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
about	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
heard	O
somebody	O
cry	O
out	O
Thieves	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
took	O
the	O
Key	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
in	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
two	O
Persons	O
rush	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Back	O
Door	O
and	O
jump	O
over	O
the	O
Wall	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
and	I-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
York	I-pers
corroborated	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Wheatley	O
denyed	O
that	O
they	O
saw	O
a	O
Dog	O
with	O
a	O
Candle	O
and	O
Lanthorn	O
in	O
his	O
Mouth	O
when	O
they	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
pleaded	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
with	O
2	O
other	O
Men	O
went	O
to	O
serve	O
a	O
Rule	O
upon	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
about	O
6	O
a	O
Clock	O
that	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
within	O
they	O
went	O
a	O
little	O
further	O
to	O
serve	O
one	O
upon	O
another	O
Person	O
;	O
and	O
coming	O
back	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Mill	O
Yard	O
as	O
going	O
Home	O
,	O
and	O
serv	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
directly	O
Home	O
with	O
his	O
Friends	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
no	O
more	O
all	O
that	O
Night	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
Dog	O
with	O
them	O
that	O
carried	O
a	O
Lanthorn	O
and	O
Candle	O
in	O
his	O
Mouth	O
to	O
light	O
them	O
along	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
bid	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
look	O
upon	O
the	O
Original	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
and	O
the	O
Original	O
too	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
ask	O
'd	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
Dog	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
answered	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
Dog	O
,	O
my	O
Bitch	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Twinny	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Durban	O
deposed	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
serve	O
the	O
Rule	O
,	O
and	O
confirmed	O
all	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
said	O
concerning	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
staid	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
till	O
10	O
or	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Durham	I-pers
,	O
Mrs.	O
Rud	O
,	O
Bennet	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
being	O
at	O
Home	O
from	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
to	O
10	O
or	O
11	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
It	O
also	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
swore	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
jumpt	O
over	O
the	O
Wall	O
;	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
swore	O
so	O
positively	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
now	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Best	I-pers
.	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
at	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Hats	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dagg	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
about	O
7	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Ale	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
warm	O
'd	O
,	O
saying	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
Physick	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Fire	O
she	O
drank	O
it	O
cold	O
;	O
that	O
while	O
the	O
Girl	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
draw	O
the	O
Drink	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Hats	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
under	O
her	O
Coats	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
down	O
about	O
Eight	O
,	O
and	O
missing	O
his	O
Hats	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
Rosemary-Lane	O
with	O
his	O
best	O
Hat	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
crying	O
,	O
Who	O
will	O
by	O
a	O
New	O
Hat	O
?	O
and	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
he	O
would	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
which	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Corder	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
22	O
Car	O
.	O
2.	O
for	O
stealing	O
22	O
Yards	O
of	O
Broad	O
Cloth	O
,	O
from	O
Racks	O
and	O
Tenters	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Cloth	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
Tenters	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
that	O
Night	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
and	O
his	O
Son	O
coming	O
over	O
the	O
Fields	O
about	O
two	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
saw	O
a	O
Boy	O
very	O
busie	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
Field	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
same	O
Field	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Ditch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Cloth	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Man	O
examin	O
'd	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
that	O
two	O
Men	O
had	O
beat	O
and	O
abused	O
him	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
and	O
thrown	O
him	O
into	O
that	O
Ditch	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
same	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Several	O
Persons	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Aunt	O
being	O
ill	O
,	O
sent	O
him	O
to	O
call	O
her	O
to	O
her	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
that	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Field	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Way	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Martin	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Rolls	B-place
Liberty	I-place
in	O
the	O
Country	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Guy	B-pers
Currier	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
,	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White	I-place
Chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Callicoe	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Quilted	O
Petticoat	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Tidman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Lawrence	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
by	O
her	O
Daughter	O
Mrs.	O
Tidman	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
away	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
Back	O
in	O
Rosemary	O
Lane	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
them	O
only	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
Friend	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
returning	O
home	O
with	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
Wife	O
of	O
Humphrey	O
,	O
alias	O
Elizabeth	O
Jones	O
Spinster	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
4	O
Stuff	O
Curtains	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
14	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Candlestick	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
Humphrey	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
handsomly	O
drest	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
Lodging	O
,	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Yates	O
told	O
him	O
they	O
had	O
one	O
to	O
let	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
ready	O
till	O
Tuesday	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
a	O
great	O
Detriment	O
to	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
one	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
engaged	O
for	O
a	O
Friend	O
for	O
10	O
l.	O
who	O
was	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
home	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
the	O
Officers	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
it	O
was	O
agreed	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
come	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
brought	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
him	O
as	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
who	O
appeared	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
mean	O
and	O
draggled	O
Condition	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
lockt	O
her	O
Doors	O
and	O
took	O
what	O
care	O
she	O
could	O
of	O
her	O
House	O
that	O
Night	O
;	O
but	O
so	O
soon	O
as	O
her	O
Husband	O
was	O
up	O
and	O
gone	O
to	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
:	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
about	O
three	O
Weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
she	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Dodsworth	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hampstead	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Mary	B-pers
Hicks	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
3	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
a	O
Steel	O
Box	O
,	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
1	O
Shilling	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
.	O
that	O
it	O
being	O
too	O
late	O
for	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
she	O
and	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Daughter	O
at	O
London	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Poole	O
over	O
the	O
Fields	O
from	O
Hampstead	O
towards	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
Haverstock	O
Hill	O
,	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
taking	O
leave	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
by	O
from	O
London	O
;	O
and	O
knowing	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Hampstead	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
stay	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
taking	O
leave	O
of	O
her	O
Friend	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
be	O
glad	O
of	O
his	O
Company	O
;	O
that	O
her	O
Friend	O
gave	O
her	O
her	O
Rings	O
,	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
a	O
Shilling	O
for	O
fear	O
she	O
should	O
meet	O
with	O
any	O
Rogues	O
going	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
most	O
dangerous	O
Way	O
;	O
having	O
taken	O
leave	O
of	O
their	O
Friend	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
Hampstead	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
they	O
came	O
along	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
wonder	O
'd	O
their	O
Friend	O
would	O
venture	O
over	O
those	O
Fields	O
by	O
her	O
self	O
so	O
late	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
dangerous	O
;	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
reply	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
fear	O
'd	O
nothing	O
,	O
having	O
left	O
her	O
Money	O
and	O
Rings	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
least	O
she	O
should	O
meet	O
with	O
any	O
Rogues	O
:	O
That	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
Hampstead	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
his	O
Service	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
West-End	O
,	O
saying	O
it	O
was	O
dangerous	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Father	O
and	O
Mother	O
were	O
robb	O
'd	O
there	O
:	O
She	O
thank	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
him	O
so	O
much	O
trouble	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Friend	O
in	O
the	O
Town	O
who	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
thither	O
,	O
so	O
parted	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Dring	O
's	O
a	O
Taylor	O
's	O
and	O
staid	O
there	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
;	O
but	O
her	O
Friend	O
she	O
expected	O
was	O
gone	O
before	O
she	O
came	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Chandlers	O
Shop	O
and	O
staid	O
there	O
a	O
little	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
going	B-place
to	I-place
West	I-place
End	I-place
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
offer	O
'd	O
his	O
Service	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
needs	O
wait	O
upon	O
them	O
to	O
West	O
End	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
she	O
used	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Words	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
prevent	O
his	O
giving	O
himself	O
that	O
trouble	O
:	O
that	O
as	O
they	O
went	O
along	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
only	O
the	O
Posts	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
a	O
little	O
further	O
he	O
gave	O
a	O
great	O
Hem	O
,	O
Hawk	O
'd	O
and	O
Spit	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
two	O
Men	O
appear	O
'd	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
Mask	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
took	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Arm	O
,	O
knockt	O
her	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Ditch	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
Rings	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Rings	O
from	O
off	O
her	O
Finger	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Pocket	O
:	O
That	O
they	O
offer	O
'd	O
not	O
to	O
touch	O
Miss	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
who	O
upon	O
this	O
ran	O
to	O
West	O
End	O
to	O
call	O
some	O
to	O
her	O
Assistance	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
,	O
but	O
speak	O
to	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
civil	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
West	O
End	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
him	O
secur	O
'd	O
,	O
judging	O
that	O
this	O
was	O
a	O
Contrivance	O
of	O
his	O
to	O
robb	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
he	O
was	O
had	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
of	O
Peace	O
;	O
where	O
he	O
declar	O
'd	O
that	O
John	O
Harris	O
and	O
Thomas	O
Lewis	O
were	O
the	O
Persons	O
who	O
committed	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
them	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
had	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Pool	O
's	O
Money	O
and	O
Rings	O
about	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Daughter	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
Company	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
acknowledged	O
it	O
with	O
this	O
Variation	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
desire	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
call	O
on	O
her	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Dring	O
's	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
meeting	O
with	O
Harris	O
and	O
Lewis	O
,	O
who	O
ask	O
'd	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
,	O
(	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
otherways	O
engaged	O
him	O
,	O
)	O
he	O
told	O
them	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
safe	O
home	O
to	O
West	O
End	O
,	O
she	O
having	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Pool	O
's	O
Money	O
and	O
Rings	O
about	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
communicate	O
it	O
with	O
any	O
ill	O
Intention	O
,	O
but	O
carelesly	O
and	O
innocently	O
:	O
He	O
called	O
several	O
people	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
an	O
Honest	O
Industrous	O
young	O
Man	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Halliday	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
180	O
Yards	O
of	O
Serge	O
value	O
12	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
Samuel	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
's	O
Warehouse	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
buying	O
Goods	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
lookt	O
on	O
some	O
Long	O
Ells	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
fix	O
'd	O
upon	O
8	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
agreed	O
to	O
pay	O
12	O
l.	O
for	O
them	O
on	O
delivery	O
;	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Berry	O
sent	O
a	O
Porter	O
with	O
them	O
and	O
a	O
Receipt	O
for	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Directions	O
,	O
ordering	O
the	O
Porter	O
not	O
to	O
leave	O
the	O
Goods	O
without	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
brought	O
a	O
Receipt	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Porter	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
spoke	O
to	O
a	O
Woman	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
Bag	O
of	O
Money	O
;	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
whether	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
it	O
all	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
Yes	O
;	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
pay	O
another	O
Man	O
some	O
Money	O
;	O
so	O
the	O
Porter	O
left	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Bag	O
of	O
Money	O
to	O
the	O
Alehouse	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
there	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
any	O
Boy	O
to	O
go	O
of	O
an	O
Errand	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
had	O
none	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
laid	O
the	O
Bag	O
of	O
Money	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
it	O
under	O
the	O
Porter	O
's	O
care	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
the	O
other	O
Man	O
himself	O
:	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
never	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Porter	O
being	O
tired	O
with	O
waiting	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Bag	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
he	O
left	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Woman	O
who	O
reach	O
'd	O
him	O
the	O
Bag	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
who	O
kept	O
the	O
House	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
no	O
Lodger	O
;	O
however	O
the	O
porter	O
staid	O
there	O
till	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
his	O
Master	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Bag	O
of	O
Money	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
,	O
prov	O
'd	O
only	O
some	O
Copper	O
Half-pence	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
Receipt	O
from	O
the	O
porter	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Ale-house	O
carryed	O
him	O
to	O
an	O
Empty	O
House	O
in	O
Red-Lyon-Square	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
bring	O
the	O
next	O
Goods	O
theither	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
first	O
deny	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
;	O
then	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
paid	O
the	O
porter	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
produc	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Berry	O
's	O
Receipt	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
Contradicted	O
by	O
the	O
porter	O
;	O
he	O
also	O
pleaded	O
that	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
Felony	O
;	O
but	O
a	O
Felonious	O
Intent	O
plainly	O
appearing	O
from	O
the	O
beginning	O
to	O
the	O
end	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
again	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
95	O
Yards	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
16	O
yards	O
of	O
printed	O
Collicoe	O
,	O
39	O
yards	O
of	O
Irish	O
Linnen	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Baylis	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
120	O
Yards	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
14	O
s.	O
20	O
Ells	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
notorious	O
Offender	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
cheated	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
of	O
their	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
amounting	O
to	O
Fellony	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
these	O
two	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Evan	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Horton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
6	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Chain	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
27	O
Moidores	O
,	O
30	O
Carolus	O
's	O
,	O
20	O
Guineas	O
and	O
14	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
Horton	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
hired	O
Servant	O
at	O
8	O
l.	O
per	O
An	O
.	O
and	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
half	O
a	O
Year	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
having	O
lost	O
several	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
good	O
reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
turn	O
'd	O
him	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
come	O
there	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
order	O
'd	O
his	O
Servants	O
not	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
in	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
going	O
the	O
Night	O
aforesaid	O
to	O
his	O
Apprentice	O
's	O
Uncle	O
's	O
Funeral	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
;	O
told	O
his	O
Daughter	O
and	O
Servant	O
that	O
the	O
Burying	O
was	O
just	O
a	O
going	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Daughter	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
lock	O
'd	O
her	O
Father	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
Maid	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Burying	O
,	O
leaving	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
back	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
and	O
had	O
lockt	O
the	O
Door	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
forc	O
'd	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
Smith	O
to	O
break	O
it	O
open	O
to	O
get	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Door	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Plate	O
and	O
Goods	O
thrown	O
about	O
the	O
Room	O
:	O
that	O
the	O
23d	O
about	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
being	O
extravagant	O
at	O
Barnet	O
,	O
and	O
shewing	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Bell-man	O
told	O
the	O
Post-master	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
who	O
having	O
heard	O
of	O
a	O
Robbery	O
committed	O
in	O
Grubstreet	B-place
,	O
sent	O
a	O
Boy	O
with	O
a	O
Horn	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
secured	O
the	O
prisoner	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
;	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
denied	O
every	O
particular	O
but	O
his	O
being	O
at	O
Barnet	O
:	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
very	O
plain	O
and	O
fully	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Roger	B-pers
Cane	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
6	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
6	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shop	O
the	O
Night	O
aforesaid	O
about	O
7	O
a	O
Clock	O
.	O
Edward	O
Lloyd	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
himself	O
coming	O
down	O
East-Smithfield	B-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
unbolted	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
(	O
the	O
Evidence	O
)	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
Woman	O
in	O
Houndsditch	B-place
for	O
6	O
s.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
with	O
Phebe	B-pers
Grisby	I-pers
,	O
He	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Raynard	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
and	O
a	O
Tobacco-Box	O
;	O
and	O
Grisby	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Assaulted	O
by	O
two	O
Men	O
in	O
Rosemary-Lane	B-place
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
the	O
Night	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
and	O
thrown	O
down	O
and	O
tumbled	O
in	O
the	O
Dirt	O
;	O
and	O
lost	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
Handkerchief	O
and	O
Tobacco-Box	O
.	O
Edw	O
.	O
Lloyd	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
himself	O
were	O
together	O
in	O
Rosemary-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
knockt	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
carry	O
'd	O
the	O
Hat	O
to	O
Grishy	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
where	O
they	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
Sold	O
it	O
for	O
them	O
for	O
20d	O
.	O
which	O
they	O
divided	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
to	O
Grisby	O
.	O
They	O
both	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
Grishy	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
against	O
them	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Cane	O
Death	O
.	O
Grisby	O
Transportation	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
9	O
Shirts	O
and	O
7	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
Phebe	O
Grisby	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
Edward	O
Lloyd	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
himself	O
committed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
Grisby	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
none	O
to	O
corroborate	O
Lloyd	O
's	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Grisby	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Cane	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Charnock	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Lawrence	I-place
Jury	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Fackney	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Hilted	O
Sword	O
,	O
9	O
Ells	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
20	O
Yards	O
of	O
Linnen	O
,	O
3	O
Moidores	O
,	O
5	O
Carolus	O
's	O
and	O
80	O
Guineas	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
113l	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
July	O
1718	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
that	O
he	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
late	O
Hours	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
particularly	O
the	O
Saturday	O
before	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
come	O
Home	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Master	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
behave	O
himself	O
better	O
he	O
must	O
part	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
15th	O
about	O
Noon	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
leaving	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
Home	O
,	O
and	O
order	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
receive	O
a	O
Bill	O
of	O
6	O
l.	O
that	O
coming	O
home	O
about	O
Two	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
his	O
Door	O
shut	O
,	O
concluded	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
receive	O
the	O
Bill	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
Spital	O
Fields	O
,	O
and	O
return	O
'd	O
about	O
6	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
his	O
Doors	O
Still	O
fast	O
,	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Box	O
Maker	O
to	O
open	O
his	O
Compting	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
in	O
found	O
his	O
Desk	O
broke	O
open	O
and	O
the	O
particulars	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
gone	O
;	O
that	O
upon	O
searching	O
after	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Ax-Inn	O
in	O
Aldermanbury	O
he	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
with	O
a	O
loose	O
Woman	O
to	O
Piccadilly	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
Constable	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
found	O
him	O
on	O
a	O
Bed	O
in	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
with	O
213	O
l.	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
all	O
but	O
10	O
or	O
12	O
s.	O
of	O
it	O
again	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
Bank	O
Note	O
of	O
100	O
l	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Desk	O
and	O
received	O
the	O
Money	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
up	O
the	O
Sum	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
jump	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
found	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
till	O
of	O
late	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
none	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hatchet	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Stephen	I-place
Coleman	I-place
street	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
6	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
32	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Steward	B-pers
Dormer	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Humphrey	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
granted	O
her	O
a	O
Coppy	O
of	O
her	O
Indictment	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
and	O
Roger	B-pers
King	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
7	O
Hats	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
7	O
Hats	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
a	O
Clock	O
the	O
Night	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
bolted	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
himself	O
committed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
that	O
King	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
Harvey	O
took	O
the	O
Hats	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
sold	O
them	O
for	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
divided	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Buglary	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
them	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Looking	O
Glass	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Brabant	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Glass	O
was	O
hung	O
up	O
at	O
the	O
Shop	O
Window	O
for	O
Sale	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
by	O
,	O
took	O
it	O
down	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
seen	O
,	O
was	O
follow	O
'd	O
and	O
taken	O
with	O
it	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Man	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
desiring	O
him	O
to	O
hold	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
drunk	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Boots	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Slaughter	I-pers
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Confession	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Hester	B-pers
Flyn	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Hugh	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
no	O
steal	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Clarkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Betsworth	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pickt	O
him	O
up	O
being	O
in	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
whether	O
he	O
wanted	O
a	O
Lodging	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Money	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
Bed	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
rose	O
he	O
mist	O
his	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
met	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
fighting	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
dirty	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
clean	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
him	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
her	O
Friends	O
scrap	O
'd	O
and	O
wash	O
'd	O
his	O
Clothes	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
him	O
as	O
clean	O
as	O
they	O
could	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
them	O
a	O
Shilling	O
to	O
fetch	O
some	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
his	O
Change	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
saw	O
no	O
other	O
Money	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
Change	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Jordan	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
formerly	O
Convicted	O
for	O
Subornation	O
of	O
Perjury	O
,	O
was	O
called	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
and	O
received	O
the	O
following	O
Judgment	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
should	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
with	O
the	O
Inscription	O
of	O
his	O
Crime	O
fasten	O
'd	O
over	O
his	O
Head	O
;	O
pay	O
a	O
Fine	O
of	O
30	O
Marks	O
,	O
suffer	O
three	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
,	O
and	O
stand	O
Committed	O
till	O
he	O
pay	O
his	O
Fine	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
followith	O
;	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
5.	O
Even	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Charnock	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Shephard	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Trippuck	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Roger	B-pers
Cane	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
2.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pursel	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Hammilton	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
,	O
25.	O
John	B-pers
Layfield	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Hinchman	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Brest	I-pers
,	O
Ralph	B-pers
Finley	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Goodchild	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Halliday	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Ashby	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hutchins	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Raven	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harwood	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Best	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Lanney	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
,	O
Martin	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
Phebe	B-pers
Grisby	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
David	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Jordan	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
formerly	O
Convicted	O
for	O
Subornation	O
of	O
Perjury	O
,	O
was	O
called	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
and	O
received	O
the	O
following	O
Judgment	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
should	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
with	O
the	O
Inscription	O
of	O
his	O
Crime	O
fasten	O
'd	O
over	O
his	O
Head	O
;	O
pay	O
a	O
Fine	O
of	O
30	O
Marks	O
,	O
suffer	O
three	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
,	O
and	O
stand	O
Committed	O
till	O
he	O
pay	O
his	O
Fine	O
.	O
ADVERTISMENT	O
.	O
A	O
Water	O
that	O
perfectly	O
cures	O
the	O
Itch	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
Itching	O
Humour	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
,	O
without	O
necessity	O
of	O
Purging	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
dangerous	O
Use	O
of	O
Mercury	O
,	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
is	O
only	O
Prepared	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
A	O
.	O
Drawing	O
Chymist	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
and	O
Hall	O
in	O
George	O
Court	O
in	O
St.	O
John	O
's	O
Leve	O
by	O
Hisk	O
's	O
Hall	O
near	O
West-Southfield	O
.	O
Where	O
also	O
may	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
the	O
best	O
Spirits	O
of	O
Scurvy-Gress	O
,	O
by	O
Wholesale	O
or	O
Retale	O
at	O
8	O
d.	O
Bottle.A	O
most	O
effectual	O
Remedy	O
for	O
the	O
Violent	O
.	O
Pain	O
in	O
the	O
Teeth	O
,	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
Also	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Remedy	O
for	O
preserving	O
the	O
Teeth	O
and	O
clearing	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
,	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
The	O
following	O
Books	O
are	O
given	O
Gratis	O
.	O
1st	O
,	O
THE	O
Practical	O
Scheme	O
of	O
the	O
Secret	O
Disease	O
and	O
Broken	O
Constitutions	O
,	O
by	O
Fast	O
Living	O
,	O
Former	O
ill	O
Cures	O
,	O
Salivations	O
and	O
Mercury	O
-	O
2ly	O
.	O
The	O
New	O
System	O
of	O
the	O
GOUT	O
and	O
Rheumatism	O
,	O
drawn	O
from	O
Reason	O
,	O
Anatomical	O
Observations	O
and	O
Experience	O
.	O
-	O
3ly	O
,	O
A	O
Rational	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Cause	O
,	O
Nature	O
,	O
and	O
Cure	O
of	O
WEAKNESSES	O
usually	O
attending	O
Persons	O
after	O
former	O
Cures	O
,	O
Over-strainings	O
,	O
Self-Abuses	O
,	O
Hard	O
Labours	O
,	O
Miscarriages	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Wherein	O
is	O
given	O
a	O
full	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
horrid	O
Nature	O
,	O
and	O
most	O
miserable	O
Consequences	O
of	O
Self-Abuses	O
in	O
particular	O
.	O
These	O
Books	O
(	O
all	O
New	O
Editions	O
)	O
are	O
given	O
Gratis	O
Up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
ANODYNE	O
.	O
NECK	O
-	O
LACE	O
,	O
without	O
Temple	O
Bar	O
.	O
At	O
Mr.	O
Coupers	O
Toy	O
shop	O
the	O
Cornor	O
of	O
Charles	O
Court	O
by	O
Hungersord-Marbet	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
And	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Garraway	O
's	O
Shop	O
at	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms	O
at	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange-Gate	O
next	O
Cornhill	O
.	O
Some	O
BOOKS	O
printed	O
for	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
Edmrad	O
Park	O
as	O
the	O
Bible	O
and	O
Crown	O
is	O
Lombard	O
Street	O
,	O
near	O
Stocks-Market	O
.	O
THE	O
London	O
New	O
Method	O
and	O
Art	O
of	O
Teaching	O
Children	O
to	O
Spell	O
and	O
Read	O
;	O
so	O
as	O
they	O
may	O
,	O
without	O
the	O
Help	O
of	O
any	O
other	O
Books	O
,	O
read	O
the	O
Bible	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
twelve	O
Months	O
.	O
Note	O
,	O
This	O
Way	O
of	O
Teaching	O
is	O
approved	O
by	O
most	O
School	O
Masters	O
as	O
the	O
best	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
6	O
d.	O
with	O
great	O
Allowance	O
to	O
those	O
who	O
sell	O
or	O
give	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
Note	O
,	O
There	O
are	O
some	O
printed	O
on	O
Fine	O
Paper	O
,	O
bound	O
up	O
with	O
Cuts	O
.	O
pr	O
.	O
8	O
d.	O
For	O
the	O
Compleating	O
of	O
Psalmody	O
.	O
The	O
Devout	O
Singer	O
's	O
Guide	O
;	O
containing	O
all	O
the	O
Common	O
Tunes	O
now	O
in	O
Use	O
,	O
with	O
Select	O
Portions	O
of	O
the	O
psalms	O
adapted	O
to	O
each	O
Tune	O
,	O
and	O
Rules	O
for	O
singing	O
Treble	O
and	O
Bass	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
A	O
Table	O
shevang	O
at	O
one	O
View	O
what	O
Psalms	O
and	O
Hymns	O
are	O
proper	O
to	O
each	O
Tune	O
both	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Vertion	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Hopkins	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Sandbold	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
New	O
Version	O
of	O
Dr.	O
Brady	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Tare	O
And	O
Directions	O
for	O
Parish	O
Clerks	O
in	O
the	O
Choice	O
of	O
proper	O
Psalms	O
on	O
most	O
Occasions	O
.	O
B	O
,	O
S	O
Sheson	O
;	O
and	O
Recommended	O
by	O
P.	O
Johnson	O
,	O
D.	O
Warner	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Singing-Masters	O
.	O
The	O
Fourth	O
Edition	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
Five	O
Tones	O
,	O
containing	O
their	O
Causm	O
,	O
Medium	O
and	O
Baffus	O
,	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
former	O
Editions	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
1	O
s.	O
Josop	O
's	O
Fables	O
,	O
with	O
Morals	O
and	O
Reflection	O
,	O
as	O
improved	O
by	O
Sir	O
Roger	O
L'Estrange	O
,	O
done	O
into	O
Variety	O
of	O
English	O
Verse	O
.	O
Illustrated	O
with	O
Cuts	O
curiously	O
engrav	O
'd	O
on	O
Copper	O
Plates	O
.	O
Very	O
useful	O
to	O
Divert	O
and	O
last	O
Young	O
Gentlemen	O
and	O
Ladies	O
in	O
the	O
Conduct	O
of	O
Human	O
Life	O
.	O
The	O
Fourth	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Arithmetick	O
made	O
easie	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
New	O
Method	O
now	O
taught	O
and	O
practis	O
'd	O
in	O
London	O
.	O
Where	O
in	O
the	O
Rules	O
of	O
that	O
necessary	O
Art	O
are	O
briefly	O
explain	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
illustrated	O
with	O
such	O
familiar	O
Examples	O
as	O
may	O
suit	O
the	O
meanest	O
Capacity	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
desire	O
to	O
learn	O
it	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
a	O
Succinct	O
Treatise	O
of	O
Decimal	O
Fractions	O
,	O
with	O
Compleat	O
Tables	O
,	O
Rules	O
,	O
and	O
Examples	O
demonstrating	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
like	O
not	O
extant	O
in	O
any	O
other	O
Treatise	O
of	O
this	O
Nature	O
.	O
The	O
Fourth	O
Edition	O
.	O
By	O
Jobes	O
Copeland	O
,	O
Writing-Master	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
1	O
s.	O
A	O
Guide	O
to	O
English	O
Juries	O
:	O
Setting	O
forth	O
their	O
Antiquity	O
,	O
Power	O
and	O
Duty	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Common	O
Law	O
and	O
Second	O
With	O
a	O
Table	O
.	O
By	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
Quality	O
.	O
Also	O
a	O
Letter	O
to	O
the	O
Author	O
upon	O
the	O
same	O
Subject	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
Orders	O
,	O
By	O
Laws	O
,	O
and	O
Ordinances	O
for	O
the	O
good	O
Government	O
and	O
Regulating	O
of	O
the	O
Persons	O
Licensed	O
to	O
Keep	O
and	O
Drive	O
Hickney-Coaches	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
Reaters	O
and	O
Drivers	O
.	O
Made	O
,	O
Publish	O
'd	O
and	O
Declar	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Commissioners	O
;	O
and	O
Allowed	O
and	O
Approved	O
by	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chancellor	O
and	O
Judges	O
as	O
the	O
Law	O
directs	O
.	O
Price	O
3	O
d.	O
Books	O
Printed	O
for	O
Daniel	O
Prate	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Bible	O
against	O
York-Buildings	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
A	O
Banquet	O
for	O
Gentlemen	O
and	O
Ladies	O
,	O
conducting	O
of	O
Nine	O
Cornical	O
Novels	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
The	O
Treachesons	O
Friend	O
.	O
The	O
prodigal	O
Reclaimed	O
.	O
The	O
Jealous	O
Husband	O
,	O
or	O
Virgimity	O
restored	O
.	O
The	O
Friendly	O
Cheat	O
.	O
The	O
Unfortunate	O
Lover	O
.	O
Jealousie	O
without	O
a	O
Cause	O
.	O
The	O
Cruel	O
Mother	O
.	O
The	O
Cuckold	O
turn	O
'd	O
Confessor	O
.	O
The	O
Biochanalians	O
;	O
intermix	O
'd	O
with	O
many	O
Pleasant	O
and	O
Delightful	O
Tales	O
and	O
Stories	O
.	O
The	O
Fifth	O
Edition	O
.	O
The	O
Universal	O
Jester	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
A	O
Compleat	O
Book	O
of	O
Jests	O
.	O
Containing	O
A	O
pleasant	O
Variety	O
of	O
English	O
Jests	O
,	O
Irish	O
Jests	O
,	O
Oxford	O
Jests	O
,	O
Cambridge	O
Jests	O
,	O
Coffee-House	O
lefts	O
,	O
Novels	O
,	O
Bulls	O
,	O
Stories	O
,	O
Jokes	O
,	O
and	O
Pass	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
Hell	O
in	O
an	O
Uproar	O
,	O
or	O
,	O
A	O
Scuffle	O
between	O
the	O
Lawyers	O
and	O
Physicians	O
for	O
Superiority	O
.	O
A	O
Satyr	O
.	O
Female	O
Policy	O
detected	O
;	O
or	O
the	O
Art	O
of	O
a	O
Designing	O
Woman	O
laid	O
open	O
:	O
By	O
the	O
Author	O
of	O
the	O
London	O
Spy	O
,	O
and	O
Trip	O
to	O
Jsrusics	O
:	O
Treating	O
1.	O
of	O
their	O
Allurements	O
,	O
inconstancy	O
,	O
Love	O
,	O
Revenge	O
,	O
Pride	O
and	O
Ingratitude	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
A	O
Pleasant	O
and	O
Profitable	O
Discourse	O
in	O
defence	O
of	O
Married	O
Men	O
,	O
against	O
Perish	O
,	O
Fretful	O
,	O
Scolding	O
Wives	O
;	O
with	O
several	O
notable	O
Examples	O
of	O
the	O
Mischiefs	O
and	O
Miseries	O
which	O
have	O
attended	O
their	O
Last	O
,	O
and	O
Pride	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
A	O
True	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
Virtuous	O
Woman	O
,	O
or	O
Wife	O
indeed	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
a	O
Poetical	O
description	O
of	O
a	O
Widow	O
,	O
Wife	O
and	O
Maid	O
.	O
The	O
Accomplish	O
'd	O
Ladies	O
Delight	O
,	O
in	O
Preserving	O
,	O
Physick	O
,	O
Beautifying	O
,	O
Cookery	O
and	O
Gardening	O
:	O
Containing	O
,	O
1	O
.	O
The	O
Art	O
of	O
Preserving	O
and	O
Candying	O
Fruits	O
and	O
Flowers	O
,	O
and	O
making	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
Conserves	O
,	O
Syrups	O
,	O
Jesties	O
and	O
Pickles	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
The	O
Physical	O
Cabinet	O
,	O
or	O
excellent	O
Receipts	O
in	O
Physics	O
and	O
Chyrurgery	O
;	O
also	O
some	O
new	O
Receipts	O
relating	O
to	O
the	O
Fair	O
Sex	O
,	O
Whereby	O
they	O
may	O
be	O
riskly	O
furnished	O
with	O
all	O
manner	O
of	O
Beautifying	O
Waters	O
to	O
add	O
loveliness	O
to	O
the	O
Face	O
and	O
Body	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
The	O
Compleat	O
Cook	O
's	O
Guide	O
,	O
or	O
Directions	O
for	O
Dressing	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
Flesh	O
,	O
Fowl	O
,	O
and	O
Faith	O
after	O
the	O
newest	O
fashion	O
now	O
in	O
use	O
at	O
the	O
British	O
Court	O
;	O
with	O
the	O
making	O
Sawees	O
for	O
Pyes	O
,	O
Pasteries	O
,	O
Tarts	O
,	O
Custards	O
.	O
4	O
.	O
The	O
Female	O
Angler	O
,	O
Instructing	O
Ladies	O
and	O
others	O
in	O
the	O
various	O
methods	O
of	O
taking	O
all	O
manner	O
of	O
Fish	O
in	O
the	O
Fish-ponds	O
or	O
Rivers	O
.	O
5	O
.	O
The	O
Ladies	O
Diversion	O
in	O
her	O
Garden	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
Compleat	O
Florist	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Nature	O
and	O
Use	O
of	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
Plants	O
and	O
Flowers	O
.	O
The	O
Teath	O
Edition	O
Enlarg	O
'd	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
same	O
Place	O
any	O
Chapmen	O
may	O
be	O
Furnished	O
with	O
all	O
sorce	O
of	O
Almanec	O
for	O
the	O
Year	O
1720	O
.	O
