TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
,	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
27th	O
,	O
28th	O
and	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
1720	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Sixth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
6	O
May	O
1720	O
.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
GEORGE	B-pers
THOROLD	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
and	O
Baronet	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
Names	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Keeble	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Brookhouse	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Littlefield	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Terret	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Whitehorn	I-pers
,	O
Philip	B-pers
Colebank	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Barnwell	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dowse	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wilford	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Giles	B-pers
Riddle	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bavan	I-pers
,	O
Jeremy	B-pers
Lewin	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Curtis	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Kendrick	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Partridge	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Lilley	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
Aaron	B-pers
Gibbs	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Salisbury	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Wheely	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
went	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Eastcheap	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
70	O
Pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Job	B-pers
Wicks	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Job	O
Wicks	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
;	O
and	O
his	O
fellow	O
Servant	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
perceiving	O
his	O
Pocket	O
to	O
stick	O
out	O
,	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
Paper	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
in	O
it	O
worth	O
about	O
18	O
d.	O
which	O
he	O
owned	O
to	O
him	O
was	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Cellar	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
also	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
confest	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
Tobacco	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
The	O
said	O
Paper	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
's	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bermundas	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Hillior	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisner	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Shop	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Hat	O
of	O
about	O
10	O
s.	O
price	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
shewed	O
several	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
they	O
agreed	O
for	O
one	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
stop	O
into	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
.	O
and	O
if	O
the	O
Coach	O
was	O
not	O
gone	O
she	O
would	O
come	O
and	O
fetch	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
but	O
he	O
perceiving	O
she	O
could	O
hardly	O
walk	O
fetcht	O
her	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Hat	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
fell	O
from	O
between	O
her	O
Legs	O
.	O
Another	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
take	O
the	O
Hat	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
Petticoats	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
two	O
Persons	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
rented	O
a	O
House	O
of	O
10	O
l.	O
a	O
Year	O
in	O
Petty	O
France	O
,	O
at	O
Westminster	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
had	O
told	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
she	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
King-Street	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Katharine	I-place
Coleman	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
12	O
pound	O
of	O
Beef	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
Bar	O
about	O
8	O
a	O
clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
here	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Fellow	O
lurking	O
about	O
her	O
House	O
;	O
that	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
Rump	O
of	O
Beef	O
which	O
hung	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
pursued	O
dropt	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
him	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sure	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
Person	O
.	O
The	O
Cook-maid	O
also	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
Beef	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
lifted	O
it	O
up	O
three	O
times	O
before	O
be	O
could	O
get	O
it	O
off	O
the	O
Hook	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
his	O
Head	O
against	O
the	O
Beef	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
fell	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
he	O
dropt	O
it	O
10	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
it	O
hung	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Mercy	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Masse	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Undershaft	I-place
;	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Silk	O
Gowns	O
and	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
a	O
Camblet	O
Cloak	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
hearing	O
a	O
Noise	O
above	O
Stairs	O
,	O
sent	O
the	O
Maid	O
up	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Gough	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
there	O
with	O
his	O
Arms	O
full	O
of	O
Clothes	O
,	O
whereupon	O
she	O
lock	O
'd	O
him	O
in	O
,	O
ran	O
down	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
Assistance	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
went	O
up	O
again	O
the	O
Clothes	O
were	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
wet	O
Floor	O
,	O
which	O
before	O
were	O
lockt	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Drawers	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
shamm	O
'd	O
being	O
Drunk	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
Chissel	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
he	O
believes	O
he	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Drawers	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Richard	I-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Abchurch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Cup	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
sworn	O
to	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
A	O
Goldsmith	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
offered	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
stopt	O
him	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Austin	O
,	O
who	O
owned	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bengodwin	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
12	O
tann	O
'd	O
Calve-Skins	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Leak	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Drugget	O
Coat	O
and	O
Wastcoat	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
Person	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
pawn	O
'd	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
accordingly	O
.	O
The	O
Pawnbroker	B-pers
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
had	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
on	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Zephaniah	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
2s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Hewet	I-pers
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Limes	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
-	O
Limes	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
Father	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
who	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
was	O
to	O
meet	O
him	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
News	O
Papers	O
,	O
walked	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
his	O
Wig	O
to	O
comb	O
,	O
which	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
doing	O
,	O
he	O
observed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Wig	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
up	O
his	O
Back	O
under	O
his	O
Coat	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
combing	O
his	O
Wig	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
then	O
seized	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
to	O
secure	O
him	O
while	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
Constable	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Wig	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
him	O
a	O
Ring	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
desiring	O
him	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
not	O
to	O
Prosecute	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Jasper	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
2	O
Holland	O
Shifts	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Garnsey	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Kitchin	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Entry	O
with	O
the	O
Clothes	O
wet	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
who	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
her	O
,	O
threw	O
them	O
down	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
followed	O
him	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
her	O
Eye	O
on	O
him	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
.	O
Another	O
corroborated	O
her	O
Evidence	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Wafer	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Odes	I-pers
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
April	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
Wastcoat	O
and	O
Breeches	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Stockings	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Medlicott	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
3	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
Silk	O
,	O
Brandy	O
,	O
Red-Wine	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
James	B-pers
Odes	I-pers
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
Francis	O
Griffith	O
pleadeth	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
against	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Swithin	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
and	O
Case	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
and	O
18	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
London-stone	O
in	O
Cannon-street	B-place
,	O
about	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
the	O
Night	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
three	O
others	O
came	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
tript	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
turn	O
'd	O
him	O
twice	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
his	O
Watch	O
and	O
Money	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
seized	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
by	O
his	O
Arm	O
and	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
him	O
fast	O
till	O
the	O
Watch	O
came	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Watchmen	O
brought	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
a	O
Watch	O
and	O
18	O
s.	O
whereupon	O
he	O
search	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
on	O
him	O
28	O
s.	O
some	O
Half-pence	O
and	O
a	O
Common-Prayer	O
Book	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
King	O
Edward	O
's	O
Shilling	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
could	O
swear	O
to	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
in	O
Drink	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Woman	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
went	O
by	O
she	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
much	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
her	O
Acquaintance	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
offer	O
'd	O
him	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
refused	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
of	O
his	O
Watch	O
and	O
Money	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
how	O
much	O
Money	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
which	O
agreed	O
with	O
what	O
they	O
found	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
search	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
charg	O
'd	O
the	O
Constable	O
with	O
each	O
other	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Dowyer	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Whalebone	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Crofts	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Warming	O
Pan	O
,	O
24	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
2	O
Shirts	O
,	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Breeches	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
Crofts	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
2	O
Silk	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
7	O
Shirts	O
,	O
4	O
Table-Cloths	O
,	O
4	O
Napkins	O
,	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
indicted	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
John	O
White	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Tower-Liberty	B-place
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
and	O
96	O
Yards	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stuff	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Fawsket	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
fourth	O
time	O
indicted	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
John	O
White	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
at	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Putty	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
12	O
Table-Cloths	O
,	O
4	O
Shifts	O
,	O
4	O
Suits	O
of	O
Head-Clothes	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
January	O
1716	O
.	O
Of	O
all	O
which	O
Felonies	O
and	O
Burglaries	O
he	O
was	O
accused	O
by	O
Isaac	B-pers
De-la-mee	I-pers
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
himself	O
was	O
an	O
Accomplice	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
them	O
:	O
But	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
better	O
Evidence	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Knapper	I-pers
alias	I-pers
How	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Knapper	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Trunk	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
5	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
DwellingHouse	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Meers	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Griffiths	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Hardey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
100	O
Yards	O
of	O
Broad-Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
45	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Javon	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Daniel	O
Javon	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
:	O
and	O
Ann	O
Hardey	O
as	O
Accessary	O
in	O
receiving	O
5	O
Yards	O
,	O
part	O
thereof	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
by	O
the	O
Year	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
Number	O
of	O
Broad-Cloths	O
brought	O
from	O
Blackwell-Hall	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
Porters	O
came	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Returns	O
,	O
2	O
Pieces	O
were	O
missing	O
.	O
The	O
Apprentice	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Journeyman	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
Cloth	O
there	O
several	O
Times	O
,	O
viz-5	O
Yards	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
30	O
Yards	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
and	O
30	O
Yards	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
February	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
Hardey	O
a	O
Bundle	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
Remnants	O
of	O
Cloth	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
a	O
Frock	O
.	O
Another	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
7	O
Remnants	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
a	O
Remnant	O
,	O
9	O
Months	O
ago	O
.	O
Another	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
Sell	O
him	O
a	O
Remnant	O
of	O
Blue	O
Cloth	O
.	O
Another	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Hardey	O
falling	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
Hardey	O
was	O
an	O
over-reaching	O
Fellow	O
,	O
owed	O
him	O
27	O
s.	O
for	O
Cloth	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
but	O
one	O
third	O
of	O
the	O
value	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Griffiths	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Hardey	O
's	O
Husband	O
had	O
made	O
him	O
a	O
Frock	O
and	O
sent	O
her	O
for	O
it	O
to	O
alter	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Bundle	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
;	O
denyed	O
what	O
the	O
Apprentice	O
swore	O
about	O
cutting	O
of	O
Cloth	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
Selling	O
of	O
Cloth	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
employed	O
by	O
several	O
Persons	O
so	O
to	O
do	O
:	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
against	O
Hardey	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Griffiths	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Charles	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Eglington	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Peters	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
star	O
'd	O
him	O
full	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
more	O
surprised	O
him	O
because	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Charge	O
about	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
felt	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
and	O
mist	O
his	O
Handker-chief	O
;	O
and	O
charging	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Barter	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
in	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
break	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
hearing	O
a	O
Noise	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
about	O
4	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
he	O
rose	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
2	O
Iron	O
Bars	O
of	O
the	O
Cellar	O
Window	O
removed	O
,	O
a	O
Third	O
bent	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
break	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stooping	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
close	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
whether	O
his	O
Hands	O
touched	O
them	O
,	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
only	O
staid	O
to	O
make	O
Water	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Winn	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Olave	I-place
's	I-place
Hart-Street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
3	O
Yards	O
and	O
half	O
of	O
Broad	O
Cloth	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
French	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Cutting-Room	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
found	O
accordingly	O
.	O
Another	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
Cloth	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Baker	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
owed	O
him	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Cloth	O
.	O
But	O
that	O
Excuse	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
in	O
Cursing	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
drinking	O
the	O
Pretender	O
's	O
Health	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Callicoe	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
quilted	O
Silk	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
3	O
Suits	O
of	O
Headclothes	O
,	O
a	O
Riding-hood	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
5	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
her	O
Lodger	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Ridding-hood	O
in	O
Particular	O
was	O
found	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
a	O
Brandy-Shop	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
confest	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
The	O
finding	O
of	O
the	O
Ridding-hood	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
confessing	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
other	O
Evidences	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ridge	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Black	O
Mare	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Gatford	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Mare	O
out	O
of	O
Boney	B-place
in	I-place
Sussex	I-place
on	O
the	O
14th	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Upton	O
's	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Upton	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
her	O
into	O
Smithfield	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
a	O
Boy	O
upon	O
her	O
to	O
sell	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
sold	O
her	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Yates	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
a	O
Shilling	O
Earnest	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
produce	O
Vouchers	O
at	O
the	O
Toll-Book	O
,	O
the	O
Mare	O
remained	O
there	O
till	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
her	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Garret	I-pers
and	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Garret	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ethelburga	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
52	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Deer	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Samuel	B-pers
Prigg	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Drugget	O
Coat	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Hat	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Samuel	O
Prigg	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Timothy	B-pers
Cary	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
in	O
forging	O
a	O
Pass	O
for	O
safe	O
Conduct	O
for	O
two	O
Mariners	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Cumberland	O
and	O
Westmoreland	O
,	O
and	O
setting	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Johnstone	I-pers
,	O
Justice	O
of	O
Peace	O
for	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
several	O
Variances	O
between	O
the	O
Pass	O
and	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Ruth	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Alhallows	B-place
Lombard-street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Dimond	O
Stone	O
value	O
25	O
l.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
de	I-pers
Rost	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
near	O
the	O
Monument	O
,	O
who	O
lookt	O
as	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
frighted	O
and	O
had	O
fallen	O
to	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
Cart	O
close	O
by	O
,	O
he	O
thought	O
the	O
might	O
have	O
received	O
some	O
Hurt	O
,	O
wherefore	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
her	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Wine	O
to	O
comfort	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Ship	B-place
Tavern	I-place
together	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
Red	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Drawer	O
said	O
was	O
21	O
d.	O
that	O
putting	O
his	O
Hand	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Pockets	O
he	O
found	O
but	O
one	O
Shilling	O
and	O
some	O
Halfpence	O
,	O
then	O
feeling	O
in	O
another	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
the	O
Diamond	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
shewed	O
to	O
the	O
Drawer	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
again	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Paper	O
.	O
The	O
Drawer	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Paper	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
feel	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
open	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
feel	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
her	O
not	O
open	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
open	O
it	O
against	O
his	O
Will	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
felt	O
something	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
bigness	O
of	O
a	O
Pea	O
:	O
that	O
they	O
lookt	O
all	O
about	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
knew	O
her	O
and	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
meeting	O
her	O
,	O
clapt	O
his	O
Arms	O
round	O
her	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
should	O
Drink	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
some	O
Wine	O
and	O
a	O
Pidgeon	O
Pye	O
,	O
and	O
among	O
other	O
Discourse	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
how	O
unfortunate	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
picking	O
up	O
Girls	O
for	O
though	O
he	O
had	O
allowed	O
them	O
2	O
Guineas	O
a	O
Week	O
,	O
yet	O
they	O
abused	O
him	O
:	O
that	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
allow	O
her	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
Week	O
to	O
leave	O
her	O
Husband	O
and	O
live	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
she	O
acknowledged	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
did	O
give	O
her	O
the	O
Paper	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
open	O
it	O
be	O
snatch	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
against	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Diamond	O
might	O
be	O
lost	O
so	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
neither	O
saw	O
nor	O
felt	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Paper	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Kein	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
in	I-place
Wood-street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Kein	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
her	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
in	O
her	O
Throat	O
of	O
the	O
Length	O
of	O
6	O
Inches	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
1	O
Inch	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
28th	O
following	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
on	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Bull	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Compter-Gate	O
about	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
a	O
Clock	O
the	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
and	O
abused	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
thro	O
'	O
and	O
held	O
her	O
with	O
Violence	O
;	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
in	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
she	O
should	O
occasion	O
more	O
Actions	O
to	O
be	O
brought	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
keep	O
him	O
there	O
his	O
Life-time	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
let	O
her	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
drinking	O
together	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
till	O
about	O
Eight	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
told	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
late	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
must	O
Lock	O
him	O
up	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Bloody	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
lying	O
in	O
her	O
Gore	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
who	O
when	O
her	O
Wounds	O
were	O
drest	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
Speech	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
:	O
That	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Knife	O
bloody	O
in	O
a	O
back	O
Yard	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Ward	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lay	O
in	O
look	O
'd	O
into	O
:	O
his	O
Hands	O
and	O
Apron	O
were	O
bloody	O
.	O
A	O
Woman	O
who	O
was	O
Prisoner	O
there	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
were	O
at	O
Variance	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
drink	O
with	O
her	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
kist	O
her	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
perswaded	O
her	O
not	O
to	O
go	O
for	O
fear	O
he	O
should	O
beat	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Bell	O
Rung	O
for	O
clearing	O
the	O
House	O
they	O
went	O
up	O
.	O
Another	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
provoking	O
Language	O
,	O
and	O
Spit	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
were	O
seemingly	O
Friends	O
afterwards	O
and	O
kist	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
by	O
to	O
Cistern	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
drinking	O
Cellar	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
some	O
distance	O
from	O
the	O
Ward	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lay	O
.	O
The	O
Surgeon	O
deposid	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Wound	O
and	O
believes	O
it	O
Mortal	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Jugular	O
Vein	O
was	O
cut	O
through	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Pipe	O
half	O
through	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Stab	O
two	O
Inches	O
deep	O
behind	O
her	O
Ear	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Wounds	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
took	O
his	O
Knife	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
be	O
reveng	O
'd	O
on	O
him	O
or	O
her	O
self	O
before	O
they	O
parted	O
,	O
and	O
believ	O
'd	O
she	O
did	O
it	O
her	O
self	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
Examined	O
as	O
to	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
having	O
wrested	O
the	O
Knife	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
give	O
her	O
the	O
Wounds	O
;	O
he	O
pleaded	O
also	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Lunatick	O
at	O
some	O
times	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Long	I-pers
of	O
Chelsea	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Col.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Chidley	I-pers
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
chared	O
in	O
her	O
Master	O
's	O
House	O
when	O
the	O
Spoon	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
taken	O
up	O
and	O
had	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
she	O
confest	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
:	O
her	O
Confessionon	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Clare	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Storey	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
being	O
at	O
Stepney	B-place
Church	I-place
he	O
felt	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
sliding	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Hand	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
therein	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
another	O
dropt	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
:	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
believing	O
him	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
China	O
Window	O
Curtains	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Skawford	I-pers
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Goods	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
his	O
Servants	O
deposed	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Fore-Room	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
Noise	O
.	O
whereupon	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
follow	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
her	O
sling	O
the	O
Goods	O
down	O
,	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Box	O
and	O
15s	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Hilton	I-pers
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Hilton	I-pers
:	O
Mary	O
Hilton	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
while	O
her	O
Brother	O
was	O
fighting	O
with	O
another	O
Man	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
thrust	O
her	O
Hand	O
into	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Box	O
and	O
Money	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Allen	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
fetcht	O
her	O
Clothes	O
out	O
of	O
Pawn	O
with	O
the	O
Money	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Charles	I-pers
Cammel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White-Chapel	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Hester	B-pers
Pepper	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High-Way	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Pocket	O
,	O
2	O
Snuff-Boxes	O
,	O
3	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
2	O
Pen	O
Knives	O
and	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Hester	O
Pepper	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
going	O
along	O
Red-Lyon-Street	B-place
in	I-place
Goodmans	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
threw	O
her	O
down	O
,	O
tore	O
off	O
her	O
Pocket	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
followed	O
him	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
two	O
others	O
that	O
were	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
followed	O
him	O
cross	O
the	O
Way	O
and	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
again	O
by	O
his	O
Sleeve	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
away	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
left	O
the	O
Cuff	O
of	O
his	O
Sleeve	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
torn	O
off	O
in	O
the	O
Scuffle	O
;	O
that	O
upon	O
her	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Cuff	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
and	O
agreed	O
with	O
his	O
Coat	O
.	O
Another	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
hearing	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
running	O
with	O
others	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
with	O
the	O
Cuff	O
of	O
his	O
Sleeve	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
Satisfaction	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Scales	O
deposed	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
pretty	O
near	O
,	O
several	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
saying	O
,	O
Ha	O
!	O
Charles	O
,	O
what	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
again	O
?	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
advised	O
him	O
to	O
tell	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
save	O
himself	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
replied	O
,	O
would	O
you	O
have	O
me	O
to	O
hang	O
others	O
for	O
what	O
I	O
did	O
?	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
his	O
Tryal	O
owned	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
tore	O
his	O
Sleeve	O
off	O
;	O
and	O
pleaded	O
that	O
he	O
ran	O
to	O
catch	O
the	O
Persons	O
who	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Hale	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Enfield	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
black	O
Horse	O
value	O
9	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Turle	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Winifred	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Ophelia	I-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
pound	O
of	O
Thread	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Darby	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Darby	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
their	O
Shop	O
and	O
Cheapen	O
'd	O
Thread	O
,	O
Tape	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
busy	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Thread	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
charg	O
'd	O
closely	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
though	O
she	O
denied	O
it	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
yet	O
owned	O
it	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
Petticoat	O
.	O
A	O
Neighbour	O
deposed	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Darby	O
sent	O
for	O
him	O
into	O
her	O
Shop	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisner	O
after	O
sometime	O
,	O
deliver	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White	I-place
Chapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
3	O
Guineas	O
and	O
9	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Law	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
.	O
House	O
of	O
-	B-pers
Milton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
left	O
his	O
Money	O
and	O
Rings	O
in	O
his	O
Breeches	O
Pocket	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
mist	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
from	O
her	O
Mistress	O
that	O
Day	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
the	O
next	O
to	O
seek	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
found	O
her	O
landing	O
at	O
St.	O
Katharines	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Rings	O
on	O
her	O
Finger	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
Brother	O
return	O
'd	O
him	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Milton	O
confirmed	O
their	O
going	O
after	O
her	O
and	O
finding	O
the	O
Rings	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
deposed	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
apprehended	O
her	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
Brother	O
3	O
Guineas	O
and	O
spent	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
two	O
Rings	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
were	O
return	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
Bed	O
the	O
2	O
Rings	O
and	O
half	O
Guinea	O
dropt	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
took	O
up	O
and	O
put	O
into	O
her	O
own	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
at	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
black	O
Mare	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
her	O
lost	O
his	O
Mare	O
from	O
the	O
Grounds	O
at	O
Eriss	B-place
in	I-place
Huntingtonshire	I-place
on	O
the	O
22nd	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
on	O
John	B-pers
Rawlinson	I-pers
.	O
John	O
Rawlinson	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
her	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Long-Lane	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
her	O
of	O
a	O
little	O
black	O
Fellow	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Hair	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Colts	O
in	O
Finsbury	O
:	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
brown	O
Mare	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jolly	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Mare	O
from	O
Upwell	O
in	O
Norfolk	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
on	O
Mr.	O
King	O
in	O
Norfolk	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Jenkins	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Mare	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
her	O
to	O
Mr.	O
King	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
her	O
of	O
Jack	B-pers
Hardwick	I-pers
in	O
Huntington	O
,	O
but	O
produced	O
none	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
,	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Beesley	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminister	I-place
;	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
committing	O
a	O
Rape	O
on	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Tennet	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Girl	O
of	O
10	O
Years	O
and	O
4	O
Months	O
old	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Flatt	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Girl	O
told	O
her	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
done	O
her	O
the	O
Wrong	O
complained	O
of	O
.	O
The	O
Midwife	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
examin	O
'd	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
very	O
much	O
abused	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
Violence	O
and	O
a	O
Penetration	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
swell	O
'd	O
to	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
degree	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
Run	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Edmund	B-pers
James	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
Night	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
own	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lain	O
with	O
her	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
.	O
The	O
girl	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
whether	O
she	O
knew	O
what	O
an	O
Oath	O
was	O
,	O
answer	O
'd	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
:	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
black	O
'd	O
Shoes	O
about	O
Crown	O
and	O
Sceptre	O
Court	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
stopt	O
her	O
Mouth	O
with	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
or	O
Cloth	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
twice	O
within	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Days	O
of	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
served	O
her	O
so	O
both	O
Times	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
discover	O
it	O
till	O
after	O
the	O
second	O
Time	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
did	O
because	O
she	O
was	O
sore	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
,	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Smallman	I-pers
and	O
Susannah	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Pockets	O
,	O
5	O
Keys	O
,	O
6	O
Guineas	O
,	O
4	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
a	O
Damask	O
Napkin	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
:	O
and	O
Susannah	O
Jones	O
for	O
receiving	O
a	O
Damask	O
Napkin	O
and	O
7	O
s.	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Money	O
and	O
Goods	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
home	O
about	O
5	O
a	O
Clock	O
he	O
mist	O
a	O
Nest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
thrown	O
down	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Bottom	O
broke	O
out	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
two	O
Pockets	O
3	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
15	O
s.	O
on	O
Smallman	O
,	O
who	O
owned	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
:	O
that	O
Jones	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
7	O
s.	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
a	O
Damask	O
Napkin	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
pawn	O
'd	O
,	O
told	O
where	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
accordingly	O
.	O
Smallman	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
on	O
her	O
Tryal	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
against	O
Jones	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Smallman	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Smallman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
alone	O
in	O
her	O
Room	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Rings	O
off	O
the	O
Chimney-Piece	O
,	O
ran	O
down	O
Stairs	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
overtake	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ryley	I-pers
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
askt	O
for	O
small	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
the	O
Servant	O
was	O
gone	O
for	O
some	O
he	O
took	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
taken	O
and	O
carried	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
he	O
confessed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
others	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
on	O
his	O
Tryal	O
;	O
his	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White	I-place
Chapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Compton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Eliz	B-pers
Campton	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
as	O
they	O
hung	O
at	O
her	O
Door	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
hearing	O
her	O
,	O
followed	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
upon	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
next	O
Door	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
none	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cranbery	I-pers
of	O
Twittenham	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Biggs	I-pers
,	O
by	O
privately	O
putting	O
White	O
Arsenick	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Poyson	O
,	O
into	O
a	O
Dish	O
of	O
Milk	O
Porridge	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
knew	O
to	O
be	O
provided	O
for	O
his	O
Breakfast	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
sick	O
from	O
8	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
till	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
,	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
on	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Tudor	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
before	O
,	O
she	O
going	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
Bed	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
her	O
self	O
lay	O
,	O
found	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
yellow	O
Silk	O
with	O
something	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
took	O
to	O
be	O
Sugar	O
,	O
but	O
putting	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
Tongue	O
found	O
it	O
hot	O
,	O
whereupon	O
she	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
little	O
of	O
it	O
and	O
put	O
into	O
a	O
Paper	O
,	O
and	O
tied	O
up	O
the	O
rest	O
again	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Window	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
toward	O
her	O
Box	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
shewed	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
reserved	O
in	O
the	O
Paper	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
they	O
knew	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
that	O
on	O
Friday	O
Night	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
her	O
Father-in-Law	O
)	O
had	O
many	O
Words	O
together	O
,	O
insomuch	O
that	O
he	O
threatned	O
to	O
turn	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
:	O
that	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Morning	O
while	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Wife	O
was	O
feeding	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
complained	O
there	O
was	O
something	O
in	O
the	O
Porridge	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
to	O
her	O
Knowledge	O
for	O
she	O
clean	O
'd	O
the	O
Sauce-Pan	O
and	O
boyled	O
it	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
thing	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
Oat-meal	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
eat	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Spoonfuls	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
complained	O
again	O
,	O
whereupon	O
she	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Spoon	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Mistresses	O
Hand	O
.	O
and	O
stirring	O
the	O
Milk	O
found	O
something	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
said	O
look	O
'd	O
like	O
Lime	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Son	O
said	O
it	O
look	O
'd	O
like	O
Starch	O
;	O
that	O
stirring	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Bottom	O
she	O
found	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
white	O
Specks	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Dog	O
,	O
who	O
vomited	O
it	O
up	O
again	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
Poisened	O
me	O
!	O
I	O
'll	O
search	O
all	O
your	O
Boxes	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
He	O
should	O
not	O
search	O
hers	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
he	O
should	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
But	O
he	O
going	O
to	O
break	O
it	O
open	O
with	O
a	O
Hammer	O
,	O
she	O
opened	O
it	O
her	O
self	O
;	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
Paper	O
which	O
she	O
said	O
was	O
Cinnamon	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
another	O
Paper	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
convey	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Deceased	O
being	O
very	O
intent	O
upon	O
the	O
search	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Head	O
as	O
it	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
perceived	O
it	O
and	O
snatch	O
'd	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
(	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
it	O
)	O
This	O
is	O
such	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
my	O
Victuals	O
.	O
He	O
sent	O
his	O
Wife	O
to	O
the	O
Doctors	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
who	O
order	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
some	O
Oil	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
ill	O
presently	O
,	O
and	O
continued	O
Vomiting	O
till	O
he	O
died	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
4	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Biggs	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
made	O
a	O
Saucepan	O
of	O
Milk-Porridge	O
,	O
as	O
usual	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
her	O
Daughter	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
her	O
Nursery	O
while	O
she	O
fed	O
her	O
Husband	O
(	O
the	O
Deceased	O
)	O
that	O
he	O
complained	O
there	O
was	O
something	O
in	O
his	O
Porridge	O
twice	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
confirmed	O
what	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
had	O
deposed	O
,	O
and	O
added	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
hoped	O
he	O
should	O
overcome	O
it	O
because	O
he	O
vomited	O
so	O
much	O
.	O
The	O
Paper	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Box	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
Dr.	O
Perkins	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
lookt	O
upon	O
it	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
White	O
Arsenick	O
,	O
White	O
Vitriol	O
,	O
and	O
Bole-Armoniac	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
rank	O
Poyson	O
;	O
that	O
heopened	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
Poysoned	O
,	O
his	O
Stomach	O
corroded	O
and	O
turn	O
'd	O
Black	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Marks	O
of	O
Poyson	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
lived	O
at	O
an	O
Apothecary	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
but	O
having	O
agreed	O
with	O
a	O
Woman	O
to	O
learn	O
her	O
to	O
wash	O
Gloves	O
,	O
she	O
gave	O
her	O
Mistress	O
warning	O
;	O
that	O
a	O
Woman	O
coming	O
one	O
Day	O
for	O
something	O
to	O
wash	O
Gloves	O
with	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Dr.	O
had	O
served	O
her	O
he	O
laid	O
the	O
rest	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
in	O
Order	O
to	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
it	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
wash	O
Gloves	O
her	O
self	O
.	O
And	O
as	O
to	O
her	O
refusing	O
to	O
have	O
her	O
Box	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
tho	O
'	O
she	O
did	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
yet	O
she	O
open	O
'd	O
it	O
her	O
self	O
presently	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Clay	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
at	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Pint	O
Pot	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Cock	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
House	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
drew	O
him	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Drink	O
in	O
a	O
Silver	O
Mug	O
,	O
but	O
missing	O
of	O
it	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
pursued	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Mug	O
under	O
his	O
Coat	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
with	O
a	O
Design	O
to	O
steal	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
bring	O
it	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Palfreman	I-pers
and	I-pers
Mary	I-pers
his	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
and	O
Mary	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
4	O
Looking	O
Glasses	O
,	O
a	O
Blanket	O
,	O
3	O
Pound	O
of	O
Brass	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Macclery	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Sands	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Hobbs	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Pidworth	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
April	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
2	O
Shirts	O
,	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Richard	O
Pidworth	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Edmund	I-place
the	I-place
King	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
350	O
Guineas	O
and	O
an	O
Half	O
,	O
30	O
Moidores	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Elias	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
Sir	O
George	B-pers
Caswell	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Jacob	B-pers
Sawbridge	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Elias	O
Turner	O
and	O
Company	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
several	O
Places	O
to	O
receive	O
several	O
Sums	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
received	O
that	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
put	O
into	O
a	O
Drawer	O
in	O
his	O
Masters	O
Office	O
;	O
with	O
a	O
Book	O
of	O
Memorandurms	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
both	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
Book	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
or	O
Wednesday	O
following	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Book	O
and	O
some	O
Money	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dover-Bag	O
in	O
the	O
Post	O
Office	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Love	I-pers
(	O
the	O
Post-Master	O
's	O
Agent	O
at	O
Dover	O
)	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
received	O
Orders	O
form	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Cornwallis	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Craigs	O
,	O
to	O
seize	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Passage	O
to	O
France	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
accordingly	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
Papers	O
and	O
some	O
Money	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
sealed	O
up	O
the	O
Papers	O
in	O
a	O
Cover	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
them	O
directed	O
to	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Post-Master-General	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Marshal	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
put	O
the	O
Seal	O
to	O
the	O
Book	O
of	O
Memorandums	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Drawer	O
with	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Newton	O
deposed	O
also	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
who	O
received	O
Money	O
abroad	O
and	O
paid	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Office	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
no	O
Trust	O
of	O
it	O
when	O
there	O
.	O
His	O
Confession	O
sign	O
'd	O
by	O
himself	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
his	O
Tryal	O
owned	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Glasford	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Drugget	O
Coat	O
,	O
Wastcoat	O
and	O
Breeches	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Laurence	B-pers
Flower	I-pers
of	O
Chelsea	B-place
;	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bay	O
Gelding	O
value	O
35	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Simms	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Horse	O
from	O
Oldfield-Common	B-place
near	I-place
Maiden-head	I-place
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
with	O
Tho	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
.	O
Tho	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
deposed	O
he	O
bought	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
Chelsea	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Lovel	O
confirmed	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Road	O
.	O
But	O
that	O
Excuse	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Goddard	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Mug	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
19	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
and	I-pers
Thomas	I-pers
Lambert	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Man	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Fountain	B-place
Tavern	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Strand	I-place
,	O
had	O
Wine	O
,	O
Veal-Cutlets	O
,	O
and	O
Small-Beer	O
in	O
a	O
Silver	O
Mug	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
away	O
without	O
paying	O
their	O
Reckoning	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Drawer	O
looking	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
mist	O
the	O
Mug	O
and	O
secur	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
offer	O
'd	O
5	O
l.	O
to	O
make	O
up	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
he	O
thought	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
(	O
who	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
a	O
Stranger	O
)	O
had	O
carry	O
'd	O
the	O
Mug	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
and	O
paid	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
believing	O
him	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Laurence	B-pers
Waldron	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
at	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Drugget	O
Coat	O
and	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
Sheets	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Walters	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Poplin	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Curtis	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
desiring	O
that	O
she	O
might	O
be	O
there	O
till	O
she	O
could	O
provide	O
her	O
self	O
a	O
Lodging	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
with	O
the	O
Clothes	O
on	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
wore	O
ever	O
since	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
on	O
at	O
her	O
Tryal	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Barbara	B-pers
Useley	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Huggins	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
up	O
Drury-Lane	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
with	O
a	O
Friend	O
,	O
they	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
,	O
who	O
ask	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
drink	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
Newtoners-Lane	B-place
together	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
with	O
his	O
Friend	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
and	O
he	O
staid	O
below	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
he	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
)	O
was	O
pleased	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
answer	O
'd	O
yes	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
paid	O
for	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
come	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
another	O
touch	O
for	O
Good-will	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
busy	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
felt	O
her	O
Hand	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
mist	O
his	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
with	O
her	O
Coats	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
afterwards	O
have	O
lain	O
with	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
refusing	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
this	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Felony	O
in	O
Marrying	O
two	O
Wives	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Deer	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
at	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Drugget	O
Coat	O
and	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Barrimore	I-pers
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Zephaniah	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Savoy	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
two	O
Perriwigs	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Griffiths	I-pers
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cullin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Muslin	O
Apron	O
,	O
2	O
Caps	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
again	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
confest	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
on	O
her	O
Tryal	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White	I-place
Chapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
,	O
a	O
Shift	O
,	O
2	O
Aprons	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Dyer	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Lewis	B-pers
Vain	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Paddington	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
black	O
Mare	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Mare	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Fields	B-place
near	I-place
Tybourn	I-place
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
advertised	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
News	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
Letter	O
of	O
advice	O
sent	O
him	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Binks	O
from	O
Topsham	O
near	O
Exeter	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
rid	O
thither	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Binks	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
reading	O
the	O
Advertisement	O
at	O
the	O
Coffee	O
House	O
,	O
found	O
by	O
the	O
Discription	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
very	O
remarkable	O
)	O
that	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
Mare	O
the	O
Prisner	O
rode	O
upon	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
come	O
a	O
Day	O
and	O
half	O
's	O
Journey	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Inn	O
and	O
secur	O
'd	O
both	O
Mare	O
and	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
a	O
Letter	O
thereof	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Baker	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
sell	O
her	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
her	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Weaver	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
in	O
taking	O
6	O
Pound	O
of	O
Lead	O
from	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Brown	I-pers
which	O
was	O
fix	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Freehold	O
.	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White-Chapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Yards	O
of	O
Broad-Cloth	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Hadley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
off	O
the	O
Tenters	O
in	O
a	O
Tenter-Ground	O
in	O
Goodmans-Fields	B-place
,	O
but	O
being	O
seen	O
by	O
two	O
Persons	O
,	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Duton	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Fustian-Frock	O
and	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Hitchcote	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Clothes	O
,	O
and	O
following	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
saw	O
them	O
fall	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Day	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
on	O
a	O
Statute	O
made	O
in	O
the	O
5th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
present	O
Majesty	O
King	O
George	O
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
altering	O
the	O
Numbers	O
of	O
two	O
Lottery	O
Tickets	O
that	O
were	O
drawn	O
Blanks	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Numbers	O
of	O
two	O
that	O
were	O
drawn	O
Prize	O
s.	O
viz	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
64590	O
,	O
to	O
61960	O
,	O
a	O
Prize	O
of	O
500l	O
.	O
and	O
64592	O
to	O
68073.	O
a	O
Prize	O
of	O
100l	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intention	O
to	O
defraud	O
our	O
Sovereign	O
Lord	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Odams	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
appointed	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Receivers	O
of	O
the	O
Lottery	O
Tickets	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Tickets	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
were	O
Lottery	O
Tickets	O
,	O
but	O
alter	O
'd	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
Lottery	O
Tickets	O
cut	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Book	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
Numbers	O
were	O
alter	O
'd	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Clerk	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
Books	O
were	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
,	O
sign	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Managers	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
Christmas	O
last	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Bed	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
lately	O
Married	O
to	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
of	O
a	O
great	O
Fortune	O
,	O
and	O
importun	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
a	O
Lottery	O
Ticket	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
Prize	O
of	O
100	O
l.	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
near	O
half	O
the	O
Money	O
for	O
himself	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
again	O
with	O
a	O
Ticket	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
a	O
500	O
l.	O
Prize	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Questions	O
.	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
indirectly	O
obtain	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
not	O
own	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
false	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
wonder	O
'd	O
that	O
this	O
Evidence	O
should	O
suspect	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
such	O
Question	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
(	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
)	O
wrote	O
a	O
Letter	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Sadler	I-pers
,	O
Goldsmith	O
in	O
Fleet-Street	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Stevenson	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
at	O
Clavering	O
in	O
Essex	O
,	O
and	O
enclosed	O
the	O
said	O
Ticket	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
Letter	O
he	O
desired	O
Mr.	O
Sadler	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
the	O
Ticket	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
pay	O
himself	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
received	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
such	O
Plate	O
as	O
was	O
bespoke	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Letter	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
put	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
a	O
Box	O
with	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
deliver	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
who	O
would	O
call	O
for	O
it	O
such	O
a	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
for	O
the	O
Box	O
with	O
the	O
Coffee-Pot	O
.	O
That	O
finding	O
Mr.	O
Sadler	O
very	O
dilatory	O
,	O
he	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Request	O
,	O
wrote	O
two	O
other	O
Letters	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
wrote	O
one	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Jennings	O
complaining	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Sadlers	O
Usage	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Sadler	O
deposed	O
he	O
received	O
the	O
three	O
Letters	O
and	O
Ticket	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
Porter	O
came	O
for	O
the	O
Box	O
of	O
Plate	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
suspecting	O
Roguery	O
,	O
carry	O
'd	O
the	O
Ticket	O
to	O
the	O
Office	O
at	O
White-Hall	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
Ticket	O
of	O
100l	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
it	O
before	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
a	O
Ticket	O
to	O
a	O
Porter	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Gandy	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
alter	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
they	O
were	O
false	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
What	O
good	O
will	O
it	O
do	O
you	O
so	O
see	O
me	O
go	O
in	O
a	O
Mourning	O
Coach	O
to	O
he	O
Hang	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Justice	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
Court	O
)	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
when	O
before	O
him	O
denied	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
false	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hurl	I-pers
the	O
Porter	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
received	O
a	O
Ticket	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Gandy	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
Examine	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
believed	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
Good	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
Money	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Jordan	O
;	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
Man	O
he	O
received	O
it	O
of	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Jordan	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Porter	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
order	O
'd	O
to	O
pay	O
her	O
100l	O
.	O
but	O
she	O
order	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
stop	O
the	O
Ticket	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
Smith	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
impeached	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Oh	O
!	O
is	O
this	O
all	O
?	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
value	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
Innocent	O
;	O
and	O
this	O
will	O
be	O
a	O
Means	O
to	O
break	O
off	O
my	O
Acquaintance	O
with	O
that	O
Smith	O
.	O
He	O
also	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Numbers	O
of	O
the	O
Tickets	O
were	O
alter	O
'd	O
was	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Books	O
that	O
checkt	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Tickets	O
,	O
were	O
produc	O
'd	O
and	O
compar	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
deliver	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
not	O
being	O
satisfied	O
with	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
given	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
alter	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Katharine	I-place
Coleman	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Linnen	O
Sheets	O
and	O
a	O
Frying	O
Pan	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Weaving	I-pers
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Neales	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Mary	B-pers
Becket	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Pocket	O
and	O
9	O
Guineas	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Money	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Becket	I-pers
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Linch	B-pers
Scarriot	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
in	O
inticing	O
John	B-pers
Drake	I-pers
to	O
go	O
away	O
from	O
his	O
Master	O
John	B-pers
Woodrose	I-pers
,	O
and	O
to	O
robb	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
workt	O
for	O
him	O
4	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
losing	O
Goods	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
charg	O
'd	O
his	O
Apprentice	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
who	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
John	O
Drake	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
wanted	O
a	O
Paper	O
of	O
Loops	O
.	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
which	O
he	O
carried	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
Book	O
to	O
set	O
them	O
down	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
bid	O
him	O
come	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
refused	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
bid	O
him	O
bring	O
him	O
Buttons	O
without	O
setting	O
down	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
30	O
Groce	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
;	O
and	O
3	O
Groce	O
he	O
took	O
off	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
Pound	O
of	O
Burras	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
use	O
to	O
Solder	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Shilling	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
discovered	O
he	O
fled	O
into	O
Holland	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Delfoise	I-pers
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
2	O
Guineas	O
,	O
3	O
Half	O
Guineas	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
French	O
Pistole	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquicted	O
her	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
21	O
Hen	O
.	O
8.	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
then	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	B-pers
Viscount	I-pers
Cobham	I-pers
,	O
did	O
imbezil	O
a	O
Brillant	O
Diamond	O
Necklace	O
value	O
1500l	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
Brillant	O
Diamond	O
pair	O
of	O
Ear-rings	O
value	O
150l	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Lord	O
Viscount	O
Cobham	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
deliver	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Halsey	I-pers
.	O
The	O
delivery	O
of	O
the	O
Jewels	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Halsey	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
by	O
Celestia	B-pers
Rosier	I-pers
and	O
Mrs	B-pers
Ashurst	I-pers
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Marquess	O
of	O
Winchester	O
's	O
and	O
shewed	O
them	O
there	O
to	O
his	O
Porter	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Meales	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
my	O
Lady	O
Cobham	O
's	O
Father	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Millwood	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
also	O
owned	O
that	O
he	O
received	O
them	O
for	O
that	O
purpose	O
,	O
and	O
pleaded	O
that	O
he	O
delivered	O
them	O
accordingly	O
;	O
to	O
make	O
out	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
and	O
examin	O
'd	O
as	O
follows	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Halsey	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
brought	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Lord	O
Cobham	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
advised	O
his	O
Wife	O
before	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
to	O
send	O
her	O
Jewels	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Halsey	O
for	O
safety	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
she	O
had	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
saw	O
them	O
since	O
.	O
The	O
Lady	O
Cobham	O
confirmed	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
Deposed	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
them	O
since	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Halsey	O
also	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
deliver	O
'd	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
Circumstance	O
that	O
he	O
deliver	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Lady	O
sent	O
him	O
next	O
day	O
to	O
her	O
Father	O
with	O
a	O
Note	O
for	O
100	O
l.	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
paid	O
him	O
all	O
in	O
Gold	O
except	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
Water	O
coming	O
Home	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
he	O
wanted	O
a	O
Guinea	O
of	O
the	O
Sum	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
went	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Mr.	O
Halsey	O
in	O
this	O
Compting	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
who	O
taking	O
his	O
Pen	O
to	O
cast	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Mistake	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Guinea	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
carried	O
the	O
100	O
l.	O
Home	O
to	O
his	O
Lady	O
.	O
But	O
this	O
was	O
contradicted	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Halsey	O
and	O
my	O
Lady	O
in	O
every	O
particular	O
.	O
He	O
also	O
called	O
Mary	B-pers
Emmerson	I-pers
,	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
Jewels	O
Home	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
Mistress	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Halsey	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
12	O
and	O
return	O
'd	O
about	O
5	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
deliver	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
for	O
100	O
l.	O
that	O
he	O
brought	O
home	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
afterwards	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
Lady	O
.	O
He	O
also	O
called	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Weston	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
him	O
have	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Halsey	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
Lady	O
,	O
who	O
returned	O
him	O
a	O
Shilling	O
for	O
his	O
Boat	O
.	O
He	O
also	O
call	O
'd	O
some	O
Persons	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
poor	O
Condition	O
about	O
that	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Goods	O
were	O
seized	O
on	O
about	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
after	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Hutchinson	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Blankets	O
and	O
2	O
Brass	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Le-Bow	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
or	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Marriot	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
2	O
Months	O
,	O
but	O
missing	O
several	O
small	O
things	O
he	O
suspected	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
his	O
Man	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
his	O
Stockings	O
on	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Feathers-Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
to	O
tell	O
her	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
Gentlemen	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
they	O
found	O
his	O
Stockings	O
on	O
her	O
Legs	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
in	O
Kent	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
and	O
the	O
Constable	O
confirmed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
in	O
Kent	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
John	O
Powel	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
for	O
lying	O
with	O
her	O
But	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
agree	O
together	O
by	O
any	O
Means	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
threatned	O
to	O
kick	O
her	O
down	O
Stairs	O
;	O
and	O
also	O
observed	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
present	O
her	O
with	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
enow	O
at	O
his	O
Command	O
that	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
fit	O
to	O
wear	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
to	O
have	O
given	O
her	O
those	O
that	O
were	O
not	O
scower	O
'd	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
Grease	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
quarrel	O
till	O
afterwards	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
wore	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
saw	O
them	O
on	O
her	O
Legs	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
her	O
up	O
;	O
she	O
also	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
entrusted	O
her	O
very	O
largely	O
,	O
as	O
with	O
Gold	O
Watches	O
.	O
Rings	O
,	O
Plate	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
several	O
Hundred	O
Pounds	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
found	O
her	O
Honest	O
.	O
And	O
one	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
brought	O
this	O
Prosecution	O
on	O
her	O
self	O
by	O
her	O
saucy	O
Tongue	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Day-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquited	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White-Chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
70	O
Pound	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bagnal	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Delamont	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
at	I-place
Hackney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Robert	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
2	O
Guineas	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Coach-Seats	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgement	O
as	O
followeth	O
;	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
.	O
9.	O
George	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
alias	O
Green	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Kein	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Ridge	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Frissith	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
alias	O
Charles	B-pers
Cammel	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cranberry	I-pers
,	O
Lewis	B-pers
Vain	I-pers
and	O
Laurence	B-pers
Flower	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
3.	O
William	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Norris	I-pers
and	O
Johanna	B-pers
Radwell	I-pers
,	O
the	O
two	O
last	O
formerly	O
Convicted	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
.	O
32.	O
James	B-pers
Heathcot	I-pers
,	O
Alice	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Mercy	I-pers
alias	O
Massey	O
,	O
Susannah	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Zephaniah	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
Jasper	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Griffiths	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Eglington	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Winn	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Hannah	B-pers
Goadman	I-pers
,	O
Hannah	B-pers
Long	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Clare	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
Winifred	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
alias	O
Ophelia	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
Martha	B-pers
Smallman	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Clay	I-pers
,	O
Anthony	B-pers
Goddard	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Walters	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cullin	I-pers
,	O
S	B-pers
-	I-pers
K	I-pers
-	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Alice	B-pers
Outon	I-pers
,	O
Laurence	B-pers
Waldron	I-pers
,	O
H	O
Hutchinson	O
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Pinfield	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Ri	O
Smith	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
Lately	O
publish	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
6th	O
Edition	O
with	O
Additions	O
of	O
,	O
YOUTH	O
,	O
Introduction	O
to	O
Trade	O
and	O
Business	O
:	O
Containing	O
,	O
I	O
.	O
Tables	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
usual	O
Clerk	O
like	O
Contractions	O
of	O
Words	O
;	O
a	O
Collection	O
of	O
English	O
Words	O
,	O
alike	O
in	O
Sound	O
,	O
but	O
different	O
in	O
Signification	O
,	O
with	O
proper	O
Directions	O
how	O
to	O
address	O
to	O
Persons	O
of	O
Rank	O
,	O
and	O
those	O
in	O
Office	O
.	O
II	O
Acquittances	O
and	O
Promissory	O
Notes	O
diversified	O
and	O
adapted	O
to	O
such	O
Circumstances	O
as	O
occur	O
in	O
real	O
Business	O
.	O
III	O
.	O
Variety	O
of	O
Bills	O
of	O
Parcels	O
,	O
and	O
Bills	O
on	O
Book	O
Debts	O
,	O
to	O
enter	O
the	O
Learner	O
in	O
the	O
Manner	O
and	O
Methods	O
of	O
Commerce	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
ready	O
at	O
Computation	O
.	O
IV	O
.	O
Bills	O
of	O
Exchange	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
necessary	O
for	O
the	O
right	O
Understanding	O
and	O
Management	O
of	O
Remittances	O
;	O
several	O
Orders	O
for	O
Goods	O
,	O
Letters	O
of	O
Credit	O
,	O
Invoyces	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Merchant-like	O
Examples	O
.	O
V.	O
Authentick	O
Forms	O
of	O
such	O
Law-Precedents	O
,	O
as	O
are	O
most	O
frequently	O
to	O
be	O
met	O
with	O
,	O
in	O
Course	O
of	O
Traffick	O
.	O
VI	O
.	O
A	O
Collection	O
of	O
Questions	O
,	O
to	O
exemplify	O
the	O
common	O
Rules	O
of	O
Arithmetick	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
reduce	O
them	O
to	O
Practice	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
Schools	O
.	O
Done	O
upon	O
the	O
Plan	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
Col.	O
Ayre	B-pers
's	O
Essay	O
,	O
By	O
M.	O
Clare	O
,	O
School	O
master	O
in	O
Soho	O
Square	O
,	O
London	O
.	O
With	O
whom	O
Youth	O
may	O
board	O
and	O
be	O
fitted	O
for	O
Business	O
.	O
price	O
2	O
s.	O
Printed	O
for	O
Ed	B-pers
Symon	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Pope's-head-Alley	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
.	O
Some	O
BOOKS	O
printed	O
for	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
Edward	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
and	O
Crown	O
in	O
Lombard	O
Street	O
,	O
near	O
Stocks	O
Market	O
.	O
THE	O
London	O
New	O
Method	O
and	O
Art	O
of	O
Teaching	O
Children	O
to	O
Spell	O
and	O
Read	O
;	O
so	O
as	O
they	O
may	O
,	O
without	O
the	O
Help	O
of	O
any	O
other	O
Books	O
,	O
read	O
the	O
Bible	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
twelve	O
Months	O
.	O
Note	O
,	O
This	O
Way	O
of	O
Teaching	O
is	O
approved	O
by	O
most	O
School	O
Masters	O
as	O
the	O
best	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
6	O
d.	O
with	O
great	O
Allowance	O
to	O
those	O
who	O
sell	O
or	O
give	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
Note	O
,	O
There	O
are	O
some	O
printed	O
on	O
Fine	O
Paper	O
,	O
bound	O
up	O
with	O
Cuts	O
.	O
pr	O
.	O
8	O
d.	O
For	O
the	O
Compleating	O
of	O
Psalmody	O
.	O
The	O
Devout	O
Singer	O
's	O
Guide	O
;	O
containing	O
all	O
the	O
Common	O
Tunes	O
now	O
in	O
Use	O
,	O
with	O
select	O
Portions	O
of	O
the	O
Psalms	O
adapted	O
to	O
each	O
Tune	O
,	O
and	O
Rules	O
for	O
singing	O
Treble	O
and	O
Bass	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
A	O
Table	O
shewing	O
at	O
one	O
View	O
what	O
Psalms	O
and	O
Hymns	O
are	O
proper	O
to	O
each	O
Tune	O
both	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Version	O
of	O
Mr.Hopkins	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Sternhold	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
New	O
Version	O
of	O
Dr.	O
Brady	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Yate	O
.	O
And	O
Directions	O
for	O
Parish	O
Clerks	O
in	O
the	O
Choice	O
of	O
proper	O
Psalms	O
on	O
most	O
Occasions	O
.	O
B	O
S.	O
Shenton	O
;	O
and	O
Recommended	O
by	O
P.	O
Joynson	B-pers
,	I-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
Warner	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Singing	O
Masters	O
.	O
The	O
Fourth	O
Edition	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
Five	O
Tunes	O
,	O
containing	O
their	O
Cansus	O
,	O
Medius	O
and	O
Bassus	O
,	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
former	O
Editions	O
,	O
Price	O
bound	O
1	O
s.	O
Aesop	O
's	O
Fables	O
,	O
with	O
Morals	O
and	O
Reflections	O
,	O
as	O
improv	O
'd	O
by	O
Sir	O
Roger	B-pers
L	I-pers
'Estrange	O
,	O
done	O
into	O
Variety	O
of	O
English	O
Verse	O
.	O
Illustrated	O
with	O
Cuts	O
curiously	O
engrav	O
'd	O
on	O
Copper	O
Plates	O
.	O
Very	O
useful	O
to	O
Divert	O
and	O
Instruct	O
Young	B-pers
Gentlemen	I-pers
and	O
Ladies	O
in	O
the	O
Conduct	O
of	O
Human	O
Life	O
.	O
The	O
Fourth	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Arithmetick	O
made	O
easie	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
New	O
Method	O
now	O
taught	O
and	O
practis	O
'd	O
in	O
London	O
.	O
Where	O
in	O
the	O
Rules	O
of	O
that	O
necessary	O
Art	O
are	O
briefly	O
explain	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
illustrated	O
with	O
such	O
familliar	O
Examples	O
as	O
may	O
suit	O
the	O
meanest	O
Capacity	O
,	O
If	O
they	O
desire	O
to	O
learn	O
it	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
a	O
Succinct	O
Treatise	O
of	O
Decimal	O
Fractions	O
,	O
with	O
Compleat	O
Tables	O
,	O
Rules	O
,	O
and	O
Examples	O
demonstrating	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
like	O
not	O
extant	O
in	O
any	O
other	O
Treatise	O
of	O
this	O
Nature	O
.	O
The	O
Fourth	O
Edition	O
.	O
By	O
John	B-pers
Copeland	I-pers
,	O
Writing-Master	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
1	O
s.	O
Maximum	O
in	O
Minimo	O
;	O
Or	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Rich	I-pers
's	O
Pens	O
Dexterity	O
compleated	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
plainest	O
and	O
easiest	O
Method	O
of	O
writing	O
SHORT-HAND	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
are	O
added	O
.	O
The	O
Terms	O
of	O
the	O
Law	O
compleat	O
in	O
Characters	O
at	O
length	O
,	O
being	O
of	O
great	O
use	O
to	O
all	O
Lawyers	O
and	O
others	O
who	O
take	O
Tryals	O
at	O
large	O
in	O
Courts	O
.	O
Never	O
done	O
till	O
now	O
.	O
By	O
Samuel	B-pers
Botley	I-pers
.	O
The	O
whole	O
curiously	O
engrav	O
'd	O
on	O
Thirty	O
Copper-plates	O
,	O
Pr	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
6d	O
.	O
A	O
Guide	O
to	O
English	O
Juries	O
;	O
Setting	O
forth	O
their	O
Antiquity	O
,	O
Power	O
and	O
Duty	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Common	O
Law	O
and	O
Statutes	O
.	O
With	O
a	O
Table	O
.	O
By	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
Quality	O
.	O
Also	O
a	O
Letter	O
to	O
the	O
Author	O
upon	O
the	O
same	O
Subject	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
Orders	O
,	O
By	O
Laws	O
,	O
and	O
Ordinances	O
for	O
the	O
good	O
Government	O
and	O
Regulating	O
of	O
the	O
Persons	O
Licensed	O
to	O
Keep	O
and	O
Drive	O
Hackney-Coaches	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
Renters	O
and	O
Drivers	O
.	O
Made	O
,	O
Publish	O
'd	O
and	O
Declar	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Commissioners	O
;	O
and	O
Allowed	O
and	O
Approved	O
by	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chancellor	O
and	O
Judges	O
as	O
the	O
Law	O
directs	O
.	O
Price	O
3	O
d.	O
A	O
Water	O
that	O
perfectly	O
cures	O
the	O
Itch	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
Itching	O
Humour	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
,	O
without	O
necessity	O
of	O
Purging	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
dangerous	O
use	O
of	O
Mercury	O
,	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
is	O
only	O
Prepared	O
and	O
Sold	O
by	O
A	O
Downing	O
Chymist	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
and	O
Ball	O
in	O
George	O
Court	O
in	O
St.	O
John	O
's	O
Lane	O
by	O
Hick	O
's	O
Hall	O
near	O
West	O
Smithfield	O
.	O
Where	O
also	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
,	O
the	O
best	O
Spirits	O
of	O
Scurvy-Grass	O
,	O
by	O
Wholesale	O
or	O
Retale	O
at	O
8	O
d.	O
a	O
Bot-tle	O
.	O
A	O
most	O
effectual	O
Remedy	O
for	O
the	O
Violent	O
Pain	O
in	O
the	O
Teeth	O
,	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
Also	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Remedy	O
for	O
preserving	O
the	O
Teeth	O
and	O
clearing	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
Scurvey	O
,	O
Price	O
2	O
s	O
.	O
