TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
,	O
ON	O
Friday	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
15th	O
and	O
16th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
January	O
,	O
1719	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Sixth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
GEORGE	B-pers
THOROLD	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
and	O
Baronet	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
The	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	B-pers
Bury	I-pers
;	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Tracy	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Page	I-pers
;	O
John	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
Names	O
'	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Longbothom	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Gaywood	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Tucker	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Lathom	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Forfeit	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Palleday	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Chadwick	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Withers	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Colebourn	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
,	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Prior	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Richbell	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Dagget	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Smitheys	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Ragdale	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Gilmore	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Heather	I-pers
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Norris	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Christophers	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
3	O
Holland	O
Aprons	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
HollandSheets	O
,	O
a	O
Pillowbear	O
,	O
16	O
ells	O
of	O
Dowlas	O
,	O
15	O
Yards	O
of	O
Muslin	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
and	O
Chain	O
,	O
1	O
dozen	O
of	O
Knives	O
and	O
Forks	O
,	O
and	O
1	O
doz	O
,	O
of	O
Buckles	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Burstal	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
January	O
;	O
and	O
Elizabeth	O
Phillips	O
as	O
Accessary	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
Norris	O
was	O
very	O
intimate	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Bustal	O
,	O
and	O
complained	O
to	O
her	O
that	O
the	O
Scarf	O
Trade	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
(	O
Norris	O
)	O
then	O
followed	O
,	O
was	O
very	O
bad	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
low	O
Condition	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
took	O
her	O
in	O
out	O
of	O
Charity	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
great	O
Confidence	O
in	O
her	O
;	O
committing	O
all	O
to	O
her	O
Charge	O
while	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
;	O
that	O
several	O
things	O
were	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
Norris	O
told	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
that	O
there	O
must	O
be	O
some	O
private	O
Thief	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
who	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
impossible	O
to	O
discover	O
while	O
he	O
kept	O
two	O
Servants	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
put	O
Norris	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
of	O
selling	O
Cutlery	O
Wares	O
to	O
the	O
Shops	O
in	O
the	O
City	O
,	O
turn	O
'd	O
away	O
several	O
Servants	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
suspect	O
Norris	O
;	O
till	O
coming	O
the	O
Day	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
to	O
look	O
out	O
Goods	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Knives	O
,	O
Forks	O
,	O
and	O
Buckles	O
off	O
the	O
Compter	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
her	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Back	O
Shop	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
whereupon	O
they	O
Secur	O
'd	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
searching	O
Phillips	O
's	O
Lodging	O
found	O
some	O
of	O
their	O
Goods	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
more	O
at	O
a	O
Pawnbrokers	O
in	O
Hounsditch	O
,	O
where	O
Phillip	O
's	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
also	O
to	O
Norris	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
several	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
and	O
own	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Pawnbroker	O
swore	O
that	O
Phillips	O
had	O
brought	O
the	O
Goods	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
in	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
called	O
some	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
positive	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
Norris	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
and	O
Phillips	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
Both	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Busby	I-pers
of	O
Alhallows	B-place
Barkin	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Barrel	O
of	O
Raisins	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Booteen	I-pers
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
January	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Norman	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
land	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Barrel	O
of	O
Raisins	O
gone	O
,	O
but	O
taken	O
presently	O
after	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Back	O
on	O
Tower-Hill	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Eastcheap	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
50	O
Ells	O
of	O
Black	O
Silk	O
value	O
12	O
l.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Jacob	B-pers
Wyam	I-pers
on	O
the	O
23	O
d	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
to	O
cheapen	O
Silk	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
Simpson	O
was	O
buying	O
,	O
Jones	O
took	O
the	O
piece	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
her	O
Riding	O
Hood	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
turning	O
back	O
again	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
on	O
Jones	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
dropt	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
Jones	O
denyed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
they	O
came	O
back	O
to	O
buy	O
more	O
Silk	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
piece	O
mention	O
'd	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
.	O
Simpson	O
pleaded	O
,	O
that	O
Jones	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
for	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
she	O
was	O
quilting	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
Jones	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Furbelow	O
Scarf	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
several	O
Shops	O
but	O
could	O
meet	O
with	O
none	O
to	O
fit	O
her	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
short	O
Woman	O
;	O
whereupon	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
to	O
buy	O
Silk	O
to	O
make	O
one	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
bought	O
Silk	O
for	O
one	O
and	O
paid	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
Home	O
,	O
bethought	O
her	O
self	O
that	O
her	O
Hood	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
old	O
and	O
rusty	O
,	O
would	O
not	O
look	O
well	O
with	O
a	O
new	O
Scarf	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
buy	O
more	O
Silk	O
for	O
a	O
Hood	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
charged	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
with	O
stealing	O
the	O
Silk	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
declared	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
very	O
full	O
and	O
positive	O
against	O
Jones	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Stephen	I-place
Colemanstreet	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Constable	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intention	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
January	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
6	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
he	O
hearing	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
breaking	O
open	O
his	O
Lock	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
let	O
him	O
alone	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Collar	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
Town	O
on	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Business	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
his	O
Order	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
Cart	O
and	O
Horses	O
with	O
Gardening	O
for	O
Stock-Market	O
,	O
which	O
having	O
deliver	O
'd	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
for	O
a	O
Load	O
of	O
Dung	O
to	O
an	O
Inn	O
next	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
just	O
as	O
he	O
came	O
against	O
his	O
Door	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
out	O
and	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
His	O
Master	O
deposed	O
he	O
sent	O
him	O
to	O
Market	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
and	O
order	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
bring	O
Home	O
a	O
Load	O
of	O
Dung	O
from	O
the	O
said	O
Inn	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bryan	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Stockwell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
January	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Pocket	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Bride-Lane	B-place
in	I-place
Fleet-Street	I-place
,	O
and	O
being	O
seen	O
by	O
another	O
Person	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
secur	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Hand	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Stephen	I-place
Coleman-street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Book	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
History	O
of	O
Genesis	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Vincent	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
pair	O
of	O
Childrens	O
Shoes	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Trefosa	B-pers
Rans	I-pers
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Blincoe	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Black	O
Mare	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Vincent	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
John	O
Blincoe	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mildred	I-place
Poultry	I-place
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Black	O
Mare	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Reeve	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
ever	O
possest	O
of	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
Mares	O
in	O
London	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
Chinkford	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Essex	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Penelope	B-pers
Dye	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
New	I-place
Fish-street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
36	O
pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
called	O
Guineas	O
,	O
8	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
number	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Canvas	O
Bag	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Paul	B-pers
Howel	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
January	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Monument	B-place
Yard	I-place
about	I-place
8	I-place
a	I-place
Clock	I-place
at	I-place
Night	I-place
,	I-place
as	I-place
he	I-place
went	I-place
towards	I-place
the	I-place
Bridge	I-place
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
Stop	O
of	O
Carts	O
and	O
Coaches	O
,	O
insomuch	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
pass	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
stood	O
up	O
till	O
the	O
Passage	O
should	O
be	O
clear	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
felt	O
her	O
take	O
the	O
Bag	O
of	O
Money	O
aforesaid	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
at	O
first	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
said	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Hoop-Tavern	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
again	O
;	O
that	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
drinking	O
there	O
,	O
she	O
sometimes	O
promised	O
him	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
at	O
other	O
times	O
denied	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
any	O
of	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
till	O
at	O
last	O
his	O
Patience	O
being	O
wore	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
some	O
under	O
the	O
Chairs	O
,	O
some	O
fell	O
from	O
her	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Bag	O
was	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
just	O
by	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Drawer	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
rung	O
and	O
sent	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
raised	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Chair	O
feeling	O
about	O
her	O
Petticoats	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
4	O
Guineas	O
under	O
the	O
Chairs	O
she	O
sat	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Bag	O
just	O
by	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
he	O
found	O
two	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
dropt	O
from	O
her	O
Petticoat	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
acknowledged	O
nothing	O
then	O
,	O
but	O
swore	O
and	O
tore	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
great	O
noise	O
for	O
a	O
long	O
while	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
of	O
the	O
Night	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
so	O
great	O
a	O
Disturbance	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
another	O
Constable	O
to	O
his	O
Assistance	O
,	O
who	O
searching	O
her	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
took	O
11	O
Guineas	O
and	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Silver	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
perceiving	O
a	O
Six	O
Pence	O
mark	O
'd	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
remarkable	O
pieces	O
among	O
his	O
Money	O
;	O
who	O
reply	O
'd	O
Yes	O
,	O
a	O
Sixpence	O
mark	O
'd	O
with	O
three	O
Letters	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
1	O
E	O
S	O
,	O
which	O
answer	O
'd	O
exactly	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Six	O
Pences	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Pocket	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Drawer	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Bag	O
,	O
also	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
remarkable	O
for	O
its	O
being	O
dearn	O
'd	O
with	O
White	O
Thread	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
also	O
described	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
Constable	O
confirmed	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
Money	O
and	O
Bag	O
were	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Bag	O
and	O
remarkable	O
Sixpence	O
swore	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Also	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
that	O
day	O
pay	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
that	O
remarkable	O
Sixpence	O
among	O
other	O
Money	O
,	O
appear	O
'd	O
and	O
justified	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
Constables	O
likewise	O
deposed	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
took	O
her	O
the	O
denied	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Money	O
,	O
or	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
also	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
about	O
5	O
l.	O
in	O
Gold	O
and	O
Silver	O
about	O
her	O
of	O
her	O
own	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
acquainted	O
together	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
received	O
several	O
Sums	O
of	O
Money	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
using	O
to	O
call	O
upon	O
her	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
Town	O
;	O
that	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
Tavern	O
together	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
complaining	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
then	O
urgent	O
Occasions	O
for	O
a	O
greater	O
Sum	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
she	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
all	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
do	O
him	O
some	O
Services	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
very	O
Friendly	O
at	O
the	O
Tavern	O
without	O
any	O
Disturbance	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
paid	O
two	O
Reckonings	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
refused	O
him	O
some	O
Requests	O
,	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
his	O
Money	O
again	O
,	O
so	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
following	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
said	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
.	O
A	O
Woman	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
met	O
her	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Wine	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
shov	O
'd	O
him	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
about	O
his	O
Business	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
then	O
going	O
by	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
saw	O
them	O
go	O
together	O
down	O
Grace-Church-Street	O
towards	O
the	O
Bridge	O
.	O
The	O
Drawer	O
of	O
the	O
Hoop-Tavern	O
being	O
also	O
call	O
'd	O
again	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
there	O
two	O
Hours	O
and	O
upwards	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
paid	O
two	O
Reckonings	O
before	O
any	O
Disturbance	O
happen	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
afterwards	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
complained	O
she	O
had	O
had	O
pickt	O
his	O
Pocket	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Constables	O
deposed	O
also	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Money	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
neither	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
fuddled	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
denied	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
acquainted	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
he	O
ever	O
saw	O
her	O
before	O
to	O
his	O
Knowledge	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
Surprise	O
when	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Money	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
calling	O
none	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
May	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Gils	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Worsted	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Poke	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
workt	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
under	O
the	O
Petticoats	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
first	O
Fact	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Helson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dunn	I-pers
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Chare-Woman	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
there	O
two	O
Nights	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Watch	O
which	O
hung	O
at	O
his	O
Beds-head	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
at	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
for	O
22	O
s.	O
she	O
confest	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
on	O
her	O
Tryal	O
,	O
nor	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
Walter	B-pers
Casey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Wooden	O
Box	O
,	O
a	O
wrought	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Petticoat	O
9	O
Holland	O
Smocks	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jemima	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
:	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Spavin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White	I-place
Chapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
64	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
White	O
Lead	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Lindsey	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Labourer	O
at	O
the	O
White-Lead-House	B-place
in	I-place
White	I-place
Chapel	I-place
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
offering	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Quarrel	O
's	O
was	O
suspected	O
and	O
apprehended	O
.	O
His	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Lead	O
was	O
left	O
at	O
his	O
house	O
in	O
a	O
bag	O
;	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Charity	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
at	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Pewter	O
pint	O
Pots	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
drinking	O
Glass	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hartley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
(	O
who	O
keeps	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
)	O
had	O
invited	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
other	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
to	O
eat	O
some	O
Rost	O
Beet	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
Day	O
after	O
Christmas-Day	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
,	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
intimate	O
Friends	O
among	O
themselves	O
,	O
and	O
Customers	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
went	O
and	O
were	O
very	O
merry	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
plentifully	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
of	O
Rum	O
as	O
other	O
Liquors	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
stealing	O
the	O
Pots	O
and	O
Glass	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
which	O
turn	O
'd	O
their	O
Mirth	O
into	O
Sorrow	O
,	O
and	O
fulfill	O
'd	O
two	O
old	O
Proverbs	O
at	O
once	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
that	O
after	O
sweet	O
Meat	O
comes	O
sower	O
Sauce	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
To	O
give	O
one	O
roast-meat	O
and	O
beat	O
one	O
with	O
the	O
Spit	O
.	O
But	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
fix	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Selby	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davenport	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
one	O
Ring	O
set	O
with	O
Stones	O
,	O
a	O
Snuff	O
Box	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
5	O
pieces	O
of	O
Silver	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Main	I-pers
;	O
and	O
Thomas	O
Davenport	O
as	O
Accessory	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
Selby	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
Davenport	O
;	O
which	O
she	O
acknowledged	O
on	O
her	O
Tryal	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
that	O
Davenport	O
knew	O
not	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
acquitted	O
Davenport	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Selby	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Child	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Black	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
January	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bridle	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Saddle	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
Reeves	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
his	O
Horse	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Stable	O
at	O
Bulford	B-place
near	I-place
Amesbury	I-place
in	I-place
Wiltshire	I-place
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Stable	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Beveridge	I-pers
,	O
whose	O
Friend	O
was	O
about	O
buying	O
him	O
for	O
7	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
Crown	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Smithfield	O
to	O
have	O
him	O
Tol	O
'd	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
produce	O
no	O
Vouchers	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
they	O
found	O
a	O
Reward	O
of	O
20	O
l.	O
publish	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
News	O
Paper	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Gelding	O
,	O
whereupon	O
they	O
secur	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
Bridle	O
and	O
Saddle	O
on	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
no	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
5	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Joyce	I-pers
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Ann	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Joyce	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
one	O
Ann	B-pers
Murfey	I-pers
came	O
to	O
her	O
Shop	O
to	O
Cheapen	O
Meat	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
mist	O
it	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
none	O
else	O
being	O
there	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
crying	O
out	O
her	O
Pocket	O
was	O
pickt	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
,	O
who	O
put	O
2	O
Half	O
Crowns	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
her	O
a	O
print	O
of	O
Wine	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
come	O
from	O
Ireland	O
but	O
7	O
weeks	O
;	O
but	O
called	O
none	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wellbone	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Liberty	B-place
of	I-place
the	I-place
Old	I-place
Artillery	I-place
Ground	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Country	I-place
of	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Geudwin	I-pers
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
January	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
value	O
14	O
s	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Parlour	O
Window	O
was	O
broke	O
and	O
his	O
Coat	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
hearing	O
a	O
Noise	O
there	O
took	O
a	O
Candle	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
jump	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
as	O
did	O
also	O
another	O
Evidence	O
;	O
that	O
crying	O
out	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Street	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
past	O
along	O
accidentally	O
they	O
seized	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
none	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
swear	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Hester	B-pers
Delamore	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Muslin	O
,	O
Turnovers	O
,	O
3	O
Stocks	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Flaxen	O
sheets	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Ward	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
let	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
Room	O
ready	O
furnish	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
Sheets	O
were	O
taken	O
off	O
the	O
Bed	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Jennings	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
Mr	O
.	O
Wards	O
Goods	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
when	O
she	O
had	O
Money	O
would	O
fetch	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
And	O
as	O
to	O
her	O
own	O
Goods	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
them	O
between	O
the	O
Mother	O
and	O
the	O
Daughter	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
carry	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
a	O
Pawnbrokers	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
found	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Mother	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
pawned	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
they	O
lay	O
together	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Portmanteau	O
Trunk	O
,	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
Wastcoat	O
and	O
Breeches	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Scarlet	O
Breeches	O
laced	O
with	O
Gold	O
Lace	O
,	O
and	O
7	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
13	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Neal	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
Captain	O
Neal	O
and	O
his	O
Servant	O
came	O
to	O
Town	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Man	O
carried	O
the	O
Horses	O
and	O
Portmanteau	O
to	O
Warwicks	B-place
Stables	I-place
,	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
more	O
were	O
busy	O
about	O
the	O
Horses	O
in	O
the	O
Stables	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
Lurking	O
about	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Portmanteau	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Stable	O
and	O
carryed	O
it	O
off	O
.	O
That	O
afterwards	O
the	O
Captain	O
's	O
Servant	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Bear	O
and	O
Harrow	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Butcher	O
Row	O
with	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Clothes	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
,	O
apprehended	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
pleaded	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Clothes	O
in	O
Newtoners	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
searched	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Leather	O
Lane	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
found	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Goods	O
;	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
former	O
he	O
called	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Beggar	I-pers
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
their	O
Landlord	O
lend	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
Guinea	O
to	O
buy	O
the	O
Clothes	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
buy	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
Colour	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
describe	O
them	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
a	O
light	O
Colour	O
,	O
lined	O
with	O
a	O
light	O
Silk	O
,	O
and	O
trim	O
'd	O
with	O
a	O
Silver	O
;	O
which	O
Description	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
wrong	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Clothes	O
being	O
produc	O
'd	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
his	O
Man	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
proved	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
light	O
,	O
but	O
lined	O
with	O
a	O
Blue	O
Silk	O
and	O
no	O
Trimming	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Laurence	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
4	O
Wooden	O
Pipes	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
New	B-pers
River	I-pers
Company	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Company	O
's	O
Servants	O
were	O
moving	O
their	O
Pipes	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
4	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
lost	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
draw	O
away	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
Wheeler	O
's	O
Yard	O
in	O
Elm-Street	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
a	O
Shilling	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
pleaded	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
a	O
Scavenger	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
with	O
his	O
Cart	O
where	O
the	O
Company	O
's	O
Servants	O
were	O
at	O
work	O
,	O
they	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
they	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
old	O
Pipes	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
lay	O
them	O
down	O
a	O
Load	O
of	O
Ashes	O
to	O
raise	O
their	O
Work	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
his	O
Bargain	O
,	O
but	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
Masters	O
he	O
had	O
served	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Row	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White-Chapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Mares	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
each	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Colt	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Jefferies	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
January	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bridle	O
,	O
a	O
Leather	O
Saddle	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Splatterdashes	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Jefferies	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
2	O
Mares	O
and	O
Colt	O
were	O
Stolen	O
from	O
his	O
Father	O
's	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Bridle	O
and	O
Saddle	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Stable	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
Red	O
Cow	O
in	O
White-Chappel	O
in	O
Possession	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
owned	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Ostler	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
Mares	O
,	O
Colt	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
into	O
the	O
Inn	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Jefferies	O
pursued	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Splatter-dashes	O
were	O
found	O
on	O
his	O
Legs	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
very	O
full	O
)	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Kidgell	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
6	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
a	O
Stone	O
Ring	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stone	O
Ear-Rings	O
set	O
in	O
Gold	O
,	O
a	O
Cypher	O
Ring	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
;	O
and	O
20	O
Yard	O
of	O
Lace	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hodgkins	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
Hodgkins	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
a	O
Pawnbroker	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
ill	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
her	O
Trunk	O
was	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Goods	O
found	O
therein	O
.	O
She	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
which	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Young	O
Master	O
kept	O
late	O
Hours	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
conceal	O
it	O
from	O
from	O
his	O
Father	O
:	O
but	O
none	O
appeared	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39s	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Ireland	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Callicoe	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Quilted	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
2	O
Holland	O
Shifts	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Clogs	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Baddiley	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
George	O
Baddiley	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Hired	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
of	O
his	O
Wives	O
Clothes	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
them	O
upon	O
her	O
about	O
a	O
Week	O
after	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Blackstone	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
in	I-place
White	I-place
Chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
18	O
Ells	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
9	O
Yards	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
a	O
Dimity	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
Child	O
's	O
Shirt	O
and	O
a	O
Pocket	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Robert	O
Clarke	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
;	O
that	O
his	O
Shutter	O
was	O
slipt	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Sash	O
lifted	O
up	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Iron	O
Bar	O
was	O
not	O
fastened	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
himself	O
committed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
opened	O
the	O
Shutter	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
stood	O
to	O
watch	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
Johnson	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
his	O
Master	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
served	O
him	O
4	O
Years	O
of	O
his	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
robbed	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
gone	O
from	O
him	O
some	O
time	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Hens	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
Cock	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
Turkey	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Frying-Pan	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Arthur	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Holstock	I-pers
and	O
Johanna	B-pers
Radwell	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Pint	O
Pot	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Elijah	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
Johanna	O
Radwell	O
as	O
Accessary	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Pot	O
the	O
27th	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
Holstock	O
the	O
29th	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
confest	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
Radwell	O
,	O
who	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
3l	O
.	O
l	O
s	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
an	O
old	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Topknots	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Pot	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
Holstock	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
gather	O
in	O
her	O
Master	O
's	O
Pots	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Pint	O
Pot	O
was	O
amongst	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
it	O
till	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
Radwell	O
.	O
Radwell	O
pleaded	O
,	O
that	O
Holstock	O
brought	O
the	O
Pot	O
to	O
her	O
before	O
the	O
was	O
up	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
great	O
Luck	O
that	O
Morning	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
found	O
a	O
Silver	O
Pot	O
,	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
out	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
Necessaries	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
believing	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
honest	O
,	O
did	O
sell	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
intended	O
to	O
let	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
have	O
the	O
full	O
value	O
as	O
she	O
shou	O
'd	O
have	O
Occasion	O
.	O
But	O
this	O
Plea	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Holstock	O
of	O
stealing	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
her	O
Master	O
,	O
Death	O
:	O
and	O
Radwell	O
as	O
Accessary	O
in	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bartram	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Blackwall	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
two	O
Brass	O
Guns	O
,	O
2	O
Iron	O
Dogs	O
,	O
Lead	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Thomas	B-pers
Earl	I-pers
of	I-pers
Strafford	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
of	O
Sir	O
H.	O
Johnson	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
hired	O
a	O
Waterman	O
's	O
Boy	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
down	O
from	O
Limus	O
to	O
Blackwall	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
made	O
the	O
Boat	O
fast	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
their	O
Houses	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
Porkstakes	O
and	O
Black-Puddings	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
had	O
put	O
the	O
Guns	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
into	O
the	O
Boat	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
they	O
called	O
him	O
to	O
bring	O
them	O
back	O
again	O
;	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Seawell	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
,	O
two	O
Custom-house	O
Watermen	O
,	O
suspecting	O
they	O
were	O
running	O
of	O
Goods	O
,	O
rowed	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
the	O
Guns	O
,	O
Lead	O
,	O
and	O
Iron	O
in	O
the	O
Boat	O
,	O
secured	O
them	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
St.	O
Catherines	O
;	O
and	O
understanding	O
by	O
the	O
Boy	O
that	O
he	O
brought	O
them	O
from	O
Blackwall	O
,	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
cry	O
'd	O
there	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
own	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
said	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Guns	O
in	O
Ditch	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
believing	O
them	O
,	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
at	I-place
Stepney	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
21	O
Ells	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Goodman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Rigby	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
value	O
8s	O
.	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Bodice	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hayes	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
took	O
her	O
Key	O
,	O
open	O
'd	O
her	O
Trunk	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
confest	O
the	O
same	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Stretch	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pawned	O
the	O
Petticoat	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Charge	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
George	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
buying	O
stolen	O
Goods	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Clarkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
6l	O
.	O
of	O
Kidney	O
Suit	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Sparkley	I-pers
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
a	O
Muslin	O
Apron	O
,	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
January	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
missing	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
sent	O
her	O
Husband	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
who	O
overtook	O
her	O
with	O
them	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Pool	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Camblet	O
Riding-Hood	O
and	O
14	O
Yards	O
of	O
Persian	O
Silk	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
30s	O
.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
and	I-pers
Richard	I-pers
Dickens	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
January	O
;	O
and	O
Elizabeth	O
Pool	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Dickens	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Evans	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
on	O
liking	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Apprentice	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
finding	O
him	O
not	O
fit	O
for	O
his	O
service	O
,	O
discharged	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
a	O
Pawnbroker	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
to	O
Pool	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
come	O
to	O
pawn	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
confest	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
Evans	O
,	O
and	O
Evans	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
Shop	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Dickens	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
theirs	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
Shop	O
.	O
The	O
Pawnbroker	O
deposed	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
from	O
Pool	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
a	O
Woman	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Silk	O
to	O
line	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
9	O
Yards	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
measuring	O
and	O
finding	O
near	O
14	O
,	O
stopt	O
her	O
and	O
gave	O
notice	O
as	O
before	O
.	O
Their	O
Confession	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
very	O
full	O
)	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
Evans	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
nor	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
some	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
did	O
Pool	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Facts	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
;	O
Evans	O
of	O
privately	O
stealing	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Death	O
:	O
and	O
Pool	O
as	O
Accessary	O
,	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Osborn	I-pers
by	O
giving	O
her	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
near	O
the	O
Left	O
Pap	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
an	O
Inch	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
6	O
Inches	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
on	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
Stabbing	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Lund	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
himself	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Tannet	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
were	O
at	O
Supper	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Griffin	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Three	B-place
Pidgeons	I-place
in	I-place
Smithfield	I-place
,	O
and	O
had	O
two	O
Bottles	O
of	O
Wine	O
after	O
Supper	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Husband	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
down	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Tannet	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
below	O
would	O
speak	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
who	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
matter	O
enough	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
was	O
shewn	O
through	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
into	O
the	O
little	O
Parlour	O
behind	O
it	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Deceased	O
lying	O
on	O
her	O
Back	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
thought	O
murder	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
Head	O
either	O
against	O
the	O
Frame	O
of	O
the	O
Table	O
or	O
on	O
the	O
Boy	O
's	O
Feet	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
how	O
it	O
came	O
and	O
was	O
answer	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Bitch	O
had	O
murder	O
'd	O
her	O
self	O
in	O
putting	O
up	O
the	O
Pewter	O
;	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Tannet	O
came	O
down	O
immediately	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
sat	O
her	O
up	O
upon	O
her	O
Breech	O
,	O
pull	O
'd	O
down	O
her	O
Clothes	O
at	O
her	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Tannet	O
put	O
his	O
Fingers	O
into	O
the	O
Wound	O
and	O
pulled	O
out	O
the	O
Clotted	O
Blood	O
;	O
She	O
was	O
almost	O
suffocated	O
with	O
the	O
Blood	O
in	O
her	O
Mouth	O
and	O
Throat	O
,	O
which	O
when	O
they	O
had	O
clear	O
'd	O
by	O
wiping	O
her	O
Mouth	O
and	O
Stroaking	O
her	O
Throat	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
Senses	O
and	O
spoke	O
a	O
little	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
whether	O
she	O
knew	O
him	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
Yes	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
us	O
both	O
?	O
Yes	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
you	O
do	O
?	O
Yes	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
Betty	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
stab	O
your	O
self	O
?	O
She	O
answered	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
;	O
who	O
did	O
then	O
?	O
She	O
answer	O
'd	O
my	O
Mistress	O
,	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
over	O
again	O
who	O
did	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
reply	O
'd	O
again	O
,	O
Her	O
Mistress	O
;	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
sure	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
Yes	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Husband	O
said	O
,	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
ask	O
her	O
no	O
more	O
Questions	O
,	O
for	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
undone	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
advised	O
her	O
Husband	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Hawkins	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
and	O
probed	O
the	O
Wound	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
Woman	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Weapon	O
found	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Blood	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
and	O
Parlour	O
was	O
mopt	O
up	O
and	O
Sand	O
strewed	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
put	O
away	O
the	O
Sand	O
with	O
his	O
Feet	O
,	O
and	O
discerned	O
the	O
Blood	O
under	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
Headclothes	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Hair	O
lookt	O
as	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
dragged	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
into	O
the	O
Parlour	O
by	O
it	O
:	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
received	O
a	O
Cut	O
on	O
her	O
Arm	O
about	O
6	O
Weeks	O
before	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
shewed	O
him	O
,	O
saying	O
her	O
Mistress	O
did	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
believed	O
she	O
should	O
be	O
Murdered	O
one	O
time	O
or	O
other	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
spoke	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
passionate	O
to	O
her	O
Maid	O
,	O
who	O
replyed	O
,	O
D-n	O
her	O
,	O
a	O
B-	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
be	O
her	O
Butcher	O
one	O
times	O
or	O
other	O
;	O
he	O
replyed	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
for	O
her	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
answered	O
,	O
that	O
for	O
believed	O
no	O
Body	O
would	O
think	O
it	O
worth	O
their	O
while	O
to	O
hang	O
her	O
for	O
killing	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Tannet	O
confirm	O
'd	O
his	O
being	O
at	O
Supper	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Lund	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Griffin	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Lund	O
's	O
being	O
called	O
down	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
his	O
finding	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
little	O
Parlour	O
,	O
the	O
raising	O
of	O
her	O
on	O
her	O
Breech	O
,	O
and	O
clearing	O
the	O
Blood	O
from	O
her	O
Wound	O
and	O
Mouth	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
several	O
Questions	O
and	O
Answers	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
declared	O
three	O
times	O
that	O
her	O
Mistress	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
before	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Lund	O
's	O
Evidence	O
;	O
and	O
farther	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
helpt	O
her	O
up	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
lent	O
Mr.	O
Griffin	O
his	O
Knife	O
to	O
cut	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Stays	O
,	O
who	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
undress	O
'd	O
her	O
and	O
laid	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
placed	O
it	O
by	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
(	O
Mr.	O
Tannet	O
)	O
asking	O
Mr.	O
Griffin	O
for	O
his	O
Knife	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
what	O
signifies	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
reach	O
'd	O
over	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Body	O
,	O
and	O
(	O
moving	O
it	O
a	O
little	O
)	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
observed	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
and	O
Parlour	O
mopp	O
'd	O
up	O
and	O
strewed	O
over	O
with	O
Sand	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
Lock	O
of	O
Hair	O
stood	O
out	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
dragg	O
'd	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
bound	O
up	O
her	O
Arm	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
cut	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
enquir	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
Weapon	O
with	O
which	O
this	O
Bloody	O
Fact	O
was	O
comitted	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Griffin	O
answer	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
search	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
often	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
abuse	O
the	O
Deceased	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
about	O
2	O
Months	O
before	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
give	O
the	O
Deceased	O
a	O
Cut	O
over	O
her	O
Arm	O
with	O
a	O
Case	O
Knife	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
said	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
her	O
Butcher	O
then	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
some	O
time	O
or	O
other	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hawkins	O
(	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
)	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
about	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
through	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
into	O
a	O
Room	O
behind	O
it	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Deceased	O
sat	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
supported	O
by	O
Two	O
Persons	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
probed	O
her	O
Wound	O
,	O
which	O
penetrated	O
into	O
her	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
all	O
the	O
Symptoms	O
of	O
Death	O
were	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
her	O
up	O
Stairs	O
and	O
laid	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
desired	O
the	O
Man	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
to	O
carry	O
up	O
some	O
clean	O
Linnen	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
very	O
Bloody	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Knockells	O
opened	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
large	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Blood	O
in	O
her	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Wound	O
near	O
through	O
her	O
Heart	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
shape	O
of	O
the	O
Wound	O
,	O
he	O
judged	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
done	O
with	O
an	O
Instrument	O
small	O
at	O
the	O
point	O
and	O
growing	O
wider	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
Bayonet	O
or	O
large	O
Iron	O
Scure	O
:	O
And	O
there	O
having	O
been	O
a	O
Report	O
given	O
out	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
they	O
opened	O
the	O
Womb	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
all	O
the	O
Demonstrations	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
(	O
Aunt	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
)	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Samuel	B-pers
Banister	I-pers
called	O
her	O
about	O
10	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
telling	O
her	O
that	O
the	O
Maid	O
was	O
very	O
bad	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Midwife	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
Betty	O
(	O
the	O
Deceased	O
)	O
died	O
suddenly	O
of	O
a	O
Convulsion	O
Fit	O
;	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Griffin	O
told	O
her	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
no	O
Words	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
by	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
fell	O
down	O
in	O
Convulsion	O
Fit	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Case	O
Knife	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
gave	O
her	O
Wine	O
in	O
a	O
Cup	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
she	O
should	O
bite	O
a	O
Glass	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
there	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
intended	O
to	O
bury	O
her	O
then	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
the	O
Coroner	O
must	O
sit	O
on	O
her	O
first	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
this	O
Evidence	O
reply	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
never	O
knew	O
the	O
Coroner	O
sit	O
on	O
any	O
that	O
dyed	O
of	O
the	O
Convulsions	O
;	O
and	O
went	O
home	O
and	O
acquainted	O
her	O
Husband	O
with	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
heard	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Wife	O
coming	O
back	O
with	O
this	O
strange	O
Story	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Knockells	O
,	O
knockt	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Deceased	O
dead	O
on	O
the	O
Floor	O
,	O
stript	O
and	O
a	O
Bloody	O
Cloth	O
over	O
her	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knockells	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Deceased	O
on	O
the	O
Floor	O
naked	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Sheet	O
over	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
probe	O
the	O
Wound	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
Probe	O
was	O
not	O
long	O
enough	O
,	O
wherefore	O
he	O
desired	O
Mr.	O
Griffin	O
to	O
lend	O
him	O
a	O
Large	O
Scure	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
refused	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
tear	O
her	O
Flesh	O
,	O
here	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
already	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
's	O
no	O
Occasion	O
.	O
That	O
himself	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Hawkins	O
opened	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
3	O
Pints	O
or	O
2	O
Quarts	O
of	O
Blood	O
poured	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Wound	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
9	O
or	O
10	O
Inches	O
deep	O
,	O
quite	O
through	O
the	O
Lungs	O
,	O
and	O
almost	O
through	O
the	O
Heart	O
:	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
with	O
Child	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
protested	O
her	O
Innocence	O
;	O
and	O
urged	O
as	O
a	O
Proof	O
thereof	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
fly	O
;	O
which	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
done	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
conscious	O
to	O
her	O
self	O
of	O
her	O
own	O
Innocency	O
,	O
having	O
Opportunity	O
enough	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
before	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
:	O
She	O
also	O
observed	O
that	O
when	O
M.	O
Lund	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Tannet	O
gave	O
their	O
Evidence	O
before	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
then	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
when	O
ask	O
'd	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Lund	O
who	O
did	O
it	O
,	O
said	O
only	O
Miss-not	O
Mistress	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
now	O
swear	O
.	O
She	O
also	O
called	O
the	O
following	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
Ironing	O
in	O
her	O
Master	O
's	O
Kitchen	O
with	O
a	O
Case	O
Knife	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
Love	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Tannet	O
,	O
who	O
slighted	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
heard	O
of	O
Love	O
Powder	O
to	O
gain	O
Mens	O
Affections	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
knew	O
of	O
any	O
such	O
,	O
or	O
where	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
had	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
told	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
read	O
in	O
Mother	O
Bunch	O
of	O
a	O
Seed	O
called	O
Cummin	O
Seed	O
,	O
which	O
beat	O
to	O
Powder	O
and	O
put	O
into	O
Ale	O
would	O
have	O
that	O
Effect	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
shewed	O
her	O
some	O
she	O
had	O
bought	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
it	O
him	O
in	O
Ale	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
signified	O
nothing	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
gave	O
him	O
another	O
Pennyworth	O
in	O
half	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Claret	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
no	O
purpose	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
gave	O
him	O
another	O
Penny	O
worth	O
in	O
Ale	O
,	O
without	O
straining	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
complained	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
Drink	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Tap-Tub	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
as	O
good	O
as	O
she	O
drank	O
herself	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Wyman	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
came	O
to	O
beg	O
a	O
Plaister	O
for	O
her	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
asking	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
Cut	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
playing	O
with	O
a	O
Hatter	O
's	O
Man	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
8	O
or	O
9	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
Mistresses	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
Relation	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
answered	O
,	O
Her	O
Sister	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
others	O
appeared	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
as	O
honest	O
and	O
industrious	O
,	O
not	O
given	O
to	O
Swear	O
,	O
nor	O
to	O
Passion	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
one	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
observed	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
very	O
orderly	O
with	O
her	O
Children	O
to	O
Church	O
of	O
a	O
Sunday	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
Evening	O
Sermon	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
into	O
a	O
Room	O
and	O
hear	O
them	O
read	O
good	O
Books	O
;	O
and	O
another	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
notice	O
of	O
her	O
promoting	O
the	O
Interests	O
of	O
her	O
Servants	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
Guilty	O
of	O
all	O
three	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dickin	I-pers
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Catherine	B-pers
Huckle	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High	O
way	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Bodily	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
Union	O
Street	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
Hand	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
refusing	O
,	O
they	O
carryed	O
her	O
by	O
force	O
into	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
drank	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Twopenny	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
threw	O
the	O
rest	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
paid	O
for	O
the	O
Pint	O
(	O
which	O
she	O
said	O
was	O
all	O
they	O
had	O
)	O
it	O
they	O
would	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
abused	O
her	O
very	O
much	O
;	O
that	O
being	O
of	O
a	O
Gore	O
Blood	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
another	O
House	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Ale	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
waylaid	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
lye	O
with	O
them	O
they	O
'd	O
Gag	O
her	O
and	O
make	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
Jones	O
took	O
her	O
Handkerchief	O
off	O
her	O
Neck	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
Words	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
cryed	O
out	O
Murder	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
over	O
the	O
Water	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
Friend	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
back	O
met	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
(	O
who	O
they	O
were	O
very	O
well	O
acquainted	O
with	O
)	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
was	O
she	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
drank	O
together	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
bragg	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
lately	O
Danced	O
for	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Pumps	O
and	O
won	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
fell	O
into	O
the	O
Kennel	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
Murder	O
as	O
if	O
the	O
Devil	O
was	O
in	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
they	O
offer	O
'd	O
her	O
no	O
harm	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Dalton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Woman	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
in	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Men	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Fine	O
Ale	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
for	O
another	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
Hot	O
Pot	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
agree	O
to	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
hearing	O
a	O
Disturbance	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
quarelling	O
about	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
they	O
wou	O
'd	O
have	O
her	O
pay	O
her	O
Share	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
refused	O
;	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
great	O
Noise	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
indict	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
Acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
10	O
pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Stockings	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Eldridge	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
enter	O
'd	O
them	O
down	O
in	O
his	O
Book	O
as	O
sold	O
to	O
other	O
Persons	O
on	O
trust	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
ask	O
the	O
Money	O
for	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
those	O
they	O
were	O
charg	O
'd	O
to	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
confest	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
where	O
the	O
Woman	O
liv	O
'd	O
who	O
was	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
them	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
at	O
whose	O
House	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
.	O
It	O
appearing	O
not	O
to	O
amount	O
to	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Cheat	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Williamson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shift	O
and	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Plate	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
at	I-place
Hackney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
12	O
truffes	O
of	O
Hay	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
trusses	O
of	O
Straw	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
January	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
11	O
Yards	O
and	O
Half	O
of	O
Stuff	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Fenwick	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
in	O
her	O
Parlour	O
behind	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
immediately	O
sent	O
her	O
Servant	O
after	O
her	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Neal	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
hearing	O
the	O
Cry	O
of	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
turn	O
'd	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drop	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
but	O
a	O
bare	O
denial	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
nor	O
none	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
of	O
St.Martins	B-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
14	O
Boards	O
,	O
a	O
Window	O
Shutter	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Timber	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
of	O
St	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
stolen	O
Goods	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Kelloe	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
stolen	O
Goods	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Josheph	B-pers
Bilson	I-pers
of	O
Enfield	B-place
.	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
8	O
Hens	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Pepper	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
January	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Enfield	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
Sheets	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
Diaper	O
Table	O
Cloth	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Shirt	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Goddard	I-pers
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
January	O
,	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
by	O
striking	O
,	O
kicking	O
and	O
Bruising	O
of	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Side	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
December	O
following	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
two	O
Men	O
called	O
out	O
one	O
Williams	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Journeyman	O
)	O
about	O
7	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
about	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
the	O
said	O
Williams	O
came	O
up	O
again	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceased	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
again	O
himself	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
going	O
down	O
Stairs	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
his	O
Master	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
met	O
him	O
about	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceased	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
,	O
who	O
answered	O
him	O
,	O
down	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
up	O
and	O
mind	O
his	O
Business	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
go	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
beat	O
him	O
,	O
kickt	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Heel	O
of	O
his	O
Shoe	O
,	O
and	O
thrust	O
him	O
down	O
Stairs	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
Lord	O
Bless	O
you	O
,	O
Master	O
,	O
for	O
Jesus	O
Christ	O
's	O
sake	O
have	O
Mercy	O
upon	O
me	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Wife	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
the	O
Deceased	O
alone	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
would	O
hurt	O
himself	O
more	O
than	O
his	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
whom	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
workt	O
any	O
more	O
that	O
Night	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
Shoes	O
that	O
must	O
be	O
done	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
his	O
Master	O
would	O
beat	O
him	O
again	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
workt	O
about	O
a	O
Week	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
home	O
to	O
his	O
Mother	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Blooded	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
Mother	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
again	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
his	O
Master	O
had	O
beat	O
him	O
,	O
thrown	O
him	O
down	O
Stairs	O
.	O
pusht	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
died	O
his	O
Master	O
was	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
his	O
Mother	O
to	O
Prosecute	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
his	O
Mother	O
his	O
Master	O
had	O
beat	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knockells	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
in	O
a	O
Fever	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Tumour	O
in	O
his	O
Side	O
;	O
when	O
open	O
'd	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
Imposthumation	O
in	O
the	O
Liver	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Bruise	O
on	O
the	O
Region	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Quart	O
of	O
Corruption	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Surgeons	O
he	O
consulted	O
,	O
were	O
of	O
Opinion	O
that	O
the	O
Bruise	O
was	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wilkins	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Deceased	O
on	O
the	O
3rd	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
Fever	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
complain	O
'd	O
of	O
a	O
pain	O
in	O
his	O
side	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
who	O
drest	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
off	O
the	O
Plaister	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
saw	O
no	O
Discolouration	O
of	O
Tumour	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
present	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
,	O
when	O
opened	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
Imposthumation	O
in	O
the	O
Liver	O
,	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
Pints	O
of	O
Corruption	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Ulcer	O
large	O
enough	O
to	O
contain	O
his	O
Fist	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Discolourment	O
outwardly	O
on	O
his	O
Side	O
.	O
Mr.Cole	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
present	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
,	O
and	O
expected	O
to	O
find	O
a	O
Depression	O
on	O
the	O
Ribs	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
none	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knockells	O
standing	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Depression	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
so	O
much	O
Matter	O
must	O
occasion	O
a	O
Tumour	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
gentle	O
Correction	O
with	O
his	O
Hand	O
only	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
kick	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Roberts	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Shop	O
joining	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
,	O
heard	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
crying	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
complained	O
to	O
him	O
of	O
an	O
ugly	O
Fall	O
he	O
had	O
coming	O
over	O
the	O
Church-Yard	O
,	O
which	O
hurt	O
his	O
Side	O
some	O
Time	O
ago	O
.	O
Another	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
beat	O
the	O
Deceased	O
with	O
his	O
hand	O
only	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
complained	O
of	O
a	O
Pain	O
in	O
his	O
Side	O
above	O
a	O
Year	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
drink	O
Geneva	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
lay	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
Day	O
for	O
Ease	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
lye	O
out	O
of	O
Nights	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
Drinker	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
two	O
who	O
had	O
served	O
their	O
Times	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
abuse	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Master	O
.	O
And	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
who	O
had	O
a	O
Nephew	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
put	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
served	O
his	O
Time	O
out	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
good	O
a	O
Master	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
another	O
to	O
put	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Trade	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
put	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
notwithstanding	O
what	O
has	O
happen	O
'd	O
.	O
A	O
great	O
many	O
more	O
appeared	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
Sober	O
Good	O
Man	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Hoe	I-pers
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
on	O
Board	O
a	O
Ship	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Rosemary-Lane	O
enquired	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
the	O
Change	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
who	O
is	O
known	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Callicoe	B-pers
Sarah	I-pers
)	O
coming	O
up	O
,	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
that	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
show	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
carryed	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
near	O
her	O
own	O
Habitation	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
put	O
him	O
right	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
feeling	O
for	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
mist	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
charging	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
put	O
his	O
Watch	O
into	O
his	O
Hand	O
again	O
;	O
however	O
he	O
kept	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
her	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
Everett	O
Everett	O
!	O
who	O
came	O
,	O
fell	O
upon	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
beat	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
High	O
Constable	O
was	O
denied	O
Entrance	O
for	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
heard	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
D	O
-n	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
Son	O
of	O
a	O
B	O
-	O
I	O
wish	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
gave	O
him	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
have	O
served	O
to	O
maintain	O
me	O
in	O
Newgate	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
given	O
him	O
it	O
again	O
but	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
to	O
convey	O
it	O
off	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
Child	O
at	O
Nurse	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
followed	O
her	O
and	O
struck	O
her	O
several	O
Blows	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
cryed	O
out	O
Murder	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
held	O
him	O
till	O
People	O
gathered	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
telling	O
Everett	O
how	O
he	O
had	O
abused	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
fell	O
on	O
him	O
and	O
beat	O
him	O
.	O
But	O
she	O
not	O
calling	O
Everett	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
Body	O
else	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
followeth	O
;	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
11.	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
,	O
Penelope	B-pers
Dye	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Child	I-pers
alias	O
Giles	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Rowe	I-pers
,	O
Hannah	B-pers
Holstock	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bartram	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
1.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
formerly	O
Convicted	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
,	O
i8	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Norris	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Busby	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bryan	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
May	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Helson	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Spavin	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Selby	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
alias	O
Williams	O
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Kidgell	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Blackstone	I-pers
,	O
Johanna	B-pers
Radwell	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Rigby	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Pool	O
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
alias	O
Ireland	O
.	O
The	O
Six	O
Women	O
Pleaded	O
their	O
Bellies	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
being	O
impannelled	O
,	O
found	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
with	O
Quick	O
Child	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Five	O
,	O
Not	O
with	O
Quick	O
Child	O
.	O
Some	O
BOOKS	O
printed	O
for	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
Edmund	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
and	O
Crown	O
in	O
Lombard	O
Street	O
,	O
near	O
Stocks-Market	O
.	O
The	O
London	O
New	O
Method	O
and	O
Art	O
of	O
Teaching	O
Children	O
to	O
Spell	O
and	O
Read	O
;	O
so	O
as	O
they	O
may	O
,	O
without	O
the	O
Help	O
of	O
any	O
other	O
Books	O
,	O
read	O
the	O
Bible	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
twelve	O
Months	O
.	O
Note	O
,	O
This	O
Way	O
of	O
Teaching	O
is	O
approved	O
by	O
most	O
School	O
Masters	O
as	O
the	O
best	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
6	O
d.	O
with	O
great	O
Allowance	O
to	O
those	O
who	O
sell	O
or	O
give	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
Note	O
,	O
There	O
are	O
ome	O
printed	O
on	O
Fine	O
Paper	O
,	O
bound	O
up	O
with	O
Cuts	O
.	O
pr	O
.	O
8	O
d.	O
For	O
the	O
Compleating	O
of	O
Psalmody	O
.	O
The	O
Devout	O
Singer	O
's	O
Guide	O
;	O
containing	O
all	O
the	O
Common	O
Tunes	O
now	O
in	O
use	O
,	O
with	O
Select	O
Portions	O
of	O
the	O
Psalms	O
adapted	O
to	O
each	O
Tune	O
,	O
and	O
Rules	O
for	O
singing	O
Treble	O
and	O
Bass	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
A	O
Table	O
shewing	O
at	O
one	O
View	O
what	O
Psalms	O
and	O
Hymns	O
are	O
proper	O
to	O
each	O
Tune	O
both	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Version	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Hopkins	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Sternhold	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
New	O
Version	O
of	O
Dr.	O
Brady	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Tate	O
.	O
And	O
Directions	O
for	O
Parish	O
Clerks	O
in	O
the	O
Choice	O
of	O
proper	O
Psalms	O
on	O
most	O
Occasions	O
.	O
B.	O
S.	O
Shenton	O
;	O
and	O
Recommended	O
by	O
P.	O
Joynson	O
,	O
D.	O
Warner	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Singing-Masters	O
.	O
The	O
Fourth	O
Edition	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
Five	O
Tunes	O
,	O
containing	O
their	O
Cansus	O
,	O
Medius	O
and	O
Bassus	O
,	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
former	O
Editions	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
1	O
s.	O
Aesop	O
's	O
Fables	O
,	O
with	O
Morals	O
and	O
Reflections	O
,	O
as	O
improv	O
'd	O
by	O
Sir	O
Roger	O
L'Estrange	O
,	O
done	O
into	O
Variety	O
of	O
English	O
Verse	O
.	O
Illustrated	O
with	O
Cuts	O
curiously	O
engrav	O
'd	O
on	O
Copper	O
Plates	O
.	O
Very	O
useful	O
to	O
Divert	O
and	O
Instruct	O
Young	O
Gentlemen	O
and	O
Ladies	O
in	O
the	O
Conduct	O
of	O
Human	O
Life	O
.	O
The	O
Fourth	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Arithmetick	O
made	O
easie	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
New	O
Method	O
now	O
taught	O
and	O
practis	O
'd	O
in	O
London	O
.	O
Where	O
in	O
the	O
Rules	O
of	O
that	O
necessary	O
Art	O
are	O
briefly	O
explain	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
illustrated	O
with	O
such	O
familiar	O
Examples	O
as	O
may	O
suit	O
the	O
meanest	O
Capacity	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
desire	O
to	O
learn	O
it	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
a	O
Succinct	O
Treatise	O
of	O
Decimal	O
Fractions	O
,	O
with	O
Compleat	O
Tables	O
,	O
Rules	O
,	O
and	O
Examples	O
demonstrating	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
like	O
not	O
extant	O
in	O
any	O
other	O
Treatise	O
of	O
this	O
Nature	O
.	O
The	O
Fourth	O
Edition	O
.	O
By	O
John	O
Copeland	O
,	O
Writing-Master	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
1	O
s.	O
A	O
Guide	O
to	O
English	O
Juries	O
:	O
Setting	O
forth	O
their	O
Antiquity	O
,	O
Power	O
and	O
Duty	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Common	O
Law	O
and	O
Statutes	O
.	O
With	O
a	O
Table	O
.	O
By	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
Quality	O
.	O
Also	O
a	O
Letter	O
to	O
the	O
Author	O
upon	O
the	O
same	O
Subject	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
Orders	O
,	O
By	O
Laws	O
,	O
and	O
Ordinances	O
for	O
the	O
good	O
Government	O
and	O
Regulating	O
of	O
the	O
Persons	O
Licensed	O
to	O
Keep	O
and	O
Drive	O
Hackney-Coaches	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
Renters	O
and	O
Drivers	O
Made	O
,	O
Publish	O
'd	O
and	O
Declar	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Commissioners	O
;	O
and	O
Allowed	O
and	O
Approved	O
by	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chancellor	O
and	O
Judges	O
as	O
the	O
Law	O
directs	O
.	O
Price	O
3	O
d.	O
Books	O
Printed	O
for	O
Daniel	O
Prate	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Bible	O
against	O
York-Buildings	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
A	O
Banquet	O
for	O
Gentlemen	O
and	O
Ladies	O
,	O
consisting	O
of	O
Nine	O
Comical	O
Novels	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
The	O
Treacherous	O
Friend	O
.	O
The	O
prodigal	O
Reclaimed	O
.	O
The	O
Jealous	O
Husband	O
,	O
or	O
Virginity	O
restored	O
.	O
The	O
Friendly	O
Cheat	O
.	O
The	O
Unfortunate	O
Lover	O
.	O
Jealousie	O
without	O
a	O
Cause	O
.	O
The	O
Cruel	O
Mother	O
.	O
The	O
Cuckold	O
turn	O
'd	O
Confessor	O
.	O
The	O
Bacchanalians	O
;	O
intermix	O
'd	O
with	O
many	O
Pleasant	O
and	O
Delightful	O
Tales	O
and	O
Stories	O
.	O
The	O
Fifth	O
Edition	O
.	O
The	O
Universal	O
Jester	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
A	O
Compleat	O
Book	O
of	O
Jests	O
.	O
Containing	O
A	O
pleasant	O
Variety	O
of	O
English	O
Jests	O
,	O
Irish	O
Jests	O
,	O
Oxford	O
Jests	O
,	O
Cambridge	O
Jests	O
,	O
Coffee-House	O
Jests	O
,	O
Novels	O
,	O
Bulls	O
,	O
Stories	O
,	O
Jokes	O
,	O
and	O
Puns	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
Hell	O
in	O
an	O
Uproar	O
,	O
or	O
,	O
A	O
Scuffle	O
between	O
the	O
Lawyers	O
and	O
Physicians	O
for	O
Superiority	O
.	O
A	O
Satyr	O
.	O
Female	O
Policy	O
detected	O
or	O
the	O
Art	O
of	O
a	O
Designing	O
Woman	O
laid	O
open	O
:	O
By	O
the	O
Author	O
of	O
the	O
London	O
Spy	O
.	O
and	O
Trip	O
to	O
Jamaica	O
:	O
Treating	O
1.	O
of	O
their	O
Allurements	O
,	O
Inconstancy	O
,	O
Love	O
,	O
Revenge	O
,	O
Pride	O
and	O
Ingratitude	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
A	O
Pleasant	O
and	O
Profitable	O
Discourse	O
in	O
defence	O
of	O
Married	O
Men	O
,	O
against	O
Pevish	O
,	O
Fretful	O
.	O
Scolding	O
Wives	O
;	O
with	O
several	O
notable	O
Examples	O
of	O
the	O
Mischiefs	O
and	O
Miseries	O
which	O
have	O
attended	O
their	O
Lust	O
and	O
Pride	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
A	O
True	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
Virtuous	O
Woman	O
,	O
or	O
Wife	O
indeed	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
in	O
added	O
a	O
Poetical	O
description	O
of	O
a	O
Widow	O
,	O
Wife	O
and	O
Maid	O
.	O
The	O
Accomplish	O
'd	O
Ladies	O
Delight	O
,	O
in	O
Preserving	O
,	O
Physick	O
,	O
Beautifying	O
,	O
Cookery	O
and	O
Gardening	O
:	O
Containing	O
,	O
1	O
.	O
The	O
Art	O
of	O
Preserving	O
and	O
Candying	O
Fruits	O
and	O
Flowers	O
,	O
and	O
making	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
Conserves	O
,	O
Syrups	O
,	O
Jellies	O
and	O
Pickles	O
,	O
2	O
.	O
The	O
Physical	O
Cabinet	O
,	O
or	O
excellent	O
Receipts	O
in	O
Physick	O
and	O
Chyrurgery	O
;	O
also	O
some	O
new	O
Receipts	O
relating	O
to	O
the	O
Fair	O
Sex	O
,	O
whereby	O
they	O
may	O
be	O
richly	O
furnished	O
with	O
all	O
manner	O
of	O
Beautifying	O
Waters	O
to	O
add	O
loveliness	O
to	O
the	O
Face	O
and	O
Body	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
The	O
Compleat	O
Cook	O
's	O
Guide	O
,	O
or	O
Directions	O
for	O
Dresing	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
Flesh	O
,	O
Fowl	O
,	O
and	O
Fish	O
after	O
the	O
newest	O
fashion	O
now	O
in	O
use	O
at	O
the	O
British	O
Court	O
;	O
with	O
the	O
making	O
Sauces	O
for	O
Pyes	O
,	O
Pasteries	O
,	O
Tarts	O
,	O
Custards	O
4	O
.	O
The	O
Female	O
Angler	O
,	O
Influcting	O
Ladies	O
and	O
others	O
in	O
the	O
various	O
methods	O
of	O
taking	O
all	O
manner	O
of	O
Fish	O
in	O
the	O
Fish-ponds	O
or	O
Rivers	O
.	O
5	O
:	O
The	O
Ladies	O
Diversion	O
in	O
her	O
Garden	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
Compleat	O
Florist	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Nature	O
and	O
Use	O
of	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
Plants	O
and	O
Flowers	O
.	O
The	O
Tenth	O
Edition	O
enlarg	O
'd	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
same	O
Place	O
all	O
Persons	O
may	O
be	O
Furnished	O
with	O
Lottery-Pictures	O
,	O
Sign-Bills	O
,	O
Bonds	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
Things	O
wrought	O
on	O
Copper	O
Plates	O
,	O
by	O
Abraham	O
Dixon	O
A	O
Water	O
that	O
perfectly	O
cures	O
the	O
Itch	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
Itching	O
Humour	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
,	O
without	O
necessity	O
of	O
Pur	O
ging	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
dangerous	O
Use	O
of	O
Mercury	O
,	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
is	O
only	O
Prepared	O
and	O
Sold	O
by	O
A	O
.	O
Downing	O
Chymist	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
and	O
Ball	O
in	O
George	O
Court	O
in	O
St.	O
John	O
's	O
Lane	O
by	O
Hicks	O
's	O
Hall	O
near	O
West-Smithfield	O
.	O
Where	O
also	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
,	O
the	O
best	O
Spirits	O
of	O
Scurvy-Grass	O
,	O
by	O
Wholesale	O
or	O
Retale	O
at	O
8	O
d.	O
a	O
Bottle	O
.	O
A	O
most	O
effectual	O
Remedy	O
for	O
the	O
Violent	O
Pain	O
in	O
the	O
Teeth	O
,	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
Also	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Remedy	O
for	O
preserving	O
the	O
Teeth	O
and	O
clearing	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
,	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
Cure	O
for	O
Agues	O
by	O
B.LILBURN	O
,	O
that	O
formerly	O
lived	O
on	O
Ludgate-Hill	O
next	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms	O
Tavern	O
near	O
Fleet	O
bridge	O
and	O
for	O
seventeen	O
Years	O
past	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Great	O
Old	O
Baily	O
,	O
now	O
lives	O
at	O
the	O
first	O
House	O
on	O
the	O
Left	O
Hand	O
through	O
Black	O
Fryers	O
Gateway	O
near	O
Ludgate	O
,	O
who	O
has	O
made	O
and	O
sold	O
near	O
Forty	O
Years	O
.	O
The	O
Water	O
for	O
taking	O
away	O
the	O
Freckles	O
,	O
Pimples	O
,	O
Worms	O
,	O
Morphew	O
,	O
and	O
Red	O
Marks	O
of	O
the	O
Small	O
Pox	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
;	O
the	O
Price	O
of	O
the	O
Half	O
Pint	O
Five	O
Shillings	O
,	O
Sealed	O
with	O
the	O
Three	O
Water-Budgets	O
,	O
and	O
B	O
L	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
Seal	O
.	O
Pray	O
take	O
notice	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
taken	O
the	O
Sale	O
of	O
the	O
Water	O
from	O
all	O
in	O
and	O
near	O
London	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
had	O
now	O
only	O
of	O
her	O
self	O
;	O
and	O
never	O
sold	O
the	O
Receipt	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
some	O
that	O
sold	O
for	O
her	O
has	O
impudently	O
pretended	O
;	O
nor	O
no	O
other	O
Receipt	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
she	O
makes	O
,	O
or	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
Manuscript	O
.	O
She	O
likewise	O
sells	O
her	O
Antiscorbutick	O
,	O
Histerick	O
,	O
and	O
Head-Pill	O
,	O
being	O
good	O
for	O
Cancers	O
,	O
King	O
's	O
Evil	O
,	O
Gout	O
and	O
Rheumatism	O
,	O
Dropsy	O
,	O
Agues	O
,	O
Surfeits	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Price	O
two	O
Shillings	O
the	O
Box	O
.	O
The	O
Elixir	O
for	O
the	O
Collick	O
and	O
Gripes	O
,	O
good	O
for	O
Agues	O
,	O
Consumptions	O
or	O
Coughs	O
,	O
Colds	O
,	O
Stone	O
or	O
Gravel	O
,	O
Vomiting	O
and	O
Looseness	O
,	O
Price	O
one	O
Shilling	O
the	O
Vial	O
,	O
or	O
Five	O
Shillings	O
the	O
Half-pint	O
The	O
Ointment	O
for	O
Bruises	O
,	O
Aches	O
,	O
Strains	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
dissolve	O
Swellings	O
,	O
one	O
Shilling	O
the	O
Pot	O
.	O
The	O
Ointment	O
for	O
sore	O
Nipples	O
,	O
the	O
Piles	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
Hair	O
grow	O
,	O
One	O
Shilling	O
the	O
Pot	O
.	O
The	O
Girdle	O
for	O
the	O
Itch	O
,	O
Eighteen	O
Pence	O
.	O
These	O
with	O
other	O
Preparations	O
,	O
both	O
for	O
Ornament	O
,	O
Easing	O
and	O
Curing	O
most	O
Distempers	O
,	O
help	O
for	O
inward	O
Bruises	O
and	O
Hurts	O
on	O
the	O
Breast	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
have	O
of	O
B.	O
Lilburn	O
At	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Red-Ball	O
in	O
Queen-Street	O
,	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
over	O
against	O
the	O
Globe-Tavern	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Three	O
Cranes	O
.	O
LIVETH	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
that	O
hath	O
a	O
most	O
incomparable	O
wash	O
to	O
Beautifie	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
which	O
far	O
exceeds	O
all	O
that	O
are	O
extant	O
,	O
as	O
abundance	O
of	O
the	O
greatest	O
Quality	O
have	O
experienced	O
,	O
to	O
their	O
entire	O
Satisfaction	O
.	O
It	O
takes	O
out	O
all	O
manner	O
of	O
Wrinkles	O
,	O
Freckles	O
,	O
Pimples	O
,	O
Redness	O
,	O
Morphew	O
,	O
Sun-burn	O
,	O
and	O
Yellowness	O
,	O
caused	O
by	O
Mercurial	O
poisonous	O
Washes	O
.	O
It	O
also	O
plumps	O
and	O
softens	O
the	O
Skin	O
,	O
making	O
it	O
as	O
tender	O
as	O
a	O
Sucking	O
Child	O
's	O
.	O
And	O
it	O
hath	O
this	O
excellent	O
Quality	O
above	O
all	O
other	O
Washes	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Young	O
it	O
keeps	O
always	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Old	O
it	O
makes	O
appear	O
Fair	O
and	O
Young	O
to	O
Admiration	O
.	O
It	O
hath	O
nothing	O
of	O
Paint	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
neither	O
doth	O
any	O
other	O
Person	O
know	O
this	O
rare	O
Secret	O
.	O
You	O
may	O
have	O
it	O
from	O
2s	O
.	O
and	O
6d	O
.	O
to	O
a	O
Guinea	O
a	O
Pottle	O
.	O
You	O
may	O
there	O
also	O
have	O
Fine	O
Spanish	O
Wool	O
,	O
and	O
Portugal	O
Dishes	O
,	O
which	O
gives	O
a	O
glorious	O
Colour	O
to	O
the	O
Cheeks	O
and	O
Lips	O
.	O
She	O
changes	O
Red	O
or	O
Grey	O
Hair	O
to	O
a	O
Natural	O
Brown	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
,	O
so	O
as	O
never	O
to	O
change	O
Colour	O
.	O
She	O
Cuts	O
Hair	O
very	O
fine	O
;	O
and	O
has	O
a	O
certain	O
infallible	O
Cure	O
for	O
the	O
Toothach	O
,	O
without	O
Drawing	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Pain	O
will	O
never	O
return	O
.	O
Likewise	O
you	O
may	O
have	O
Dr.	O
Reddrop	O
's	O
fine	O
purging	O
Elixir	O
,	O
approved	O
of	O
by	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
Quality	O
in	O
England	O
,	O
at	O
15	O
d	O
a	O
.	O
Bottle	O
,	O
good	O
for	O
all	O
Distempers	O
incident	O
to	O
Men	O
and	O
Women	O
.	O
Note	O
,	O
A	O
Light	O
hanging	O
in	O
the	O
Entry	O
at	O
Night-time	O
.	O
The	O
following	O
Books	O
are	O
given	O
Gratis	O
.	O
1st	O
,	O
The	O
Practical	O
Scheme	O
of	O
the	O
Secret	O
Disease	O
and	O
Broken	O
Constitutions	O
,	O
by	O
Fast	O
Living	O
,	O
Former	O
ill	O
Cures	O
,	O
Salivations	O
and	O
Mercury	O
-aly	O
,	O
The	O
New	O
System	O
of	O
the	O
GOUT	O
and	O
Rhuematism	O
drawn	O
from	O
Reason	O
,	O
Anatomical	O
Observations	O
and	O
Experience	O
,	O
-	O
3ly	O
,	O
A	O
Rational	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Cause	O
,	O
Nature	O
and	O
Cure	O
of	O
WEAKNESSES	O
usually	O
attending	O
Persons	O
after	O
former	O
Cures	O
,	O
Over-strainings	O
,	O
Self-Abuses	O
,	O
Hard	O
Labours	O
,	O
Miscarriages	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Wherein	O
is	O
given	O
a	O
full	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
horrid	O
Nature	O
,	O
and	O
most	O
miserable	O
Consequences	O
of	O
Self-Abuses	O
in	O
particular	O
.	O
These	O
Books	O
(	O
all	O
New	O
Editions	O
)	O
are	O
given	O
Gratis	O
Up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
ANODYNE	O
.	O
NECK-LACE	O
,	O
without	O
Temple	O
Bar	O
.	O
At	O
Mr.	O
Cowpers	O
Toy	O
shop	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Charles	O
Court	O
by	O
Hungerfond-Market	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
And	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Garraway	O
's	O
Shop	O
at	O
the	O
Kings	O
Arms	O
at	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange-Gate	O
next	O
Cornhill	O
.	O
