TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
,	O
ON	O
Thursday	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
2d	O
and	O
3d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
June	O
,	O
1720	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Sixth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
GEORGE	B-pers
THOROLD	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
and	O
Baronet	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
King	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Ayres	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Mountague	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Country	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
Names	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Bradford	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Parr	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Sambrook	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Sheaf	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gourd	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Shelley	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Pitman	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Street	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hamphreys	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Jackman	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Walkingame	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hirons	I-pers
,	O
Abraham	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wedgeborough	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Saul	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Sudbury	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Cullum	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
in	O
Attempting	O
to	O
Fire	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Wallis	I-pers
,	O
by	O
putting	O
a	O
lighted	O
Candle	O
to	O
a	O
Basket	O
of	O
Wooden	O
Chips	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
(	O
who	O
keeps	O
the	O
Nags	B-place
Head	I-place
Alehouse	I-place
in	I-place
Nags	I-place
Head	I-place
Court	I-place
in	I-place
Grace-Church	I-place
Street	I-place
)	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Night	O
aforesaid	O
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
Children	O
having	O
been	O
gone	O
to	O
Bed	O
about	O
an	O
Hour	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
none	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
bid	O
him	O
draw	O
him	O
a	O
little	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
for	O
it	O
the	O
Watchman	O
knock	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
for	O
a	O
Pipe	O
,	O
who	O
spying	O
a	O
Light	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
through	O
the	O
Cracks	O
in	O
the	O
Floor	O
,	O
told	O
him	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
)	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Candle	O
lighted	O
put	O
to	O
the	O
Chips	O
in	O
the	O
Basket	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
set	O
them	O
on	O
Fire	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
just	O
done	O
he	O
put	O
it	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Water	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
no	O
occasion	O
to	O
go	O
by	O
or	O
near	O
the	O
Basket	O
of	O
Chips	O
for	O
the	O
Drink	O
.	O
The	O
Watchman	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
wherein	O
he	O
owned	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
three	O
Men	O
advised	O
him	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
three	O
Guineas	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
confest	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
being	O
Whipt	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
believing	O
him	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Fined	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
to	O
suffer	O
One	O
Month	O
's	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
value	O
1	O
s	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Illidge	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
May	O
Last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
over	O
Fleet-Bridge	B-place
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
immediately	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Bosom	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Christopher	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Sills	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Douglass	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Day-time	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
thence	O
18	O
Guineas	O
and	O
40	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Sarah	O
Douglass	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stretch	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Katharine	I-place
Creed-Church	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
s	O
6	O
d.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Streight	I-pers
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
.	O
Another	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
who	O
lived	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
)	O
take	O
the	O
Money	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
go	O
after	O
a	O
Coachman	O
(	O
who	O
came	O
in	O
for	O
some	O
Gin	O
)	O
to	O
change	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
Queen	O
Ann	O
's	O
half	O
Crown	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Request	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Daughter	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Higgins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mildred	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Poultry	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Taster	O
value	O
14s	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Kendal	I-pers
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
for	O
some	O
Pickled	O
Cucumbers	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Taster	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
follow	O
'd	O
,	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
it	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gambol	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Alhallows	B-place
Barkin	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Gabriel	B-pers
Whitacre	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
thence	O
a	O
Leather	O
Trunk	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
5	O
Guineas	O
,	O
3	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Gabriel	B-pers
Whitacre	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Lock	O
of	O
his	O
Closet	O
Door	O
was	O
broke	O
off	O
and	O
his	O
Trunk	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Trunk	O
several	O
Lottery	O
Tickets	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
a	O
Prize	O
of	O
10	O
l.	O
a	O
Note	O
for	O
100	O
l.	O
a	O
Sword-Blade-Bond	O
for	O
100	O
l.	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
besides	O
those	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
that	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Writings	O
were	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
Custom-house	O
Key	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
Note	O
and	O
Bond	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
the	O
Ticket	O
of	O
10	O
l.	O
Prize	O
:	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Journeyman	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
been	O
gone	O
from	O
him	O
about	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Brother	O
telling	O
him	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
Night	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
within	O
30	O
Yards	O
of	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
enquired	O
after	O
him	O
and	O
followed	O
him	O
to	O
Rochester	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Man	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
,	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
sell	O
him	O
a	O
10	O
l.	O
Prize	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
the	O
Number	O
of	O
the	O
Ticket	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
he	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
East-Malling	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Bed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
shewed	O
the	O
Ticket	O
at	O
Rochester	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
him	O
a	O
Bond	O
for	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
produced	O
some	O
small	O
pieces	O
of	O
Paper	O
saying	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
Ticket	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
tore	O
so	O
very	O
small	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
the	O
Letters	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
left	O
the	O
Trunk	O
on	O
the	O
Custom-house	O
Keys	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
Sheets	O
were	O
left	O
at	O
a	O
Cooks	O
;	O
but	O
going	O
there	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Cook	O
declared	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
nothing	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
workt	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
Six	O
Weeks	O
,	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
Opportunities	O
enough	O
to	O
have	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
wrong	O
'd	O
him	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
used	O
to	O
leave	O
his	O
Door	O
open	O
for	O
his	O
Brother	O
to	O
come	O
in	O
at	O
late	O
Hours	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
a	O
Candle	O
for	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Entry	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
any	O
Body	O
might	O
come	O
in	O
and	O
rob	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Cauthorn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Hill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
12	O
pound	O
Weight	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jeffry	B-pers
Adamson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
keeps	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Tobacco	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Box	O
in	O
his	O
Cellar	O
made	O
up	O
in	O
Penny	O
Papers	O
for	O
his	O
Customers	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Tobacconist	O
's	O
Name	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
his	O
Neighbour	O
)	O
on	O
the	O
Papers	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
Bottles	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
some	O
Brandy	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
deposed	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
on	O
his	O
Watch	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
by	O
with	O
a	O
Box	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
reply	O
'd	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
in	O
London	O
,	O
afterwards	O
he	O
said	O
at	O
Limehouse	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Tobacco	O
being	O
very	O
loose	O
in	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
put	O
out	O
of	O
Papers	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
into	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
Bottom	O
of	O
it	O
found	O
a	O
Paper	O
unopen	O
'd	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
he	O
found	O
out	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Box	O
and	O
Paper	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
were	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
impeach	O
two	O
more	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
Bond	O
of	O
20	O
l.	O
not	O
to	O
prosecute	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Bedford	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Strawbridge	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Stephen	I-place
Coleman-Street	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Meakins	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
drinking	O
up	O
Stairs	O
at	O
the	O
Star	B-place
Tavern	I-place
in	I-place
Coleman-Street	I-place
with	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
Spoon	O
for	O
their	O
use	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
appointed	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Collier	O
who	O
was	O
drinking	O
below	O
Stairs	O
,	O
to	O
meet	O
them	O
at	O
another	O
Place	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
the	O
Spoon	O
was	O
mist	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
askt	O
Mr.	O
Collier	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Kings-Arms-Inn	O
in	O
Leaden-Hall-Street	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
thither	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
found	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Spoon	O
was	O
found	O
under	O
the	O
Bench	O
which	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Strawbridge	I-pers
sat	O
on	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
confirmed	O
the	O
finding	O
the	O
Spoon	O
in	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
denied	O
their	O
taking	O
the	O
Spoon	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
they	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Man	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
them	O
might	O
put	O
it	O
there	O
,	O
whom	O
they	O
let	O
get	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
alis	I-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
an	O
Iron	O
Padlock	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Grew	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Nicholson	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
work	O
about	O
3	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
the	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Man	O
on	O
St.	O
Dunstan's-Hill	O
,	O
who	O
parted	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
follow	O
'd	O
the	O
other	O
Man	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
a	O
Bag	O
on	O
his	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
the	O
other	O
Way	O
;	O
that	O
this	O
Evidence	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Tackle	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
back	O
to	O
Mincing	O
Lane	O
saw	O
Mr	O
.	O
Grew	O
's	O
Vault	O
Door	O
pusht	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Grew	O
's	O
Servant	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Door	O
safe	O
at	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
called	O
him	O
up	O
at	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Padlock	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Lane	O
had	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
Wife	O
in	O
St.	O
Thomas	O
's	O
Hospital	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Child	O
at	O
Nurse	O
in	O
Southwark	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
going	O
along	O
they	O
seized	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
Lock	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
was	O
become	O
of	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Body	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
nor	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Lock	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
lost	O
one	O
,	O
the	O
Man	O
whom	O
they	O
talkt	O
of	O
might	O
have	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
at	I-place
Queenhith	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Nest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
Knives	O
and	O
Forks	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Waterman	O
's	O
Boy	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Boat	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
who	O
judging	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
Marbles	O
in	O
the	O
Drawers	O
by	O
the	O
Noise	O
of	O
their	O
rowling	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
play	O
with	O
some	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
owned	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
him	O
the	O
Drawers	O
again	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
opened	O
them	O
with	O
his	O
Stretcher	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
on	O
his	O
Tryal	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bayley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
an	O
Assault	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Fined	O
13	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
d	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Liberty	B-place
of	I-place
the	I-place
Old	I-place
Artillery	I-place
Ground	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Mary	B-pers
Baldwin	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Canvas	O
Pocket	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Pocket-Book	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
9	O
a	O
Clock	O
the	O
Night	O
aforesaid	O
she	O
was	O
thrown	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
Pocket-Book	O
and	O
Money	O
taken	O
from	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket-Book	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Note	O
of	O
31	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
her	O
Knowledge	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
committed	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Hotchet	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
stopt	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
the	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
hearing	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
stopt	O
by	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drop	O
the	O
Pocket	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stuck	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Breast	O
with	O
a	O
Penknife	O
because	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
aimed	O
at	O
his	O
Throat	O
afterwards	O
,	O
but	O
missing	O
it	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
large	O
Wound	O
in	O
his	O
Cheek	O
,	O
both	O
which	O
Wounds	O
appeared	O
in	O
Court	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
Pick	O
Lock	O
Keys	O
found	O
on	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stedman	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Pick	O
Lock	O
Keys	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
wound	O
Hall	O
with	O
a	O
Pen-knife	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
wounded	O
this	O
Evidence	O
in	O
the	O
Arm	O
with	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
which	O
Wound	O
not	O
being	O
well	O
yet	O
,	O
he	O
shewed	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
going	O
by	O
saw	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
down	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Keys	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
himself	O
was	O
wounded	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
under	O
the	O
Arm	O
.	O
The	O
Pocket	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
swore	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
be	O
hers	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
several	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
dropt	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Pick	O
Lock	O
Keys	O
were	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Prisner	O
deny	O
'd	O
all	O
,	O
saying	O
they	O
wounded	O
one	O
another	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
two	O
Persons	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
gave	O
him	O
an	O
ill	O
Character	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pancras	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Thomas	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
,	O
putting-him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
3	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
John	O
Morgan	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
on	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
Of	O
both	O
which	O
Facts	O
he	O
was	O
Accused	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Whinship	I-pers
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
himself	O
was	O
an	O
Accomplice	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
them	O
:	O
But	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
better	O
Evidence	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Birch	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Drugget	O
Coat	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Rowland	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
affecting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Mongo	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
drawn	O
Sword	O
under	O
the	O
Right	O
Pap	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
5	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
Instantly	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
between	O
5	O
and	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
she	O
heard	O
a	O
knocking	O
very	O
hard	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Pitman	O
's	O
Door	O
in	O
Manchester	B-place
Court	I-place
in	I-place
Channel	I-place
Row	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
and	O
thinking	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
their	O
own	O
Door	O
,	O
she	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Pitman	O
's	O
House	O
with	O
his	O
naked	O
Sword	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
follow	O
him	O
,	O
buttoning	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
by	O
his	O
side	O
in	O
the	O
Scabbard	O
;	O
that	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
off	O
the	O
Steps	O
the	O
Deceased	O
pusht	O
at	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
Do	O
you	O
call	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Bed	O
to	O
Murder	O
me	O
?	O
That	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
got	O
about	O
three	O
Doors	O
further	O
the	O
Deceased	O
pusht	O
at	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
wounded	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Left	O
Hand	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drew	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
received	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Wound	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
not	O
retreat	O
,	O
the	O
Rails	O
being	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
before	O
him	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Read	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
knockr	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Pitman	O
's	O
Door	O
(	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodged	O
)	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
opened	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
spoke	O
very	O
civilly	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
left	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Dining	O
Room	O
together	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
this	O
unhappy	O
Accident	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
some	O
hot	O
Pots	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
till	O
Morning	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
persuaded	O
the	O
Deceased	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
;	O
that	O
as	O
they	O
went	O
along	O
Channel	O
Row	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
upper	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
to	O
Shift	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
stay	O
there	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
while	O
he	O
staid	O
,	O
hearing	O
the	O
Clashing	O
of	O
Swords	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
part	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
bloody	O
,	O
retreated	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Steps	O
and	O
died	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Cornforth	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Deceased	O
and	O
former	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
Deceased	O
say	O
,	O
stay	O
here	O
while	O
I	O
go	O
and	O
call	O
him	O
up	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
the	O
Court	O
and	O
knockt	O
very	O
hard	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Benson	I-pers
and	O
Eliz	O
-	O
deposed	O
that	O
they	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
say	O
,	O
Did	O
you	O
call	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
Bed	O
to	O
Murder	O
me	O
?	O
Mr	O
.	O
Bland	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
Right	O
Breast	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
5	O
Inches	O
deep	O
;	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
Mortal	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
a	O
Pistol	O
in	O
one	O
Hand	O
which	O
he	O
put	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
near	O
the	O
Rails	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
retreat	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
no	O
other	O
way	O
to	O
defend	O
himself	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Speerman	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
at	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
7	O
Guineas	O
and	O
25	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Buxton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
lay	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
to	O
sleep	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
a	O
Girl	O
)	O
lay	O
in	O
another	O
Bed	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
lay	O
down	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Guineas	O
together	O
in	O
a	O
Paper	O
in	O
one	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Silver	O
loose	O
in	O
another	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
rose	O
both	O
were	O
gone	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
next	O
Day	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Ogden	O
's	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
in	O
Southwark	O
,	O
who	O
confest	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
Mr.	O
Ogden	O
5	O
Guineas	O
and	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
spent	O
2	O
.	O
Guineas	O
that	O
Night	O
;	O
that	O
Mr.	B-pers
Ogden	I-pers
return	O
'd	O
him	O
3	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
6	O
s.	O
4	O
d.	O
of	O
his	O
Money	O
again	O
,	O
the	O
rest	O
was	O
spent	O
on	O
Clothes	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Simmons	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Ogden	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
then	O
5	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Ogden	O
to	O
put	O
up	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
scrupeling	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
good	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
she	O
could	O
have	O
more	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Daughter	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Ogden	O
's	O
with	O
her	O
Father	O
,	O
and	O
confirmed	O
his	O
Evidence	O
,	O
adding	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
refused	O
to	O
go	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
without	O
a	O
Constable	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
her	O
Father	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
Gold	O
and	O
the	O
Silver	O
together	O
in	O
a	O
Paper	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
by	O
the	O
Bed-side	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
believing	O
her	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
of	O
Isleworth	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Alexander	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Alexander	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Alexander	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
14	O
pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Stockings	O
,	O
two	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
3	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
5	O
Wax	O
Candles	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Messervy	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
and	O
Ann	O
and	O
Mary	O
as	O
Accessory	O
in	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
going	O
up	O
to	O
his	O
Trunk	O
,	O
found	O
it	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
his	O
Goods	O
gone	O
,	O
particularly	O
those	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Trunk	O
that	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
others	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
charg	O
'd	O
with	O
it	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
owned	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Key	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
that	O
would	O
open	O
the	O
two	O
Trunks	O
which	O
were	O
not	O
broke	O
.	O
R.	O
Howard	O
confirmed	O
her	O
confessing	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
several	O
places	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
disposed	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Elizabeth	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
bound	O
Apprentice	O
to	O
R	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
to	O
Matt	O
Chairs	O
,	O
and	O
turn	O
'd	O
off	O
to	O
his	O
Brother-in-Law	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
hard	O
used	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
for	O
want	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
to	O
fix	O
any	O
thing	O
on	O
Ann	O
and	O
Mary	O
Alexander	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
found	O
Elizabeth	O
Alexander	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Cartwright	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
at	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
ounces	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
Silver	O
Plate	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Hurdsman	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Walter	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
entrusted	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
Spin	O
on	O
Silk	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Hurdsman	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
make	O
Lace	O
,	O
and	O
lockt	O
them	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Drawer	O
under	O
the	O
Dresser	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
three	O
Kings	O
in	O
Newgate	O
Street	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
stopt	O
:	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
who	O
workt	O
for	O
him	O
)	O
confest	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
off	O
the	O
Dresser	O
,	O
but	O
refused	O
to	O
sign	O
his	O
Examination	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
:	O
and	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
stopt	O
the	O
Goods	O
not	O
appearing	O
to	O
fix	O
it	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
the	O
3d	O
.	O
and	O
4th	O
,	O
of	O
King	O
William	O
and	O
Queen	O
Mary	O
,	O
(	O
entituled	O
An	O
Act	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
the	O
Clergy	O
from	O
some	O
Offenders	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
bring	O
others	O
to	O
Punishment	O
.	O
)	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Linnen	O
Sheets	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Hornsby	I-pers
,	O
and	O
also	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
James	O
Hornsby	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
,	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
let	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
Lodging	O
for	O
1	O
s.	O
per	O
Week	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
7	O
Weeks	O
,	O
he	O
suspecting	O
her	O
,	O
asked	O
her	O
for	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
;	O
which	O
she	O
refusing	O
to	O
deliver	O
,	O
he	O
opened	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
mist	O
the	O
Sheets	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
charging	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
accordingly	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Saul	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
lent	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
4	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
Spoon	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
Sheets	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
on	O
her	O
Tryal	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Leg	O
of	O
Veal	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Foulk	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Leg	O
of	O
Veal	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Larder	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
immediately	O
mist	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
who	O
was	O
passing	O
by	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
along	O
with	O
it	O
at	O
Arms	O
length	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
it	O
,	O
ran	O
after	O
and	O
seized	O
him	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
.	O
Lewis	B-pers
Golston	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
4	O
Shillings	O
and	O
5	O
Pence	O
3	O
Farthings	O
in	O
Money	O
number	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Gladman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
kept	O
Halfpence	O
and	O
Farthings	O
by	O
him	O
for	O
Change	O
in	O
a	O
Mug	O
in	O
a	O
Corner	O
Cupboard	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
his	O
Cupboard	O
open	O
and	O
missing	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
ask	O
'd	O
his	O
Wife	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
any	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Mug	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
saying	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
,	O
he	O
charged	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
remarkable	O
Halfpenny	O
which	O
he	O
knew	O
,	O
among	O
the	O
rest	O
in	O
his	O
Lap	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisner	O
owned	O
to	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Mug	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
be	O
favourable	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
on	O
his	O
Trial	O
,	O
but	O
beg	O
'd	O
for	O
Mercy	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
promissing	O
never	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
any	O
more	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Grey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Sharp	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
under	O
a	O
pretence	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Penny-worth	O
of	O
Cheese	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
coming	O
from	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
's	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
step	O
off	O
the	O
Threshold	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Cup	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Another	O
deposed	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Cup	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Cheese	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Cup	O
off	O
the	O
Compter	O
to	O
draw	O
some	O
Water	O
in	O
;	O
not	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
steal	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
bring	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Maynard	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Canvas	O
Bag	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
3	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
5	O
l.	O
piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
10	O
pieces	O
of	O
Silver	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
103	O
Guineas	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Jarvis	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
Maynard	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
and	O
had	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
2	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
Price	O
was	O
her	O
Sweet	O
Heart	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
Price	O
's	O
Master	O
he	O
search	O
'd	O
and	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
found	O
the	O
Bag	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
Guineas	O
but	O
17	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Rings	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gelder	I-pers
,	O
Price	O
's	O
Master	O
,	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
finding	O
the	O
Bag	O
of	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Rings	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
,	O
and	O
farther	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Price	O
lay	O
out	O
all	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
next	O
Day	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
work	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
bought	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
again	O
and	O
bought	O
Shirts	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
observing	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
often	O
to	O
the	O
Vault	O
,	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
ailed	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
answered	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
Order	O
with	O
Drinking	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
Piles	O
.	O
That	O
perceiving	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
uneasy	O
he	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
leave	O
him	O
tell	O
him	O
so	O
:	O
whereupon	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Brother	O
had	O
listed	O
themselves	O
for	O
Soldiers	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Brother	O
's	O
Master	O
had	O
got	O
him	O
off	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
heard	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
known	O
where	O
himself	O
was	O
,	O
therefore	O
must	O
leave	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
shot	O
to	O
Death	O
if	O
taken	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Vault	O
was	O
a	O
common	O
Vault	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Calhorn	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Bag	O
of	O
Guineas	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Vault	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jarvis	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
Price	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
lurking	O
about	O
his	O
Uncle	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
be	O
often	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
let	O
him	O
in	O
at	O
3	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
;	O
that	O
one	O
Night	O
finding	O
his	O
Shoes	O
and	O
Buckles	O
Wet	O
and	O
dirty	O
under	O
the	O
Dresser	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
the	O
Door	O
which	O
led	O
to	O
the	O
Maid	O
's	O
Chamber	O
lockt	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
believes	O
they	O
were	O
then	O
together	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Proof	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
put	O
it	O
there	O
,	O
they	O
Acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
and	O
a	O
Gold	O
Locket	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Tilbury	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
8	O
Days	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Fellow	O
came	O
after	O
her	O
whom	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
her	O
to	O
a	O
Tavern	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
her	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
not	O
going	O
,	O
the	O
Vintner	O
came	O
to	O
know	O
the	O
Reason	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
his	O
Maid	O
Servant	O
should	O
not	O
go	O
after	O
Men	O
to	O
Taverns	O
;	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
hearing	O
was	O
very	O
uneasie	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
Mistress	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
who	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
withal	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
she	O
went	O
,	O
she	O
should	O
lie	O
there	O
no	O
more	O
:	O
that	O
his	O
Wife	O
found	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
Shifts	O
bundled	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Apron	O
,	O
afterwards	O
mist	O
the	O
Ring	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
Locket	O
and	O
Watch	O
;	O
whereupon	O
they	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
sent	O
him	O
by	O
an	O
unknown	O
Hand	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Baker	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
she	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
own	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Watch	O
and	O
Ring	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
Ring	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
;	O
but	O
going	O
to	O
enquire	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
Goldsmith	O
told	O
them	O
it	O
was	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Shift	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
having	O
sould	O
it	O
had	O
put	O
it	O
with	O
some	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
got	O
some	O
Soap	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
wash	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Farrar	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bass	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Moreton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
Silver	O
Haft	O
of	O
a	O
Fork	O
and	O
3	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Silver	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Morley	I-pers
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
next	O
Door	O
,	O
a	O
surprise	O
came	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
ran	O
in	O
his	O
Head	O
that	O
he	O
must	O
lose	O
something	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
went	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
his	O
Apprentice	O
)	O
coming	O
down	O
Stairs	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
answered	O
,	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
Garret	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Lodgers	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
to	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
searcht	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
,	O
but	O
finding	O
nothing	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
Company	O
again	O
,	O
made	O
an	O
end	O
of	O
his	O
Tankard	O
,	O
paid	O
his	O
Reckoning	O
and	O
came	O
home	O
:	O
but	O
it	O
still	O
running	O
in	O
his	O
Head	O
that	O
he	O
must	O
lose	O
something	O
,	O
at	O
Night	O
searching	O
more	O
narrowly	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Haft	O
of	O
a	O
Fork	O
in	O
the	O
Sweep	O
Tub	O
and	O
the	O
Silver	O
in	O
a	O
Tin	O
box	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
search	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
on	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Greenwood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
value	O
34	O
s	O
.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Flannel	O
Shirt	O
,	O
3	O
Flannel	O
Petticoats	O
and	O
2	O
Frocks	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Claridge	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Deely	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Cowley	B-place
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Bruise	O
on	O
the	O
Right	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
Belly	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Eyles	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
a	O
Butcher	O
)	O
came	O
for	O
a	O
Calf	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
the	O
Deceased	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
help	O
it	O
up	O
on	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
was	O
riding	O
home	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
gamed	O
him	O
about	O
a	O
Woman	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
gamed	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
back	O
and	O
fight	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
continuing	O
to	O
jear	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
got	O
off	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
a	O
Stick	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
strike	O
the	O
Deceased	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
pusht	O
him	O
down	O
with	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
got	O
up	O
again	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
raised	O
his	O
Stick	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
strike	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
pusht	O
him	O
down	O
with	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
as	O
before	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Deceased	O
got	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
tell	O
his	O
Father	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
should	O
thresh	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
died	O
within	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
taken	O
ill	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
Plow	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
do	O
his	O
Business	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Eyles	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cage	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
seeing	O
the	O
Deceased	O
look	O
pale	O
,	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
ailed	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
his	O
Breath	O
was	O
beat	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Body	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
died	O
within	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
:	O
And	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
state	O
of	O
Health	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
before	O
,	O
answered	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
very	O
bad	O
with	O
an	O
Ague	O
for	O
a	O
Week	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Batty	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
view	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
he	O
opened	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
full	O
of	O
Blood	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Bruise	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
thing	O
broke	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
he	O
died	O
of	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Fellows	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
opened	O
him	O
farther	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Vena	O
Cava	O
burst	O
;	O
but	O
thought	O
it	O
impossible	O
for	O
that	O
Vein	O
to	O
be	O
burst	O
by	O
any	O
thrust	O
or	O
blow	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
upon	O
inquiry	O
he	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
reach	O
'd	O
much	O
to	O
vomit	O
before	O
,	O
which	O
might	O
burst	O
the	O
Vein	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Reputation	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
as	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
peaceable	O
and	O
well	O
behaved	O
young	O
Man	O
,	O
not	O
given	O
to	O
quarrel	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
perfect	O
Friendship	O
between	O
the	O
Deceased	O
Youth	O
and	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
confirmed	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
having	O
been	O
ill	O
of	O
an	O
Ague	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
coming	O
home	O
very	O
bad	O
from	O
Flow	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
,	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
her	O
a	O
mortal	O
Bruise	O
on	O
the	O
Left	O
part	O
of	O
her	O
Body	O
near	O
the	O
Left	O
Pap	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Boreham	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
her	O
Landlady	O
(	O
Mrs.	O
Lisle	O
)	O
House	O
and	O
abused	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
hearing	O
her	O
cry	O
out	O
Murder	O
,	O
came	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
if	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
her	O
Landlady	O
's	O
House	O
to	O
Murder	O
her	O
;	O
who	O
reply	O
'd	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
too	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
her	O
strike	O
the	O
Deceased	O
on	O
her	O
Breast	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Lisle	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Boy	O
she	O
Nurst	O
6	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
her	O
House	O
and	O
complain	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
hurt	O
her	O
Son	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
her	O
to	O
beat	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
till	O
his	O
Mother	O
came	O
home	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
abused	O
her	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
laying	O
her	O
Hand	O
on	O
her	O
Shoulder	O
to	O
put	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
she	O
turn	O
'd	O
again	O
,	O
pull	O
'd	O
her	O
Head	O
Clothes	O
off	O
,	O
threw	O
down	O
her	O
Aged	O
Mother	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
Assistance	O
,	O
threw	O
this	O
Evidence	O
upon	O
her	O
Mother	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
upon	O
them	O
both	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
declared	O
the	O
Blow	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
her	O
was	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
her	O
Death	O
:	O
but	O
being	O
asked	O
whether	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
in	O
Health	O
before	O
,	O
answered	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
ill	O
of	O
an	O
Ague	O
and	O
Fever	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Maiden	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Deceased	O
the	O
Day	O
after	O
the	O
Quarrel	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
bad	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
she	O
believed	O
that	O
the	O
Blow	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
struck	O
her	O
would	O
be	O
her	O
Death	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
heard	O
the	O
Deceased	O
say	O
,	O
the	O
Blow	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
her	O
was	O
her	O
Death	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
Lisle	O
was	O
gone	O
for	O
a	O
Warrant	O
when	O
she	O
gave	O
the	O
Deceased	O
the	O
Blow	O
.	O
Roderick	B-pers
Forbes	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
complained	O
of	O
a	O
Pain	O
in	O
her	O
side	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
received	O
a	O
Blow	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
let	O
her	O
Blood	O
and	O
sent	O
her	O
a	O
Plaister	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
again	O
two	O
Days	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
Fever	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
said	O
her	O
side	O
was	O
better	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
Dead	O
he	O
opened	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
no	O
settled	O
Blood	O
,	O
no	O
Discolouration	O
nor	O
swelling	O
,	O
nor	O
sign	O
of	O
a	O
Bruise	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
opened	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
no	O
Extravasated	O
Blood	O
,	O
no	O
Imposthumation	O
nor	O
any	O
sign	O
of	O
a	O
Bruise	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
died	O
of	O
a	O
Malignant	O
Fever	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
above	O
a	O
Hundred	O
Purple	O
Spots	O
on	O
her	O
Body	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
Flesh	O
was	O
so	O
Rotten	O
and	O
Nauseous	O
with	O
her	O
Distemper	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
hardly	O
endure	O
to	O
touch	O
her	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Briggs	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
at	O
Lisle	O
's	O
persuasion	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
laid	O
her	O
Death	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
God	O
forbid	O
that	O
she	O
should	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
strike	O
her	O
:	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
very-thick	O
of	O
the	O
Purples	O
and	O
died	O
of	O
a	O
Fever	O
:	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
heard	O
Lisle	O
say	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
trouble	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
pay	O
the	O
Charges	O
of	O
the	O
Coroner	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Deceased	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
dying	O
,	O
who	O
put	O
down	O
the	O
Bed-clothes	O
and	O
laid	O
her	O
Hand	O
on	O
her	O
Breast	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
speak	O
to	O
her	O
:	O
And	O
that	O
she	O
heard	O
Lisle	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
her	O
Mother	O
died	O
within	O
a	O
Year	O
and	O
a	O
Day	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
hang	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
that	O
she	O
struck	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
prosecuted	O
out	O
of	O
Malice	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Boswell	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Boswell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Edminton	B-place
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Ewe	O
Sheep	O
value	O
11	O
s.	O
each	O
,	O
and	O
10	O
Lambs	O
value	O
11	O
s.	O
each	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Grounds	O
of	O
Judith	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
lost	O
2	O
Sheep	O
and	O
to	O
Lambs	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Grounds	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
them	O
there	O
over	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Next	O
Morning	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
whereupon	O
they	O
made	O
diligent	O
enquiry	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
William	O
Boswell	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
in	O
Drury	O
Lane	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Sheep	O
and	O
3	O
of	O
the	O
Lambs	O
kill	O
'd	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
Market	O
,	O
the	O
rest	O
alive	O
:	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
met	O
John	B-pers
Boswell	I-pers
coming	O
up	O
Stairs	O
Aaron	B-pers
Plummer	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
himself	O
did	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
drove	O
them	O
to	O
Drury	O
Lane	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
kill	O
'd	O
3	O
Lambs	O
and	O
one	O
Ewe	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
John	O
Boswell	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
stealing	O
and	O
Dressing	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
Butchers	O
,	O
but	O
kept	O
no	O
Shop	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Boswell	I-pers
would	O
have	O
excused	O
John	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
Plummer	O
and	O
himself	O
called	O
John	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Bed	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
John	O
Boswell	O
,	O
also	O
owned	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Quintum	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Quin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
East	B-place
Barnet	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
felonionsly	O
stealing	O
18	O
ounces	O
of	O
Human	O
Hair	O
,	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
stuff	O
petticoat	O
,	O
6	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Sacer	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
Hertfordshire	B-place
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Vanderbrook	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Vandermark	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Todd	I-pers
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
by	O
Force	O
30	O
Guineas	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
a	O
Stay-Maker	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
some	O
Jurneymen	O
to	O
work	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
happen	O
'd	O
into	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Half	B-place
Moon	I-place
and	I-place
Candle	I-place
in	I-place
Bedford-Bury	I-place
,	O
which	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
House	O
of	O
Call	O
for	O
Mens	O
Taylors	O
only	O
;	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
Noon	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
work	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
go	O
to	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
Heat	O
of	O
the	O
Day	O
,	O
let	O
us	O
have	O
a	O
Game	O
at	O
All-Fours	O
,	O
or	O
at	O
Putt	O
;	O
that	O
another	O
Person	O
plaid	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
the	O
Conqueror	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
play	O
'd	O
at	O
first	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
afterwards	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Sider	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
dry	O
,	O
then	O
for	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
Game	O
;	O
till	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
won	O
all	O
their	O
Money	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
first	O
Reckonings	O
were	O
paid	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
asked	O
them	O
to	O
stay	O
and	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
won	O
their	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
treat	O
them	O
with	O
what	O
they	O
pleased	O
:	O
that	O
about	O
7	O
a	O
Clock	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
stay	O
no	O
longer	O
:	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
hoped	O
he	O
would	O
pay	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
refusing	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
out	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
threw	O
up	O
the	O
Sash	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
gone	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pulled	O
him	O
down	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
struck	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
struck	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
threw	O
his	O
Head	O
in	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
Head	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
Murder	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Evidence	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
the	O
30	O
Guineas	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
that	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
at	O
home	O
since	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
places	O
since	O
he	O
saw	O
his	O
Guineas	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Company	O
;	O
though	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
them	O
till	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
And	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
verily	O
believed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
not	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
Bond	O
to	O
indemnifie	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
prosecute	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Grace	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Napkin	O
,	O
2	O
China	O
Tea-pots	O
a	O
Sugar-Dish	O
and	O
Cover	O
,	O
a	O
Slop	O
Bason	O
,	O
a	O
Milk	O
pot	O
8	O
Dishes	O
9	O
Saucers	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
China	O
Wares	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hayward	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Maund	O
's	O
in	O
Pye	O
Corner	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Maund	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
(	O
who	O
lived	O
within	O
a	O
Door	O
or	O
two	O
of	O
her	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
turn	O
'd	O
away	O
from	O
her	O
place	O
but	O
that	O
Morning	O
)	O
brought	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
desiring	O
her	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
they	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
a	O
Friend	O
of	O
hers	O
that	O
was	O
burnt	O
out	O
at	O
Holbourn	O
Bridge	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
again	O
at	O
Night	O
to	O
fetch	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
asked	O
what	O
her	O
Friend	O
's	O
Name	O
was	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
refusing	O
to	O
tell	O
,	O
made	O
her	O
suspect	O
her	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
deliver	O
'd	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
(	O
and	O
kept	O
some	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
she	O
could	O
find	O
the	O
right	O
Owner	O
)	O
and	O
sent	O
her	O
Kinsman	O
to	O
see	O
where	O
she	O
carried	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Holbourn	O
Bridge	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Fire	O
was	O
,	O
to	O
enquire	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
owned	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Maund	O
's	O
Kinsman	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
followed	O
her	O
to	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
in	O
Barbakin	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
pawn	O
them	O
,	O
who	O
questioning	O
her	O
he	O
appeared	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
he	O
believed	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
honestly	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
followed	O
her	O
thence	O
to	O
Saffron	O
Hill	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
her	O
secured	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
at	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
an	O
Ax	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Hammer	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Oakley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
make	O
Hay	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
White	B-place
Lyon	I-place
Inn	I-place
Yard	I-place
at	I-place
Islington	I-place
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
at	I-place
Hackney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Table	O
Cloths	O
,	O
Towels	O
,	O
Aprons	O
,	O
Pillowbears	O
,	O
&	O
C	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
and	O
other	O
persons	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
lives	O
at	O
Shackelwell	B-place
,	O
and	O
takes	O
in	O
Washing	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
were	O
hung	O
in	O
her	O
Garden	O
to	O
dry	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
got	O
in	O
,	O
took	O
them	O
off	O
the	O
Bushes	O
and	O
threw	O
them	O
over	O
the	O
Hedge	O
into	O
the	O
Field	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
round	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
seen	O
,	O
was	O
follow	O
'd	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
perceiving	O
,	O
threw	O
the	O
Goods	O
down	O
in	O
a	O
Ditch	O
and	O
ran	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
two	O
Fields	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
stopt	O
by	O
a	O
Brook	O
and	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
6	O
Cloths	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
following	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
hers	O
she	O
might	O
have	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
Great	O
House	O
in	O
Hendon	O
parish	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
now	O
repairing	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Crasy	O
sometimes	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
Lunatick	O
this	O
Twelve-Month	O
:	O
but	O
called	O
none	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Counterfeiting	O
and	O
Forging	O
a	O
Six	O
penny	O
Stamp	O
or	O
Mark	O
for	O
Stamping	O
Paper	O
,	O
Parchment	O
,	O
or	O
Vellum	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
defraud	O
the	O
King	O
thereby	O
,	O
contrary	O
to	O
the	O
Statutes	O
of	O
the	O
5th	O
and	O
9th	O
of	O
King	O
William	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Subsequent	O
Acts	O
of	O
Parliament	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Price	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Graver	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
him	O
a	O
Steal	O
Punch	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Parchment	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Draught	O
of	O
a	O
Rose	O
and	O
Crown	O
and	O
Garter	O
done	O
by	O
a	O
Pen	O
and	O
Ink	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
agreed	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
grave	O
the	O
said	O
Draught	O
on	O
the	O
said	O
Steal	O
Punch	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
leave	O
a	O
Space	O
at	O
the	O
Bottom	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
tell	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
should	O
Grave	O
there	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
the	O
Draught	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
must	O
put	O
VI	O
PENCE	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
by	O
him	O
while	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
before	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
agreed	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
25	O
s.	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
1	O
s.	O
before	O
he	O
began	O
,	O
10	O
s.	O
while	O
doing	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Note	O
for	O
10	O
s.	O
more	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Clay	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
having	O
Information	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
at	O
the	O
Stamp	O
Office	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
he	O
follow	O
'd	O
into	O
the	O
Roe	O
Buck	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Tibbolds	O
Row	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
(	O
pulling	O
the	O
Stamp	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
)	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
detain	O
me	O
for	O
this	O
Stamp	O
?	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
made	O
only	O
to	O
Stamp	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
two	O
Deeds	O
that	O
were	O
burnt	O
.	O
And	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hopkins	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Bott	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
Alehouse	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Clay	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
confirmed	O
Mr.	O
Clay	O
's	O
Evidence	O
.	O
The	O
Stamp	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
the	O
prisoner	O
deliver	O
'd	O
to	O
Mr	O
Clay	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
same	O
same	O
that	O
Price	O
made	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Rolles	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
perfect	O
Resemblance	O
of	O
their	O
Six	O
Penny	O
Stamp	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
made	O
any	O
Use	O
or	O
is	O
,	O
neither	O
did	O
he	O
intend	O
it	O
:	O
and	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
some	O
who	O
had	O
Dealt	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
who	O
knew	O
him	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
an	O
Honest	O
and	O
Industrious	O
Man	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
Wife	O
and	O
Eight	O
Children	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
now	O
reduced	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
,	O
(	O
Death	O
.	O
)	O
And	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
recommended	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Mercy	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
in	O
consideration	O
of	O
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
Children	O
.	O
Gilbert	B-pers
Beard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
at	I-place
Hackney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Shirt	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
House	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
next	O
Room	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Shirt	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
followed	O
him	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Bosom	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Armstrong	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Muslin	O
Neckcloth	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joshua	B-pers
Laney	I-pers
,	O
one	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Aaron	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Bedfont	B-place
in	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
Pound	O
of	O
Bread	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
2	O
ounces	O
of	O
Butter	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
2	O
ounces	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
2	O
Combs	O
value	O
8	O
d	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Ives	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judment	O
as	O
followeth	O
;	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
.	O
3.	O
John	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Speerman	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
2.	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
the	O
last	O
formerly	O
Convicted	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
.	O
11.	O
Mary	B-pers
Higgins	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Cauthorn	I-pers
,	O
Eliz	B-pers
Alexander	I-pers
,	O
Grace	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
Eliz	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Grey	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	O
Gilbert	B-pers
Beard	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Boswell	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Boswell	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
,	O
4.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
Lewis	B-pers
Goleston	I-pers
.	O
Williams	O
Cullum	O
,	O
Fined	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
to	O
suffer	O
one	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
,	O
Fined	O
13s	O
.	O
4	O
d.	O
Linch	O
Scarriot	O
,	O
formerly	O
Convicted	O
,	O
Fined	O
20	O
s.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
Lately	O
publish	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
6th	O
Edition	O
with	O
Additions	O
of	O
,	O
YOUTH	O
's	O
introduction	O
to	O
Trade	O
and	O
Business	O
:	O
Containing	O
I	O
.	O
Tables	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
usual	O
Clerk-like	O
Contradictions	O
of	O
Words	O
;	O
a	O
Collection	O
of	O
English	O
Words	O
alike	O
in	O
Sound	O
,	O
but	O
different	O
in	O
Signification	O
;	O
with	O
proper	O
Directions	O
how	O
to	O
address	O
to	O
Persons	O
of	O
Elevated	O
Rank	O
,	O
and	O
those	O
in	O
Office	O
.	O
II	O
.	O
Acquittances	O
and	O
Promissory	O
Notes	O
diversified	O
,	O
and	O
adapted	O
to	O
such	O
Circumstances	O
as	O
occur	O
in	O
real	O
Business	O
III	O
.	O
Variety	O
of	O
Bills	O
of	O
Parcels	O
,	O
and	O
Bills	O
on	O
Book	O
Debts	O
,	O
to	O
enter	O
the	O
Learner	O
in	O
the	O
Manner	O
and	O
Methods	O
of	O
Commerce	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
ready	O
at	O
Computation	O
.	O
IV	O
.	O
Bills	O
of	O
Exchange	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
necessary	O
for	O
the	O
right	O
understanding	O
and	O
Management	O
of	O
Remittances	O
;	O
several	O
Orders	O
for	O
Goods	O
,	O
Letters	O
of	O
Credit	O
,	O
Invoyces	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Merchants	O
like	O
Examples	O
.	O
V.	O
Authentick	O
Forms	O
of	O
such	O
Law-Proceedings	O
,	O
as	O
are	O
most	O
frequently	O
to	O
be	O
met	O
with	O
,	O
in	O
Course	O
of	O
Traffick	O
.	O
VI	O
.	O
A	O
Collection	O
of	O
Questions	O
,	O
to	O
exemplify	O
the	O
common	O
Rules	O
of	O
Arithmetick	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
reduce	O
them	O
to	O
Practice	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
Schools	O
.	O
Done	O
upon	O
the	O
Plan	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
Col.	O
Ayre	O
's	O
Essay	O
,	O
By	O
M.	O
Clare	O
,	O
School-master	O
in	O
Soho	O
Square	O
,	O
London	O
.	O
With	O
whom	O
Youth	O
may	O
board	O
and	O
be	O
fitted	O
for	O
Business	O
.	O
price	O
2s	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
Ed	O
Symon	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Pope's-head-Alley	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
.	O
A	O
Water	O
that	O
perfectly	O
cures	O
the	O
Itch	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
Itching	O
Humour	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
,	O
without	O
necessity	O
of	O
Purging	O
or	O
the	O
dangerous	O
use	O
of	O
Mercury	O
,	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
is	O
only	O
Prepared	O
and	O
Sold	O
by	O
A	O
.	O
Downing	O
Chymist	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
and	O
Ball	O
in	O
George	O
Court	O
in	O
St.	O
John	O
's	O
Lane	O
by	O
Hitch	O
Hall	O
near	O
West-Smithfield	O
.	O
Where	O
also	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
,	O
the	O
best	O
Spirits	O
of	O
Scurvy-Grass	O
,	O
by	O
Wholesale	O
or	O
Retale	O
at	O
8	O
d.	O
a	O
Bottle	O
.	O
A	O
most	O
effectual	O
Remedy	O
for	O
the	O
Violent	O
Pain	O
in	O
the	O
Teeth	O
,	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
Also	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Remedy	O
for	O
preserving	O
the	O
Teeth	O
and	O
clearing	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
,	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
The	O
following	O
Books	O
are	O
given	O
Gratia	O
.	O
1st	O
,	O
THE	O
Practical	O
Scheme	O
of	O
the	O
Secret	O
Disease	O
and	O
Broken	O
Constitutions	O
,	O
by	O
Fast	O
Living	O
,	O
Former	O
ill	O
Cures	O
,	O
Salivations	O
and	O
Mercury	O
,	O
--	O
2ly	O
,	O
The	O
New	O
system	O
of	O
the	O
GOUT	O
and	O
Rheumatism	O
,	O
drawn	O
from	O
Reason	O
Anatomical	O
Observations	O
and	O
Experience	O
,	O
--	O
3ly	O
.	O
A	O
Rational	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Cause	O
,	O
Nature	O
,	O
and	O
Cure	O
of	O
WEAKNESSES	O
usually	O
attending	O
Persons	O
after	O
former	O
Cures	O
,	O
Over-strainings	O
,	O
Self-Abuses	O
,	O
Hard	O
Labours	O
,	O
Miscarriages	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Whereas	O
is	O
given	O
a	O
full	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
horrid	O
Nature	O
,	O
and	O
most	O
miserable	O
Consequences	O
of	O
Self-Abuses	O
in	O
particulars	O
.	O
These	O
Books	O
(	O
all	O
New	O
Editions	O
)	O
are	O
given	O
Gratis	O
Up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
ANODYNE	O
.	O
NECKLACE	O
,	O
without	O
Temple-Bar	O
.	O
At	O
Mr.	O
Cowpers	O
Toy	O
shop	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Charles	O
Court	O
by	O
Hungerford-Market	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
And	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Garraway	O
's	O
Shop	O
at	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms	O
at	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange-Gate	O
next	O
Cornhill	O
.	O
Some	O
BOOKS	O
printed	O
for	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
Edmund	O
Parker	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
and	O
Crown	O
in	O
Lombard	O
Street	O
,	O
near	O
Stocks	O
Market	O
.	O
ENGLAND	O
's	O
Perfect	O
School-Master	O
;	O
with	O
Directions	O
for	O
exact	O
Spelling	O
,	O
Reading	O
,	O
Writing	O
and	O
Arithmetick	O
.	O
Shewing	O
how	O
to	O
Spell	O
or	O
Read	O
any	O
Chapter	O
in	O
the	O
Bible	O
by	O
Four	O
and	O
Twenty	O
Words	O
only	O
,	O
with	O
Examples	O
of	O
most	O
Words	O
from	O
One	O
to	O
Six	O
Syllables	O
,	O
both	O
in	O
whole	O
Words	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
divided	O
:	O
with	O
Rules	O
how	O
to	O
Spell	O
them	O
.	O
Al	O
o	O
how	O
to	O
Spell	O
all	O
such	O
Words	O
which	O
are	O
alike	O
in	O
sound	O
,	O
yet	O
different	O
in	O
their	O
Sense	O
and	O
Spelling	O
.	O
Together	O
with	O
the	O
true	O
Meaning	O
and	O
use	O
of	O
all	O
Stops	O
and	O
Points	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
observed	O
by	O
all	O
that	O
would	O
Read	O
and	O
Write	O
well	O
.	O
With	O
a	O
Table	O
of	O
Orthography	O
,	O
shewing	O
how	O
to	O
Write	O
true	O
English	O
:	O
with	O
several	O
Copies	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
usual	O
Hands	O
Engraven	O
in	O
Copper	O
.	O
As	O
also	O
variety	O
of	O
Pieces	O
in	O
English	O
Verse	O
on	O
the	O
most	O
remarkable	O
passages	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
Scripture	O
;	O
very	O
useful	O
for	O
Writing	O
Schools	O
.	O
Lastly	O
,	O
Direction	O
for	O
Writing	O
of	O
Letters	O
,	O
Acquittances	O
,	O
Bills	O
of	O
Exchange	O
,	O
Bills	O
of	O
Parcels	O
,	O
Bills	O
of	O
Debt	O
,	O
Bonds	O
,	O
etc	O
.	O
How	O
to	O
state	O
Accompts	O
aright	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
By	O
Nathaniel	O
Strong	O
,	O
late	O
School	O
Master	O
in	O
London	O
.	O
The	O
Tenth	O
Edition	O
,	O
Corrected	O
and	O
much	O
Enlarged	O
.	O
A	O
Rich	O
Treasure	O
at	O
an	O
easy	O
Rate	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
The	O
ready	O
way	O
to	O
True	O
Content	O
.	O
A	O
Short	O
and	O
Pleasant	O
Discourse	O
,	O
manifestly	O
shewing	O
how	O
inconsistent	O
Riches	O
is	O
with	O
Piety	O
usually	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
Opposite	O
Poverty	O
is	O
often	O
.	O
Together	O
with	O
the	O
happy	O
Agreement	O
and	O
Conjunction	O
of	O
Honest	O
Labour	O
,	O
Real	O
Godliness	O
,	O
and	O
Soul	O
Content	O
.	O
The	O
Preacher	O
sought	O
to	O
find	O
out	O
acceptable	O
words	O
(	O
words	O
of	O
delight	O
)	O
and	O
thus	O
which	O
was	O
Written	O
was	O
upright	O
,	O
even	O
words	O
of	O
Truth	O
,	O
Eccles	O
.	O
10,12	O
.	O
Omne	O
tulit	O
Panctum	O
,	O
qui	O
miscuit	O
utile	O
Dulci	O
.	O
The	O
Third	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
6	O
d.	O
Aesop	O
's	O
Fables	O
,	O
with	O
Morals	O
and	O
Reflections	O
,	O
as	O
improved	O
by	O
Sir	O
Roger	O
L'Estrange	O
,	O
done	O
into	O
Variety	O
of	O
English	O
Verse	O
.	O
Illustrated	O
with	O
Cuts	O
curiously	O
engraved	O
on	O
Copper	O
Plates	O
.	O
Very	O
useful	O
to	O
Divert	O
and	O
Instruct	O
Young	O
Gentlemen	O
and	O
Ladies	O
in	O
the	O
Conduct	O
of	O
Human	O
Life	O
.	O
The	O
Fourth	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Arithmetick	O
made	O
easie	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
New	O
Method	O
now	O
taught	O
and	O
practis	O
'd	O
in	O
London	O
.	O
Wherein	O
the	O
Rules	O
of	O
that	O
necessary	O
Art	O
are	O
briefly	O
explain	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
illustrated	O
with	O
such	O
familiar	O
Examples	O
as	O
may	O
suit	O
the	O
meanest	O
Capacity	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
desire	O
to	O
learn	O
it	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
a	O
Succinct	O
Treatise	O
of	O
Decimal	O
Fractions	O
,	O
with	O
Compleat	O
Tables	O
,	O
Rules	O
and	O
Examples	O
demonstrating	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
like	O
not	O
extant	O
in	O
any	O
other	O
Treatise	O
of	O
this	O
Nature	O
.	O
The	O
Fourth	O
Edition	O
.	O
By	O
Johns	O
Copeland	O
,	O
Writing-Master	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
1	O
s.	O
Maximum	O
in	O
Minimo	O
:	O
Or	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Jeremiah	O
Rich	O
's	O
Pens	O
Dexterity	O
completed	O
,	O
Being	O
the	O
plainest	O
and	O
easiest	O
Method	O
of	O
writing	O
SHORT-HAND	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
are	O
added	O
.	O
The	O
Terms	O
of	O
the	O
Law	O
complete	O
in	O
Characters	O
at	O
length	O
,	O
being	O
of	O
great	O
use	O
to	O
all	O
Lawyers	O
and	O
others	O
who	O
take	O
Tryals	O
at	O
large	O
in	O
Courts	O
.	O
Never	O
done	O
till	O
now	O
.	O
By	O
Samuel	O
Botley	O
.	O
The	O
whole	O
continously	O
engrav	O
'd	O
on	O
Thirty	O
Copper	O
Plates	O
.	O
Pr	O
.	O
I	O
s.	O
6	O
d	O
.	O
