TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Qyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
,	O
ON	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
25th	O
,	O
26th	O
,	O
and	O
27th	O
,	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
,	O
1721	O
,	O
In	O
the	O
Seventh	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
FRYER	I-pers
,	O
Bart	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
King	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Eyre	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Mountagu	I-pers
,	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
Names	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Church	I-pers
,	O
Jerom	B-pers
Knapp	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Read	I-pers
,	O
Thompson	B-pers
Haynes	I-pers
,	O
Seth	B-pers
Partridge	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Cady	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Budgett	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Branson	I-pers
,	O
Watkinson	B-pers
Wildman	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Halford	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Gwinnett	I-pers
,	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Beckington	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Orbell	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Walkingame	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hearn	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Saul	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hirons	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wedgeborough	I-pers
,	O
Abraham	B-pers
Browns	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Henley	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Cane	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk-Handkerchief	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Socket	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
Hounsditch	B-place
she	O
met	O
3	O
Men	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
snatched	O
her	O
Handkerchief	O
off	O
her	O
Neck	O
,	O
and	O
wrapt	O
it	O
round	O
his	O
Finger	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
sure	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
Person	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
saw	O
him	O
plainly	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
sight	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
:	O
that	O
he	O
offered	O
her	O
a	O
Crown	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
;	O
which	O
she	O
refused	O
,	O
then	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
an	O
India	O
Handkerchief	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
unless	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
her	O
own	O
again	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Poney	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
hearing	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
cry	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
stopt	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
then	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
pickt	O
his	O
pocket	O
of	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
back	O
and	O
take	O
it	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
drunk	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
made	O
what	O
Resistance	O
he	O
could	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
secured	O
him	O
till	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
up	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
her	O
a	O
Crown	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
called	O
none	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
very	O
positive	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
late	O
Act	O
of	O
Parliament	O
for	O
the	O
more	O
Effectual	O
Transporting	O
of	O
Felons	O
,	O
Ec	O
.	O
For	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
formerly	O
Convicted	O
of	O
a	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
Transported	O
among	O
other	O
Convicts	O
from	O
Newgate	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
had	O
returned	O
into	O
Great	O
Britain	O
without	O
any	O
Lawful	O
Cause	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
also	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Half	O
a	O
Pound	O
of	O
Coffee	O
,	O
2	O
ounces	O
of	O
Bohee	O
Tea	O
,	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Garlick	O
Holland	O
,	O
8	O
quire	O
of	O
Paper	O
,	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
and	O
an	O
Iron	O
Key	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Gigg	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Trunk	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
he	O
confest	O
when	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
very	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bow	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Arthur	B-pers
Greenhill	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
and	O
cheapen	O
'd	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
those	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
missing	O
them	O
,	O
followed	O
her	O
to	O
Bow	O
Church-Yard	O
,	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
when	O
she	O
fell	O
down	O
on	O
her	O
Knees	O
and	O
begg	O
'd	O
Pardon	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Biggs	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
bring	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
Stockings	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Peticoat	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
only	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
to	O
look	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
and	O
snatcht	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
charging	O
her	O
with	O
stealing	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
But	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
believing	O
her	O
against	O
such	O
plain	O
Proof	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Josephs	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Great	B-place
St.	I-place
Helens	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Byfield	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
2	O
Perriwigs	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Randolph	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Laurence	I-place
Jewry	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spur	O
value	O
11	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Greystone	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Fire	O
happening	O
at	O
Blossoms	B-place
Inn	I-place
they	O
shut	O
the	O
Gates	O
to	O
keep	O
out	O
Thieves	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
was	O
let	O
in	O
to	O
help	O
them	O
;	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
Spur	O
and	O
Handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
the	O
Spur	O
in	O
Foster-Lane	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
confest	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Room	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Green	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
Spur	O
to	O
sell	O
to	O
her	O
(	O
her	O
Husband	O
being	O
out	O
)	O
that	O
she	O
questioning	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
produced	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
full	O
value	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
Said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Surprize	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
being	O
never	O
before	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
till	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Platt	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Moldin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Antholin	I-place
.	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
SilkHandkerchief	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
and	O
6	O
other	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
he	O
mist	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
;	O
and	O
(	O
looking	O
)	O
saw	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Hand	O
,	O
who	O
dropt	O
it	O
just	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
his	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
served	O
him	O
two	O
Years	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
6	O
Handkerchiefs	O
more	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Ash	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
in	I-place
Botolph	I-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Biggs	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Day-time	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
a	O
Brass	O
Pot	O
,	O
2	O
Brass	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Snuffers	O
,	O
3	O
Knives	O
etc	O
.	O
in	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Paul	B-pers
Petit	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Biggs	O
deposed	O
that	O
M.	O
Petit	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
formerly	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
gone	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
having	O
left	O
his	O
Goods	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
:	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Petit	O
sent	O
his	O
two	O
Nephews	O
up	O
for	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
and	O
Cup	O
wanting	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Journeyman	O
;	O
who	O
telling	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
observed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
his	O
Apprentice	O
)	O
full	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
etc	O
.	O
they	O
detected	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
work	O
'd	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Biggs	O
,	O
and	O
observing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
full	O
of	O
Money	O
askt	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
had	O
left	O
him	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
Room	O
of	O
Furniture	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
for	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
had	O
other	O
things	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
asking	O
him	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
to	O
buy	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
pretended	O
(	O
by	O
contrivance	O
of	O
his	O
Master	O
)	O
to	O
buy	O
them	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
out	O
on	O
purpose	O
to	O
give	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
bring	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
come	O
in	O
the	O
interim	O
and	O
see	O
what	O
Goods	O
they	O
were	O
;	O
that	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
brought	O
down	O
the	O
Goods	O
(	O
which	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
those	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
)	O
his	O
Master	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
caught	O
him	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
consult	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Room	O
by	O
means	O
of	O
a	O
false	O
Key	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
into	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Shop	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
.	O
Which	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
wait	O
on	O
Mr.	O
Petit	O
when	O
he	O
lodged	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
much	O
in	O
his	O
Favour	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
his	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
sell	O
them	O
when	O
he	O
would	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
nothing	O
else	O
but	O
those	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
H.	O
Curling	O
and	O
J.	O
Ticknell	O
,	O
(	O
Mr.	O
Petit	O
's	O
Nephews	O
)	O
deposed	O
that	O
there	O
Uncle	O
gave	O
them	O
his	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
on	O
purpose	O
to	O
send	O
his	O
Goods	O
down	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
and	O
mist	O
the	O
Tankand	O
and	O
Cup	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
were	O
there	O
:	O
that	O
they	O
bad	O
written	O
to	O
the	O
Country	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
received	O
an	O
Answer	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
:	O
that	O
their	O
Uncle	O
was	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
being	O
Bed-rid	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Key	O
would	O
open	O
the	O
Lock	O
as	O
well	O
or	O
better	O
than	O
his	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Rippon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
Botolph	I-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
4	O
Pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Hankey	I-pers
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Laurence	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
going	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
Gates	O
of	O
the	O
Wharf	O
the	O
Morning	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
Saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
reading	O
a	O
Ballad	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
opened	O
them	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
followed	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
a	O
dark	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Wharf	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
observing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
going	O
off	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
followed	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Casar	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
employed	O
to	O
watch	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
one	O
watcht	O
him	O
,	O
another	O
held	O
him	O
in	O
Discourse	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
cut	O
open	O
the	O
Hogshead	O
,	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
and	O
hid	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
dark	O
Place	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
3d	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
he	O
lay	O
at	O
the	O
Gates	O
till	O
they	O
were	O
open	O
'd	O
,	O
then	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
met	O
another	O
in	O
the	O
dark	O
place	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Tobacco	O
in	O
a	O
Painters	O
Apron	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
Gates	O
at	O
each	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
Wharf	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
one	O
pair	O
,	O
his	O
Accomplice	O
at	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
His	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
his	O
taking	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Hogshead	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
at	I-place
Billingsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
21	O
Pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Blackham	I-pers
.	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
in	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
and	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Drugget	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Oliver	B-pers
Cartwright	I-pers
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
ordered	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Recognizance	O
to	O
be	O
Estreated	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Carl	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le-Bow	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Marriot	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17	O
th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
to	O
cheapen	O
Stockings	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
perceiving	O
something	O
under	O
his	O
Coat	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
followed	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
put	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
and	O
begg	O
'd	O
Pardon	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Gervis	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
intend	O
to	O
steal	O
them	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
taking	O
his	O
Word	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hare	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
with	O
a	O
Stone	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Braithwait	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pearce	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Porridge	O
pot	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Goodman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Pot	O
from	O
his	O
shop	O
Window	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
saw	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Arms	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Forster	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
Porridge	O
Pot	O
off	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
Window	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
followed	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Holden	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
caught	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Pot	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
but	O
knew	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Ruth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Yeomans	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Christchurch	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Skin	O
of	O
Morocco	O
Leather	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Thorn	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
Shop	O
to	O
cheapen	O
Goods	O
;	O
that	O
Jones	O
pretended	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
to	O
match	O
some	O
Silk	O
while	O
Yeomans	O
bought	O
the	O
Leather	O
,	O
but	O
going	O
the	O
contrary	O
way	O
,	O
he	O
suspected	O
her	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Skin	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
Petticoat	O
;	O
who	O
then	O
said	O
Yeomans	O
drew	O
her	O
in	O
and	O
betrayed	O
her	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
;	O
Jones	O
in	O
Excuse	O
said	O
that	O
Yeomans	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Leather	O
and	O
bid	O
her	O
go	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
:	O
but	O
Yeomans	O
denied	O
that	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
her	O
taking	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficent	O
against	O
Yeomans	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Ruth	O
Jones	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Edgerly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
6	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Cocoa	O
Nuts	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Green	I-pers
;	O
and	O
1	O
pound	O
and	O
half	O
of	O
indico	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Dias	B-pers
Ferdinando	I-pers
.	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
March	O
Last	O
.	O
And	O
Edgerly	O
as	O
Accessory	O
in	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
Chapman	O
was	O
head	O
Porter	O
to	O
Sir	O
Samuel	B-pers
Ongley	I-pers
,	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Ware-House	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
Edgerley	O
.	O
Chapman	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
pickt	O
up	O
the	O
Indico	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
in	O
small	O
pieces	O
in	O
sweeping	O
the	O
Ware-House	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
against	O
Edgerley	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
:	O
and	O
found	O
Chapman	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Frow	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
in	I-place
Foster-Lane	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
10	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hasleton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27	O
th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
(	O
together	O
with	O
Sarah	B-pers
Green	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rhodes	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Purse	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
13	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Miles	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Painter	I-pers
,	O
on	O
12th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
ordered	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Recognizance	O
to	O
be	O
Estreated	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Godfrey	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Perkins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Withers	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
were	O
severally	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
late	O
Act	O
for	O
the	O
more	O
effectual	O
Transporting	O
of	O
Felons	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
For	O
that	O
they	O
having	O
been	O
formerly	O
Convicted	O
of	O
two	O
different	O
Felonies	O
,	O
and	O
Transported	O
among	O
other	O
Convicts	O
from	O
Newgate	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
had	O
returned	O
into	O
Great	O
Britain	O
without	O
any	O
Lawful	O
Cause	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Checkley	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Browne	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Purse	O
value	O
2.s	O
;	O
13	O
Guineas	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Miles	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
:	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
ordered	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Recognizance	O
to	O
be	O
Estreated	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rhodes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Purse	O
,	O
13	O
Guineas	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
4s	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Miles	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Painter	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Phillip	B-pers
Large	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Snuff-Box	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Roach	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficent	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bensley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hampstead	B-place
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Spurs	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
Margaret	O
Thompson	O
for	O
receiving	O
them	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Felony	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Seddal	I-pers
and	I-pers
Alice	I-pers
his	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
and	O
Alice	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
of	O
St.	O
Martin	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Humphrey	B-pers
Anges	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Malicious	O
Prosecution	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
granted	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Rayner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
in	I-place
White	I-place
Chapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
the	O
Properly	O
of	O
Samuel-Barret	B-pers
the	O
12th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
and	O
being	O
sent	O
up	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
She	O
broke	O
open	O
a	O
Cupboard	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Guinea	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
confest	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
which	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Grout	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
at	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
.	O
in	O
the	O
Day	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Ridinghood	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Jane	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
her	O
Hood	O
hung	O
up	O
in	O
her	O
Room	O
behind	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Amhurst	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lift	O
up	O
the	O
Latch	O
and	O
go	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
4	O
Minutes	O
after	O
saw	O
him	O
come	O
out	O
with	O
the	O
Ridinghood	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
followed	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
the	O
Ridinghood	O
at	O
a	O
place	O
called	O
the	O
Tenters	O
.	O
-	O
Gigg	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
hearing	O
the	O
cry	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
and	O
drop	O
the	O
Ridinghood	O
.	O
The	O
Ridinghood	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cauthrey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
in	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
3s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
another	O
Perriwig	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Stern	I-pers
,	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Glass	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Pancroft	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Journeyman	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
him	O
but	O
3	O
Days	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
askt	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
White-Horse-Inn	O
at	O
Cripplegate	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
the	O
Carrier	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
Six	O
Pence	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
)	O
askt	O
him	O
to	O
stay	O
and	O
dine	O
first	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
back	O
in	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
;	O
so	O
went	O
,	O
but	O
came	O
no	O
more	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
mist	O
the	O
Wigs	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Boxes	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
enquiring	O
he	O
heard	O
an	O
ill	O
Character	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
a	O
Friend	O
of	O
his	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
)	O
met	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
City	O
last	O
May-Day	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Wigs	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
made	O
a	O
Debt	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
a	O
Wig	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
askt	O
two	O
Guineas	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
have	O
taken	O
15	O
s.	O
whereupon	O
his	O
Master	O
stopt	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
this	O
Evidence	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
his	O
Character	O
;	O
that	O
as	O
they	O
went	O
along	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
offer	O
'd	O
him	O
5	O
s.	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
refusing	O
,	O
the	O
Prisner	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
their	O
Shop	O
and	O
owned	O
the	O
Wig	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
he	O
took	O
3	O
Wigs	O
off	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shelf	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
made	O
a	O
Debt	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Pencost	O
junior	O
confirmed	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
and	O
judging	O
it	O
not	O
to	O
come	O
within	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
Shop-lifting	O
(	O
he	O
being	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
)	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Coolham	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniouly	O
stealing	O
a	O
long	O
Saw	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Hand-Saws	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
an	O
Iron	O
Screw	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutors	O
deposed	O
that	O
themselves	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Sergeantson	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
were	O
at	O
work	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Richardson	O
's	O
in	O
Clarges	B-place
Street	I-place
;	O
and	O
at	O
Night	O
they	O
lockt	O
up	O
their	O
Tools	O
in	O
their	O
Several	O
Chests	O
;	O
that	O
their	O
Chests	O
were	O
broke	O
and	O
the	O
Tools	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
taken	O
out	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
that	O
himself	O
and	O
Sergeantson	O
committed	O
the	O
Facts	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
watcht	O
whilst	O
Sergeantson	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
broke	O
his	O
Chest	O
where	O
his	O
own	O
Tools	O
were	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
not	O
be	O
suspected	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
carried	O
them	O
away	O
in	O
2	O
Bags	O
,	O
he	O
carried	O
one	O
,	O
Sergeantson	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
that	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
sold	O
for	O
35	O
s.	O
and	O
he	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
had	O
17	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
His	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
workt	O
for	O
Sergeantson	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
apprehensive	O
of	O
Trouble	O
,	O
and	O
askt	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
a	O
Bag	O
of	O
Tools	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
they	O
should	O
be	O
seized	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
thought	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
own	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
Sergeantson	O
owed	O
him	O
above	O
40	O
s.	O
for	O
Work	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
17	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
part	O
of	O
Payment	O
,	O
he	O
called	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
of	O
worth	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
Considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
2	O
Pocket-Books	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Case	O
of	O
Spectacles	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Gervas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
Home	O
about	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
a	O
dark	O
Night	O
in	O
Lincolns-Inn-Fields	B-place
near	O
Tunnstile	O
he	O
mist	O
his	O
Pocket-Books	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
back	O
about	O
100	O
Yards	O
he	O
seized	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
being	O
the	O
first	O
Person	O
he	O
met	O
with	O
)	O
charged	O
the	O
Watch	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
searcht	O
in	O
the	O
Watch-House	O
his	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
off	O
his	O
Rounds	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Watch-House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Two	O
Watchmen	O
confirmed	O
the	O
Constable	O
's	O
Evidence	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Bank-Bill	O
of	O
25	O
l.	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Pocket-Books	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Felton	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
carried	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-House	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
along	O
Lincolns-Inn-Fields	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
rude	O
and	O
would	O
follow	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
perceiving	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Papers	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
thought	O
they	O
might	O
be	O
dropt	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Bundle	O
,	O
so	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
believing	O
her	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Allcock	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Grey	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
and	O
a	O
Muslin	O
Cravat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Blanchard	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Spurs	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
-Barlow	B-pers
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
lost	O
her	O
Gelding	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Stable	O
in	O
Hatchet-Lane	B-place
in	I-place
Berkshire	I-place
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
Cuthbert	B-pers
Harwood	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
Mr.Barlow	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
Horse	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
before	O
he	O
received	O
the	O
Letter	O
.	O
Mr.Barlow	O
(	O
who	O
lives	O
in	O
Hatchet-Lane	O
)	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lived	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
allowed	O
him	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Week	O
,	O
that	O
having	O
been	O
out	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
Home	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Horse	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Spurs	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
House	O
;	O
that	O
suspecting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
wrote	O
to	O
Cuthbert	O
Harwood	O
to	O
apprehend	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
when	O
carried	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
which	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Kendish	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
apprehended	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Linnen	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Blanchard	I-pers
(	O
which	O
he	O
produced	O
)	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
Spurs	O
.	O
Mrs.Powel	O
had	O
her	O
Horse	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hancock	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Peter	B-pers
Angels	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
near	O
the	O
High-Way	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
.	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silver	O
Chain	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Cuthbert	B-pers
Wharton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
in	I-place
White	I-place
Chapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Handkerchief	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
,	O
Martha	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
lost	O
her	O
Handkerchief	O
about	O
7	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
;	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
it	O
till	O
a	O
Woman	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Price	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
her	O
before	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
it	O
quite	O
out	O
(	O
he	O
being	O
some	O
time	O
about	O
it	O
)	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Petticoat	O
was	O
over	O
her	O
Head	O
(	O
it	O
Raining	O
)	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lifted	O
up-her	O
Pocket	O
with	O
one	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
pickt	O
it	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Smithson	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
in	I-place
White	I-place
Chapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
value	O
10	O
'	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Inkley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
workt	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
for	O
him	O
and	O
pawned	O
them	O
.	O
lent	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
7	O
l.	O
6d	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
,	O
Job	B-pers
Orchard	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
in	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Perriwigs	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Miles	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
May	O
,	O
1720	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
(	O
two	O
Perriwigs	O
)	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Head	O
,	O
who	O
then	O
owned	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cornelius	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pocket-Book	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Duplie	I-pers
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
about	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
and	O
hurt	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
meeting	O
a	O
Woman	O
with	O
a	O
Child	O
in	O
her	O
Arms	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
askt	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
have	O
Plaister	O
,	O
and	O
lie	O
there	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
yes	O
,	O
had	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
Room	O
where	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Woman	O
in	O
Bed	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
him	O
gone	O
to	O
Bed	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
refuse	O
desiring	O
to	O
sit	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
carried	O
him	O
into	O
another	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
him	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
Chair	O
in	O
the	O
dark	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
who	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
lay	O
in	O
a	O
Bed	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
asleep	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
sat	O
in	O
his	O
Lap	O
,	O
was	O
very	O
fond	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
pickt	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
Book	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
60	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
had	O
a	O
Husband	O
this	O
20	O
Years	O
The	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Mother	O
of	O
Pearl	O
Snuff	O
Box	O
set	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
2	O
Callico	O
Gowns	O
,	O
a	O
Crape	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Embroidered	O
Apron	O
3	O
Cambrick	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Hood	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Philip	O
Davis	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecetor	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
about	O
10	O
Day	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Harrow	O
to	O
see	O
his	O
Wife	O
who	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Prisoner	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Clothes	O
left	O
.	O
That	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
others	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
disposed	O
of	O
them	O
:	O
that	O
she	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
it	O
also	O
at	O
her	O
Trial	O
:	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Philip	O
Davis	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
those	O
that	O
were	O
his	O
did	O
not	O
amount	O
to	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
rest	O
being	O
his	O
Daughters	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
in	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Diaper	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Chadwick	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stole	O
the	O
Piece	O
of	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shop	O
last	O
Thursday	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Bartley	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Shop	O
and	O
agreed	O
for	O
some	O
rough	O
Muslin	O
,	O
left	O
18	O
d.	O
Earnest	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
come	O
for	O
it	O
in	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
suspecting	O
her	O
followed	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Piece	O
of	O
Diaper	O
under	O
her	O
Ridinghood	O
.	O
Two	O
other	O
Evidences	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
saw	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
Cloak.The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
James	B-pers
Bartley	I-pers
had	O
been	O
in	O
her	O
Company	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
asked	O
her	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
something	O
,	O
pay	O
his	O
Master	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
accordingly	O
she	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Goods	O
she	O
was	O
now	O
charged	O
with	O
she	O
called	O
none	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
nor	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
and	O
Daniel	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
.	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cotten	O
and	O
Linnen	O
Cheque	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
in	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
the	O
Instant	O
May	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
Palmer	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Watson	O
workt	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
that	O
whilst	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
were	O
gone	O
out	O
Palmer	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
confest	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
Watson	O
persuaded	O
her	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
.	O
Her	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
against	O
Watson	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Mary	O
Palmer	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Worsley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
in	I-place
Clerkwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Margaret	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Ridinghood	O
and	O
a	O
Linnen	O
sheet	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
the	O
Night	O
aforesaid	O
at	O
Cow-Cross	O
,	O
who	O
asked	O
her	O
where	O
she	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
)	O
was	O
going	O
so	O
late	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
her	O
to	O
Billingsgate	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Sheernest	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
fit	O
that	O
a	O
Woman	O
of	O
her	O
Years	O
should	O
go	O
so	O
far	O
and	O
so	O
late	O
by	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
therefore	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
:	O
but	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
Peters-Lane	B-place
the	O
Prisoner	O
pull	O
'd	O
her	O
into	O
an	O
Alley	O
,	O
stript	O
her	O
Ridinghood	O
off	O
and	O
,	O
had	O
like	O
to	O
Throttle	O
her	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
knew	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
again	O
,	O
they	O
both	O
living	O
in	O
one	O
Alley	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sure	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
lived	O
by	O
them	O
Two	O
Years	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
in	I-place
Westminister	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
4	O
Guineas	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Higgins	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
the	O
Night	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Pall	B-place
Mall	I-place
,	O
that	O
Price	O
thrust	O
her	O
Hand	O
into	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
laid	O
his	O
hand	O
to	O
his	O
Fob	O
,	O
having	O
most	O
Money	O
there	O
,	O
to	O
secure	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
4	O
Guineas	O
were	O
in	O
his	O
side	O
Pocket	O
;	O
that	O
Johnson	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
did	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
immediately	O
mist	O
his	O
Guineas	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
followed	O
and	O
seized	O
Johnson	O
;	O
and	O
calling	O
out	O
the	O
Watch	O
stopt	O
Price	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Guineas	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
Half	O
an	O
Hour	O
before	O
at	O
Richard	O
's	O
Coffee-House	O
at	O
Temple-Bar	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Friend	O
came	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
just	O
parted	O
with	O
as	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
met	O
no	O
Body	O
by	O
the	O
Way	O
that	O
could	O
take	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
Drunk	O
.	O
-	O
Mongomry	O
(	O
the	O
Watchman	O
)	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
held	O
Johnson	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
Price	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
put	O
them	O
all	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
Roundhouse	O
:	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
carried	O
Johnson	O
and	O
Price	O
to	O
Prison	O
before	O
for	O
Night-Walking	O
.	O
Johnson	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Price	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Chelsea	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
Home	O
Price	O
stopt	O
to	O
tye	O
her	O
Garter	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
by	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
up	O
her	O
Coats	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
(	O
Johnson	O
)	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
civil	O
to	O
Price	O
she	O
being	O
with	O
Child	O
:	O
whereupon	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
to	O
her	O
(	O
Johnson	O
)	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
up	O
her	O
Coats	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
so	O
Fat	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
feel	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
;	O
so	O
went	O
to	O
Price	O
again	O
,	O
who	O
he	O
ran	O
against	O
a	O
Door	O
;	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
lain	O
with	O
her	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
People	O
opening	O
it	O
they	O
had	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
fallen	O
in	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
forced	O
her	O
to	O
another	O
Door	O
,	O
then	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
because	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
comply	O
called	O
the	O
Watch	O
and	O
charged	O
them	O
with	O
picking	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
Drunk	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
lain	O
with	O
a	O
Woman	O
in	O
the	O
Roundhouse	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Trenworth	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
from	O
the	O
Coffee-House	O
,	O
saw	O
he	O
had	O
Gold	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
drunk	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
called	O
some	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
that	O
both	O
of	O
them	O
could	O
not	O
take	O
the	O
4	O
Guineas	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
Person	O
,	O
as	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
found	O
Mary	O
Price	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
Transportation	O
:	O
and	O
Sarah	O
Johnson	O
,	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pancrass	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Richard	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Bags	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
2	O
Perriwigs	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
6	O
Printed	O
Books	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Fish	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
:	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
stole	O
the	O
Spoon	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
stopt	O
in	O
selling	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bellham	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Pelham	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
felonlously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Whitton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
2d	O
.	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Cotterell	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
Durham	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
28	O
Pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Iron	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
May	O
and	O
Durham	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
lost	O
several	O
pieces	O
of	O
Iron	O
which	O
cost	O
her	O
4	O
d.	O
1/2	O
per	O
Pound	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Courland	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
askt	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Fletcher	O
's	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Iron	O
in	O
her	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
handed	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
under	O
Shoar	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
Durham	O
for	O
2d	O
.	O
1/2	O
per	O
Pound	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
but	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
Old	O
Offenders	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Jarborne	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Sharborne	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
3	O
Linnen	O
Shifts	O
,	O
4	O
Aprons	O
,	O
a	O
Pillowbear	O
and	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Headclothes	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Garter	I-pers
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
.	O
The	O
fact	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Downes	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
in	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Holland	O
Shifts	O
and	O
5	O
Aprons	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Price	I-pers
:	O
which	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Rhodes	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
an	O
Optick	O
Glass	O
,	O
an	O
ivory	O
Box	O
,	O
2	O
Silver	O
Tea-Spoons	O
and	O
3	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Caton	I-pers
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
hid	O
under	O
the	O
Bed	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
who	O
in	O
excuse	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Liquor	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Stewart	I-pers
,	I-pers
and	I-pers
Alice	I-pers
his	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Alice	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
at	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Leather	O
Bag	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
5	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bland	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2	O
d.	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Bag	O
,	O
and	O
9	O
l.	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dyer	I-pers
,	O
and	O
10	O
l.	O
9	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Flowryman	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Humphrey	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
John	O
Dyer	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
mend	O
his	O
Box	O
in	O
which	O
were	O
the	O
2	O
Bags	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
found	O
where	O
he	O
told	O
them	O
he	O
had	O
laid	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Emanuel	B-pers
Giles	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
in	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
,	O
together	O
with	O
Elizabeth	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bryne	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
much	O
disorder	O
'd	O
in	O
Liquor	O
lost	O
his	O
Watch	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Wife	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
pickt	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
fell	O
asleep	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
be	O
gone	O
:	O
that	O
a	O
Stranger	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Giles	I-pers
had	O
pawned	O
his	O
Watch	O
in	O
Petticoat	O
Lane	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
be	O
came	O
home	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
in	O
his	O
Bed	O
very	O
Drunk	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
before	O
he	O
could	O
wake	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
asking	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
Two	O
Women	O
brought	O
him	O
thither	O
:	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
his	O
Watch	O
or	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Raine	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
in	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Harburst	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Moor	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Barnet	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
the	O
Lock	O
of	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Rawson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
in	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
Quilted	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
Ridinghood	O
,	O
2	O
Lace	O
Caps	O
,	O
2	O
Cambrick	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Clogs	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Goods	O
of	O
Terence	B-pers
Redman	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Redman	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3	O
d	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
nurst	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
in	O
her	O
Lying	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
the	O
Morning	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
That	O
when	O
taken	O
she	O
confest	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
suit	O
of	O
Clothes	O
were	O
found	O
accordingly	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Browne	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Bucklept	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Bowyer	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Browley	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Bartur	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Bruce	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Bartey	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Thomas	I-pers
Battler	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
Chelsea	B-place
Yeoman	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
Convicted	O
of	O
a	O
Felony	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
for	O
Marrying	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Elliot	I-pers
,	O
his	O
former	O
Wife	O
Hannah	O
Blackham	O
being	O
then	O
living	O
,	O
was	O
now	O
indicted	O
For	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sattin	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
Damask	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
35	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Elliot	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
May	O
1720	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Fairless	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
very	O
full	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
Notorious	O
in	O
those	O
vile	O
Practices	O
,	O
and	O
Married	O
all	O
his	O
Wives	O
with	O
a	O
Felonious	O
Intent	O
to	O
Rob	O
them	O
of	O
their	O
Money	O
and	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Indictment	O
found	O
a	O
special	O
Verdict	O
whether	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
Felony	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
Barbara	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Dawling	I-pers
,	O
Alice	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Complin	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bray	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
in	O
Counterfeiting	O
the	O
Current	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Miles	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
Spencer	O
and	O
her	O
self	O
went	O
to	O
Hall	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
;	O
that	O
Hall	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
Home	O
,	O
but	O
Bray	O
was	O
there	O
and	O
made	O
them	O
both	O
Fuddled	O
,	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
lie	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
and	O
not	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
till	O
she	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
)	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
back	O
and	O
waked	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
Hall	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
came	O
Home	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
staid	O
there	O
all	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
they	O
all	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
and	O
Drank	O
at	O
a	O
Brandy-Shop	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
;	O
that	O
Spencer	O
call	O
'd	O
Hall	O
aside	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
more	O
bad	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
Hall	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
might	O
go	O
home	O
to	O
her	O
Room	O
and	O
make	O
some	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
the	O
has	O
any	O
occasion	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
meet	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
Bell	O
and	O
Horse-shoe	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-Street	O
at	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
strange	O
Woman	O
then	O
being	O
in	O
Company	O
)	O
that	O
they	O
met	O
accordingly	O
,	O
and	O
Hall	O
brought	O
the	O
Metal	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
Drank	O
Two	O
or	O
Three	O
Pints	O
of	O
Beer	O
and	O
Ale	O
,	O
Hall	O
bid	O
Spencer	O
,	O
Bray	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Evidence	O
go	O
to	O
her	O
Room	O
and	O
make	O
a	O
Fire	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
be	O
with	O
them	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
lighted	O
;	O
that	O
as	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
Room	O
Bray	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
Shop	O
and	O
bought	O
the	O
Materials	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
Molds	O
;	O
that	O
Hall	O
came	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
Fire	O
was	O
made	O
,	O
lockt	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
melted	O
and	O
refined	O
the	O
Metal	O
whilst	O
Spencer	O
and	O
Bray	O
made	O
the	O
Molds	O
:	O
that	O
Hall	O
melted	O
the	O
Metal	O
and	O
Spencer	O
cast	O
the	O
Counterfeit	O
Shillings	O
to	O
the	O
Number	O
of	O
40	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
all	O
they	O
made	O
that	O
Day	O
:	O
that	O
Spencer	O
gave	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
apiece	O
to	O
Hall	O
and	O
Bray	O
for	O
their	O
Trouble	O
;	O
took	O
the	O
Flasks	O
or	O
Molds	O
with	O
a	O
Shilling	O
in	O
them	O
,	O
telling	O
them	O
that	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
their	O
House	O
it	O
were	O
enough	O
to	O
take	O
20	O
Peoples	O
Lives	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
to	O
carry	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
she	O
should	O
be	O
taken	O
up	O
being	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Person	O
dealing	O
that	O
way	O
;	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Ladle	O
and	O
File	O
in	O
Hall	O
's	O
Room	O
in	O
a	O
Cupboard	O
over	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
saying	O
,	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
make	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
them	O
if	O
they	O
should	O
find	O
them	O
:	O
That	O
Spencer	O
had	O
Five	O
of	O
the	O
Forty	O
that	O
were	O
made	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
had	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
justly	O
how	O
many	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
being	O
given	O
to	O
her	O
wrapt	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Paper	O
.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
being	O
in	O
Fleet	O
Street	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Fenton	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Nichols	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
Spencer	O
(	O
whom	O
he	O
knew	O
)	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Miles	I-pers
(	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
he	O
was	O
inform	O
'd	O
carry	O
'd	O
bad	O
Money	O
for	O
Spencer	O
)	O
coming	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Fenton	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Nichols	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
Coining	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
searching	O
found	O
28	O
.	O
Counterfeit	O
Shillings	O
and	O
the	O
Molds	O
with	O
a	O
Shilling	O
in	O
it	O
on	O
Miles	O
;	O
but	O
nothing	O
on	O
Spencer	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
wrapt	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Paper	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Molds	O
in	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Leather	O
and	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Molds	O
from	O
Miles	O
and	O
laid	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
(	O
not	O
knowing	O
then	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
)	O
Spencer	O
snatcht	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
Bitch	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
to	O
hang	O
us	O
both	O
:	O
and	O
they	O
struggled	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
before	O
they	O
could	O
get	O
them	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
Then	O
Spencer	O
called	O
him	O
out	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
30	O
l	O
;	O
to	O
let	O
them	O
go	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Fenton	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Nichols	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
with	O
this	O
Difference	O
only	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Fenton	O
deposed	O
Spencer	O
offered	O
them	O
30	O
l.	O
a	O
piece	O
to	O
let	O
them	O
go	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Plumridze	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
Spencer	O
say	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
Woman	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
28	O
s.	O
and	O
the	O
Molds	O
with	O
a	O
Shilling	O
in	O
them	O
were	O
sealed	O
up	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
them	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
ever	O
since	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
what	O
he	O
then	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
were	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Leather	O
and	O
Handkerchief	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
wrapt	O
in	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Bridgeman	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Hall	O
and	O
Bray	O
lodgd	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
Ladle	O
and	O
File	O
in	O
a	O
Cupboard	O
over	O
the	O
Door	O
in	O
Hall	O
and	O
Bray	O
's	O
Room	O
the	O
Evening	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Plumridge	O
being	O
called	O
again	O
and	O
shewed	O
Counterfeit	O
Shillings	O
that	O
were	O
kept	O
by	O
themselves	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Pinkney	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Pinkney	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
from	O
Mill	O
and	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Plumridge	O
.	O
Miles	O
being	O
called	O
again	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
that	O
of	O
Spencer	O
in	O
the	O
Prison	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Pinkney	O
Mrs.	O
Bunn	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
saw	O
Spencer	O
pull	O
5	O
Shillings	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Bosom	O
in	O
the	O
Prison	O
Yard	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
them	O
to	O
Miles	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
perceived	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
Counterfeit	O
.	O
All	O
of	O
them	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
Spencer	O
and	O
Hall	O
called	O
some	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
Hall	O
and	O
Bray	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Barbara	O
Spencer	O
Guilty	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Burnt	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Wade	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stanwell	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
James	B-pers
Hickes	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High-Way	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Bay	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Pratley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
2	O
Males	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
and	O
Fifty	O
Leather	O
Bags	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
our	O
Sovereign	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Hicks	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
between	O
Colebrook	B-place
and	I-place
Long-Ford	I-place
between	O
4	O
and	O
5	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
;	O
who	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Horse	O
's	O
Bridle	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
stand	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
but	O
a	O
poor	O
Post-Boy	O
,	O
going	O
with	O
the	O
Bristol	O
Male	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
reply	O
'd	O
G	O
...	O
d	O
D	O
...	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
is	O
it	O
you	O
that	O
I	O
want	O
,	O
and	O
bad	O
him	O
get	O
off	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
carried	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
Field	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Bristol	O
Male	O
off	O
the	O
Horse	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
2	O
Bags	O
under	O
a	O
Hay	O
Reek	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
this	O
Evidence	O
go	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Hay-Reek	O
but	O
he	O
saw	O
his	O
Face	O
several	O
Times	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
Star-Light	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Light	O
of	O
a	O
Dark	O
Lanthorn	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
to	O
do	O
this	O
Business	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sure	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
Person	O
,	O
his	O
Face	O
being	O
bare	O
and	O
not	O
disguised	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
New	O
Prison	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
him	O
from	O
the	O
other	O
Men	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
some	O
Letters	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Bag	O
and	O
left	O
him	O
to	O
put	O
up	O
the	O
rest	O
:	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
on	O
Foot	O
,	O
Booted	O
and	O
Spurr	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
his	O
Horse	O
was	O
at	O
Colebrook	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Reading	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
Shaw	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Bed	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
thing	O
sent	O
to	O
him	O
would	O
be	O
the	O
making	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
Shuffle	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Nick-Name	O
amongst	O
them	O
)	O
had	O
Robb	O
'd	O
the	O
Bristol	O
Male	O
:	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
Shaw	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
where	O
he	O
found	O
Dickinson	O
:	O
that	O
he	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
Dickinson	O
two	O
Letters	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Bristol	O
Male	O
:	O
giving	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
some	O
Money	O
coming	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
Pack-Horses	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Waggon	O
:	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
hired	O
a	O
Horse	O
for	O
Dickinson	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
hired	O
one	O
for	O
Shaw	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
in	O
quest	O
of	O
the	O
Booty	O
:	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
overpower	O
'd	O
and	O
pursued	O
and	O
Dickinson	O
's	O
Mare	O
was	O
rid	O
to	O
Death	O
:	O
that	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
very	O
uneasy	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
trusted	O
such	O
an	O
Affair	O
in	O
their	O
Hands	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
betray	O
'd	O
,	O
or	O
they	O
should	O
cheat	O
him	O
of	O
his	O
Snack	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
Dickinson	O
return	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
this	O
Evidence	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
Horse	O
to	O
Shuffle	O
:	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
no	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
afraid	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Barlow	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
2	O
Highway	O
Men	O
whilst	O
they	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
Exeter	O
Coach	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
rob	O
the	O
Coach	O
himself	O
,	O
but	O
stood	O
by	O
,	O
anst	O
Rode	O
off	O
with	O
the	O
two	O
that	O
did	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
Evidence	O
riding	O
by	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
knockt	O
him	O
off	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
mind	O
to	O
Shoot	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
Drinking	O
with	O
Snow	O
on	O
Tanbam	O
Green	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Road	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Archer	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
Hickes	O
and	O
Barlow	O
to	O
New-Prison	O
to	O
let	O
them	O
see	O
if	O
they	O
knew	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
Directions	O
that	O
they	O
should	O
not	O
speak	O
to	O
one	O
another	O
,	O
but	O
give	O
him	O
their	O
Opinion	O
separate	O
:	O
that	O
they	O
both	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
walking	O
first	O
with	O
one	O
Man	O
,	O
then	O
with	O
another	O
,	O
not	O
alone	O
,	O
but	O
about	O
12	O
or	O
14	O
People	O
walking	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
them	O
no	O
hint	O
to	O
discover	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
by	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bell	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Office	O
when	O
the	O
Male	O
came	O
in	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
January	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Bristol	O
and	O
Bath	O
Bags	O
were	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
above	O
600	O
Letters	O
taken	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
bred	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Sea	O
and	O
liv	O
'd	O
very	O
well	O
while	O
he	O
followed	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
till	O
he	O
received	O
a	O
Hurt	O
in	O
his	O
Should	O
r	O
,	O
about	O
5	O
Years	O
ago	O
,	O
which	O
disabled	O
him	O
for	O
that	O
Service	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
unfit	O
to	O
rob	O
on	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
:	O
that	O
having	O
saved	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
set	O
up	O
a	O
Chandler	O
's	O
Shop	O
in	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
,	O
and	O
lived	O
very	O
honestly	O
and	O
in	O
credit	O
there	O
ever	O
since	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
the	O
following	O
Persons	O
to	O
invalidate	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
Reading	O
and	O
Hickes	O
.	O
One	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
Reading	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
rather	O
than	O
be	O
Hang	O
'd	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
'd	O
Hang	O
half	O
the	O
Nation	O
;	O
nay	O
he	O
'd	O
Hang	O
the	O
Devil	O
.	O
That	O
Reading	O
told	O
Strut	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Evidence	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
him	O
5	O
pieces	O
he	O
would	O
hang	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
Strut	O
gave	O
him	O
3	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Note	O
for	O
2	O
more	O
;	O
which	O
not	O
being	O
paid	O
,	O
he	O
swore	O
a	O
Felony	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
One	O
Johnson	O
(	O
a	O
Soldier	O
)	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
Reading	O
say	O
in	O
New	O
Prison	O
,	O
that	O
Wade	O
had	O
brought	O
it	O
upon	O
himself	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
Fault	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
met	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
come	O
down	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
Rapt	O
at	O
once	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Wagland	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
New	O
Prison	O
when	O
one	O
Strut	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
that	O
Reading	O
got	O
2	O
Guineas	O
out	O
of	O
Strut	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
give	O
him	O
more	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bailed	O
a	O
Friend	O
of	O
his	O
out	O
of	O
New	O
Prison	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
Reading	O
would	O
sweat	O
away	O
his	O
Life	O
;	O
that	O
Strut	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Constable	O
had	O
2	O
Guineas	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
gave	O
Reading	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
Person	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Mr.	O
Burroughs	O
(	O
Ostler	O
at	O
the	O
George	O
at	O
Hounslow	O
being	O
subpoena	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
askt	O
)	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
James	B-pers
Hickes	I-pers
(	O
the	O
Post	O
Boy	O
)	O
had	O
taken	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
several	O
times	O
;	O
that	O
one	O
time	O
he	O
caught	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
his	O
Money	O
again	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
dragg	O
'd	O
him	O
thro	O
the	O
Horse-Pond	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Davis	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Cheesbrook	O
's	O
Sons	O
at	O
the	O
Post-Office	O
in	O
the	O
Hay-Market	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
James	O
Hickes	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
but	O
be	O
believed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
dark	O
Rainy	O
Morning	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Hickes	I-pers
being	O
called	O
again	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Davis	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Cheesebrook	O
's	O
Sons	O
followed	O
him	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Days	O
,	O
advising	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
swear	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
it	O
had	O
Rained	O
just	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
cleared	O
up	O
then	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
this	O
Soldier	O
(	O
pointing	O
to	O
Johnson	O
)	O
offered	O
him	O
20l	O
.	O
not	O
to	O
swear	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Wade	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
askt	O
him	O
as	O
they	O
went	O
along	O
,	O
Whether	O
if	O
Mrs.	O
Wade	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
10	O
or	O
20	O
l.	O
and	O
put	O
him	O
out	O
Appentice	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
was	O
stifle	O
his	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Johnson	O
being	O
called	O
again	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
saw	O
Hicks	O
in	O
his	O
Life	O
before	O
this	O
time	O
.	O
Hicks	O
again	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
like	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Turvel	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
the	O
Soldier	O
that	O
came	O
with	O
Hickes	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
this	O
is	O
not	O
the	O
same	O
Soldier	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Carron	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Boy	O
and	O
Wilks	O
the	O
Soldier	O
together	O
,	O
not	O
this	O
Soldier	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
What	O
signifies	O
it	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
his	O
Life	O
?	O
Had	O
not	O
you	O
better	O
take	O
10	O
or	O
20	O
Guineas	O
?	O
That	O
Wilks	O
is	O
an	O
ill	O
Man	O
.	O
and	O
owed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
Grudge	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
also	O
called	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
of	O
his	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
Dealings	O
with	O
;	O
seven	O
of	O
whom	O
were	O
Sworn	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
Riding	O
Posture	O
,	O
either	O
Booted	O
or	O
with	O
Spurs	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Savoy	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Milton	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
on	O
the	O
Forehead	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
19th	O
.	O
and	O
then	O
Died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Barns	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
John	B-pers
Milton	I-pers
,	O
(	O
the	O
Deceased	O
)	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
Walk	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
walk	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Green	O
Trees	O
by	O
the	O
Canal	O
side	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Wife	O
with	O
a	O
Man	O
against	O
a	O
Tree	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
will	O
you	O
make	O
the	O
Kings	O
Park	O
a	O
Bawdyhouse	O
?	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
to	O
carry	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Lodge	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
said	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
;	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
the	O
Deceased	O
and	O
himself	O
over	O
their	O
Heads	O
before	O
their	O
Swords	O
were	O
drawn	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
Advance	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
will	O
run	O
you	O
through	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
drew	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
part	O
them	O
:	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
ran	O
cross	O
the	O
Grass	O
and	O
sat	O
in	O
a	O
Centry	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
advised	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
set	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Sword	O
was	O
not	O
drawn	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
his	O
Bayonet	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Gary	I-pers
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Love	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
bloody	O
next	O
Morning	O
;	O
being	O
Easter-Day	O
;	O
complained	O
of	O
his	O
Head	O
on	O
Monday	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
under	O
Arms	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
Guard	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
was	O
sent	O
home	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
and	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
light	O
Headed	O
,	O
and	O
complained	O
of	O
a	O
Pain	O
in	O
his	O
Back	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
Thursday	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Fever	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
struck	O
him	O
over	O
the	O
Face	O
first	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
retired	O
till	O
his	O
Foot	O
slipt	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
darted	O
his	O
Bayonet	O
at	O
him	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
walking	O
in	O
the	O
Park	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
quarrelled	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
abuse	O
the	O
Woman	O
for	O
?	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
Wife	O
:	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
drew	O
and	O
darted	O
his	O
Sword	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
retreated	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
advanced	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Carefoot	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
.	O
The	O
Surgeons	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
Dead	O
his	O
Scull	O
was	O
opened	O
and	O
the	O
Wound	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
simple	O
Wound	O
,	O
not	O
Mortal	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Malignant	O
Fever	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
only	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Chiswick	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
her	O
Female	O
Bastard	O
Child	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
May	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
Second	O
time	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Pepper	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Barker	O
's	O
Family	O
as	O
a	O
Chorewoman	O
for	O
6	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
his	O
Servant	O
)	O
that	O
she	O
perceived	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
at	O
first	O
denied	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
take	O
that	O
Key	O
and	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Wash-house	O
she	O
should	O
find	O
a	O
Thing	O
:	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
Cheese-Press-stone	O
behind	O
the	O
Press	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
a	O
Female	O
Child	O
at	O
full	O
Growth	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
her	O
Knowledge	O
:	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
no	O
Marks	O
of	O
Violence	O
upon	O
the	O
Child	O
:	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
Stiff	O
but	O
very	O
Limp	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
sent	O
for	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Bed	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
work	O
Condition	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
born	O
Dead	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
no	O
Marks	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
limber	O
that	O
one	O
might	O
wrap	O
it	O
about	O
one	O
's	O
Hand	O
like	O
a	O
Cloth	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
Hands	O
were	O
open	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Allsshaw	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
both	O
the	O
Arm	O
bones	O
of	O
the	O
Child	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
opened	O
it	O
the	O
blood	O
gushed	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Bowels	O
;	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
limber	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
born	O
alive	O
it	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
Stiff	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
no	O
Marks	O
of	O
Violence	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
not	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
a	O
Scratch	O
.	O
Two	O
other	O
Evidences	O
produced	O
some	O
Childbed	O
Linnen	O
which	O
they	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Trunk	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Vincent	I-pers
,	O
Junior	O
of	O
Fulham	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Holden	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Mortal	O
Bruise	O
on	O
the	O
Left	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Body	O
near	O
the	O
short	O
Ribs	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
February	O
following	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Died	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
Second	O
time	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	B-place
Crown	I-place
at	I-place
North-End	I-place
,	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Hammond	I-pers
and	O
Giles	B-pers
Millet	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
his	O
Father	O
and	O
his	O
Brother	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
2	O
Violins	O
and	O
a	O
Bass	O
Viol	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Father	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
quarrelled	O
about	O
a	O
Game	O
Cock	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Father	O
put	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
off	O
with	O
his	O
Fiddlestick	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
that	O
Giles	O
Millet	O
said	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
Case	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
him	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
struck	O
Millet	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
Poker	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Fire	O
and	O
Burnt	O
and	O
Cut	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Father	O
in	O
a	O
dangerous	O
manner	O
;	O
that	O
Richard	B-pers
Vincent	I-pers
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Brother	O
)	O
ran	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
playing	O
to	O
Company	O
in	O
another	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
askt	O
him	O
what	O
made	O
him	O
what	O
made	O
him	O
stay	O
playing	O
there	O
whilst	O
his	O
Father	O
was	O
kill	O
'd	O
?	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
Kill	O
'd	O
!	O
who	O
has	O
Kill	O
'd	O
him	O
?	O
and	O
his	O
Brother	O
answered	O
,	O
Giles	B-pers
Millet	I-pers
.	O
That	O
during	O
this	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Mills	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
Deceased	O
and	O
Millet	O
up	O
Stairs	O
and	O
lockt	O
them	O
into	O
her	O
Room	O
:	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Brother	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
where	O
is	O
the	O
Rogue	O
that	O
has	O
Kill	O
'd	O
my	O
Father	O
?	O
set	O
his	O
Foot	O
against	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
flew	O
,	O
open	O
;	O
(	O
that	O
their	O
Father	O
followed	O
them	O
)	O
that	O
he	O
fell	O
upon	O
Millet	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Browne	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Adams	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
believed	O
the	O
Bruises	O
hasten	O
'd	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
went	O
abroad	O
for	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
Weeks	O
afterwards	O
seemingly	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
declared	O
to	O
several	O
Persons	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
,	O
only	O
had	O
a	O
little	O
Hurt	O
on	O
his	O
Eye	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
as	O
active	O
and	O
vigorous	O
as	O
before	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Askew	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Coffee-Pot	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tea-Pot	O
and	O
Lamp	O
,	O
10	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
11	O
Silver	O
Forks	O
,	O
1	O
Silver	O
Salver	O
,	O
4	O
Silver	O
Salts	O
,	O
7	O
Silver	O
Tea-Spoons	O
,	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Tongs	O
,	O
2	O
Yards	O
of	O
Lawn	O
,	O
a	O
Ridinghood	O
,	O
a	O
Cambrick	O
Neckcloth	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
32	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jacob	B-pers
Henriques	I-pers
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Davis	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
to	O
be	O
hired	O
for	O
a	O
Chamber	O
Maid	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
where	O
she	O
liv	O
'd	O
last	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
might	O
enquire	O
after	O
her	O
Character	O
,	O
told	O
them	O
at	O
Madam	O
Green	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Curtis	O
's	O
in	O
New-North-Street	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
away	O
because	O
her	O
Lady	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
Worcestershire	O
and	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
bear	O
being	O
there	O
,	O
because	O
her	O
Father	O
who	O
lived	O
there	O
had	O
Married	O
a	O
Second	O
Wife	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
abused	O
her	O
Sister	O
and	O
turn	O
'd	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
.	O
That	O
going	O
to	O
enquire	O
according	O
to	O
her	O
Directions	O
,	O
the	O
Lady	O
Green	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Askew	O
alias	O
Green	O
,	O
who	O
indeed	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
4	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
exprest	O
some	O
concern	O
for	O
her	O
leaving	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
persuade	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
came	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
persuading	O
her	O
Mistress	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
out	O
betimes	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
following	O
to	O
get	O
some	O
May-Dew	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Wash	O
to	O
take	O
out	O
Pimples	O
and	O
Freckles	O
from	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
took	O
that	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
carry	O
off	O
the	O
Goods	O
before	O
any	O
in	O
the	O
Family	O
were	O
up	O
.	O
Davis	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Master	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Goods	O
for	O
Favours	O
received	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
having	O
kept	O
her	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
to	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
mistaken	O
in	O
the	O
describing	O
of	O
the	O
Place	O
;	O
but	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
Court	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
Second	O
time	O
to	O
answer	O
to	O
some	O
Questions	O
.	O
It	O
not	O
appearing	O
that	O
Askew	O
alias	O
Green	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
stealing	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
Chief	O
Disposer	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
afterwards	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Davis	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
in	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
in	O
defrauding	O
James	B-pers
Brass	I-pers
of	O
12	O
Yards	O
of	O
Sattin	O
,	O
9	O
Yards	O
of	O
Callicoe	O
,	O
8	O
Yards	O
of	O
Muslin	O
,	O
5	O
Yards	O
of	O
Soosee-Silk	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
14	O
l.	O
18	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
Askew	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
telling	O
his	O
Wife	O
that	O
her	O
Lady	O
wanted	O
some	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
best	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
must	O
bring	O
them	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
accordingly	O
to	O
a	O
reputable	O
House	O
in	O
New-North-Street	O
;	O
that	O
Davis	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
richly	O
drest	O
)	O
carried	O
them	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Lady	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
liked	O
them	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
must	O
go	O
and	O
fetch	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
her	O
Goods	O
for	O
Linings	O
;	O
that	O
Askew	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
must	O
give	O
her	O
the	O
Buying	O
of	O
what	O
she	O
wanted	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
for	O
helping	O
her	O
to	O
so	O
good	O
a	O
Customer	O
,	O
for	O
her	O
Lady	O
always	O
pay	O
'd	O
ready	O
Money	O
for	O
what	O
she	O
bought	O
;	O
she	O
would	O
take	O
the	O
Advice	O
of	O
a	O
Friend	O
who	O
would	O
be	O
there	O
by	O
that	O
time	O
she	O
could	O
return	O
with	O
the	O
Linings	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Bass	O
seeing	O
every	O
thing	O
look	O
very	O
Grand	O
,	O
went	O
home	O
to	O
fetch	O
some	O
Linings	O
for	O
her	O
Ladyship	O
,	O
well	O
pleas	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
so	O
good	O
a	O
ready	O
Money	O
Lady	O
for	O
her	O
Customer	O
;	O
but	O
alas	O
!	O
when	O
she	O
return	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Lady	O
,	O
her	O
Maid	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
she	O
left	O
before	O
,	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
.	O
For	O
which	O
Misdemeanour	O
Elizabeth	O
Askew	O
alias	O
Green	O
was	O
fined	O
20	O
Marks	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
upon	O
the	O
Pillory	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Cornish	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
in	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
in	O
taking	O
54	O
Pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Lead	O
from	O
the	O
Freehold	O
of	O
Elihu	B-pers
Yale	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Fined	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
to	O
suffer	O
3	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Whalebone	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
at	I-place
Stepney	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
in	O
entering	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tapping	I-pers
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
steal	O
his	O
Goods	O
.	O
Which	O
being	O
Fully	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Fined	O
10	O
l.	O
and	O
to	O
undergo	O
4	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Berridge	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
at	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Richard	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Hilted	O
Sword	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tooth-pick-Case	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Box	O
,	O
a	O
Penknife	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Bed-Gown	O
,	O
and	O
9	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Diana	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
who	O
should	O
have	O
given	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
before-mentioned	O
William	B-pers
Berridge	I-pers
,	O
but	O
instead	O
thereof	O
cleared	O
him	O
,	O
by	O
saying	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
in	O
receiving	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
proved	O
by	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
and	O
her	O
own	O
Confession	O
on	O
her	O
Trial	O
,	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
But	O
her	O
Sentence	O
is	O
Respited	O
till	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
in	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Rowley	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
54	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
stood	O
Mute	O
,	O
and	O
refused	O
to	O
plead	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
Money	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
her	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
should	O
be	O
restored	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
And	O
notwithstanding	O
the	O
Admonition	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
was	O
so	O
obstinate	O
as	O
to	O
suffer	O
three	O
Whipcords	O
to	O
be	O
broke	O
in	O
tying	O
her	O
Thumbs	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Law	O
requires	O
in	O
such	O
Cases	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Pleaded	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
And	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
in	O
publishing	O
a	O
Forged	O
and	O
Counterfeit	O
Lease	O
under	O
the	O
Hands	O
of	O
the	O
Principal	O
Officers	O
of	O
the	O
Ordinance	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
certain	O
Armory-Mill	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Crown	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
before	O
the	O
last	O
General	O
Pardon	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Deborah	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
in	O
charging	O
Michael	B-pers
Stockwell	I-pers
with	O
a	O
Bastard	O
Child	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
8.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
alias	O
Cane	O
,	O
Barbara	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
alias	O
Dawling	O
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Godfrey	I-pers
alias	O
Perkins	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Witherell	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Allcock	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Worsley	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
14.	O
John	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
C	O
-	O
F	O
-	O
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Coolham	I-pers
,	O
Michael	B-pers
Pickes	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Carreck	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Underhill	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Rawford	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Ingledew	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Pettit	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Field	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
alias	O
Millard	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Hixon	I-pers
alias	O
Newton	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Farres	I-pers
.	O
The	O
last	O
11	O
Formerly	O
Convicted	O
,	O
and	O
Nixon	O
and	O
Farres	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Work-House	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
,	O
27	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
,	O
Randolph	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Ash	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Earl	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Moldin	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Rippon	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pearce	I-pers
,	O
Ruth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Rayner	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Grout	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Cauthrey	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
alias	O
Smith	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Cotterell	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Durham	I-pers
Sarah	B-pers
Jarborne	I-pers
alias	O
Sharborne	O
,	O
Susannah	B-pers
Downes	I-pers
alias	O
Robinson	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Raine	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Rawson	I-pers
:	O
Cuthbert	B-pers
Wharton	I-pers
,	O
Job	B-pers
Orchard	I-pers
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Rhodes	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
,	O
4.	O
Edward	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Smithson	I-pers
,	O
Grace	B-pers
Woolley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Jonas	B-pers
Hilary	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Two	O
last	O
formerly	O
Convicted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Askew	I-pers
alias	O
Green	O
,	O
for	O
her	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
was	O
Fined	O
20	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
upon	O
the	O
Pillory	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
alias	O
Whalebone	O
,	O
Fined	O
10	O
Pounds	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
suffer	O
Four	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cornish	I-pers
,	O
Fined	O
5	O
Pounds	O
and	O
to	O
suffer	O
3	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
Diana	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
's	O
Sentence	O
is	O
Respited	O
till	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
,	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
in	O
a	O
Special	O
Verdict	O
.	O
Barbara	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
pleaded	O
their	O
Bellies	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
being	O
impannelled	O
,	O
found	O
Ann	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
only	O
with	O
quick	O
Child	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
Two	O
Not	O
.	O
