TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KINGS	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
.	O
During	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
the	O
Rt	O
.	O
Honble	O
Sir	O
William	O
Stewart	O
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
8th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
1722	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
BENJAMIN	B-pers
MOTTE	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Aldersgate	O
Street	O
.	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
:	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
,	O
Monday	O
,	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
and	O
Wednesday	O
being	O
the	O
6th	O
,	O
7th	O
,	O
9th	O
,	O
11th	O
,	O
12th	O
,	O
and	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
1721.	O
in	O
the	O
Eighth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
STEWART	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Rt	O
.	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
King	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr	O
:	O
Justice	O
Eyre	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Montague	I-pers
;	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
;	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
Robert	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Colborn	I-pers
William	B-pers
Polliday	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Gaywood	I-pers
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Forfit	I-pers
William	B-pers
Withers	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
Matthew	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
Roger	B-pers
Dewhurst	I-pers
Benjamin	B-pers
Birch	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Mitchell	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
John	B-pers
Meard	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
Allan	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Fairchild	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Wrenh	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Coleston	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Beatniff	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Eady	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Cash	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Crowder	I-pers
,	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Wingfield	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Harman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Peters	I-place
Cbeap	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Skinner	I-pers
,	O
6	O
Ells	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
3	O
Ells	O
of	O
Dowlas	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
1	O
Yard	O
of	O
Muslin	O
,	O
3	O
s.	O
1	O
Linnen	O
Handkerchief	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
4	O
d.	O
a	O
Check	O
Apron	O
,	O
1	O
s.	O
8	O
d.	O
and	O
20	O
Guineas	O
in	O
Money	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Richard	O
Skinner	O
and	O
David	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Wingfield	O
,	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
missing	O
his	O
Money	O
and	O
Goods	O
,	O
he	O
charg	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
who	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Till	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
kept	O
Company	O
with	O
Mary	O
Harman	O
,	O
who	O
pretending	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
Child	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
seduced	O
him	O
to	O
rob	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
to	O
provide	O
for	O
her	O
Lying	O
in	O
.	O
Mary	O
Harman	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
William	B-pers
Wingfield	I-pers
gave	O
her	O
6	O
Guineas	O
.	O
2	O
Remnants	O
of	O
Dowlas	O
,	O
and	O
1	O
Remnant	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
but	O
knew	O
not	O
how-he	O
came	O
by	O
either	O
the	O
Money	O
or	O
Goods	O
.	O
Wingfield	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
being	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
reaching	O
Harman	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Nicholls	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Alhallows	B-place
,	I-place
Lombard	I-place
street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Mary	O
Dry	O
.	O
18	O
Yards	O
of	O
Silk	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Dry	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
consess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fryer	I-pers
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
sold	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
one	O
Beachcrest	O
,	O
a	O
Slopseller	O
at	O
Billinsgate	O
,	O
who	O
bid	O
her	O
bring	O
any	O
thing	O
she	O
could	O
get	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
Money	O
for	O
it	O
Her	O
said	O
Confession	O
being	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Scoon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
Crocked	I-place
Lane	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
12	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Bathmetal	O
Buttons	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
a	O
Copper	O
gilt	O
Watch	O
Ch	O
in	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Lock	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Glass	O
Case	O
rattle	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
stepping	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Glass	O
Case	O
,	O
and	O
stopt	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Glass	O
Case	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
missing	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
Woman	O
take	O
up	O
the	O
Gross	O
of	O
Buttons	O
from	O
under	O
the	O
Stall	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
Watch	O
Chain	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
charg	O
'd	O
a	O
Constable	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
search	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
and	O
after	O
some	O
time	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave'em	O
the	O
Chain	O
from	O
the	O
Wastband	O
of	O
his	O
Breeches	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
William	B-pers
Limbry	I-pers
the	O
Constable	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
laid	O
he	O
won	O
the	O
Chain	O
at	O
Southwark	O
Fair	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
bring	O
no	O
proof	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Langly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Alhallows	B-place
Barkin	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
28	O
Pound	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Micajah	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
by	O
Brewer	B-place
's	I-place
Key	I-place
Gate-way	I-place
,	O
he	O
saw	O
2	O
Men	O
taking	O
Tobacco	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Watch	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
2	O
Men	O
then	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Shirt	O
and	O
Tobacco	O
behind'em	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
,	O
this	O
Evidence	O
,	O
followed	O
and	O
stopt	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
2	O
Hands	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
in	O
his	O
Coat	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
Man	O
got	O
off	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
he	O
believed	O
the	O
Tobacco	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Goods	O
because	O
they	O
afterwards	O
found	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Hogshead	O
cut	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
and	O
Watchmen	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Shirt	O
and	O
Tobacco	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
he	O
met	O
a	O
Man	O
who	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
help	O
him	O
carry	O
the	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
thereupon	O
lent	O
him	O
his	O
Shirt	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
;	O
but	O
bringing	O
no	O
body	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edmund	B-pers
Ogden	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Alhallows	B-place
Barkin	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Pound	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
.	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Micajah	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hoskins	I-pers
,	O
Watchman	O
on	O
the	O
Keys	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
Tobacco	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Hogshead	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
this	O
Evidence	O
,	O
follow	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Tobacco	O
lying	O
on	O
a	O
Table	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
restore	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
a	O
scandalous	O
drunken	O
Fellow	O
,	O
that	O
had	O
ow	O
'd	O
him	O
a	O
spite	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Tobacco	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Man	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Corder	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
a	O
wooden	O
Drawer	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
19	O
s	O
and	O
three	O
Half	O
pence	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
on	O
the	O
2d	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
as	O
the	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
a	O
back	O
Room	O
,	O
about	O
7	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Drawer	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
hearing	O
,	O
ran	O
out	O
and	O
stopt	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
till	O
some	O
others	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
Assistance	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
laid	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Drunk	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
l.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Pool	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
;	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Stable	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Douce	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Livery	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
30s	O
.	O
a	O
great	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
;	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
Fustian	O
Frock	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Douce	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Cass	I-pers
.	O
Parts	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Confession	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fryer	I-pers
being	O
read	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Carvel	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Gear	I-pers
,	O
31	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
;	O
2	O
Moidores	O
,	O
1	O
half	O
broad	O
piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
1	O
quarter	O
piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Gear	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecu-tor	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
were	O
together	O
at	O
Gear	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Gear	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
with	O
8	O
Guineas	O
more	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
China	O
Bason	O
in	O
the	O
sight	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
That	O
Mrs.	O
Gear	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
alone	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
That	O
afterwards	O
the	O
two	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
lockt	O
the	O
Door	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
returning	O
in	O
about	O
3	O
Hours	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
Door	O
lockt	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
down	O
the	O
Bason	O
found	O
but	O
8	O
Guineas	O
in	O
it	O
:	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
being	O
charged	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
and	O
paid	O
19	O
Guineas	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
promis	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
up	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
frighten	O
'd	O
into	O
the	O
Confession	O
by	O
the	O
dread	O
of	O
going	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
.	O
She	O
called	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Gear	O
had	O
charged	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
one	O
Dollifield	O
a	O
Waterman	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Gear	O
had	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
her	O
Door	O
was	O
open	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
received	O
16	O
Guineas	O
of	O
two	O
several	O
Persons	O
a	O
Day	O
or	O
two	O
before	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
she	O
paid	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Several	O
Witnesses	O
of	O
Credit	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Alice	B-pers
Peak	I-pers
by	O
beating	O
,	O
kicking	O
,	O
and	O
bruising	O
the	O
said	O
Alice	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
Stomach	O
,	O
Belly	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
parts	O
of	O
her	O
Body	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
languish	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Month	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Murder	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Lansdown	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Joice	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ellenor	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
(	O
being	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Barthow	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
near	O
Smithfield	O
Bars	O
)	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
grasp	O
the	O
Deceased	O
by	O
the	O
Throat	O
,	O
and	O
force	O
her	O
into	O
a	O
Coach	O
;	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Blood	O
issue	O
from	O
the	O
Mouth	O
and	O
Nose	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
who	O
lay	O
dead	O
(	O
to	O
appearance	O
)	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
made	O
some	O
resistance	O
,	O
and	O
begg	O
'd	O
for	O
Bail	O
;	O
that	O
next	O
Day	O
the	O
Deceased	O
being	O
bail	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
sent	O
to	O
bleed	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
dying	O
Woman	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
being	O
then	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
never	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
after	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Hart	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
being	O
just	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
was	O
arrested	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
that	O
this	O
Deponent	O
offering	O
to	O
get	O
Bail	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
struck	O
her	O
with	O
his	O
Cane	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
her	O
Old	O
Bitch	O
;	O
that	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
for	O
Bail	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Coach	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
threw	O
her	O
down	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
if	O
it	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
for	O
Lad	O
who	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
foot	O
of	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
she	O
should	O
have	O
fell	O
down	O
another	O
pair	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
stampt	O
on	O
her	O
Belly	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
laid	O
her	O
Death	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Uriah	B-pers
Rimington	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
to	O
bail	O
the	O
Deceased	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
begg	O
'd	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
get	O
her	O
out	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
was	O
afraid	O
she	O
should	O
be	O
murdered	O
;	O
adding	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
thrown	O
her	O
down	O
Stairs	O
.	O
But	O
being	O
cross	O
examin	O
'd	O
.	O
Rimington	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Deceased	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Hart	O
ask	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
pardon	O
for	O
assaulting	O
him	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Harly	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Deceased	O
on	O
her	O
Death-bed	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
bodily	O
Health	O
before	O
the	O
prisoner	O
arrested	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
her	O
Death	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
freely	O
forgave	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
hoped	O
God	O
would	O
also	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
,	O
this	O
Deponent	O
,	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
to	O
Hart	O
,	O
Ye	O
old	O
Bitch	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
rescue	O
my	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
and	O
then	O
struck	O
her	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Hart	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Key	O
.	O
Grace	B-pers
Duffy	I-pers
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
having	O
arrested	O
the	O
Deceased	O
at	O
her	O
own	O
Door	O
,	O
Hart	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
struck	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
with	O
a	O
Key	O
,	O
thrust	O
the	O
Deceased	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
shut	O
thee	O
Door	O
upon	O
her	O
:	O
That	O
then	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
two	O
more	O
(	O
she	O
strugling	O
and	O
catching	O
hold	O
of	O
every	O
thing	O
she	O
could	O
reach	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Coach	O
;	O
where	O
being	O
prest	O
by	O
the	O
Mob	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
his	O
Head	O
against	O
the	O
edge	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
Door	O
which	O
let	O
his	O
Nose	O
a	O
bleeding	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
if	O
any	O
Blood	O
was	O
seen	O
on	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
it	O
came	O
from	O
his	O
Nose	O
and	O
not	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hawkins	O
,	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
opening	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
fair	O
and	O
fresh	O
with	O
in	O
;	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
nicest	O
inspection	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
perceive	O
she	O
had	O
received	O
any	O
outward	O
injury	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Frances	O
,	O
Apothecary	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Week	O
before	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
death	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
Malignant	O
Fever	O
,	O
somewhat	O
delirious	O
,	O
her	O
Pulse	O
very	O
irregular	O
;	O
that	O
her	O
illne	O
's	O
did	O
not	O
proceed	O
from	O
any	O
Blows	O
or	O
Bruises	O
,	O
but	O
from	O
other	O
Hardships	O
,	O
as	O
Cold	O
,	O
and	O
want	O
of	O
Necessaries	O
,	O
Alice	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Barthow	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
that	O
bled	O
and	O
not	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
;	O
that	O
all	O
the	O
Evidences	O
for	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
were	O
scandalous	O
Persons	O
,	O
and	O
particularly	O
,	O
that	O
Hart	O
was	O
a	O
wicked	O
abandon	O
'd	O
Wretch	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
swear	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Arthur	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Baillie	I-pers
Esq	O
in	O
Great	B-place
Marlborough-street	I-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
Ravish	O
and	O
Carnally	O
know	O
Grizel	B-pers
the	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Alexander	I-pers
Murray	I-pers
against	O
her	O
will	O
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Murray	O
deposed	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
October	O
about	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
enter	O
'd	O
her	O
Room	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Baillie	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
with	O
a	O
Pistol	O
in	O
one	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
naked	O
Sword	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
telling	O
her	O
that	O
there	O
being	O
such	O
a	O
vast	O
disparity	O
in	O
their	O
Fortunes	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
hopes	O
of	O
succeeding	O
any	O
other	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
was	O
fully	O
resolv	O
'd	O
to	O
ravish	O
or	O
kill	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
us	O
'd	O
what	O
entreaties	O
she	O
could	O
to	O
dissuade	O
him	O
from	O
his	O
design	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
still	O
persisting	O
,	O
laid	O
the	O
Sword	O
on	O
the	O
Bolster	O
,	O
and	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
pull	O
down	O
the	O
Bed	O
Cloaths	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
beg	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
delay	O
till	O
she	O
had	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
further	O
,	O
asking	O
him	O
it	O
nothing	O
would	O
prevail	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
desist	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
already	O
ventur	O
'd	O
his	O
Life	O
for	O
her	O
sake	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
was	O
resolv	O
'd	O
to	O
pursue	O
his	O
design	O
,	O
be	O
the	O
consequence	O
what	O
it	O
would	O
,	O
adding	O
that	O
all	O
the	O
Family	O
was	O
a	O
sleep	O
and	O
if	O
she	O
made	O
a	O
noise	O
he	O
'd	O
shoot	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Pistol	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
then	O
offering	O
again	O
to	O
take	O
off	O
the	O
Bed-Cloaths	O
,	O
she	O
pusht	O
him	O
against	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
wrench	O
'd	O
the	O
Pistol	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
her	O
other	O
Hand	O
rung	O
the	O
Bell	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
ran	O
out	O
and	O
she	O
followed	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
Murder	O
,	O
which	O
rais	O
'd	O
the	O
Family	O
:	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
her	O
Chamber	O
3	O
quarters	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Trimnel	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
waited	O
on	O
Mrs.	O
Murray	O
to	O
Bed	O
about	O
one	O
a	O
Clock	O
and	O
shut	O
the	O
Door	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
by	O
the	O
Door	O
again	O
about	O
3	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
open	O
again	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
then	O
shut	O
it	O
again	O
and	O
left	O
it	O
shut	O
and	O
believ	O
'd	O
it	O
was	O
fast	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
put	O
several	O
Questions	O
to	O
this	O
Evidence	O
about	O
the	O
Lock	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
made	O
in	O
effect	O
the	O
following	O
answers	O
.	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
brass	O
spring	O
Lock	O
that	O
open	O
'd	O
and	O
shut	O
without	O
a	O
Key	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Lock	O
was	O
faulty	O
,	O
difficult	O
to	O
make	O
fast	O
,	O
and	O
apt	O
to	O
slip	O
back	O
and	O
open	O
of	O
it	O
self	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
believed	O
might	O
be	O
the	O
reason	O
she	O
found	O
Mrs.	O
Murrays	O
Door	O
open	O
the	O
second	O
time	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Park	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
hearing	O
a	O
noise	O
near	O
5	O
a	O
Clock	O
he	O
stept	O
out	O
of	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
down	O
Stairs	O
in	O
his	O
Shirt	O
,	O
thinking	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
Thieves	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
finding	O
nobody	O
below	O
went	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Lady	O
Baillie	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Murray	O
at	O
the	O
Stairs	O
head	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
heard	O
Mrs.	O
Murray	O
say	O
,	O
The	O
Rogue	O
is	O
just	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Rooms	O
down	O
Stairs	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Lady	O
Baillie	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
Arthur	O
had	O
attempted	O
to	O
ravish	O
her	O
Daughter	O
Mrs.	O
Murray	O
.	O
That	O
afterward	O
going	O
in	O
search	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
Mr.	O
Hays	O
who	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
a	O
Key	O
and	O
askt	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
it	O
,	O
this	O
Evidence	O
answered	O
yes	O
,	O
then	O
Hays	O
said	O
if	O
he	O
'd	O
follow	O
him	O
he	O
'd	O
bring	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
owner	O
of	O
the	O
Key	O
,	O
that	O
Hays	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
Room	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
be	O
law	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lying	O
on	O
a	O
Bed	O
without	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Shoes	O
.	O
where	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hughs	I-pers
afterwards	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
this	O
Evidence	O
askt	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
Mrs.	O
Murray	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
and	O
Pistol	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
lye	O
with	O
her	O
?	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
yes	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
then	O
askt	O
what	O
possest	O
him	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
?	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
answer	O
'd	O
he	O
believed	O
the	O
Devil	O
possest	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Deponent	O
askt	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
Drank	O
,	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
he	O
was	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hughs	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
in	O
Bed	O
he	O
arose	O
at	O
the	O
Noise	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
Blunderbuss	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
thinking	O
Thieves	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
none	O
.	O
That	O
afterwards	O
hearing	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
that	O
disturbance	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
search	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
that	O
morning	O
found	O
him	O
on	O
Hays	O
's	O
Bed	O
with	O
neither	O
Shoes	O
nor	O
Hat	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
Mrs.	O
Murrays	O
Room	O
in	O
the	O
manner	O
aforesaid	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
sorry	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
Evidence	O
did	O
not	O
remember	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
say	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
Ravish	O
Mrs.	O
Murray	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
Parks	O
ask	O
Gray	O
on	O
what	O
account	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
Confession	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Blany	O
was	O
read	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
He	O
open	O
'd	O
and	O
entered	O
the	O
Chamber	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Murray	O
with	O
a	O
design	O
to	O
ravish	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
Sword	O
and	O
Pistol	O
,	O
to	O
put	O
her	O
in	O
fear	O
and	O
oblige	O
her	O
to	O
comply	O
.	O
Several	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Letters	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
(	O
directed	O
to	O
the	O
Honourable	O
and	O
most	O
Christian	B-pers
Lady	I-pers
Bennyng	I-pers
.	O
)	O
was	O
openly	O
read	O
where	O
he	O
says	O
.	O
I	O
must	O
acknowledge	O
my	O
fault	O
,	O
and	O
pray	O
forgiveness	O
of	O
God	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Lady	O
of	O
the	O
Family	O
whom	O
I	O
have	O
offended	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
having	O
been	O
out	O
making	O
merry	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
fellow	O
Servants	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
very	O
much	O
disorder	O
'd	O
with	O
Liquor	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
up	O
Stairs	O
to	O
Bed	O
without	O
his	O
Shoes	O
as	O
he	O
usually	O
did	O
.	O
)	O
he	O
thought	O
he	O
heard	O
somebody	O
in	O
Mrs.	O
Murray	O
's	O
Room	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
brought	O
up	O
a	O
Sword	O
and	O
Pistol	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
Mrs.	O
Murray	O
's	O
Chamber	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
laid	O
down	O
the	O
Sword	O
to	O
look	O
behind	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
time	O
Mrs.	O
Murray	O
rung	O
the	O
Bell	O
and	O
alarmed	O
the	O
Family	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Vandercome	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
more	O
,	O
were	O
in	O
Company	O
together	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
the	O
Night	O
preceeding	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
drank	O
4	O
pints	O
and	O
half	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
quarts	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
home	O
between	O
3	O
and	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
not	O
quite	O
Drunk	O
but	O
very	O
mellow	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Ruffield	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Cook	O
was	O
drunk	O
over	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
did	O
not	O
observe	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
others	O
.	O
That	O
in	O
the	O
half	O
Year	O
she	O
lived	O
with	O
the	O
Lady	O
Baillie	O
,	O
she	O
never	O
knew	O
Mrs.	O
Murray	O
's	O
door	O
to	O
be	O
lockt	O
fast	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
Mrs.	O
Murray	O
's	O
Chamber	O
every	O
morning	O
to	O
light	O
a	O
Fire	O
.	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Brass	O
Spring	O
Lock	O
very	O
faulty	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
never	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
lock	O
'd	O
with	O
a	O
Key	O
.	O
All	O
the	O
Evidences	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
general	O
Character	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Youth	O
of	O
civil	O
and	O
modest	O
behaviour	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
(	O
after	O
about	O
an	O
hours	O
Consultation	O
,	O
)	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Vincent	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
Bridget	B-pers
Prichard	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Rea	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Wimberly	I-pers
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
publishing	O
a	O
forg	O
'd	O
and	O
Counterfeit	O
Will	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
real	O
and	O
genuine	O
Will	O
and	O
Testament	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hutchinson	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
St.	O
James	O
Westminster	O
Inn-holder	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
September	O
1720	O
.	O
The	O
Council	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
open	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
falling	O
sick	O
at	O
Vincent	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
Robert	O
Hutchinson	O
(	O
Brother	O
to	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
)	O
coming	O
to	O
visit	O
him	O
found	O
him	O
Speechless	O
.	O
That	O
Hutchinson	O
went	O
out	O
again	O
to	O
fetch	O
the	O
Surgeons	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
his	O
return	O
found	O
his	O
Brother	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Hutchinson	O
and	O
others	O
with	O
him	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
drawing	O
up	O
a	O
Will	O
,	O
he	O
the	O
deceased	O
being	O
then	O
dead	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Will	O
was	O
then	O
unfinish	O
'd	O
and	O
neither	O
sign	O
'd	O
nor	O
seal	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoners	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
hinder	O
Hutchinson	O
from	O
seeing	O
the	O
Will	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
Counterfeit	O
Will	O
,	O
the	O
prisoners	O
shar	O
'd	O
among	O
themselves	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Chattels	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
except	O
50	O
l.	O
which	O
they-bequeath	O
'd	O
to	O
Hutchinson	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
prov	O
'd	O
the	O
Will	O
at	O
Doctors	O
Commons	O
.	O
The	O
Council	O
for	O
the	O
prisoners	O
pleaded	O
that	O
the	O
Will	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
)	O
having	O
been	O
prov	O
'd	O
in	O
Doctors	O
Commons	O
,	O
the	O
determinative	O
sentence	O
of	O
that	O
prerogative	O
Court	O
in	O
a	O
Will	O
touching	O
a	O
personal	O
Estate	O
only	O
,	O
must	O
stand	O
in	O
full	O
force	O
;	O
And	O
thereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Laws	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Ware-house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
.	O
15	O
Hundred	O
weight	O
of	O
Cork	O
value	O
15	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	O
Allen	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
Laws	O
confest	O
the	O
Factand	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
enticed	O
to	O
commit	O
it	O
by	O
Richards	O
.	O
Several	O
Evidences	O
proved	O
that	O
Richards	O
was	O
seen	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Ware	O
house	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
(	O
Richards	O
)	O
assisted	O
in	O
loading	O
the	O
Cork	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
.	O
Richards	O
brought	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
Laws	O
was	O
a	O
person	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
Commisson	O
'd	O
by	O
Merchants	O
to	O
sell	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Cork	O
of	O
Laws	O
and	O
paid	O
him	O
the	O
full	O
price	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
brought	O
home	O
publickly	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
it	O
lye	O
openly	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Shop	O
He	O
brought	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
of	O
his	O
Neighbour	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Laws	O
Guilty	O
John	B-pers
Sergeant	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
John	I-pers
Higgons	I-pers
.	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Leg	O
of	O
Pork	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
5	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Driver	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
Man	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Pork	O
to	O
carry	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
Excuse	O
being	O
frivolous	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Trippet	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
Clock	O
Bells	O
value	O
13s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Pinkstone	I-pers
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
fact	O
being	O
committed	O
before	O
the	O
last	O
Act	O
of	O
Grace	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
Charles	B-pers
Beddo	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Magnus	I-place
the	I-place
Martyr	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cask	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
and	O
9	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Ale	O
value	O
11	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hodges	I-pers
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Osborn	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25	O
th	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hull	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Hall	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
Wood-street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
to	O
Wife	O
Ann	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
6	O
th	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
Majesties	O
Reign	O
,	O
his	O
former	O
Wife	O
Susan	B-pers
Purser	I-pers
being	O
then	O
alive	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
fact	O
being	O
committed	O
before	O
the	O
last	O
Act	O
of	O
Grace	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquited	O
.	O
Amey	B-pers
Peasy	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Saviour	I-place
Southwark	I-place
indicted	O
for	O
Perjury	O
,	O
in	O
making	O
an	O
Affidavit	O
in	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
the	O
Kings	O
Bench	O
,	O
contradictory	O
to	O
a	O
former	O
Affidavit	O
by	O
her	O
made	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Court	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
full	O
enough	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
latter	O
Affidavit	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Bembridge	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Constance	B-pers
Radison	I-pers
,	O
by	O
kicking	O
and	O
bruising	O
the	O
said	O
Constance	O
Radison	O
on	O
several	O
parts	O
of	O
her	O
Body	O
,	O
and	O
giving	O
her	O
one	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
on	O
the	O
lower	O
part	O
of	O
her	O
Back	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Month	O
and	O
then	O
dyed	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Langhorn	O
,	O
Chambers	O
,	O
and	O
Keeling	O
,	O
Watchmen	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
Sunday	O
,	O
Nov.	O
5	O
about	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
were	O
drinking	O
a	O
Dram	O
in	O
Princes	O
street	O
,	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
that	O
quickly	O
after	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
shreek	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
found	O
her	O
all	O
bloody	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
stuck	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
helpt	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
That	O
about	O
2	O
Hours	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Princes	B-place
street	I-place
,	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
undrawn	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
Keeling	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
stuck	O
an	O
old	O
Whore	O
in	O
the	O
Arse	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
sent	O
her	O
about	O
her	O
Business	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Watch	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
prickt	O
the	O
Woman	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
make	O
Satisfaction	O
and	O
pay	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Turner	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
carried	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Clarges	I-pers
,	O
where	O
he	O
at	O
first	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
confest	O
.	O
He	O
believ	O
'd	O
he	O
struck	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
in	O
the	O
Scabbord	O
.	O
The	O
Sword	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
misty	O
(	O
with	O
Blood	O
)	O
at	O
the	O
point	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
bent	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
sign	O
of	O
Blood	O
on	O
the	O
Scabbord	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Dolben	I-pers
and	O
Aigail	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
wnt	O
out	O
well	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
between	O
5	O
and	O
6	O
o	O
Clock	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Cellar	O
where	O
she	O
lodg	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
stuck	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
groan	O
'd	O
continually	O
and	O
neither	O
eat	O
nor	O
drink	O
,	O
nor	O
make	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
dy	O
'd	O
next	O
Day	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
Rogue	O
had	O
stab	O
'd	O
ber	O
,	O
be	O
stampt	O
upon	O
her	O
Stomach	O
and	O
Belly	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
G	O
-	O
D	O
-	O
ye	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
stick	O
ye	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
snatch	O
'd	O
his	O
Sword	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
with	O
struggling	O
got	O
from	O
her	O
again	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
sticking	O
her	O
,	O
except	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
accidentally	O
in	O
the	O
struggle	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Tyler	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
at	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
at	O
her	O
Landlady	O
's	O
Window	O
very	O
drunk	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
often	O
was	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Tyler	I-pers
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
her	O
a	O
dying	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
lay	O
on	O
a	O
cold	O
brick	O
Floor	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Vaughan	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Sherword	O
,	O
Surgeons	O
,	O
and	O
Edw	B-pers
Lampton	I-pers
,	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Vaughan	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
Inflamation	O
in	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Lungs	O
,	O
occasion	O
'd	O
by	O
her	O
hard	O
drinking	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
cold	O
place	O
she	O
lay	O
in	O
,	O
which	O
in	O
their	O
Opinion	O
caus	O
'd	O
her	O
Death	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Wounds	O
she	O
receiv	O
'd	O
were	O
not	O
mortal	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Biss	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
in	O
the	O
right	O
Thigh	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
1	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
8	O
Inches	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Dyed	O
.	O
Wardel	O
and	O
Phipps	O
,	O
two	O
Servants	O
at	O
the	B-place
Mews	I-place
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
10	O
the	O
Night	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
hearing	O
an	O
Outcry	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
drawn	O
,	O
standing	O
by	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
who	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
on	O
his	O
Hands	O
and	O
Knees	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
toward	O
the	O
Mews	O
Gate	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
shut	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
afterwards	O
return	O
'd	O
and	O
surrendred	O
himself	O
civilly	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Douglas	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
wounded	O
,	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Foot	O
slipt	O
in	O
the	O
Action	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
stab	O
'd	O
him	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
down	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Macartney	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Charles	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
fell	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Rummer	O
Tavern	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
fought	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
prevented	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
Tom	O
's	O
Coffee	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
some	O
stay	O
there	O
,	O
they	O
parted	O
;	O
that	O
as	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Charles	O
were	O
going	O
together	O
,	O
they	O
met	O
the	O
Deceased	O
again	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
talk	O
'd	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Charles	O
went	O
to	O
Tom	O
's	O
Coffee	O
House	O
;	O
that	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
away	O
and	O
left	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Charles	O
further	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
wounded	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
three	O
fair	O
Bouts	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
run	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Throat	O
or	O
Breast	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
he	O
felt	O
his	O
Sword	O
in	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Shaw	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Martyn	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
death	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
left	O
Mr.	O
Charles	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
waited	O
for	O
his	O
coming	O
out	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
avoid	O
Fighting	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
coming	O
by	O
the	O
Mews	O
Gate	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
pulled	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Mews	O
,	O
drew	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
nor	O
Fight	O
,	O
he	O
'd	O
kill	O
him	O
upon	O
the	O
spot	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
drew	O
to	O
defend	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
Consequence	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
unhappy	O
Accident	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Westbrook	O
,	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
when	O
in	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
,	O
was	O
his	O
Patient	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
Wound	O
in	O
his	O
Breast	O
,	O
which	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Barlow	O
,	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
his	O
death	O
,	O
confest	O
in	O
his	O
hearing	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Sword	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
wounded	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Duffus	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
and	O
committing	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Leader	I-pers
,	O
the	O
unnatural	O
Sin	O
of	O
Sodomy	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
Nicholas	O
Leader	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
at	O
a	O
Meeting	O
house	O
in	O
Old	O
Gravel	O
lane	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
after	O
Service	O
was	O
ended	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
seeming	O
very	O
religious	O
,	O
began	O
some	O
Discourse	O
in	O
commendation	O
of	O
the	O
Minister	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
then	O
preach	O
'd	O
;	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
(	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Sundays	O
successively	O
)	O
he	O
insinuated	O
himself	O
into	O
the	O
good	O
Opinion	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
invited	O
him	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Powels	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
askt	O
this	O
Evidence	O
where	O
he	O
might	O
hear	O
of	O
him	O
another	O
time	O
;	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
3	B-place
merry	I-place
Potters	I-place
,	I-place
at	I-place
the	I-place
Hermitage	I-place
.	O
That	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
promis	O
'd	O
he	O
'd	O
come	O
and	O
see	O
him	O
the	O
first	O
opportunity	O
,	O
which	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
he	O
performed	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
staying	O
late	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
telling	O
him	O
he	O
lived	O
a	O
great	O
way	O
off	O
,	O
desired	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
lie	O
with	O
him	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
granted	O
.	O
After	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
Bed	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
began	O
to	O
kiss	O
and	O
embrace	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
thrust	O
his	O
Tongue	O
in	O
his	O
Mouth	O
,	O
called	O
him	O
his	O
dear	O
Friend	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
on	O
his	O
Back	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
resisting	O
,	O
threw	O
him	O
off	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
times	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
still	O
,	O
he	O
'd	O
turn	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
Bed	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
then	O
seizing	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
by	O
the	O
Throat	O
almost	O
strangled	O
him	O
,	O
turned	O
him	O
on	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
forcibly	O
entred	O
his	O
Body	O
about	O
an	O
Inch	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
still	O
strugling	O
,	O
threw	O
off	O
the	O
prisoner	O
once	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
prevented	O
the	O
prisoner	O
from	O
making	O
an	O
Emissio	O
Seminis	O
in	O
his	O
Body	O
;	O
but	O
having	O
thus	O
forced	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
withdraw	O
,	O
he	O
(	O
the	O
prisoner	O
)	O
emitted	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Hand	O
,	O
clapping	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
tail	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shirt	O
.	O
Saying	O
,	O
Now	O
you	O
have	O
it	O
!	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
then	O
turned	O
the	O
prisoner	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
,	O
but	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
disturbing	O
his	O
ancient	O
Grandmother	O
,	O
who	O
lay	O
Ill	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
Room	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
he	O
need	O
not	O
be	O
so	O
concerned	O
at	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
several	O
others	O
,	O
naming	O
in	O
particular	O
a	O
Cabbin	O
Boy	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
from	O
Justice	O
Tiller	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
it	O
the	O
next	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
to	O
the	O
Meeting	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Constable	O
whispering	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
sitting	O
down	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
being	O
conscious	O
of	O
Guilt	O
,	O
and	O
suspecting	O
some	O
Design	O
,	O
immediately	O
took	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
seeing	O
,	O
began	O
to	O
run	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
pursuing	O
,	O
and	O
crying	O
out	O
stop	O
him	O
.	O
soon	O
overtook	O
him	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
entreated	O
for	O
Mercy	O
,	O
and	O
begg	O
'd	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
expose	O
him	O
to	O
open	O
shame	O
;	O
adding	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
Sinners	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
hard	O
for	O
a	O
Man	O
to	O
suffer	O
for	O
the	O
first	O
Fault	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Powel	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
first	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
a	O
Lecture	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
no	O
sooner	O
over	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
very	O
devout	O
Face	O
,	O
began	O
his	O
Discourse	O
with	O
some	O
lavish	O
Encomiums	O
on	O
what	O
the	O
Preacher	O
had	O
just	O
delivered	O
in	O
his	O
Sermon	O
;	O
telling	O
this	O
Evidence	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
him	O
any	O
other	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
the	O
Lord	O
's	O
Day	O
,	O
he	O
(	O
having	O
a	O
very	O
tender	O
and	O
scrupulous	O
Conscience	O
)	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
a	O
Publick	O
house	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
they	O
made	O
an	O
Agreement	O
to	O
meet	O
as	O
this	O
Evidence	O
's	O
Father	O
's	O
House	O
(	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
)	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
Oct.	O
last	O
,	O
where	O
,	O
after	O
some	O
Religious	O
Discourse	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
laid	O
that	O
his	O
Wife	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
a	O
pretty	O
way	O
home	O
,	O
desired	O
to	O
lie	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
which	O
this	O
Deponent	O
(	O
taking	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
really	O
a	O
sanctified	O
Member	O
)	O
agreed	O
to	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
long	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
prisoner	O
began	O
to	O
kiss	O
this	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Privities	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
How	O
lean	O
you	O
be	O
!	O
Do	O
but	O
feel	O
how	O
fat	O
I	O
am	O
?	O
and	O
then	O
convey	O
'd	O
this	O
Deponent	O
's	O
Hand	O
to	O
his	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
)	O
Secrets	O
.	O
Soon	O
after	O
(	O
as	O
the	O
Deponent	O
was	O
lying	O
on	O
his	O
Back	O
)	O
the	O
prisoner	O
got	O
on	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
keeping	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
thrust	O
his	O
Penis	O
betwixt	O
the	O
Deponent	O
's	O
Thighs	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
emitted	O
.	O
He	O
afterwards	O
told	O
this	O
Deponent	O
he	O
need	O
not	O
be	O
troubled	O
,	O
or	O
wonder	O
at	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
what	O
was	O
very	O
common	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
often	O
practised	O
it	O
with	O
many	O
others	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
desiring	O
the	O
Deponent	O
to	O
act	O
the	O
same	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
refused	O
,	O
replying	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
stranger	O
to	O
all	O
such	O
Practices	O
and	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
before	O
,	O
what	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
lain	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Bed	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Spermatick	O
Injection	O
not	O
being	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
directed	O
the	O
Jury	O
to	O
bring	O
in	O
their	O
Verdict	O
Special	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Hogrel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Salt	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
8	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Canaway	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
Nov	O
,	O
ber	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
(	O
being	O
a	O
Fidler	O
)	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
to	O
play	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
time	O
he	O
took	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
convey	O
away	O
the	O
Salt	O
.	O
That	O
missing	O
the	O
Salt	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
upon	O
enquiry	O
,	O
found	O
it	O
at	O
a	O
Goldsmiths	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
stole	O
it	O
was	O
discover	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
coming	O
to	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Salt	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
24	O
Ounces	O
of	O
unwrought	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
48	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Charpentier	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
His	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
being	O
read	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Brocken	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Macdonnel	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
value	O
15	O
s	O
Silver	O
Tea	O
Spoon	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
5	O
l.	O
in	O
Mony	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Alexander	O
Macdonnel	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
.	O
Barbara	B-pers
Macdonnel	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
to	O
rise	O
early	O
the	O
said	O
Morning	O
she	O
left	O
a	O
Lamp	O
burning	O
:	O
about	O
2	O
a	O
Clock	O
hearing	O
a	O
Noise	O
she	O
drew	O
the	O
Curtain	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
his	O
Body	O
half	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
taking	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
draw	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
surpris	O
'd	O
and	O
afraid	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
then	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
arose	O
in	O
her	O
Shift	O
ran	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
stop	O
Thief	O
.	O
She	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
planly	O
,	O
knew	O
him	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
positive	O
she	O
was	O
rob	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
same	O
Man	O
that	O
then	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
.	O
The	O
Circumstance	O
of	O
the	O
lamp	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
another	O
Witness	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
call	O
'd	O
his	O
Comrade	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
he	O
lay	O
with	O
him	O
from	O
8	O
that	O
Night	O
to	O
9	O
next	O
Morning	O
;	O
and	O
prov	O
'd	O
by	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
rob	O
'd	O
her	O
was	O
a	O
short	O
Man	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
tall	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
offer	O
'd	O
Money	O
to	O
a	O
Woman	O
to	O
swear	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
Several	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Drew	I-pers
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Purse	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d	O
5	O
Guineas	O
,	O
1	O
half	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
31	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Money	O
being	O
miss	O
'd	O
and	O
she	O
suspected	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
pursued	O
and	O
taken	O
at	O
Stanes	O
,	O
with	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
done	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
the	O
over	O
perswasion	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Drew	I-pers
;	O
but	O
no	O
proof	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Gill	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Peruque	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Thrasher	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2nd	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Calves	O
Skins	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
;	O
of	O
both	O
which	O
Indictments	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Slater	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
black	O
quilted	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rook	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
Her	O
Confession	O
being	O
read	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Alcock	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hornsey	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Peruque	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jeremy	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Jeremy	O
Spencer	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
to	O
be	O
shav	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
Boy	O
(	O
no	O
body	O
else	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
)	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
to	O
change	O
,	O
which	O
whilst	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Wig	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Hannah	B-pers
Nicholson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pauls	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
quilted	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
Fan	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
2	O
Handkerchiefs	O
and	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Salt	I-pers
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Farthing	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
Outwich	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Cloth	O
Breeches	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Fustian	O
Frock	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
Knight	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
making	O
it	O
appear	O
that	O
be	O
bought	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Beton	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Farthing	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
Outwich	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
,	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
120	O
Yards	O
of	O
Brocas	O
Canvas	O
,	O
value	O
42	O
s.	O
30	O
Yards	O
of	O
Hessian	O
Canvas	O
value	O
17	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
and	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Plat	I-pers
.	O
in	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
Knight	O
and	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Plat	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
;	O
and	O
Richard	O
Farthing	O
for	O
being	O
accessary	O
in	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
prisoners	O
got	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Servant	O
,	O
by	O
buying	O
some	O
slips	O
of	O
Buckram	O
of	O
him	O
(	O
which	O
Slips	O
were	O
the	O
said	O
Apprentices	O
Perquisites	O
)	O
and	O
afterwards	O
perswaded	O
the	O
said	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
to	O
rob	O
his	O
Master	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
which	O
Beton	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
to	O
Farthing	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
As	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
sold	O
off	O
,	O
they	O
brought	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Servant	O
share	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
but	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Canvas	O
being	O
at	O
last	O
stopt	O
on	O
suspicion	O
,	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
apprehended	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutors	O
Apprentice	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
himself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Frazier	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Peter	I-place
Cornhil	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
5	O
walking	O
Canes	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Arthur	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
Octo	O
.	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
begin	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
calling	O
many	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
,	O
careful	O
,	O
industrious	O
Man	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Bun	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mob	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Etbelburg	I-place
within	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Bag	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
l	O
19	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
John	O
Foster	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
about	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
going	O
to	O
his	O
Inn	O
.	O
(	O
the	O
Vine	O
without	O
Bishopsgate	O
)	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
who	O
stopt	O
him	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
give'em	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
refusing	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
forwards	O
,	O
they	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
stopping	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
them	O
a	O
Pint	O
,	O
they	O
'd	O
give	O
him	O
one	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
waited	O
on'em	O
to	O
the	O
Queens	B-place
head	I-place
Tavern	I-place
,	O
but	O
had	O
scarcely	O
drank	O
round	O
,	O
before	O
they	O
began	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
fond	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
Mob	O
flung	O
her	O
Arms	O
round	O
his	O
Neck	O
,	O
and	O
kiss	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
she	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
of	O
the	O
Bag	O
and	O
Money	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Bun	O
,	O
who	O
hid	O
it	O
betwixt	O
her	O
Legs	O
.	O
That	O
perceiving	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
search	O
Bun	O
who	O
conveyed	O
it	O
again	O
to	O
Mob	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
upon	O
this	O
alarm	O
'd	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
who	O
coming	O
to	O
his	O
assistance	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Bag	O
and	O
Money	O
upon	O
Mob	O
.	O
The	O
Bag	O
and	O
Money	O
were	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
,	O
Bun	O
said	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
whilst	O
he	O
talk	O
'd	O
with	O
Mob	O
in	O
private	O
.	O
And	O
Mob	O
to	O
vindicate	O
herself	O
,	O
said	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Money	O
for	O
what	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
doing	O
together	O
alone	O
,	O
Bun	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
M	O
b	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Harvy	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Coate	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Bshopsgate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Cassel	I-pers
,	O
a	O
silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Dancel	O
Cassel	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
As	O
be	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
von	O
Night	O
,	O
very	O
merry	O
vid	O
Liquor	O
,	O
dese	O
two	O
Vomen	O
(	O
de	O
prisoners	O
at	O
de	O
bar	O
)	O
fell	O
in	O
his	O
vay	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	O
Harvy	O
ask	O
a	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
vid	O
her	O
to	O
her	O
loshing	O
,	O
and	O
ven	O
da	O
came	O
dare	O
,	O
she	O
no	O
find	O
de	O
key	O
of	O
de	O
Door	O
Den	B-pers
Ann	I-pers
Parker	I-pers
told	O
a	O
him	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
loshing	O
in	O
Petty	B-place
France	I-place
;	O
and	O
to	O
he	O
ventvid	O
em	O
to	O
dat	O
loshing	O
,	O
and	O
vent	O
up	O
von	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
;	O
and	O
dare	O
Mary	O
Harvy	O
and	O
he	O
tumbel	O
upon	O
de	O
Bed	O
togeder	O
;	O
and	O
den	O
Harvy	O
pick	O
a	O
his	O
Vash	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
is	O
to	O
Parker	O
,	O
and	O
Parker	O
run	O
away	O
vid	O
de	O
Vash	O
,	O
and	O
Harvy	O
get	O
off	O
de	O
Bed	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
too	O
;	O
but	O
his	O
Breeshes	O
vare	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
cou	O
'd	O
no	O
run	O
after	O
dem	O
,	O
to	O
cash'em	O
.	O
Den	O
anoder	O
Voman	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
a	O
him	O
,	O
vat	O
vill	O
you	O
give	O
for	O
your	O
Vash	O
again	O
?	O
and	O
he	O
say	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
Money	O
left	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
will	O
give	O
a	O
you	O
von	O
pot	O
of	O
Beer	O
;	O
she	O
lay	O
dat	O
is	O
too	O
leetle	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
again	O
.	O
Den	O
he	O
make	O
a	O
very	O
mush	O
noise	O
,	O
and	O
den	O
de	O
Vashman	O
and	O
de	O
Connestable	O
come	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
den	O
dese	O
two	O
Vomen	O
at	O
de	O
Bar	O
come	O
in	O
after	O
dem	O
;	O
and	O
den	O
he	O
say	O
to	O
de	O
Connestable	O
.	O
Maitre	O
Connestable	O
dese	O
2	O
Vomen	O
have	O
steal	O
a	O
my	O
Vash	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
den	O
de	O
Connestable	O
,	O
and	O
de	O
Vashman	O
take	O
a	O
dem	O
all	O
to	O
de	O
Compter	O
.	O
Harvy	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
met	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
in	O
Bishopsgate	O
street	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
carry	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
this	O
House	O
in	O
Petty	O
France	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
up	O
with'em	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
staid	O
below	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
;	O
that	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
he	O
sent	O
her	O
down	O
a	O
Shilling	O
to	O
fetch	O
two	O
penny	O
worth	O
of	O
Rods	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
for	O
the	O
Rods	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
Constable	O
and	O
Watchmen	O
there	O
;	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
Watch	O
.	O
but	O
he	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
)	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
who	O
had	O
it	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
Harvy	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
,	O
known	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
squinting	O
Abigail	O
,	O
go	O
into	O
her	O
Neighbour	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
Petty	O
France	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
up	O
Stairs	O
together	O
;	O
that	O
Ann	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
up	O
with	O
`	O
em	O
,	O
but	O
staid	O
below	O
to	O
tend	O
the	O
Child	O
.	O
The	O
Watchmen	O
coming	O
in	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
Harvy	O
had	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
of	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
squinting	O
Abigail	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
Ann	O
Parker	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
good	O
honest	O
Woman	O
.	O
Parker	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	O
Harvey	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
2	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Tong	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Red	O
Cow	O
in	O
Turnbul	O
street	O
to	O
ask	O
for	O
a	O
Lodging	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
there	O
a	O
drinking	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
could	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
a	O
Lodging	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
-	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
home	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
a	O
Room	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
lay	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
next	O
Morning	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Rings	O
and	O
Buckles	O
;	O
and	O
asking	O
the	O
prisoner	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of'em	O
,	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
Son	O
of	O
a	O
Bitch	O
,	O
and	O
turn	O
'd	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
.	O
He	O
charged	O
a	O
Constable	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
found	O
the	O
Buckles	O
in	O
the	O
Lining	O
of	O
his	O
Breeches	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
told	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
he	O
knew	O
but	O
of	O
one	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
should	O
give	O
him	O
that	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
not	O
going	O
to	O
Bed	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
early	O
to	O
his	O
Wife	O
's	O
Room	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
in	O
Bed	O
with	O
his	O
Wife	O
;	O
and	O
asking	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
satisfied	O
your	O
Wife	O
for	O
what	O
I	O
have	O
done	O
;	O
that	O
afterwards	O
his	O
Wife	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
the	O
Buckles	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
gave	O
`	O
em	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Graystock	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Gregory	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
Handkerchief	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
Atchcomb	I-pers
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
apprehended	O
in	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Brindly	I-pers
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
the	O
Boat	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Matson	I-pers
,	O
12	O
pint	O
bottles	O
of	O
white	O
Wine	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
belonging	O
to	O
several	O
Persons	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Killet	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
his	O
Master	O
was	O
just	O
then	O
arrested	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
while	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
as	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
proved	O
,	O
)	O
carried	O
the	O
Boat	O
a	O
cross	O
the	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Lease	I-pers
of	O
Fulham	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Sir	O
Charles	B-pers
Wager	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
17	O
Muscovy	O
Ducks	O
5	O
s.	O
4	O
Geess	O
3	O
s.	O
2	O
Turkies	O
3	O
s.	O
31	O
Hens	O
and	O
4	O
Cocks	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
being	O
mist	O
,	O
were	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
near	O
Chelsea	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
Drunk	O
and	O
a	O
Man	O
hired	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
a	O
draw	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
8	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
John	O
Smith	O
.	O
His	O
Confession	O
before	O
Justice	O
Butler	O
was	O
read	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Christian	B-pers
Salner	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Saw	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Cutler	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Indictment	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Seaton	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Peirce	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Peruke	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Laurence	B-pers
Maning	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Butler	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Sir	O
Edward	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
silk	O
Purse	O
,	O
one	O
Guinea	O
,	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
6	O
pound	O
of	O
Chocolate	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
Sir	O
Edward	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Huntington	O
Coach	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
rob	O
'd	O
by	O
two	O
Highway	O
Men	O
in	O
disguise	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
(	O
Hawkins	O
)	O
was	O
discovered	O
by	O
offering	O
2	O
Shirts	O
to	O
Sale	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
hired	O
a	O
Horse	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Norris	O
at	O
Finsbury	O
(	O
November	O
1	O
)	O
to	O
go	O
on	O
the	O
High	O
way	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
rob	O
the	O
Chichester	O
stage	O
Coach	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
did	O
next	O
Morning	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
.	O
This	O
Evidence	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Inn	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
Passengers	O
went	O
in	O
the	O
Huntington	O
Coach	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
both	O
waited	O
for	O
it	O
at	O
Mount	B-place
Mill	I-place
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stopt	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Evidence	O
rob	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
that	O
coming	O
to	O
Moorfields	O
the	O
Evidence	O
took	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Horses	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
afterwards	O
shar	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
Hawkins	O
following	O
him	O
,	O
)	O
brought	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Fustian	O
,	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
blew	O
Cloth	O
,	O
3	O
Books	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
suspecting	O
they	O
were	O
stole	O
,	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
them	O
be	O
left	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Hawkins	O
made	O
some	O
Chocolate	O
there	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
brought	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
That	O
Hawkins	O
owing	O
this	O
Evidence	O
Money	O
brought	O
him	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Muslin	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
brought	O
from	O
Holland	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
bought	O
at	O
4	O
s.	O
per	O
Yard	O
for	O
28	O
s	O
that	O
he	O
set	O
14	O
s.	O
off	O
Hawkins	O
's	O
Score	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
the	O
other	O
14	O
s	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Pawn	O
broker	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
lent	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Wife	O
15	O
s.	O
upon	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Fustian	O
,	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
blew	O
Cloth	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Norris	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
hir	O
'd	O
the	O
Horse	O
of	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Croydon	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
4	O
a	O
Clock	O
next	O
Morning	O
returned	O
with	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Horse	O
,	O
both	O
which	O
he	O
left	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
coming	O
again	O
soon	O
after	O
fetch	O
'd	O
away	O
the	O
strange	O
Horse	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
Hawkin	O
's	O
information	O
,	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
House	O
he	O
found	O
him	O
there	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Wife	O
then	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
Husband	O
.	O
Ay	O
you	O
Rouge	O
!	O
this	O
is	O
your	O
Friend	O
Hawkins	O
's	O
doings	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Hawkins	O
in	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
Debt	O
due	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
A	O
great	O
number	O
of	O
Gentlemen	O
and	O
Shopkeepers	O
appeared	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
an	O
Extraordinary	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
not	O
Guilty	O
;	O
but	O
2	O
other	O
Robberies	O
being	O
Charged	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
ordered	O
to	O
remain	O
in	O
Custody	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Like	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
her	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
in	O
the	O
right	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
1	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
depth	O
of	O
8	O
Inches	O
,	O
by	O
discharging	O
a	O
Pistol	O
laden	O
with	O
Powder	O
and	O
Bullets	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
23d	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Month	O
and	O
then	O
dyed	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
.	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Woodhouse	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Celler	O
(	O
at	O
the	O
Vine	O
Tavern	O
Long	O
Acre	O
,	O
)	O
heard	O
a	O
Pistol	O
go	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
a	O
minute	O
heard	O
another	O
,	O
then	O
coming	O
up	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
set	O
all	O
the	O
old	O
Women	O
a	O
scolding	O
with	O
letting	O
off	O
his	O
Pistols	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Bull	O
head	O
Inn	O
,	O
(	O
opposite	O
to	O
the	O
Vine	O
,	O
)	O
she	O
heard	O
a	O
Pistol	O
go	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
minute	O
after	O
heard	O
another	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Deceased	O
(	O
whom	O
she	O
then	O
held	O
by	O
the	O
Arm	O
,	O
)	O
turning	O
to	O
her	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
shot	O
in	O
the	O
Side	O
.	O
She	O
this	O
Deponent	O
then	O
carry	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceased	O
into	O
a	O
Barbers	O
Shop	O
just	O
by	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
who	O
drest	O
the	O
Wound	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Deceased	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
had	O
shot	O
,	O
whom	O
they	O
soon	O
found	O
and	O
brought	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
expressed	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Sorrow	O
,	O
bidding	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
her	O
want	O
for	O
nothing	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
'd	O
satisfy	O
him	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
Woman	O
,	O
but	O
believed	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
did	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
designedly	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
died	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Nelson	I-pers
,	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
deposed	O
he	O
found	O
1	O
Bullet	O
on	O
her	O
Shoulder	O
blade	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
in	O
her	O
Chest	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
believed	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
her	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
in	O
a	O
Chaise	O
to	O
the	O
Vine	O
Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
remembering	O
his	O
Pistols	O
were	O
Charged	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
discharge	O
them	O
in	O
his	O
Chaise	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
fir	O
'd	O
upwards	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
the	O
Chaise	O
jogging	O
might	O
cause	O
the	O
Bullet	O
to	O
fly	O
lower	O
than	O
he	O
intended	O
.	O
Several	O
Witnesses	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
good	O
natur	O
'd	O
,	O
civil	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
not	O
given	O
to	O
be	O
mischiecvous	O
.	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Mary	B-pers
Ferguson	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High	O
way	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Pocket	O
,	O
value	O
2d	O
a	O
prayer	O
Book	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	O
Ferguson	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
Mary	O
Ferguson	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
about	O
6	O
at	O
Night	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
King-street	B-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
jostled	O
her	O
against	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
snatched	O
her	O
Pocket	O
from	O
her	O
side	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
that	O
keeping	O
her	O
Eye	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
and	O
crv	O
'd	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
not	O
be	O
suspected	O
walk	O
'd	O
slowly	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
stood	O
still	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
then	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Pocket	O
which	O
he	O
dropt	O
,	O
lying	O
by	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
coming	O
to	O
her	O
Assistance	O
they	O
secured	O
him	O
.	O
Several	O
other	O
Evidences	O
were	O
positive	O
both	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Christian	B-pers
Henry	I-pers
Kleinsmeide	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
silk	O
Cap	O
,	O
a	O
Penknife	O
,	O
2	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Ring	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Marquess	O
Peter	B-pers
Carraccioli	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Marquess	O
,	O
going	O
to	O
Paris	O
,	O
ordered	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
to	O
pack	O
up	O
his	O
Goods	O
in	O
London	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
they	O
landed	O
in	O
France	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
were	O
missing	O
;	O
and	O
asking	O
the	O
prisoner	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
he	O
answered	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
forgot	O
to	O
pack'em	O
up	O
,	O
had	O
left'em	O
at	O
London	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Marquess	O
was	O
pretty	O
well	O
satisfied	O
with	O
that	O
Answer	O
;	O
but	O
soon	O
after	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
Paris	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
play	O
'd	O
some	O
Tricks	O
with	O
the	O
Marquess	O
's	O
Mistress	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
discharg	O
'd	O
from	O
his	O
Service	O
.	O
The	O
Marquess	O
returning	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
finding	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
caus	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
apprehended	O
for	O
stealing	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
his	O
Master	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
witness	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
often	O
wore	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Service	O
.	O
As	O
for	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Marquess	O
could	O
bring	O
no	O
proof	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
taken'em	O
.	O
The	O
whole	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
malicions	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Haws	I-pers
of	O
Finchly	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Richard	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
this	O
Indictment	O
the	O
prisoner	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
plead	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
liv	O
'd	O
like	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
resolv	O
'd	O
to	O
die	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
shabby	O
Coat	O
as	O
he	O
then	O
appear	O
'd	O
in	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
a	O
good	O
Suit	O
of	O
Cloaths	O
at	O
his	O
Lodging	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
pray	O
'd	O
might	O
be	O
return	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
till	O
this	O
was	O
granted	O
,	O
he	O
positively	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
plead	O
.	O
His	O
Thumbs	O
were	O
then	O
ty	O
'd	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Cord	O
pull	O
'd	O
till	O
it	O
broke	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
still	O
refusing	O
to	O
plead	O
,	O
was	O
at	O
last	O
sentenc	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
prest	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
lain	O
in	O
the	O
Press	O
about	O
7	O
Minutes	O
,	O
with	O
250	O
pound	O
Weight	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
carried	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
pleaded	O
Not	O
Guilt	O
.	O
Richard	O
Hall	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Novem	O
.	O
24	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
on	O
Finchly	B-place
Common	I-place
,	O
and	O
holding	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
his	O
Breast	O
,	O
bid	O
him	O
dismount	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
thereupon	O
gave	O
the	O
prisoner	O
4	O
s.	O
who	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
alight	O
himself	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
observing	O
,	O
while	O
his	O
Back	O
was	O
towards	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
suddenly	O
seiz	O
'd	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
wrench	O
'd	O
the	O
Pistol	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
clapping	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
Breast	O
,	O
bid	O
him	O
surrender	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
A	O
Drayman	O
coming	O
by	O
,	O
assisted	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
Highgate	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
secured	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
prisoner	O
there	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
broke	O
out	O
of	O
New	O
Prison	O
but	O
the	O
Sunday	O
before	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
insisted	O
to	O
have	O
his	O
Cloaths	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Weston	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
,	O
Ravishing	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
her	O
Will	O
,	O
Carnally	O
knowing	O
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Lockwood	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
.	O
Aged	O
13	O
Years	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
Ann	O
Lockwood	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
Apprentice	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Mistress	O
being	O
gone	O
a	O
Nurse-keeping	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
one	O
Night	O
gave	O
her	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Ale	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
her	O
go	O
to	O
his	O
Bed	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
to	O
Bed	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
to	O
her	O
private	O
Parts	O
,	O
and	O
thrust	O
his	O
Finger	O
into	O
her	O
Body	O
,	O
which	O
hurt	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
her	O
scream	O
out	O
:	O
that	O
he	O
then	O
stopt	O
her	O
Mouth	O
,	O
and	O
threatned	O
to	O
kill	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
made	O
a	O
noise	O
;	O
telling	O
her	O
he	O
must	O
serve	O
her	O
so	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
serv	O
'd	O
her	O
Mistress	O
so	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
then	O
put	O
something	O
else	O
into	O
her	O
Body	O
,	O
she	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
something	O
where	O
the	O
little	O
Boys	O
Cocks	O
are	O
;	O
that	O
it	O
hurt	O
her	O
sadly	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
her	O
cry	O
out	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Midwife	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
privy	O
Parts	O
were	O
very	O
much	O
hurt	O
,	O
extended	O
,	O
torn	O
and	O
ulcerated	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
believ	O
'd	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
poxt	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Damage	O
was	O
done	O
her	O
by	O
having	O
Carnal	O
Copulation	O
with	O
a	O
Man	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Pickersgill	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
own	O
that	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
Finger	O
into	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
Body	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bid	O
the	O
Child	O
go	O
to	O
his	O
Bed	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
frighten	O
'd	O
when	O
she	O
lay	O
alone	O
;	O
that	O
coming	O
home	O
in	O
drink	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
asleep	O
;	O
that	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
thorowly	O
awake	O
,	O
he	O
laid	O
his	O
Hand	O
upon	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
thinking	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
his	O
Wife	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
found	O
his	O
mistake	O
,	O
withdrew	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
no	O
wonder	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
poxt	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
she	O
was	O
born	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
Mother	O
was	O
poxt	O
before	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
was	O
intirely	O
malicious	O
.	O
The	O
Mother	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Child	O
came	O
home	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
two	O
Weeks	O
after	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
so	O
sore	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
sit	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
said	O
,	O
her	O
Master	O
threatned	O
to	O
put	O
her	O
in	O
Bridewell	O
if	O
she	O
told	O
any	O
body	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
always	O
lock	O
'd	O
her	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
Woman	O
that	O
wash	O
'd	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
Shift	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Shift	O
any	O
ways	O
bloody	O
,	O
or	O
stain	O
'd	O
:	O
and	O
the	O
Child	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
Question	O
,	O
confest	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
her	O
Shift	O
's	O
being	O
bloody	O
when	O
she	O
pulled	O
it	O
off	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
she	O
herself	O
had	O
bled	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
William	I-pers
Armstrong	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Humphrey	B-pers
Finger	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Richard	B-pers
Philpot	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Broad	O
piece	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
:	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Frost	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Will	O
.	O
Cross	O
,	O
20	O
Guineas	O
,	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
;	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Gerrard	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Cawderoy	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Looking	O
Glass	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
Table	O
Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Callico	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Robert	O
Smith	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Byhew	I-pers
(	O
who	O
was	O
the	O
only	O
Evidence	O
)	O
having	O
escap	O
'd	O
from	O
New	O
Prison	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
other	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Leekie	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ash	I-pers
by	O
giving	O
her	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Tipstaff	O
near	O
the	O
Left	O
Breast	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
7th	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
languish	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
November	O
following	O
and	O
then	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Husband	O
,	O
Simeon	B-pers
Ash	I-pers
,	O
being	O
apprehensive	O
of	O
an	O
Arrest	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
some	O
Persons	O
coming	O
up	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
and	O
Alice	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
stood	O
with	O
their	O
Backs	O
against	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
which	O
was	O
shut	O
:	O
That	O
the	O
prisoner	O
broke	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
thrown	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
as	O
if	O
she	O
were	O
dead	O
;	O
but	O
recovering	O
,	O
they	O
set	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
wounded	O
her	O
thro	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Tipstaff	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
Left	O
Breast	O
:	O
that	O
she	O
continued	O
spitting	O
of	O
Blood	O
till	O
she	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
Susan	B-pers
Stead	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Midwife	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
hard	O
Labour	O
,	O
and	O
complain	O
'd	O
of	O
a	O
pain	O
at	O
her	O
Heart	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
open	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Surgeons	O
said	O
,	O
whatever	O
ail	O
she	O
had	O
had	O
,	O
her	O
Labour	O
had	O
thrown	O
it	O
off	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
appearance	O
of	O
any	O
hurt	O
left	O
.	O
The	O
Coroner	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
only	O
a	O
little	O
dent	O
under	O
her	O
Left	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Surgeons	O
who	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
declared	O
on	O
Oath	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
her	O
Death	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
had	O
examin	O
'd	O
particularly	O
those	O
Parts	O
where	O
she	O
most	O
complain	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
up	O
to	O
arrest	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Husband	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
in	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Husband	O
from	O
behind	O
the	O
Bed	O
;	O
which	O
the	O
Deceased	O
seeing	O
,	O
fell	O
into	O
a	O
Fit	O
:	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
soon	O
recovered	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Husband	O
afterwards	O
arrested	O
him	O
in	O
an	O
Action	O
of	O
20	O
l.	O
for	O
an	O
Assault	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
give'em	O
40	O
l.	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
they	O
'd	O
charge	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
heard	O
the	O
Deceased	O
say	O
she	O
had	O
received	O
a	O
small	O
Wound	O
,	O
but	O
knew	O
not	O
who	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Stephen	I-place
Walbrook	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Calamanco	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
Fan	O
.	O
2	O
Muslin	O
Aprons	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Eads	I-pers
.	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
:	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
confest	O
she	O
stole	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Marriot	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Alhallows	B-place
Barkin	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
20	O
Yards	O
of	O
Lace	O
,	O
2	O
Yards	O
of	O
Tape	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Benjam	B-pers
.	I-pers
Laughton	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Whipt	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
24	O
s.	O
a	O
Chain	O
,	O
a	O
Seal	O
a	O
Coral	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Girdles	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Owen	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
reaching	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Subornation	O
of	O
Perjury	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
Francis	B-pers
Valentine	I-pers
,	O
having	O
brought	O
an	O
Action	O
in	O
the	O
Marshal	O
's	O
Court	O
against	O
Henry	B-pers
Dissington	I-pers
,	O
on	O
a	O
promissory	O
Note	O
for	O
20	O
s.	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
Henry	O
Dissington	O
,	O
employ	O
'd	O
the	O
prisoner	O
as	O
his	O
Solicitor	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
him	O
the	O
Money	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
said	O
promissory	O
Note	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
putting	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Pocket	O
.	O
procur	O
'd	O
Tho	B-pers
Dry	I-pers
,	O
for	O
5	O
s.	O
to	O
swear	O
at	O
the	O
Marshal	O
's	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
by	O
,	O
when	O
Diffington	O
paid	O
the	O
30	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
promissory	O
Note	O
to	O
Valentine	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Fin	O
'd	O
20	O
Marks	O
.	O
and	O
Security	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
for	O
3	O
Years	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Woolham	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Carrick	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Addis	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Subornation	O
of	O
Perjury	O
,	O
in	O
procuring	O
Mary	B-pers
Deanly	I-pers
,	O
to	O
swear	O
a	O
Robbery	O
against	O
William	B-pers
Charlesworth	I-pers
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Pot	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
John	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
positive	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
19	O
Sheep	O
Skins	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
14	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dunse	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Martha	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Terence	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
No	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Drugget	O
Coats	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Cropper	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Gold	O
Chain	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elias	B-pers
Dagly	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Angel	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
16	O
Pound	O
of	O
Suet	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
8	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mark	B-pers
Bows	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
His	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Emanuel	B-pers
Giles	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Doubleton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Peruque	O
,	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Buckles	O
,	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
9	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
7th	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
too	O
weak	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hargrove	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Murdock	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Murdock	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Duke	O
street	O
,	O
Westminster	O
,	O
he	O
observ	O
'd	O
the	O
prisoner	O
following	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
turning	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Crown	B-place
Court	I-place
,	O
he	O
stood	O
to	O
make	O
Water	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
put	O
one	O
Hand	O
round	O
his	O
Neck	O
,	O
kiss	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Pint	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
turning	O
about	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
her	O
Hand	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
gone	O
;	O
and	O
thereupon	O
called	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
who	O
secured	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
,	O
the	O
Prosector	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
pull	O
'd	O
her	O
into	O
an	O
empty	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
her	O
Money	O
to	O
be	O
rude	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
which	O
she	O
refusing	O
,	O
he	O
beat	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
tore	O
her	O
Headcloaths	O
;	O
she	O
cry	O
'd	O
Murder	O
,	O
the	O
Watch	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
then	O
told'em	O
she	O
had	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
constable	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
she	O
knew	O
where	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
was	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Walton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
black	O
Mare	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Tinke	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
Richard	O
Tinke	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
missing	O
the	O
Mare	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Stable	O
,	O
in	O
Rochester	B-place
,	O
he	O
got	O
instant	O
notice	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
riding	O
upon	O
her	O
(	O
the	O
Mare	O
being	O
very	O
well	O
known	O
.	O
)	O
He	O
pursued	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Turnpike	O
at	O
Chalk	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
heard	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
(	O
pretending	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Servant	O
)	O
was	O
rid	O
forward	O
without	O
molestation	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
still	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
gaining	O
fresh	O
Intelligence	O
on	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
found	O
the	O
Mare	O
in	O
a	O
Stable	O
at	O
the	O
Bull	O
Inn	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
bed	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Inn	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
caused	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
before	O
Justice	O
Tilliard	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
confest	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Mare	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Stable	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
meerly	O
out	O
of	O
Necessity	O
.	O
In	O
his	O
Defence	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
in	O
Debt	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
leave	O
London	O
privately	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
to	O
Rochester	O
,	O
accidentally	O
met	O
with	O
an	O
old	O
Acquaintance	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
a	O
Farrier	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
Entertainment	O
for	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Days	O
.	O
One	O
Night	O
it	O
happen	O
'd	O
(	O
as	O
each	O
was	O
relating	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
his	O
Misfortunes	O
)	O
that	O
the	O
Farrier	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
most	O
wicked	O
Wife	O
at	O
London	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
about	O
to	O
sell	O
all	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
conclusion	O
of	O
the	O
Story	O
,	O
told	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
'd	O
go	O
to	O
his	O
(	O
the	O
Farrier	O
's	O
Father	O
)	O
in	O
London	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
prevent	O
his	O
Goods	O
being	O
sold	O
,	O
he	O
'd	O
hire	O
him	O
a	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
bear	O
his	O
Charges	O
.	O
This	O
Request	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
(	O
in	O
gratitude	O
)	O
knew	O
not	O
how	O
to	O
refuse	O
.	O
The	O
Farrier	O
then	O
brought	O
him	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Mare	O
on	O
which	O
he	O
rid	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
up	O
in	O
Sboreditch	O
,	O
because	O
it	O
was	O
most	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
of	O
his	O
Creditors	O
.	O
-	O
But	O
the	O
Farrier	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harper	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	O
Robinson	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoners	O
(	O
whom	O
she	O
knew	O
before	O
)	O
came	O
into	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Yorkshire	B-place
Gray	I-place
in	I-place
Anniseed	I-place
Clear	I-place
,	O
to	O
drink	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
she	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Tankard	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
taxing	O
Sarah	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
,	O
she	O
confest	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
prosecute	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
'd	O
return	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Sarah	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
sell	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
the	O
Tankard	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
her	O
Husband	O
found	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Lay-stall	O
.	O
The	O
pieces	O
of	O
the	O
Tankard	O
were	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
's	O
Confession	O
read	O
.	O
She	O
took	O
the	O
Fact	O
wholly	O
upon	O
herself	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Tho	B-pers
Harper	I-pers
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
its	O
being	O
taken	O
;	O
but	O
added	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Drunk	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
.	O
Harper	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
asaulting	O
Samuel	B-pers
Towers	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
6th	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
.	O
Samuel	O
Towers	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
January	O
the	O
22d	O
,	O
1719.	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
Hackny	O
Coach	O
,	O
in	O
Marlboro	B-place
street	I-place
,	O
three	O
Men	O
disguis	O
'd	O
,	O
on	O
Horseback	O
,	O
stop	O
'd	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
