TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Termmer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
,	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
12th	O
,	O
13th	O
,	O
14th	O
and	O
15th	O
,	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
July	O
1721	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Seventh	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
FRYER	I-pers
,	O
Bart	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	B-pers
Bury	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Powys	O
,	O
Mr.Justice	O
Tracey	O
,	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlefex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
Names	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
James	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hammond	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Yerbury	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Cheesebrook	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Greggs	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Rolphe	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Yeomans	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Knapp	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Stockall	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
,	O
Middlefex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ingram	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Gass	I-pers
William	B-pers
Tame	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fenn	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Witt	I-pers
,	O
Guy	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Whiten	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Duck	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Timbrell	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Green	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Philip	B-pers
Jersey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.Michael	B-place
in	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brook	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
July	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
stood	O
talking	O
against	O
the	O
Royal-Exchange	B-place
the	O
Sunday	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
fee	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
saw	O
it	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Mitten	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
secured	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
off	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Read	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
in	O
defrauding	O
Richard	B-pers
Rickey	I-pers
of	O
40	O
s.	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
procuring	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
Free	O
of	O
the	O
Barber	O
Surgeons	O
Company	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Rickey	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisner	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
Still-Yard	O
and	O
askt	O
her	O
what	O
Business	O
she	O
had	O
to	O
shave	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
had	O
a	O
Right	O
having	O
been	O
a	O
Soldier	O
many	O
Years	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
Shave	O
unless	O
,	O
her	O
Husband	O
was	O
Free	O
of	O
the	O
Barber	O
's	O
Company	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Chamberlain	O
's	O
Officer	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
an	O
Action	O
against	O
her	O
Husband	O
for	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
:	O
that	O
he	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
their	O
Friend	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
procure	O
her	O
Husband	O
his	O
Freedom	O
of	O
that	O
Company	O
only	O
paying	O
the	O
Charges	O
of	O
taking	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
which	O
would	O
be	O
very	O
small	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
saw	O
her	O
Husband	O
give	O
him	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
her	O
self	O
raised	O
30	O
s.	O
more	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
on	O
that	O
Account	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Fined	O
20	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
suffer	O
Three	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
Wastcoat	O
and	O
Breeches	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
2	O
Linnen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Peckman	I-pers
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Alice	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
at	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Camblet	O
Bed-Curtains	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
Counerpain	O
,	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
a	O
Callicoe	O
Sheet	O
,	O
11	O
Napkins	O
,	O
3	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Calloway	I-pers
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
in	O
Hounsditch	O
,	O
others	O
in	O
Southwark	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
which	O
she	O
kept	O
as	O
well	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
Service	O
as	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
being	O
in	O
want	O
;	O
but	O
with	O
a	O
Design	O
to	O
restore	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
;	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Farren	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
felt	O
somebody	O
pull	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
about	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
thrusting	O
his	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
)	O
Handkerchief	O
into	O
his	O
Bosom	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Benfield	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Sherwood	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Shirt	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Gibbons	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
his	O
Passage	O
from	O
Feversham	O
to	O
London	O
in	O
his	O
Vessel	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
Voyage	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
aboard	O
again	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
lye	O
there	O
that	O
Night	O
;	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
leave	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
his	O
,	O
Victuals	O
and	O
Drink	O
also	O
;	O
that	O
his	O
Man	O
William	O
Gibbons	O
askt	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Bed	O
when	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
would	O
set	O
up	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
Gibbons	O
arose	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
about	O
3	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
off	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Annable	I-pers
(	O
a	O
Boy	O
)	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cotton	O
Handkerchief	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Barnard	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
stood	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
play	O
at	O
Cudgels	O
in	O
Smithfield	B-place
,	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
taken	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
Charged	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
but	O
of	O
his	O
Breeches	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Bussey	I-pers
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Heymarn	B-pers
Curtis	I-pers
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
July	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
in	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Perriwing	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Handkerchief	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Ford	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
above	O
Stairs	O
with	O
her	O
Landlady	O
's	O
Daughter	O
(	O
who	O
then	O
lay-in	O
)	O
her	O
Husband	O
brought	O
her	O
up	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
their	O
Chamber	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
:	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
the	O
Boxes	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
gone	O
:	O
whereupon	O
the	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
found	O
near	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
were	O
her	O
Husband	O
's	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
also	O
swore	O
to	O
the	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
hearing	O
Mrs.	O
Ford	O
cry	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
washing	O
her	O
Master	O
's	O
Door	O
in	O
Plumb-Tree-Court	O
,	O
turn	O
'd	O
about	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
with	O
the	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
whereupon	O
she	O
threw	O
her	O
Pattens	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Swan-Inn	O
Tap-House	O
at	O
Holbourn-Bridge	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
threw	O
them	O
under	O
the	O
Table	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gardener	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
hearing	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
down	O
the	O
Swan-Inn	O
and	O
a	O
Baker	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
followed	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
knowing	O
which	O
might	O
be	O
the	O
Thief	O
he	O
seized	O
the	O
Baker	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
drag	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Tap	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
creeping	O
under	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
was	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
Hat	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
brought	O
from	O
Bristol	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Name	O
was	O
Writ	O
in	O
a	O
Paper	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
inside	O
the	O
Lining	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
indeed	O
a	O
very	O
small	O
piece	O
of	O
Paper	O
rolled	O
up	O
very	O
close	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Hat	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
refused	O
to	O
deliver	O
the	O
Hat	O
to	O
be	O
kept	O
by	O
the	O
Constable	O
till	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
my	O
Lord	O
's	O
order	O
when	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
(	O
saying	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
whether	O
he	O
should	O
prosecute	O
him	O
or	O
no	O
)	O
that	O
Circumstance	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
:	O
he	O
also	O
called	O
some	O
to	O
invalidate	O
Jackson	O
's	O
Evidence	O
,	O
urging	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
it	O
for	O
the	O
sake	O
of	O
the	O
30	O
l.	O
reward	O
for	O
convicting	O
him	O
:	O
but	O
the	O
Court	O
assur	O
'd	O
him	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
reward	O
at	O
all	O
provided	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
very	O
positive	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
old	O
offender	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dunn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
in	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Callicoe	O
Handkerchief	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
July	O
:	O
Which	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Katharine	I-place
Creedchurch	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Pot	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bagget	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
July	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Dexter	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
a	O
Cobler	O
's	O
Stall	O
adjoyning	O
to	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Trowel	I-pers
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
Steal	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Richmond	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
over	O
Night	O
he	O
shut	O
up	O
his	O
Stall	O
,	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Mincing-Lane	B-place
in	I-place
Fenchurch-Street	I-place
;	O
and	O
about	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
he	O
was	O
called	O
by	O
the	O
Watch	O
to	O
shut	O
it	O
up	O
again	O
.	O
William	B-pers
James	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
beating	O
his	O
Rounds	O
at	O
one	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bolted	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Cobler	O
's	O
Stall	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
Evidence	O
calling	O
out	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Stall	O
being	O
open	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
Sleep	O
,	O
intending	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
Francis	B-pers
Nicholas	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Week	O
before	O
Easter	O
;	O
and	O
is	O
a	O
dangerous	O
Person	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Fined	O
Ten	O
Marks	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Prior	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Tremain	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
in	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
in	O
Courterfeiting	O
the	O
Current	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Giles	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
in	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
defraud	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
of	O
5	O
s.	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
changing	O
a	O
Guinea	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gould	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Woolnoth	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
in	O
exposing	O
and	O
uttering	O
a	O
Counterfeit	O
Moidore	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
Counterfeit	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Bostock	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Bartholomew	I-place
the	I-place
Less	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
d.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
:	O
And	O
the	O
Court	O
ordered	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Recognizance	O
to	O
be	O
Estreated	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Gosling	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Green	O
Livery	O
.	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
Breeches	O
and	O
Hat	O
,	O
9	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Porringer	O
,	O
2	O
Silver	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Snuffers	O
and	O
Snuffer	O
Case	O
,	O
2	O
Silver	O
Salts	O
,	O
3	O
Silver	O
Castors	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Mustard	O
Spoon	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
46	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mark	B-pers
Winn	I-pers
,	O
Senior	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tooth-pick-case	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Stockings	O
,	O
2	O
Carolus	O
's	O
12	O
Guineas	O
and	O
42	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Mark	B-pers
Winn	I-pers
,	O
Junior	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Mark	O
Winn	O
,	O
Senior	O
;	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Winn	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
as	O
Butler	O
,	O
from	O
Christmas	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
liking	O
of	O
him	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Month	O
's	O
Warning	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
of	O
a	O
sudden	O
3	O
Weeks	O
before	O
his	O
Warning	O
was	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
were	O
missing	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cregnall	I-pers
,	O
Ostler	O
of	O
the	O
Crown-Inn	O
at	O
Hardest	O
in	O
Suffolk	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
their	O
House	O
on	O
Whitson-Monday	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
Plate	O
of	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
his	O
Master	O
looking	O
over	O
it	O
and	O
finding	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Sleeves	O
of	O
a	O
Livery	O
Coat	O
,	O
suspecting	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
questioning	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Tenant	O
for	O
Rent	O
,	O
who	O
having	O
no	O
Money	O
gave	O
him	O
that	O
old	O
Plate	O
.	O
That	O
his	O
Master	O
stopt	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
ask	O
Advice	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
best	O
do	O
in	O
the	O
Case	O
:	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
rode	O
away	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
got	O
Horses	O
,	O
followed	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
asleep	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
beyond	O
Framingham	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Horse	O
Grasing	O
by	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
Bridle	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Fore	O
Legs	O
tied	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
Ring	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
was	O
cut	O
off	O
his	O
Finger	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
swell	O
'd	O
.	O
His	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
Grays	O
in	O
Essex	O
,	O
there	O
bought	O
a	O
Mare	O
,	O
rode	O
to	O
Hardust	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
discovered	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
foregoing	O
Evidence	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
bundled	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Wash-House	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
that	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Washerwomen	O
intended	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
;	O
to	O
prevent	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
himself	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Cope	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
Bassishaw	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Snuff	O
Box	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Hilliard	I-pers
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
Guild	B-place
Hall	I-place
to	O
hear	O
a	O
Cause	O
in	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
.	O
Pleas	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
whom	O
he	O
very	O
well	O
remember	O
'd	O
)	O
stood	O
next	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
Box	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
remarkable	O
one	O
)	O
just	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
two	O
Minutes	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
he	O
mist	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
him	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
being	O
accidentally	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
afterwards	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
speaking	O
of	O
his	O
Loss	O
,	O
describing	O
his	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
suspected	O
,	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
could	O
help	O
him	O
to	O
it	O
again	O
;	O
for	O
that	O
his	O
Description	O
answered	O
what	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
brought	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Champman	O
to	O
pawn	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Chapman	O
,	O
redeemed	O
the	O
Box	O
for	O
5	O
s.	O
1	O
1\2	O
which	O
he	O
swore	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
who	O
he	O
swore	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
Person	O
that	O
stood	O
next	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
Guild	O
Hall	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Chapman	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
sell	O
her	O
two	O
old	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
seem	O
'd	O
very	O
weary	O
,	O
sat	O
down	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
Distress	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
ask	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
knew	O
any	O
body	O
that	O
would	O
buy	O
a	O
Snuff	O
Box	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
one	O
in	O
pawn	O
,	O
but	O
wanting	O
Money	O
would	O
sell	O
it	O
outright	O
;	O
that	O
a	O
Friend	O
of	O
hers	O
came	O
it	O
,	O
who	O
she	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
again	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
Snuff-Box	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
a	O
Friend	O
had	O
redeemed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
askt	O
her	O
to	O
buy	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
brought	O
it	O
a	O
little	O
sooner	O
a	O
Friend	O
of	O
hers	O
was	O
there	O
who	O
she	O
believed	O
would	O
have	O
bought	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
pawn	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
Friend	O
have	O
it	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
5	O
half	O
Crowns	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
redeemed	O
,	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
Pawn	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
it	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
yes	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
would	O
bring	O
the	O
Money	O
by	O
8	O
a	O
Clock	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
a	O
little	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
askt	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
coming	O
immediately	O
they	O
secured	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
a	O
Person	O
against	O
St.	O
Dunstan	O
's	O
Court	O
who	O
owed	O
him	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
not	O
having	O
Money	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
nor	O
call	O
'd	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Zechariah	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
.	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
at	I-place
Billinsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
23	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bedman	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
sent	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
Maid	O
to	O
Church	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
self	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
lock	O
up	O
the	O
Doors	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
return	O
'd	O
,	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Back	O
Door	O
,	O
took	O
his	O
own	O
things	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
but	O
the	O
Monday	O
before	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
at	O
Epsom	O
,	O
where	O
by	O
means	O
of	O
a	O
Counterfeit	O
Recommendation	O
he	O
was	O
got	O
into	O
Service	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
owned	O
the	O
Fact	O
when	O
taken	O
saying	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
first	O
to	O
Eltham	O
and	O
spent	O
5	O
s.	O
brought	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
back	O
to	O
his	O
Mother	O
to	O
fetch	O
his	O
Clothes	O
out	O
of	O
pawn	O
.	O
His	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
at	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
50	O
Straw	O
Hats	O
value	O
33	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Elton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Burdett	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
Silk	O
String	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Seal	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Jeffery	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
a	O
Man	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
some	O
Bread	O
and	O
Cheese	O
,	O
a	O
Pen	O
and	O
Ink	O
and	O
a	O
Sheet	O
of	O
Paper	O
to	O
write	O
a	O
Letter	O
on	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
askt	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
lend	O
him	O
a	O
Seal	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Seal	O
hanging	O
to	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
both	O
before	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
draw	O
some	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
his	O
Customer	O
and	O
Watch	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
fix	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Humphrey	B-pers
Hutton	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Coulston	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
,	I-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
together	O
with	O
Richard	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
Wastcoat	O
and	O
Breeches	O
,	O
a	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
in	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
9	O
l.	O
9	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Kinsulloe	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Coulston	I-pers
,	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
late	O
Act	O
of	O
Parliament	O
for	O
the	O
more	O
effectual	O
Transporting	O
of	O
Felons	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
having	O
been	O
formerly	O
Convicted	O
of	O
a	O
Felony	O
and	O
Transported	O
among	O
other	O
Convicts	O
from	O
Newgate	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
had	O
returned	O
into	O
Great	O
Britain	O
without	O
any	O
Lawful	O
Cause	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Winship	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pancras	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Christopher	B-pers
Lowther	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
High-Way	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
Purse	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
10	O
Guineas	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Size	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
driving	O
Mr.	O
Lowthar	O
in	O
his	O
Coach	O
to	O
Hatfield	O
and	O
so	O
to	O
Yorkshire	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
May	O
between	O
4	O
and	O
8	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
a	O
Man	O
rode	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
between	B-place
St.	I-place
Pancras-Church	I-place
and	I-place
the	I-place
Half-way-house	I-place
,	O
with	O
a	O
Pistol	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
stand	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
swore	O
G	O
...	O
d	O
d	O
..	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
your	O
Watch	O
,	O
your	O
Purse	O
,	O
deliver	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
:	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Grey	O
Horse	O
with	O
a	O
whisk	O
Tail	O
,	O
had	O
a	O
white	O
Fustian	O
Frock	O
and	O
a	O
black	O
Mask	O
on	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
put	O
the	O
Frock	O
on	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
like	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
a	O
White	O
Frock	O
and	O
a	O
long	O
Hunting-Whip	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Wife	O
fell	O
on	O
her	O
Knees	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
discover	O
the	O
Frock	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gibson	O
deposed	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
drinking	O
by	O
St.	O
Pancras-church	O
with	O
a	O
Friend	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
(	O
whom	O
he	O
knew	O
before	O
)	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
quartern	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
ask	O
'd	O
this	O
Evidence	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
it	O
(	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
)	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
drink	O
the	O
Waters	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Wells	O
not	O
being	O
open	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
a	O
Ride	O
up	O
to	O
Highgate	O
and	O
come	O
back	O
and	O
drink	O
them	O
:	O
that	O
he	O
rode	O
that	O
Way	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
came	O
Riding	O
back	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
towards	O
London	O
,	O
Hallowing	O
as	O
he	O
past	O
by	O
:	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
turn	O
'd	O
of	O
Four	O
on	O
Thursday	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
May	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Grey	O
Horse	O
with	O
a	O
Whisk	O
Yall	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
White	O
Frock	O
button	O
'd	O
up	O
;	O
he	O
also	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
finding	O
the	O
White	O
Frock	O
and	O
Whip	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
's	O
falling	O
down	O
on	O
her	O
Knees	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nottage	I-pers
(	O
about	O
16	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
)	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
behind	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
met	O
it	O
and	O
past	O
it	O
but	O
turn	O
'd	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
close	O
behind	O
the	O
Coach	O
he	O
put	O
on	O
his	O
Mask	O
,	O
drew	O
his	O
Pistol	O
,	O
rode	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Coachman	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
stand	O
,	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
;	O
whereupon	O
this	O
Evidence	O
leapt	O
from	O
behind	O
the	O
Coach	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Field	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
Pancras	O
Road	O
for	O
London	O
;	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
May	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Grey	O
Horse	O
with	O
a	O
Whisk	O
Tail	O
,	O
had	O
on	O
a	O
light	O
Fustian	O
Frock	O
,	O
a	O
Bob	O
Perriwig	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
long	O
Hunting	O
Whip	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
:	O
And	O
being	O
askt	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
behind	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Father	O
was	O
a	O
Carpenter	O
at	O
Work	O
at	O
Highgate	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
thither	O
to	O
Work	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Coach	O
going	O
that	O
Way	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
behind	O
it	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
plain	O
before	O
he	O
put	O
on	O
his	O
Mask	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sure	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
Person	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
when	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
go	O
to	O
Highgate	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
back	O
the	O
same	O
Way	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
a	O
State	O
of	O
Health	O
capable	O
to	O
undertake	O
such	O
an	O
Enterprize	O
;	O
and	O
called	O
his	O
Surgeon	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
His	O
Surgeon	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
so	O
weak	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
hardly	O
go	O
,	O
being	O
just	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Sallivation	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
advised	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
Walk	O
Morning	O
and	O
Evening	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
able	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
advised	O
him	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
Horse	O
and	O
ride	O
into	O
the	O
Air	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
May	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Grays-Inn-Lane	O
on	O
a	O
Grey	O
Horse	O
in	O
,	O
a	O
White	O
Frock	O
before	O
4	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
One	O
Evidence	O
spoke	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
his	O
Mother	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
knew	O
no	O
ill	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
before	O
been	O
an	O
Evidence	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Court	O
and	O
convicted	O
several	O
whom	O
he	O
swore	O
had	O
been	O
concerned	O
with	O
himself	O
in	O
divers	O
Robberies	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
John	B-pers
Amable	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
in	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
by	O
driving	O
the	O
near	O
Wheel	O
of	O
his	O
Cart	O
drawn	O
by	O
4	O
Horses	O
,	O
over	O
her	O
Loins	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
means	O
whereof	O
they	O
were	O
bruised	O
and	O
broken	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquest	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Manslaughter	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Atwood	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
Child	O
was	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
before	O
the	O
Cart	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Carman	O
was	O
riding	O
in	O
the	O
Cart	O
(	O
an	O
empty	O
Brick-Cart	O
)	O
in	O
Red-Lion-Street	B-place
,	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
;	O
that	O
he	O
called	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
stopt	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
near	O
Wheel	O
upon	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
Back	O
of	O
the	O
Child	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Shipley	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Cart	O
drawn	O
by	O
4	O
Horses	O
,	O
the	O
Child	O
on	O
her	O
Face	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
Foot	O
before	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Wheel	O
go	O
over	O
her	O
Body	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Inmnan	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stoke	B-place
Newington	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
her	O
Female	O
Bastard	O
Child	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Chare-woman	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
about	O
in	O
Burns	O
where	O
she	O
could	O
)	O
then	O
lay	O
in	O
an	O
Outpart	O
in	O
her	O
Master	O
's	O
Yard	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
heard	O
a	O
Child	O
Cry	O
twice	O
,	O
and	O
acquainted	O
her	O
Master	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
who	O
bid	O
her	O
go	O
down	O
and	O
get	O
the	O
Door	O
broke	O
open	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
open	O
it	O
:	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
went	O
in	O
the	O
Prisner	O
denied	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Child	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
search	O
they	O
found	O
that	O
she	O
sat	O
upon	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Straw	O
and	O
turning	O
her	O
off	O
found	O
it	O
dead	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
heard	O
the	O
Child	O
cry	O
once	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Gretty	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
Noise	O
like	O
the	O
Crying	O
of	O
a	O
Child	O
;	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
Women	O
the	O
Candle	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
saw	O
the	O
Child	O
dead	O
.	O
Mrs.Fielder	O
(	O
a	O
Midwife	O
)	O
deposed	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
full	O
Growth	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
believed	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
smothered	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
when	O
her	O
Child	O
was	O
born	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Merrit	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Waldon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
in	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
an	O
Indian	O
Wastcoat	O
and	O
Breeches	O
,	O
two	O
Gowns	O
and	O
others	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
3	O
l.	O
17	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
lockt	O
her	O
Door	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
Home	O
found	O
it	O
open	O
,	O
her	O
Drawers-broke	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
gone	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
found	O
her	O
two	O
Gowns	O
hanging	O
up	O
for	O
Sale	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
of	O
her	O
Goods	O
at	O
several	O
Shops	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Fair	O
.	O
The	O
several	O
Persons	O
where	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
deposed	O
that	O
they	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
to	O
sell	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
not	O
knowing	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
honestly	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Ann	B-pers
Merrit	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Walden	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
with	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Field	I-pers
(	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Field	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
stuff	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
9	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Autherly	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Lock	O
of	O
her	O
Door	O
was	O
pickt	O
and	O
her	O
Goods	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
found	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Mackain	O
's	O
Shop	O
in	O
Field	O
Lane	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mackain	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
Elizabeth	O
Harris	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Harris	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
William	B-pers
Field	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Merrit	I-pers
alias	O
Walden	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Field	I-pers
,	O
and	O
her	O
self	O
committed	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
that	O
William	O
Field	O
pickt	O
the	O
Lock	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
Ann	O
Merrit	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
down	O
to	O
this	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Mackain	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
Money	O
to	O
William	O
Field	O
and	O
Merrit	O
to	O
the	O
Salutation	O
Tavern	O
(	O
where	O
they	O
waited	O
)	O
and	O
divided	O
it	O
.	O
That	O
Mrs.	O
Davis	O
and	O
Mackain	O
had	O
her	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
's	O
)	O
Gold	O
Necklace	O
,	O
and	O
17	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Note	O
for	O
more	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
not	O
making	O
due	O
Payment	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
Warrant	O
and	O
brought	O
on	O
this	O
Prosecution	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Haborn	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
them	O
when	O
they	O
made	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Acherly	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
Harris	O
was	O
taken	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
and	O
Brokers	O
were	O
willing	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Taylor	O
's	O
(	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
)	O
that	O
the	O
Brokers	O
were	O
persuading	O
them	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
told	O
them	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
without	O
a	O
Justice	O
:	O
That	O
Harris	O
's	O
Gold	O
Necklace	O
was	O
given	O
to	O
Taylor	O
to	O
make	O
Satisfaction	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Harris	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
doult	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
shou	O
'd	O
find	O
the	O
Thieves	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
against	O
Elizabeth	O
Field	O
(	O
whose	O
Husband	O
was	O
swore	O
to	O
be	O
present	O
)	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
found	O
Ann	O
Merrit	O
alias	O
Walden	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Ann	O
Merrit	O
alias	O
Walden	O
,	O
was	O
Arraigned	O
for	O
three	O
other	O
Felonies	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
Indictments	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Matth.ew	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
of	O
Wilsden	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Goldington	I-pers
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
her	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
Throat	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Length	O
of	O
5	O
Inches	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Ralph	I-pers
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Bealey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
67	O
Glass	O
Bottles	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Ward	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Meers	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
Bed	O
at	O
Midnight	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Watch	O
house	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Bottles	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
Edward	O
,	O
Meers	O
deposed	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
and	O
Watchmen	O
were	O
going	O
their	O
Rounds	O
,	O
they	O
saw	O
three	O
Boys	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
made	O
his	O
Escape	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
putting	O
Bottles	O
into	O
a	O
Canvas	O
Bag	O
:	O
that	O
they	O
owned	O
they	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Ward	O
's	O
Yard	O
,	O
that	O
Bailey	O
was	O
hoisted	O
over	O
the	O
Wall	O
and	O
let	O
the	O
rest	O
in	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
carried	O
and	O
hid	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
Bunhill-Fields	O
.	O
Their	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Shields	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
in	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
with	O
James	B-pers
Sharrard	I-pers
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Rowley	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
2	O
Guineas	O
and	O
12	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Millicent	B-pers
Clouds	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Hood	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mark	B-pers
Flint	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Lodger	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
pawned	O
them	O
for	O
10	O
s.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
sent	O
her	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
pawn	O
for	O
a	O
Week	O
to	O
raise	O
a	O
little	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Grimes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
in	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
8	O
d.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
than	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
her	O
Charewoman	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
mist	O
so	O
soon	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
:	O
Michael	B-pers
Price	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
confest	O
that	O
she	O
carried	O
away	O
the	O
Tankard	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
another	O
Woman	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Camsey	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
her	O
Sister	O
)	O
deliver	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
in	O
her	O
Lap	O
to	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Pot	O
or	O
a	O
Tankard	O
;	O
Isaac	B-pers
Bowman	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
Tankard	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
own	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
askt	O
what	O
Letters	O
were	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
named	O
the	O
wrong	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
Mothers	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
kept	O
the	O
Tankard	O
and	O
sent	O
a	O
Porter	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
enquire	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
or	O
no	O
;	O
and	O
also	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
her	O
Character	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
:	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
with	O
the	O
Porter	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
a	O
good	O
Account	O
of	O
her	O
from	O
whence	O
she	O
liv	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
having	O
enquir	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
buy	O
it	O
and	O
she	O
demanding	O
it	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
return	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Her	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Flemming	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Hilted	O
Sword	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
July	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Fleet-street	O
about	O
two	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
near	O
Chancery	O
Lane	O
end	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
chuckt	O
him	O
under	O
the	O
Chin	O
,	O
and	O
askt	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
walk	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
he	O
answered	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
Peters	B-place
Lane	I-place
in	I-place
Cow	I-place
Cross	I-place
,	O
where	O
she	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
flourisht	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
with	O
it	O
into	O
an	O
Alley	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
followed	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
had	O
convey	O
'd	O
the	O
Sword	O
away	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
her	O
Husband	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
his	O
Note	O
for	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
refused	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
and	O
another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
present	O
when	O
her	O
Husband	O
offer	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
his	O
Note	O
for	O
4	O
l.	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
of	O
Privately	O
stealing	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Solomon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
in	I-place
White	I-place
Chapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Petticoat	O
2	O
Pewter	O
Porringers	O
6	O
Napkins	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Hood	O
,	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Sheet	O
,	O
a	O
Shift	O
,	O
6	O
Bottles	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
23	O
s.	O
and	O
3	O
half	O
Guineas	O
and	O
22	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Repentance	B-pers
Twist	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Slade	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
complaining	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
well	O
,	O
she	O
left	O
her	O
a	O
Bed	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
return	O
'd	O
her	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
were	O
gone	O
:	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
left	O
none	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Pearson	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
(	O
a	O
Cook	O
's	O
Shop	O
)	O
and	O
sold	O
her	O
a	O
Porringer	O
and	O
some	O
Linnen	O
for	O
4	O
s.	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
heard	O
they	O
were	O
stolen	O
,	O
she	O
delivered	O
them	O
up	O
.	O
Three	O
other	O
Persons	O
confirmed	O
Mrs.	O
Pearson	O
's	O
Evidence	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
produced	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lent	O
her	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
pawn	O
to	O
raise	O
Money	O
to	O
fetch	O
her	O
Gown	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
her	O
been	O
a	O
Witness	O
,	O
telling	O
her	O
that	O
she	O
should	O
get	O
Money	O
enough	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
not	O
consenting	O
to	O
,	O
this	O
Prosecution	O
was	O
brought	O
against	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
23	O
s.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Blackwell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Sheet	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Court	O
ordered	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Recognizance	O
to	O
be	O
Estreated	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Lambeth	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
in	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Child	O
's	O
Coat	O
value	O
6	O
d	O
a	O
Shirt	O
4	O
d.	O
a	O
Clout	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Towel	O
4	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Brotherton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Tableclothes	O
,	O
4	O
Window	O
Curtains	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
l.	O
13	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Walter	B-pers
Aubery	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
1718	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Tottenham	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ralph	B-pers
Skinson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
2	O
Butten	O
Cloths	O
value	O
1st	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Susannah	B-pers
Calvert	I-pers
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
July	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
hung	O
on	O
a	O
Hedge	O
to	O
dry	O
with	O
other	O
Linnen	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
seen	O
to	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Ditch	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
was	O
secured	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
that	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
:	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
nor	O
call	O
any	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
Susannah	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
with	O
Katharine	B-pers
Speed	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bag	O
,	O
25	O
Guineas	O
,	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
broad	O
Gold	O
value	O
23	O
s.	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
up	O
Holbourn	O
by	O
Drury	O
Lane	O
two	O
Women	O
pickt	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Newtoners-Lane	B-place
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
Money	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
staid	O
there	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
mist	O
it	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Katharine	O
Speed	O
and	O
her	O
self	O
pickt	O
up	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
into	O
Mary	O
Roberts	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
that	O
Marsh	O
brought	O
up	O
a	O
quartern	O
of	O
All	O
Fours	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
short	O
Measure	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
round	O
.	O
That	O
Roberts	O
brought	O
up	O
a	O
second	O
quartern	O
:	O
That	O
while	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
feeling	O
Katharine	O
Speed	O
,	O
she	O
bid	O
her	O
go	O
and	O
sink	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
his	O
Breeches	O
was	O
so	O
stiff	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
.	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
their	O
Custom	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
had	O
pickt	O
any	O
Man	O
's	O
Pocket	O
,	O
Roberts	O
(	O
the	O
Woman	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
)	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
5	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
Pound	O
and	O
3	O
d.	O
in	O
the	O
shilling	O
of	O
what	O
they	O
got	O
:	O
and	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
and	O
finding	O
that	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Money	O
,	O
would	O
undertake	O
it	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
that	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
it	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
stand	O
to	O
the	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Pound	O
but	O
would	O
have	O
half	O
snacks	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Evidence	O
and	O
Speed	O
should	O
have	O
the	O
other	O
half	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
(	O
Mary	O
Roberts	O
)	O
pull	O
'd	O
up	O
her	O
Coats	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
feel	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
spoke	O
;	O
(	O
which	O
signified	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
his	O
Money	O
)	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
hard	O
by	O
,	O
desiring	O
the	O
Woman	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
to	O
lay	O
it	O
up	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
her	O
Maid	O
was	O
Drunk	O
.	O
That	O
Marsh	O
(	O
Roberts	O
's	O
Maid	O
)	O
only	O
brought	O
up	O
the	O
first	O
quartern	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
went	O
to	O
Roberts	O
for	O
her	O
share	O
;	O
who	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
give	O
her	O
any	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
13	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
Broad	O
Piece	O
to	O
Miller	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Trimner	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Roberts	O
brought	O
20	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
Broad	O
Piece	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
lay	O
up	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
her	O
Maid	O
was	O
drunk	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Miller	O
offer	O
'd	O
him	O
13	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
Broad	O
piece	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
Roberts	O
in	O
Charterhouse	O
Lane	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Robinson	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
;	O
and	O
farther	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Roberts	O
had	O
left	O
her	O
House	O
and	O
mov	O
'd	O
her	O
Goods	O
:	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
when	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
'em	O
that	O
Marsh	O
was	O
one	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	O
Roberts	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Grey	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
declar	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
hang	O
a	O
Hundred	O
before	O
she	O
would	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
her	O
self	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
in	O
the	O
Roundhouse	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
her	O
(	O
Mary	O
Roberts	O
)	O
but	O
the	O
little	O
Bitch	O
below	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
made	O
it	O
up	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Jasper	B-pers
Battle	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
in	O
the	O
Roundhouse	O
,	O
that	O
Roberts	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
Woman	O
that	O
pickt	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
but	O
Grey	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
call	O
'd	O
again	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
Roberts	O
offer	O
'd	O
him	O
7	O
Guineas	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
saying	O
if	O
he	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
he	O
must	O
let	O
them	O
all	O
go	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
pickt	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
against	O
Miller	O
and	O
Marsb	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Mary	O
Roberts	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
at	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Boots	O
,	O
7	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Slippers	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Siggins	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
July	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
seen	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
a	O
Handbasket	O
,	O
and	O
askt	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
at	O
Islington	O
:	O
but	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
carrying	O
to	O
Newgate	O
confest	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
and	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
Mr.	O
King	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
owned	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilt	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Lithgoe	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Katharine	I-place
by	I-place
the	I-place
Tower	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Riley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Riggol	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
in	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Boots	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Edmunds	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Boots	O
which	O
hung	O
at	O
a	O
post	O
the	O
outside	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
at	O
a	O
Cellar	O
against	O
the	O
New	O
Church	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
.	O
Theodore	B-pers
Christopher	I-pers
Fabritius	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
in	I-place
Shorditch	I-place
,	O
Gent	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Grace	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
by	O
Striking	O
,	O
Wounding	O
and	O
Bruising	O
her	O
with	O
a	O
Wooden	O
Staff	O
over	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
Face	O
,	O
Neck	O
,	O
Back	O
and	O
Belly	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
;	O
of	O
which	O
Beating	O
Wounding	O
and	O
Bruising	O
she	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Month	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
House	O
to	O
the	O
Doctor	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Shrieks	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Doctor	O
beat	O
her	O
several	O
times	O
in	O
a	O
Day	O
,	O
even	O
on	O
Sundays	O
,	O
sometimes	O
with	O
his	O
Fist	O
,	O
other	O
times	O
with	O
a	O
Whip	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
June	O
he	O
barbarously	O
used	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
reproved	O
him	O
several	O
times	O
:	O
but	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
her	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
hold	O
her	O
Tongue	O
.	O
And	O
being	O
askt	O
,	O
said	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
but	O
,	O
the	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
whether	O
the	O
was	O
under	O
cure	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
beat	O
the	O
Deceased	O
severely	O
in	O
his	O
Garden	O
(	O
as	O
she	O
thought	O
)	O
with	O
a	O
Whip	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
shov	O
'd	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
doors	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Evidence	O
heard	O
him	O
give	O
her	O
some	O
Stripes	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
That	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
beat	O
the	O
Deceased	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Ear	O
Bled	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
drove	O
her	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
heard	O
Blows	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
And	O
being	O
askt	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lookt	O
after	O
Mad	O
People	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Deceased	O
to	O
be	O
as	O
a	O
servant	O
about	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Green	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
Weeks	O
ago	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
with	O
a	O
Couch-Bed	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
lockt	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
with	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
Black	O
round	O
both	O
her	O
Eyes	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
her	O
Master	O
did	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
her	O
before	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
.	O
Katharine	B-pers
Greenhall	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
strike	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
but	O
heard	O
him	O
almost	O
every	O
Day	O
for	O
2	O
Months	O
,	O
particularly	O
the	O
Sunday	O
before	O
her	O
Death	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
saw	O
her	O
run	O
out	O
from	O
the	O
Doctor	O
,	O
and	O
belives	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
person	O
she	O
heard	O
Cry	O
out	O
and	O
beat	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Cowell	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
House	O
looks	O
into	O
the	O
Doctor	O
's	O
Garden	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
as	O
Grace	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
was	O
Weeding	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
her	O
Headclothes	O
,	O
struck	O
her	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
Blows	O
with	O
his	O
Hand	O
over	O
her	O
Head	O
,	O
3	O
Weeks	O
before	O
her	O
Death	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
May	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
wheeling	O
a	O
Barrow	O
in	O
the	O
Garden	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
about	O
a	O
Dozen	O
Blows	O
with	O
a	O
Broomstick	O
,	O
beat	O
her	O
Hat	O
and	O
Headclothes	O
off	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
strings	O
to	O
the	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
almost	O
choakt	O
her	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Deval	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
5	O
Weeks	O
before	O
the	O
Deceased	O
died	O
,	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
a	O
clock	O
of	O
a	O
Sunday	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
dismal	O
Cry	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
run	O
out	O
and	O
say	O
for	O
the	O
Lord	O
sake	O
bear	O
me	O
.	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
beat	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
all	O
over	O
Bloody	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Smithiman	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
beat	O
the	O
Deceased	O
three	O
times	O
,	O
that	O
once	O
he	O
struck	O
her	O
down	O
with	O
his	O
Hand	O
in	O
the	O
Garden	O
,	O
another	O
time	O
she	O
let	O
him	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
beat	O
her	O
from	O
the	O
Gate	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Sunday	O
fornnight	O
before	O
her	O
Death	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Frampton	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Deceased	O
cry	O
out	O
Murder	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Thursday	O
before	O
she	O
died	O
she	O
ran	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
into	O
another	O
Room	O
all	O
Bloody	O
with	O
her	O
Cap	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Troughtman	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
visited	O
the	O
Doctor	O
often	O
,	O
that	O
once	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
beat	O
the	O
Deceased	O
with	O
a	O
Stick	O
,	O
or	O
Whip	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
which	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Stick	O
was	O
a	O
small	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
misuse	O
it	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
That	O
another	O
time	O
she	O
had	O
kill	O
'd	O
a	O
Hen	O
with	O
Feeding	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Doctor	O
beat	O
it	O
about	O
her	O
Head	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
his	O
seen	O
him	O
beat	O
her	O
about	O
the	O
Face	O
and	O
every	O
where	O
with	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
an	O
Imposthume	O
in	O
her	O
Ear	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Doctor	O
broke	O
it	O
with	O
a	O
Blow	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
Blood	O
and	O
Matter	O
ran	O
out	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
a	O
Passion	O
,	O
but	O
seen	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
opening	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
of	O
a	O
Sunday	O
between	O
and	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Doctor	O
was	O
very	O
angry	O
the	O
Sunday	O
Evening	O
before	O
her	O
Death	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
would	O
not	O
work	O
unless	O
forc	O
'd	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
her	O
right	O
Senses	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
Doctor	O
use	O
her	O
both	O
roughly	O
and	O
gently	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Pike	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
lay	O
the	O
Deceased	O
out	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
had	O
Black	O
places	O
on	O
her	O
Head	O
,	O
Face	O
,	O
Arms	O
,	O
Neck	O
,	O
Shoulders	O
,	O
Back	O
and	O
Legs	O
,	O
a	O
sad	O
Ear	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Cap	O
Bloody	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
said	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
been	O
barbarously	O
used	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
by	O
a	O
Fall	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hobbs	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Gardener	O
,	O
and	O
oftentimes	O
saw	O
him	O
strike	O
the	O
Deceased	O
over	O
the	O
Shoulders	O
and	O
Small	O
of	O
the	O
Back	O
with	O
his	O
Walking	O
Cane	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
in	O
her	O
Face	O
with	O
his	O
Fist	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
saw	O
no	O
occasion	O
.	O
That	O
once	O
he	O
beat	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
thick	O
end	O
of	O
a	O
Stick	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
crying	O
out	O
he	O
said	O
D	O
-	O
you	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
cry	O
out	O
?	O
and	O
ran	O
the	O
other	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Stick	O
into	O
her	O
Mouth	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Blood	O
ran	O
out	O
;	O
That	O
another	O
time	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
Weeding	O
in	O
the	O
Garden	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
D	O
-	O
you	O
cant	O
you	O
kneel	O
?	O
Struck	O
her	O
down	O
with	O
his	O
Fist	O
and	O
Stampt	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Knighting	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
beat	O
the	O
Deceased	O
frequently	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
has	O
often	O
heard	O
her	O
Shrieks	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
her	O
Voice	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
lookt	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
put	O
up	O
his	O
Window-shutters	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
made	O
her	O
set	O
up	O
a	O
very	O
heavy	O
Ladder	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
feed	O
his	O
Pidgeons	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
up	O
a	O
Bowl	O
of	O
Water	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
Steps	O
up	O
the	O
Ladder	O
,	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Bowl	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
kickt	O
her	O
down	O
.	O
Here	O
being	O
askt	O
whether	O
she	O
saw	O
his	O
Foot	O
touch	O
her	O
,	O
answered	O
no	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
saw	O
it	O
stand	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
beat	O
her	O
intollerably	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Frenolt	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
view	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
Head	O
contused	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Temporal	O
Muscles	O
and	O
Ear	O
likewise	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
bruised	O
between	O
her	O
Shoulders	O
,	O
had	O
a	O
small	O
Wound	O
on	O
her	O
Lip	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Tooth	O
out	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
of	O
Opinion	O
that	O
those	O
Wounds	O
and	O
Bruises	O
were	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
her	O
Death	O
.	O
And	O
being	O
askt	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
not	O
any	O
single	O
Wound	O
or	O
Bruise	O
about	O
her	O
was	O
Mortal	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
her	O
Ear	O
might	O
be	O
an	O
Imposthume	O
,	O
which	O
might	O
alone	O
have	O
been	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
her	O
Death	O
;	O
that	O
her	O
,	O
Temporal	O
Muscles	O
were	O
much	O
contused	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
found	O
no	O
Fracture	O
.	O
And	O
being	O
askt	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
what	O
shape	O
the	O
Temporal	O
Muscles	O
were	O
of	O
,	O
made	O
no	O
Answer	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Body	O
in	O
the	O
Coffin	O
,	O
but	O
viewed	O
the	O
Head	O
only	O
;	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Fore	O
Teeth	O
of	O
the	O
upper	O
Jaw	O
was	O
wanting	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
inner	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Lip	O
against	O
it	O
,	O
a	O
small	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
Scalp	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
the	O
Cartilage	O
of	O
the	O
Nose	O
was	O
broke	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Wound	O
that	O
he	O
thought	O
Mortal	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wallis	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Body	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
,	O
(	O
she	O
died	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
before	O
)	O
found	O
a	O
Contusions	O
under	O
her	O
Ear	O
,	O
her	O
Nose	O
broke	O
,	O
her	O
Temporal	O
Muscles-bruised	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
any	O
Wound	O
was	O
Mortal	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Fletcher	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
several	O
Contusions	O
in	O
her	O
Face	O
,	O
the	O
Cartilage	O
of	O
her	O
Nose	O
broke	O
,	O
a	O
Tooth	O
out	O
,	O
her	O
Ear	O
and	O
Temporal	O
Muscles	O
bruised	O
,	O
but	O
cou	O
'd	O
not	O
say	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
her	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
him	O
as	O
a	O
Lunatick	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
her	O
Service	O
for	O
her	O
Cure	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
him	O
some	O
time	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
bruised	O
by	O
a	O
Fall	O
down	O
Stairs	O
and	O
fell	O
on	O
her	O
Face	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
Temper	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
held	O
up	O
but	O
a	O
Stick	O
she	O
would	O
cry	O
out	O
Murder	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
she	O
used	O
to	O
fall	O
down	O
and	O
beat	O
her	O
self	O
in	O
her	O
Fits	O
very	O
much	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Grover	I-pers
Deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Mother	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
the	O
Doctor	O
to	O
take	O
her	O
Daughter	O
in	O
and	O
give	O
her	O
Cure	O
for	O
what	O
Service	O
he	O
found	O
her	O
capable	O
of	O
doing	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
often	O
Assaulted	O
her	O
Mother	O
and	O
beat	O
her	O
in	O
her	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
Mother	O
went	O
in	O
danger	O
of	O
her	O
Life	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
run	O
away	O
one	O
Morning	O
from	O
the	O
Doctor	O
to	O
her	O
Brother	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Mother	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
this	O
Evidence	O
to	O
go	O
back	O
again	O
with	O
her	O
:	O
That	O
the	O
Doctor	O
came	O
to	O
ask	O
her	O
to	O
look	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
again	O
willingly	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
observed	O
the	O
Deceased	O
to	O
have	O
some	O
Black	O
Marks	O
on	O
her	O
Face	O
and	O
Nose	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Swelling	O
in	O
her	O
Ear	O
,	O
askt	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
sometimes	O
said	O
by	O
a	O
Fall	O
,	O
sometimes	O
by	O
a	O
Blast	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
went	O
and	O
acquainted	O
her	O
Mother	O
with	O
the	O
Marks	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
and	O
talk	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Doctor	O
,	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
correct	O
her	O
moderately	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
.	O
That	O
her	O
Mother	O
desired	O
she	O
might	O
continue	O
there	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
told	O
her	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
that	O
she	O
fell	O
down	O
a	O
Ladder	O
,	O
but	O
made	O
no	O
Complaint	O
of	O
her	O
Master	O
.	O
That	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
Days	O
,	O
before	O
her	O
Death	O
she	O
was	O
ill	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
Purging	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Sunday	O
before	O
she	O
died	O
this	O
Evidence	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Doctor	O
's	O
found	O
the	O
Deceased	O
with	O
her	O
Head	O
leaning	O
on	O
a	O
Chair	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
well	O
.	O
That	O
afterwards	O
when	O
she	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
reading	O
to	O
her	O
Master	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
she	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
in	O
haste	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
,	O
the	O
Maid	O
was	O
dead	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Doctor	O
then	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
had	O
had	O
two	O
Convulsion-Fits	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
recovered	O
her	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
died	O
in	O
the	O
last	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
sent	O
her	O
to	O
call	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Mother	O
,	O
saying	O
she	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
moved	O
till	O
her	O
Friends	O
came	O
.	O
And	O
this	O
Evidence	O
being	O
askt	O
,	O
farther	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
fell	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
her	O
other	O
Fall	O
was	O
from	O
the	O
Ladder	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Knighting	I-pers
being	O
call	O
'd	O
again	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
House	O
the	O
Doctor	O
lives	O
in	O
was	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
had	O
a	O
Passage	O
through	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
now	O
that	O
Passage	O
was	O
shut	O
up	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
forced	O
to	O
go	O
a	O
great	O
way	O
about	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
fall	O
off	O
.	O
the	O
Ladder	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Doctor	O
took	O
the	O
Bowl	O
from	O
her	O
but	O
did	O
did	O
not	O
stir	O
his	O
Foot	O
;	O
that	O
her	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
's	O
)	O
Eye	O
was	O
lacent	O
on	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
the	O
Doctor	O
had	O
kickt	O
her	O
the	O
must	O
have	O
seen	O
it	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Grover	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
put	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
cured	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
nothing	O
for	O
the	O
cure	O
but	O
her	O
service	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
stubborn	O
and	O
stomach	O
full	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
Mother	O
told	O
her	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
forc	O
'd	O
to	O
put	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
Workhouse	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Scadon	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
divers	O
inconsiderable	O
Bruises	O
on	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
Head	O
and	O
Neck	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
;	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
Ear	O
was	O
bad	O
,	O
but	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
from	O
an	O
Imposthime	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Fracture	O
in	O
her	O
Skull	O
,	O
not	O
any	O
Wound	O
that	O
affected	O
her	O
Life	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Tanner	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
Surgeons	O
on	O
the	O
Kings	O
side	O
were	O
there	O
)	O
deposed	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
slight	O
Bruises	O
on	O
her	O
Face	O
,	O
2	O
Stripes	O
cross	O
her	O
Shoulders	O
which	O
might	O
be	O
made	O
by	O
a	O
Whip	O
or	O
Rattan	O
.	O
That	O
her	O
Temporal	O
Muscles	O
were	O
not	O
contused	O
,	O
her	O
Lips	O
not	O
swell	O
'd	O
nor	O
black	O
,	O
no	O
Braise	O
on	O
her	O
Nose	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
appeared	O
fatal	O
or	O
injurious	O
.	O
And	O
gave	O
his	O
Reasons	O
for	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Temporal	O
Muscles	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Simmons	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
present	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Tanner	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Surgeons	O
)	O
was	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Opinion	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Tanner	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Graschman	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
Visit	O
the	O
Doctor	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
there	O
when	O
his	O
Maid	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
used	O
the	O
Doctor	O
and	O
himself	O
very	O
ill.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Braithwait	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Doctor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
steps	O
of	O
the	O
Ladder	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
3	O
Foot	O
perpendicular	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
Whip	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
slight	O
one	O
)	O
and	O
a	O
small	O
Stick	O
which	O
they	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
Doctor	O
used	O
about	O
his	O
patients	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
were	O
very	O
much	O
enrag	O
'd	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
shut	O
up	O
the	O
passage	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
Conjuring	O
Rogue	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
dealt	O
with	O
the	O
Devil	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Knighting	I-pers
rail	O
'd	O
particularly	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
formerly	O
under	O
the	O
misfortune	O
of	O
Lunacy	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Doctor	O
cured	O
him	O
effectually	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
conversant	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
since	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
thing	O
misbecoming	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
never	O
made	O
any	O
Complaint	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Deering	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
John	B-pers
Deval	I-pers
express	O
himself	O
very	O
Hotly	O
and	O
Maliciously	O
against	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
complained	O
of	O
the	O
stopping	O
up	O
the	O
passage	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
them	O
go	O
a	O
great	O
way	O
round	O
about	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
Mild	O
well	O
temper	O
'd	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
mentioned	O
several	O
Cures	O
he	O
had	O
perform	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Master	O
,	O
brought	O
in	O
their	O
Verdict	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bickerton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Charles	B-pers
Edwin	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3rd	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
perriwig	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
the	O
night	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
he	O
crost	O
Middle	O
Row	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Broad	O
Place	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
peceived	O
a	O
soldier	O
with	O
a	O
Trull	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Soldier	O
behind	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
not	O
liking	O
to	O
be	O
between	O
such	O
Company	O
,	O
stood	O
to	O
let	O
the	O
soldier	O
that	O
was	O
behind	O
him	O
get	O
before	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
Woman	O
cry	O
out	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Man	O
Murdering	O
his	O
Wife	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
supposing	O
what	O
sort	O
of	O
Cattle	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
walkt	O
on	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
till	O
he	O
got	O
into	O
Monmouth	B-place
street	I-place
,	O
then	O
slacken	O
'd	O
his	O
Pace	O
;	O
that	O
his	O
Wig	O
was	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
his	O
Head	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
followed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
whose	O
Feet	O
flew	O
up	O
in	O
his	O
Flight	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
presently	O
got	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
threw	O
away	O
the	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
into	O
a	O
Brewhouse-Yard	O
,	O
thence	O
to	O
other	O
places	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
pursued	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Waller	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
acknowledged	O
the	O
Fact	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
done	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
sorry	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Humphrey	B-pers
Beven	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
Wig	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
seized	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Edminton	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Porridge	O
Pot	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
a	O
Brass	O
Kettle	O
5s	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
Skimmer	O
6d	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Scroggs	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
Hay	O
for	O
him	O
Seven	O
Days	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
in	O
his	O
Barn	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
he	O
mist	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
followed	O
her	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
selling	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
first	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Newby	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Haslip	I-pers
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Guy	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Keys	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
in	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Necklace	O
value	O
4.	O
l	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Gold	O
Ear-Drops	O
8s	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
French	O
Pistole	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Whitecoss	I-pers
:	O
and	O
7	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Charlesworth	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
Charlesworth	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
trusted	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
missing	O
and	O
found	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
.	O
Her	O
confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
was	O
that	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
Necklace	O
and	O
Drops	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Charlesworth	O
's	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
believed	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
.	O
But	O
on	O
her	O
Tryal	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
found	O
them	O
on	O
a	O
Dunghill	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39s	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Atwater	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Paddington	B-place
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Thomas	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Pocket-Book	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
a	O
Rasor	O
,	O
1	O
Pound	O
of	O
Bacon	O
,	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
10s	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
and	O
Frances	B-pers
Wildgoose	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Linnen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
3	O
Muslin	O
Pinners	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
in	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Muslin	O
Neckcloths	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
,	O
had	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
formerly	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
she	O
mist	O
her	O
Goods	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
suspect	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
believed	O
the	O
Drawer	O
was	O
open	O
where	O
there	O
lay	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
turn	O
'd	O
away	O
her	O
Washerwoman	O
upon	O
it	O
:	O
And	O
that	O
going	O
to	O
Newgate	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Confinement	O
there	O
,	O
saw	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
Neckcloths	O
in	O
his	O
custody	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Eades	I-pers
,	O
(	O
indicted	O
last	O
Sessions	O
)	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
in	O
receiving	O
stolen	O
Goods	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Bland	I-pers
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Brass	O
Tops	O
of	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Trinity	B-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Minories	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Drugget	O
Coat	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Lewis	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
July	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Spencer	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
seeing	O
the	O
shadow	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Entry	O
,	O
followed	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Shop-Door	O
,	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Coat	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
saw	O
the	O
Coat	O
3	O
Minutes	O
before	O
in	O
the	O
Parlour	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Unwin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
in	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Ann	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Pocket	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
2	O
Keys	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
was	O
fuily	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
that	O
he	O
put	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
Post	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
in	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
2	O
Silver	O
Cups	O
,	O
1	O
Silver	O
Salver	O
,	O
2	O
Silver	O
Castors	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Salts	O
,	O
7	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Pepper	O
Box	O
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
and	O
Chain	O
,	O
a	O
Seal	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
60	O
l.	O
a	O
Worsted	O
Purse	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
.	O
At	O
the	O
Request	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
were	O
examined	O
apart	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
Watch	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
May	O
at	O
Night	O
(	O
being	O
Constable	O
)	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
home	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
in	O
Bedford	B-place
Court	I-place
in	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
between	O
4	O
and	O
5	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
25th	O
.	O
he	O
found	O
his	O
Scrutore	O
broke	O
and	O
his	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
gone	O
;	O
that	O
his	O
Maid	O
was	O
in	O
Bed	O
but	O
his	O
Man	O
gone	O
out	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Hunter	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
askt	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
help	O
him	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
some	O
Plate	O
for	O
a	O
Friend	O
of	O
his	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
not	O
knowing	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
lawful	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
a	O
Bankrupt	O
's	O
Goods	O
sent	O
his	O
Wife	O
to	O
a	O
Justice	O
to	O
enquire	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
best	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
who	O
advised	O
him	O
to	O
endeavour	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
Plate	O
or	O
as	O
much	O
of	O
it	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
into	O
his	O
Hands	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
met	O
Hunter	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
sat	O
on	O
the	O
Bank	O
of	O
Rosamonds	O
Pend	O
in	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
Park	O
;	O
where	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Plate	O
that	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
made	O
Sarah	B-pers
Brotherton	I-pers
Drunk	O
,	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Scrutore	O
with	O
a	O
Chissel	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
described	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
Seal	O
,	O
Chain	O
and	O
Plate	O
,	O
which	O
agreed	O
with	O
that	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
exactly	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
post	O
had	O
the	O
Watch	O
in	O
his	O
Possession	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
plate	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
send	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
but	O
never	O
did	O
:	O
that	O
he	O
afterwards	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
George	O
was	O
not	O
willing	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
his	O
Master	O
and	O
he	O
were	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
get	O
a	O
Chap	O
for	O
the	O
Place	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
weigh	O
'd	O
28	O
Pound	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
,	O
against	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
Town	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
several	O
Conferences	O
together	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
deposed	O
;	O
that	O
between	O
the	O
24th	O
and	O
25th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
1	O
a	O
Clock	O
he	O
hearing	O
Somebody	O
Knock	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
it	O
and	O
let	O
in	O
George	B-pers
Post	I-pers
,	O
who	O
Courted	O
Sarah	O
Brotherton	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Hunter	O
there	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
Post	O
very	O
well	O
who	O
came	O
often	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
at	O
unseasonable	O
times	O
;	O
and	O
had	O
seen	O
Hunter	O
pass	O
through	O
the	O
Court	O
with	O
Post	O
,	O
several	O
times	O
before	O
:	O
That	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
let	O
them	O
in	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
fell	O
asleep	O
,	O
leaving	O
them	O
together	O
.	O
This	O
Evidence	O
being	O
askt	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
accused	O
one	O
Burdon	O
nor	O
no	O
body	O
else	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Fact	O
before	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
Master	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
an	O
Agony	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
remember	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
there	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
charge	O
Burdon	O
.	O
And	O
being	O
asked	O
how	O
he	O
could	O
see	O
them	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
of	O
Night	O
,	O
answered	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Candle	O
set	O
up	O
for	O
his	O
Master	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
the	O
Scrutore	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
saw	O
them	O
by	O
the	O
Light	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Sarah	O
Brotherton	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
George	B-pers
Post	I-pers
was	O
her	O
Sweetheart	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
and	O
Hunter	O
came	O
about	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
Browne	O
let	O
them	O
in	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
she	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Stairs	O
Foot	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Parlour	O
going	O
out	O
with	O
the	O
Plate	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
askt	O
them	O
what	O
they	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Plate	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Candle	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Candle	O
set	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Parlour	O
for	O
her	O
Master	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
shewed	O
her	O
the	O
Chissel	O
which	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
endeavourd	O
to	O
invalidate	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
Webb	O
,	O
Browne	O
and	O
Brotherton	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
could	O
prove	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
elsewhere	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
the	O
following	O
Evidence	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
Colonel	O
Pursor	B-pers
's	O
Lodging	O
at	O
10	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
to	O
fetch	O
Hunter	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Beasely	O
,	O
that	O
Hunter	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
without	O
paying	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
staid	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
for	O
his	O
Money	O
.	O
That	O
when	O
Hunter	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
bid	O
him	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
stay	O
,	O
for	O
be	O
had	O
something	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
do	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Beasely	O
was	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
had	O
no	O
Friends	O
but	O
her	O
Cousin	O
Hunter	O
so	O
would	O
have	O
him	O
take	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
what	O
there	O
was	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
wrote	O
the	O
Inventory	O
;	O
and	O
Knew	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
by	O
the	O
Date	O
there	O
of	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
after	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
leaving	O
Hunter	O
behind	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
sent	O
Bishop	O
for	O
Hunter	O
corroborated	O
his	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
farther	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
Bishop	O
,	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
Hunter	O
was	O
sitting	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Beasely	O
's	O
Bedside	O
,	O
bad	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
there	O
till	O
between	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
And	O
being	O
askt	O
where	O
Mrs.	O
Beasely	O
is	O
now	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
Ancient	O
and	O
ill	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
come	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
lay	O
that	O
Night	O
with	O
George	B-pers
Post	I-pers
.	O
And	O
being	O
askt	O
who	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
he	O
remember	O
'd	O
the	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
Month	O
,	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
Servant	O
to	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Dirvers	I-pers
6	O
Months	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
away	O
from	O
him	O
that	O
Day	O
,	O
when	O
Sir	O
Robert	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Discharge	O
;	O
or	O
Letter	O
of	O
Recommendation	O
which	O
he	O
produced	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
That	O
being	O
askt	O
where	O
his	O
Master	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
at	O
Froom	O
in	O
Somersetshire	O
;	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
place	O
He	O
was	O
Member	O
for	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
Persons	O
in	O
Court	O
Who	O
knew	O
Sir	O
Robert	O
(	O
who	O
is	O
Knight	O
of	O
the	O
Shire	O
for	O
Suffolk	O
)	O
better	O
than	O
this	O
Evidence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
soon	O
detected	O
;	O
for	O
upon	O
perusing	O
the	O
Discharge	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
discover	O
'd	O
that	O
it	O
,	O
was	O
signed	O
Da	O
instead	O
of	O
Davers	O
;	O
and	O
comparing	O
it	O
with	O
Bishop	O
's	O
Inventory	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
both	O
Writ	O
by	O
the	O
same	O
Hand	O
.	O
And	O
Bishop	O
and	O
Smith	O
were	O
taken	O
into	O
Custody	O
.	O
Notwithstanding	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
went	O
on	O
in	O
calling	O
others	O
to	O
invalidate	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
Webb	O
,	O
Browne	O
,	O
and	O
Brotherton	O
.	O
They	O
also	O
called	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
worthy	O
Gentlemen	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
them	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
them	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
to	O
receive	O
Sentence	O
,	O
they	O
acknowledged	O
the	O
Forgery	O
and	O
Perjury	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
;	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
intend	O
to	O
have	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
any	O
such	O
Method	O
:	O
but	O
that	O
one	O
Strickland	O
came	O
to	O
them	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
Way	O
for	O
them	O
to	O
come	O
off	O
;	O
and	O
accordingly	O
procured	O
the	O
said	O
Persons	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
2	O
Guineas	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Hugh	B-pers
Rawlins	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Witherley	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Tanner	I-pers
;	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
at	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Day-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
2	O
Gowns	O
and	O
2	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
3	O
Rings	O
,	O
a	O
Hood	O
and	O
Scarf	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
in	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
stolen	O
Goods	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
:	O
And	O
the	O
Court	O
order	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosector	O
's	O
Indictment	O
to	O
be	O
Entreated	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Grantham	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Norton	B-pers
Fitzgerald	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
Mortal	O
wound	O
on	O
the	O
Right	O
fide	O
of	O
the	O
Belley	O
near	O
the	O
Navel	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
9	O
Inches	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
25th	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Died	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
were	O
intimate	O
Friends	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
Company	O
together	O
most	O
past	O
of	O
the	O
Day	O
;	O
that	O
walking	O
together	O
about	O
the	O
Fountain	O
in	O
the	O
Middle	B-place
Temple	I-place
about	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
a	O
Difference	O
happen	O
'd	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Library-Door	O
,	O
drew	O
their	O
Swords	O
and	O
fought	O
between	O
that	O
and	O
the	O
First	O
Fruits-Office	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
both	O
Wounded	O
:	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
came	O
to	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Gremers	O
Coffee	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
dress	O
the	O
Deceased	O
first	O
and	O
Deceased	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
dress	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
first	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
then	O
seemed	O
no	O
manner	O
of	O
Resentment	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
4	O
wounds	O
,	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
Belley	O
near	O
The	O
Navel	O
was	O
Mortal	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
wound	O
in	O
the	O
Left	O
Pap	O
,	O
stretching	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Left	O
Shoulder	O
.	O
It	O
not	O
appearing	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
premeditated	O
Malice	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
it	O
arose	O
from	O
a	O
sudden	O
.	O
Heart	O
of	O
Passion	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Gentlemen	O
appearing	O
to	O
the	O
Reputation	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
quit	O
and	O
peaceable	O
Behaviour	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Gowbert	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Marchbank	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
for	O
extorting	O
several	O
sums	O
of	O
Money	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Thursby	I-pers
and	O
Isaac	B-pers
Beach	I-pers
,	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
helping	O
them	O
to	O
Places	O
:	O
Which	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Fined	O
20	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
suffer	O
3	O
Month	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
in	O
Publishing	O
a	O
false	O
Certificate	O
and	O
Affidavit	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
calling	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Persons	O
of	O
Credit	O
to	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Cass	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
etc	O
.	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
l	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Ruker	I-pers
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Soley	I-pers
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
at	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
5	O
l	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bland	I-pers
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
was	O
called	O
to	O
plead	O
to	O
an	O
Indictment	O
found	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
his	O
Recognizance	O
was	O
orderder	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
Estreated	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Court	O
Order	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
all	O
Persons	O
who	O
shall	O
be	O
bound	O
in	O
Recognizance	O
to	O
appear	O
,	O
either	O
to	O
Prosecute	O
,	O
to	O
give	O
Evidence	O
or	O
to	O
Surrender	O
themselves	O
,	O
and	O
shall	O
neglect	O
so	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
that	O
their	O
Recognizances	O
be	O
Estreated	O
into	O
the	O
Exchequer	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
followeth	O
;	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death,12	O
William	B-pers
Gosling	I-pers
,	O
Anthony	B-pers
Cope	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Winship	I-pers
Mary	O
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Merrit	I-pers
alias	O
Wardon	O
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
Howard	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
alias	O
Guemes	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bickerton	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Post	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Gaulston	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand,14	O
John	B-pers
Amable	I-pers
,	O
Theodore	B-pers
Christopher	I-pers
Fabricius	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Granthem	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Solomon	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Guy	I-pers
alias	O
Keys	O
,	O
Stephen	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Claxton	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Westwood	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Stringer	I-pers
,	O
Williams	O
Earl	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Ash	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
The	O
9	O
last	O
formerly	O
Convicted	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
,	O
16	O
Alice	B-pers
Hurding	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Benfield	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
,	O
Zachariah	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
,	O
Philip	B-pers
Jersey	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	O
,	O
Taylor	O
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Annable	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dunn	I-pers
,	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Flemming	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Unwin	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Balph	I-pers
,	O
Harry	B-pers
Bealey	I-pers
.	O
Millicent	B-pers
Cloud	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
6.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Riggot	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Carrell	I-pers
,	O
Job	O
Orchard	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Headly	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Three	O
last	O
Formerly	O
Convicted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Read	I-pers
,	O
Fined	O
20	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
suffer	O
three	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Dexter	I-pers
Fined	I-pers
10	O
Marks	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Gowbert	I-pers
alias	O
Marchbank	O
,	O
Fined	O
20	O
Marks	O
and	O
to	O
Suffer	O
Three	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Merrit	I-pers
alias	O
Waldon	O
,	O
Hannab	O
