TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
,	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
1st	O
,	O
2d	O
,	O
3d	O
,	O
and	O
4th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
March	O
,	O
1720	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Seventh	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
FRYER	I-pers
,	O
Bart	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Powys	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Dormer	O
,	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
Names	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Coope	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Cornforth	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Conder	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Tredway	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Steed	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hodges	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Skin	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Ovin	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Fitzhugh	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Croucher	I-pers
,	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Chase	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Diston	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bush	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Cash	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Chad	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Southwood	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Chandler	I-pers
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Tomlinson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
William	B-pers
Claxton	I-pers
and	O
Frances	B-pers
Claxton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Christ-church	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
Ounce	O
of	O
Mace	O
,	O
1	O
Ounce	O
of	O
Nutmegs	O
,	O
half	O
a	O
Pound	O
of	O
Bohea	O
Tea	O
,	O
half	O
a	O
Pound	O
of	O
Chocolate	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
Pound	O
of	O
Citron	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
'	I-pers
Pledger	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
:	O
and	O
Frances	O
Claxton	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
William	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Mace	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Drawer	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
Dinner	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
Brother	O
,	O
who	O
sold	O
some	O
for	O
a	O
Penny	O
to	O
a	O
Woman	O
who	O
told	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
William	O
owned	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
though	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
on	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Confession	O
was	O
Read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
to	O
charge	O
his	O
Mother	O
(	O
Frances	O
)	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Westwood	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Brice	I-pers
and	O
Philip	B-pers
Brice	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Abchurch	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
6	O
dozen	O
of	O
Steal	O
Cork-Skrews	O
,	O
14	O
Ivory-Handle	O
Knives	O
and	O
Forks	O
,	O
14	O
Maple-Handle	O
Knives	O
,	O
and	O
Forks	O
,	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
Scissors	O
and	O
5	O
Horn	O
Snuff-Boxes	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
38	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Goodchild	I-pers
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
;	O
and	O
Philip	O
Brice	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
Knives	O
,	O
Forks	O
and	O
Scissors	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Ann	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Philip	O
came	O
after	O
her	O
as	O
a	O
Sweetheart	O
;	O
that	O
his	O
Wife	O
overhearing	O
her	O
bid	O
him	O
`	O
come	O
again	O
a	O
Sunday	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
something	O
else	O
;	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
search	O
'd	O
her	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
his	O
Cork	O
Skrews	O
and	O
Boxes	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
at	O
first	O
;	O
but	O
afterwards	O
confest	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
,	O
saying	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
wrong	O
'd	O
him	O
of	O
one	O
pennyworth	O
more	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
also	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
refused	O
to	O
tell	O
where	O
Philip	O
liv	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
at	O
last	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
search	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
House	O
(	O
he	O
being	O
an	O
Apprentice	O
)	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Knives	O
,	O
Forks	O
and	O
Scissors	O
in	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
Press	O
where	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
Clothes	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
Knives	O
and	O
Forks	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Press	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
then	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
at	O
her	O
Master	O
's	O
Door	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
sorry	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
bewitch	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
had	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Mark	O
on	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
swore	O
to	O
by	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Confessions	O
of	O
them	O
both	O
were	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
Notwith	O
standing	O
all	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Ann	O
on	O
her	O
Tryal	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
nor	O
how	O
the	O
Goods	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
her	O
Box	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Brice	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
from	O
her	O
at	O
her	O
Master	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
;	O
and	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Festrop	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
Carolus	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Spicer	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Fleet-street	B-place
about	O
one	O
a	O
Clock	O
the	O
Night	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Cloak	O
slipt	O
off	O
;	O
that	O
while	O
his	O
Hands	O
were	O
employ	O
'd	O
in	O
putting	O
it	O
on	O
again	O
,	O
she	O
pickt	O
his	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Fob	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
felt	O
her	O
Hand	O
under	O
his	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
seiz	O
'd	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
instant	O
;	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
search	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
call	O
out	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
brought	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Boddington	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
hearing	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
call	O
,	O
Watch	O
,	O
turn	O
'd	O
back	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
have	O
hold	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
pickt	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Two	O
Watchmen	O
corroberated	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
farther	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
common	O
Night-walker	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Hill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cotton	O
Handkerchief	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
;	O
and	O
2	O
Silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Linnen	O
ones	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
to	O
Billinsgate	B-place
his	O
Pocket	O
was	O
pickt	O
of	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
:	O
that	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Lad	O
lurking	O
about	O
under	O
the	O
Piazza	O
,	O
suspected	O
them	O
,	O
searcht	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
and	O
4	O
more	O
in	O
a	O
private	O
Pocket	O
behind	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
Boy	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
nor	O
called	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Olave	I-place
in	I-place
Hart-street	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
of	O
Alhallows	B-place
Barkin	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Walcraven	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
formerly	O
lodg	O
'd	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
about	O
4	O
Months	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
found	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
:	O
that	O
she	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
sent	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
by	O
her	O
Grandmother	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Page	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
that	O
Spoon	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
6	O
s.	O
on	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
told	O
her	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
Grandmother	O
's	O
The	O
Spoon	O
was	O
produced	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
:	O
and	O
her	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
wash	O
'd	O
and	O
scower	O
'd	O
for	O
her	O
living	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
intrusted	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
Spoon	O
produced	O
into	O
her	O
Bosom	O
unawares	O
:	O
she	O
called	O
none	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
her	O
Excuse	O
(	O
which	O
contradicted	O
her	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
)	O
had	O
been	O
true	O
,	O
she	O
ought	O
to	O
have	O
brought	O
it	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
to	O
have	O
pawned	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
500	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Iron	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
1718	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Pitts	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
black	O
Cloth	O
Coach-Seat	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Linnet	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Gate	O
with	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Coach-Seat	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
:	O
that	O
he	O
struck	O
up	O
his	O
Heels	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
his	O
Man	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
a	O
Funeral	O
with	O
a	O
Mourning	O
Coach	O
:	O
and	O
owned	O
the	O
Seat	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
ease	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Seat	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
But	O
that	O
poor	O
Excuse	O
not	O
availing	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Picket	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Woolnoth	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
,	O
stealing	O
3	O
Sheets	O
,	O
3	O
Shirts	O
,	O
2	O
Shifts	O
,	O
2	O
Holland	O
Necks	O
,	O
2	O
Suits	O
of	O
Headclothes	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
48	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lathymm	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
Lombard-Street	B-place
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
a	O
Clock	O
the	O
Night	O
aforesaid	O
with	O
his	O
Basket	O
of	O
Linnen	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stood	O
at	O
a	O
Bookseller	O
's	O
Shop-Door	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
It	O
's	O
no	O
matter	O
,	O
here	O
's	O
one	O
will	O
go	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
over	O
to	O
the	O
Stationer	O
's	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
the	O
Post-Office	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
for	O
Madam	O
Saunders	O
's	O
Scarlet	O
Ridinghood	O
:	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
a	O
Man	O
stood	O
ready	O
to	O
receive	O
his	O
Message	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
bring	O
a	O
Token	O
he	O
would	O
deliver	O
it	O
(	O
that	O
he	O
then	O
carried	O
his	O
Goods	O
with	O
him	O
)	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
back	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
(	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
who	O
sent	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
so	O
far	O
as	O
the	O
Oyl	O
Shop	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
then	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
his	O
Watch	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
Token	O
,	O
bidding	O
him	O
set	O
down	O
his	O
Goods	O
in	O
that	O
Shop	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
look	O
after	O
them	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
again	O
to	O
the	O
Stationer	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
there	O
the	O
Man	O
who	O
sent	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
Token	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
and	O
enquiring	O
of	O
the	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
for	O
Madam	O
Saunders	O
's	O
Ridinghood	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
knew	O
no	O
such	O
Person	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
him	O
that	O
sent	O
him	O
and	O
for	O
his	O
Goods	O
;	O
but	O
to	O
his	O
Great	O
Grief	O
and	O
surprise	O
,	O
could	O
find	O
neither	O
;	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
care	O
to	O
go	O
off	O
with	O
all	O
his	O
Linnen	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
3	O
l.	O
that	O
the	O
Watch	O
he	O
sent	O
by	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
Token	O
(	O
which	O
he	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
)	O
was	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Watch	O
,	O
such	O
as	O
are	O
commonly	O
sold	O
for	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
piece	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
3	O
d.	O
for	O
his	O
going	O
of	O
the	O
Errand	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
very	O
well	O
by	O
sight	O
having	O
seen	O
him	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
times	O
at	O
the	O
Black	O
Raven	O
,	O
in	O
Fetter	O
Lane	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
acquainted	O
his	O
Master	O
with	O
his	O
Loss	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
that	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
had	O
served	O
him	O
so	O
used	O
the	O
Raven	O
,	O
whereupon	O
his	O
Master	O
advised	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
sure	O
before	O
he	O
charged	O
any	O
body	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
should	O
ruine	O
an	O
innocent	O
Man	O
;	O
that	O
pursuant	O
to	O
him	O
Ac	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Raven	O
several	O
times	O
before	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
there	O
(	O
though	O
they	O
both	O
used	O
the	O
House	O
)	O
that	O
he	O
set	O
with	O
him	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
full	O
view	O
of	O
him	O
so	O
m	O
Hour	O
;	O
that	O
being	O
fully	O
,	O
satisfied	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
Person	O
,	O
he	O
enquired	O
after	O
his	O
Character	O
of	O
the	O
Man	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
eat	O
and	O
drank	O
well	O
,	O
paid	O
very	O
honestly	O
,	O
and	O
liv	O
'd	O
after	O
the	O
rate	O
of	O
200	O
l.	O
per	O
Annum	O
.	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
begg	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Taylor	O
who	O
keeps	O
the	O
Oylshop	O
,	O
and	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
at	O
the	O
Stationers	O
Shop	O
,	O
(	O
both	O
in	O
Lombard-street	O
,	O
)	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
Mr	O
.	O
Brewer	O
who	O
keeps	O
the	O
Black	O
Raven	O
,	O
corroborated	O
his	O
Evidence	O
in	O
what	O
respectively	O
related	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
confirmed	O
his	O
Wife	O
's	O
begging	O
to	O
make	O
up	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
denied	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
or	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
and	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
they	O
knew	O
no	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Staymaker	O
and	O
Coatmaker	O
,	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Workman	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
business	O
he	O
minded	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
his	O
Wife	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
industrious	O
Woman	O
,	O
made	O
Headclothes	O
for	O
the	O
Shops	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
15	O
or	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Week	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
sometimes	O
he	O
assisted	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Ambler	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
,	I-place
Dukes	I-place
Place	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Gown	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Best	I-pers
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
enquired	O
for	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
told	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
,	O
went	O
away	O
as	O
going	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
came	O
back	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
)	O
wanted	O
her	O
Ridinghood	O
to	O
come	O
home	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
sent	O
her	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
being	O
refused	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
her	O
Gown	O
sent	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
also	O
denied	O
,	O
she	O
snatch	O
'd	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
That	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
great	O
Intimacy	O
between	O
them	O
formerly	O
;	O
now	O
as	O
great	O
a	O
Jealousy	O
of	O
their	O
being	O
too	O
familiar	O
with	O
each	O
other	O
's	O
Husband	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
positively	O
swore	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Frederick	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Dionis	I-place
Backchurch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Forward	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Servant	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
to	O
warm	O
him	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
found	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Spoon	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Grant	O
sell	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
under	O
the	O
Shore	O
at	O
Deptford	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
suspecting	O
him	O
,	O
had	O
him	O
committed	O
Bridewell	O
on	O
suspicion	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
confest	O
he	O
stole	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
He	O
also	O
confest	O
it	O
on	O
his	O
Trial	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Gwin	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Godfrey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
Assaulting	O
Ann	B-pers
Parthyday	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
on	O
the	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Moidore	O
,	O
a	O
Jacobus	O
,	O
2	O
Silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
the	O
Standard	B-place
Tavern	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Minories	I-place
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
the	O
Night	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
Wood	O
kist	O
her	O
and	O
held	O
while	O
Godfrey	O
robb	O
'd	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
Wood	O
said	O
,	O
It	O
's	O
to	O
kill	O
her	O
,	O
it	O
's	O
enough	O
to	O
take	O
her	O
Money	O
;	O
or	O
else	O
God	O
would	O
have	O
kill	O
'd	O
her	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
knew	O
them	O
both	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
being	O
askt	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
her	O
Husband	O
who	O
they	O
were	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
her	O
till	O
he	O
went	O
Holland	O
and	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
being	O
with	O
her	O
in	O
Hounsditch	O
they	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
Persons	O
who	O
robb	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
advised	O
her	O
to	O
over	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
askt	O
Godfrey	O
what	O
satisfaction	O
she	O
must	O
have	O
for	O
her	O
Moidore	O
,	O
Jacobus	O
,	O
Money	O
and	O
Handkerchiefs	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
sold	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Handkerchiefs	O
for	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
18	O
d.	O
That	O
Wood	O
said	O
he	O
kist	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
took	O
nothing	O
from	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
told	O
her	O
of	O
it	O
before	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
and	O
Godfrey	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
arrested	O
him	O
for	O
20	O
s.	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
put	O
in	O
Bail	O
,	O
whereupon	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
make	O
a	O
40	O
l.	O
Man	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
swear	O
a	O
Robbery	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
called	O
the	O
following	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bites	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
sent	O
for	O
Godfrey	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
got	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
and	O
Arrested	O
him	O
for	O
20	O
s.	O
which	O
she	O
told	O
this	O
Evidence	O
was	O
for	O
paying	O
his	O
Reckonings	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
pay	O
the	O
Debt	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
make	O
a	O
40	O
l.	O
Man	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
varied	O
in	O
her	O
Evidence	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
bail	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
charged	O
a	O
Constable	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
Felony	O
:	O
but	O
this	O
Evidence	O
being	O
askt	O
whether	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
herself	O
say	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
make	O
40	O
l.	O
Man	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
answered	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Officer	O
say	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
sent	O
by	O
her	O
.	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Chamber	I-pers
's	O
deposed	O
being	O
present	O
when	O
her	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
)	O
Husband	O
askt	O
her	O
for	O
the	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
heard	O
her	O
answer	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
was	O
that	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
asking	O
her	O
why	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
the	O
Lives	O
of	O
the	O
Prisners	O
she	O
said	O
:	O
she	O
was	O
sorry	O
for	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
;	O
and	O
Godfrey	O
's	O
Mother	O
would	O
come	O
down	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
throw	O
in	O
a	O
Ig	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hutchins	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Husband	O
,	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
Room	O
to	O
enquire	O
if	O
she	O
knew	O
where	O
his	O
Wife	O
was	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
up	O
also	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
askt	O
her	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
answered	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
liked	O
better	O
than	O
to	O
be	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
was	O
become	O
of	O
the	O
2	O
Handkerchiefs	O
and	O
she	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
them	O
to	O
whom	O
she	O
liked	O
better	O
than	O
him	O
to	O
Cuckold	O
him	O
.	O
Phebe	B-pers
Peterson	I-pers
and	O
another	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
made	O
it	O
her	O
common	O
practice	O
to	O
arrest	O
People	O
for	O
small	O
Sums	O
to	O
get	O
Money	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
call	O
'd	O
again	O
and	O
owned	O
that	O
she	O
arrested	O
Godfrey	O
for	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
for	O
several	O
Reckonings	O
she	O
had	O
paid	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
lived	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Thomas	I-place
the	I-place
Apostle	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Cloth	O
Coats	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Cane	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Muslin	O
Turnover	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Barber	I-pers
;	O
and	O
60	O
pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
value	O
6	O
l	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stiles	I-pers
;	O
and	O
5	O
pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Hose	O
value	O
55	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
John	O
Barber	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Barber	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
on	O
liking	O
on	O
3d	O
of	O
January	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Apprentice	O
;	O
but	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
every	O
Night	O
without	O
his	O
Leave	O
he	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
)	O
would	O
not	O
bind	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Cane	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
then	O
owned	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
had	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
pawned	O
the	O
2	O
Coats	O
,	O
and	O
promised	O
to	O
help	O
him	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
the	O
Hose	O
again	O
;	O
but	O
afterwards	O
said	O
the	O
Man	O
who	O
had	O
them	O
was	O
gone	O
away	O
.	O
deposed	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
2	O
Coats	O
(	O
which	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
)	O
were	O
pawned	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
their	O
House	O
;	O
that	O
one	O
came	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
him	O
own	O
his	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
:	O
His	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
very	O
full	O
and	O
particular	O
,	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
however	O
on	O
his	O
Trial	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
had	O
no	O
Friends	O
to	O
appear	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
in	O
London	O
but	O
10	O
Weeks	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Yeomans	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Booth	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Hester	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
together	O
with	O
Ann	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
,	O
not	O
.	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
privately	O
steal	O
3	O
.	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Pearl	O
Snuff-Box	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Bulis	O
in	O
Hanging-Sword-Alley	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
out	O
was	O
met	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
another	O
House	O
and	O
staid	O
till	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
then	O
went	O
home	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
Yeoman	O
's	O
House	O
and	O
drank	O
Cherry	O
Brandy	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
his	O
Goods	O
in	O
their	O
Hands	O
several	O
times	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
pretty	O
much	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
sure	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
when	O
he	O
set	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
below	O
Stairs	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
took'em	O
from	O
him	O
:	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
when	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
said	O
that	O
Ross	O
had	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
all	O
had	O
them	O
in	O
their	O
Hands	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
they	O
must	O
be	O
amongst	O
them	O
.	O
Two	O
of	O
the	O
Warders	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
deposed	O
that	O
Yeomans	O
kept	O
a	O
Bawdy	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Bennet	O
lived	O
there	O
.	O
Yeomans	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Bennet	O
lodged	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
drinking	O
together	O
at	O
the	O
next	O
House	O
at	O
2	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
ask	O
Bennet	O
to	O
come	O
home	O
;	O
when	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
her	O
Husband	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
just	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
told	O
Bennet	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
her	O
Husband	O
she	O
might	O
take	O
him	O
home	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
would	O
go	O
up	O
and	O
throw	O
the	O
Stocking	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
of	O
their	O
coming	O
home	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
,	O
of	O
Alhallows	B-place
Staining	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
30	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Drawer	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
also	O
confest	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
on	O
his	O
Tryal	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Katharine	I-place
Coleman	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Faro	I-pers
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
2	O
Coats	O
a	O
Wastcoat	O
4	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
and	O
2	O
linnen	O
Bags	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
Faro	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Trunk	O
,	O
a	O
Stuft	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Hester	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
lockt	O
their	O
Door	O
last	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
came	O
back	O
about	O
9	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
found	O
their	O
Door	O
broke	O
and	O
their	O
Goods	O
gone	O
.	O
Hester	O
Evans	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
left	O
her	O
Trunk	O
of	O
Clothes	O
at	O
her	O
Uncle	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
and	O
her	O
things	O
gone	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Field	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Trantum	I-pers
,	O
Dick	B-pers
Trantum	I-pers
and	O
himself	O
committed	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
that	O
John	O
Trantum	O
broke	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
Trunk	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
carried	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Glanister	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
all	O
for	O
40	O
s.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
Accquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Rex	I-pers
and	O
Amy	B-pers
Parrot	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
28	O
yards	O
of	O
Venetian	O
Poplin	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Bavell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Neal	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Wooden	O
Snuff	O
Box	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
2	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
and	O
12	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Whitburn	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pickt	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
run	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
White-House	B-place
Inn	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
asleep	O
pickt	O
his	O
Money	O
and	O
Snuff-Box	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
but	O
her	O
pulling	O
off	O
the	O
last	O
Ring	O
from	O
his	O
Finger	O
waked	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
secured	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
gave	O
the	O
Snuff-Box	O
to	O
the	O
Watchman	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
dropt	O
6	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
1/2	O
.	O
which	O
the	O
Watchman	O
pickt	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
pawned	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Rings	O
at	O
the	O
Compter	O
for	O
5	O
s.	O
that	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
prosecute	O
her	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
his	O
Rings	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
confirmed	O
her	O
dropping	O
the	O
Money	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
received	O
the	O
Snuff-Box	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
)	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
in	I-place
Foster-Lane	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
5	O
Silver	O
Sword-Hilts	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
4	O
Silver	O
Handles	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
James	O
Smith	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Robinson	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
Smith	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
confest	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
on	O
his	O
Tryal	O
;	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
:	O
It	O
also	O
appeared	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
told	O
his	O
Man	O
had	O
sold	O
Goods	O
to	O
Smith	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
readily	O
owned	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
very	O
freely	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
discover	O
the	O
Matter	O
;	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
full	O
value	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
Robinson	O
to	O
be	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
broke	O
and	O
some	O
without	O
a	O
Mark	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
James	O
Smith	O
but	O
Robinson	O
's	O
Confession	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
found	O
Robinson	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
38	O
s.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Dennis	B-pers
Connel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wix	I-pers
;	O
for	O
that	O
William	B-pers
Hargrove	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
Assault	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
Wix	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
1	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
drawn	O
Sword	O
in	O
the	O
Left	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Body	O
near	O
the	O
Short-Ribs	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
6	O
Inches	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
Dennis	B-pers
Connel	I-pers
being	O
present	O
did	O
Aid	O
,	O
Comfort	O
,	O
Assist	O
,	O
and	O
Abett	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
Hargrove	O
in	O
committing	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
Thomas	O
Wix	O
(	O
the	O
Deceased	O
)	O
and	O
William	O
Hargrove	O
were	O
drinking	O
together	O
very	O
early	O
in	O
a	O
Friendly	O
manner	O
the	O
Morning	O
aforesaid	O
at	O
Mr	O
.	O
Bent	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
Peterborough	O
Court	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
quartern	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
together	O
about	O
6	O
a	O
Clock	O
.	O
That	O
about	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
minutes	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
they	O
heard	O
a	O
Man	O
was	O
kill	O
'd	O
in	O
Raquet-Court	B-place
in	I-place
Fleet-street	I-place
;	O
which	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
Mr.	O
Wix	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Hargrove	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
Evidence	O
to	O
fix	O
the	O
Charge	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Browning	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
in	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Shirts	O
and	O
2	O
Brass	O
Handle	O
Swords	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
36	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
.	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
by	O
the	O
same	O
Name	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tooth	O
Pick	O
Case	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
le	I-pers
Bass	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Le	O
Bass	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Cook	O
's	O
Sister	O
,	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
them	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictments	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Dunnington	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
at	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Saw	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Bradbury	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
at	O
Work	O
in	O
,	O
Garden-Alleys	B-place
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
askt	O
for	O
Business	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Saw	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Queen	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Jame	I-place
's	I-place
at	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
an	O
Iron	O
Chain	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Streak	O
of	O
a	O
Coach	O
Wheel	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Wire	O
Male	O
value	O
5	O
s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Brew-house	O
for	O
Grains	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Son	O
seeing	O
the	O
Chain	O
hang	O
out	O
at	O
a	O
Pattin-maker	O
's	O
,	O
he	O
askt	O
him	O
who	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
fuddled	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
lying	O
without	O
the	O
Gate	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gordon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
in	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
an	O
Iron	O
Tool	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Delowe	I-pers
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Glass-House	O
to	O
warm	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Iron	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
follow	O
'd	O
,	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
it	O
on	O
his	O
shoulder	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Forster	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Norton	B-place
Falgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
32	O
Yards	O
of	O
Garlick	O
Holland	O
value	O
24	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Patterson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
in	O
his	O
Compting-house	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Servant	O
behind	O
a	O
Pile	O
of	O
Goods	O
marking	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
supposing	O
no	O
body	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
,	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
piece	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
said	O
Pile	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
followed	O
and	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
two	O
Masters	O
he	O
had	O
workt	O
with	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White-Chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
5	O
Guineas	O
and	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Atwell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Lion	O
and	O
Lamb	O
in	O
Gun-Alley	O
with	O
another	O
Creature	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
she	O
halled	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Alehouse	O
to	O
her	O
Quarters	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
Breeches	O
under	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Nurse	O
lockt	O
them	O
in	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
but	O
not	O
so	O
drunk	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
feel	O
her	O
take	O
his	O
Breeches	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
from	O
25	O
l.	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
a	O
Rag	O
.	O
Being	O
askt	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
acquainted	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lain	O
with	O
her	O
before	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
with	O
her	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Gravel-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
time	O
upon	O
Saltpetre-Bank	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
has	O
a	O
Husband	O
.	O
Being	O
askt	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
have	O
so	O
much	O
Money	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
Words	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
in	O
a	O
Huff	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
while	O
she	O
went	O
for	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Drink	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
lay	O
with	O
the	O
Nurse	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Levy	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Jane	B-pers
Cummins	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Pocket	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Bag	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
27	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
in	I-place
White-Chappel	I-place
,	O
were	O
Indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Kettle	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Humphreys	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Day	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
opened	O
her	O
House	O
(	O
the	O
Kings	B-place
Arms	I-place
in	I-place
White-Chappel	I-place
)	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
in	O
about	O
Noon	O
and	O
staid	O
till	O
8	O
at	O
Night	O
;	O
that	O
Fletcher	O
was	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
Pot	O
going	O
towards	O
White-Chappel-Fields	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
back	O
her	O
Apron	O
was	O
all	O
crockt	O
on	O
the	O
Inside	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Walker	O
,	O
who	O
staid	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Fletcher	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Beau	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Katharine	B-pers
Pars	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Smith	I-pers
;	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
in	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
Jones	O
and	O
Beau	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
3	O
Silver	O
Snuff-Boxes	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Crags	I-pers
;	O
and	O
Katharine	O
Smith	O
,	O
(	O
together	O
with	O
Roberts	B-pers
Pars	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
her	O
Husband	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
Jones	O
and	O
Bean	O
with	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Askew	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop-Window	O
;	O
that	O
Jones	O
thrust	O
his	O
Hand	O
into	O
the	O
Glass	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
Elizabeth	O
Askew	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
Smith	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
that	O
Katharine	O
Smith	O
received	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Husband	O
paid	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Children	O
were	O
disguised	O
next	O
Day	O
and	O
sent	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
that	O
if	O
they	O
could	O
get	O
nothing	O
there	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Market	O
,	O
and	O
bring	O
home	O
a	O
Fowl	O
or	O
two	O
;	O
that	O
Smith	O
keeps	O
3	O
Children	O
of	O
her	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
others	O
on	O
purpose	O
to	O
go	O
a	O
Thieving	O
.	O
Their	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
wherein	O
Jones	O
confest	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
Boxes	O
,	O
and	O
Beau	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
5	O
s.	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
but	O
was	O
got	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
stealing	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Katherine	O
Smith	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
never	O
had	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
help	O
what	O
her	O
Husband	O
did	O
;	O
but	O
Askew	O
deposed	O
positively	O
that	O
she	O
received	O
them	O
of	O
her	O
first	O
of	O
all	O
,	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
her	O
Pocket	O
Apron	O
,	O
then	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
saying	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
dispose	O
of	O
them	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
being	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
acquitted	O
Beau	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Jones	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
Katharine	O
Pars	O
alias	O
Smith	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
both	O
.	O
Vincent	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
at	I-place
Hackney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bell	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
9	O
Iron	O
Hoops	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Basket	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Ganen	I-pers
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Water	O
Tub	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
fourth	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
in	O
taking	O
the	O
Handle	O
of	O
a	O
Pump	O
fixt	O
to	O
a	O
Freehold	O
.	O
The	O
three	O
first	O
Indictments	O
being	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
:	O
and	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Humphry	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
and	O
Ann	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
in	I-place
Westminster	I-place
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
5	O
Window	O
Curtains	O
,	O
4	O
Bed	O
Curtains	O
and	O
Vallains	O
,	O
2	O
Sheets	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Blankets	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
by	O
her	O
Husband	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Humphrey	O
Jones	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
in	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Planes	O
1	O
Ax	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Church	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
It	O
Appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stole	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
an	O
empty	O
House	O
between	O
4	O
and	O
5	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
the	O
Watch	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Rouse	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
stealing	O
6	O
Yards	O
of	O
Silver	O
Fringe	O
value	O
12	O
l.	O
and	O
2	O
Yards	O
of	O
Silver	O
Lace	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Pinnock	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
a	O
rich	O
Chariot	O
for	O
my	O
Lord	O
Craven	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
hired	O
to	O
set	O
up	O
to	O
watch	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
about	O
10	O
Nights	O
,	O
then	O
cut	O
out	O
the	O
Fringe	O
and	O
Lace	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
upon	O
his	O
Trail	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Shop	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Lindsey	I-pers
and	O
Ann	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
in	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
James	B-pers
Gibbs	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
1	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
,	O
2	O
Necks	O
,	O
2	O
Neckcloths	O
,	O
4	O
Turnovers	O
,	O
and	O
15	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
just	O
come	O
from	O
Richmond	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Ann	B-pers
Lindsey	I-pers
in	O
Grays-Inn	O
Lane	O
,	O
who	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
good	O
Ale	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
him	O
up	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
,	O
Dick	O
;	O
telling	O
him	O
he	O
need	O
not	O
fear	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
for	O
Dick	O
was	O
but	O
a	O
Boy	O
of	O
6	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
;	O
but	O
instead	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
Youth	O
,	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
knockt	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
him	O
,	O
while	O
she	O
took	O
his	O
Shirt	O
off	O
his	O
Back	O
and	O
rifled	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Ann	B-pers
Lindsey	I-pers
advised	O
her	O
Husband	O
to	O
cut	O
his	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
)	O
Throat	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
in	O
Rose	O
and	O
Crown	O
Court	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
about	O
10	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
a	O
Bed	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
got	O
up	O
they	O
found	O
a	O
Shirt	O
and	O
a	O
Glove	O
in	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
swore	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Richard	O
he	O
had	O
but	O
2	O
Shirts	O
,	O
one	O
on	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
clean	O
on	O
the	O
Drawers	O
to	O
go	O
on	O
Guard	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
clean	O
Shirt	O
on	O
the	O
Drawers	O
besides	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
had	O
on	O
and	O
a	O
Third	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Bed	O
.	O
The	O
Watchman	O
confirmed	O
the	O
Constable	O
's	O
Evidence	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
that	O
what	O
the	O
Woman	O
did	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Presence	O
of	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Richard	O
Lindsey	O
Guilty	O
for	O
felony	O
only	O
.	O
Transportation	O
John	B-pers
Shouel	I-pers
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
4	O
Plates	O
,	O
4	O
Dishes	O
,	O
2	O
Porringers	O
,	O
1	O
Pewter	O
Bason	O
,	O
a	O
Looking-Glass	O
and	O
1	O
Brass	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hooper	I-pers
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
felo	O
niously	O
stealing	O
an	O
Anchor	O
of	O
a	O
Ship	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Trigg	I-pers
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
Indictment	O
were	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
Ship	B-place
lying	I-place
at	I-place
Union-Stairs	I-place
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Accomplices	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
handed	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Ship	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
them	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
His	O
Confession	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
Ship	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
sound	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cane	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Savoy	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Personof	O
Richard	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
Which	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hubbard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Pulps	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
the	O
Shoes	O
off	O
his	O
Shop-board	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
5	O
Saws	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Abraham	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Vernew	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
at	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
24	O
Yards	O
of	O
Silk	O
value	O
48	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Lewis	B-pers
Malecot	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Journeyman	O
and	O
workt	O
and	O
lay	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
took	O
a	O
Candle	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
as	O
going	O
to	O
Bed	O
;	O
that	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
after	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
that	O
one	O
going	O
to	O
shut	O
the	O
Door	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
bid	O
her	O
not	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
again	O
presently	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
have	O
something	O
under	O
his	O
Coat	O
;	O
that	O
soon	O
after	O
his	O
Shop-mate	O
going	O
up	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Work	O
cutout	O
and	O
gone	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
apprehended	O
him	O
about	O
a	O
Week	O
after	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
why	O
he	O
absented	O
himself	O
,	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
discharged	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
being	O
paid	O
to	O
his	O
Content	O
he	O
kept	O
away	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
overpaid	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
promised	O
the	O
next	O
Week	O
's	O
Work	O
should	O
make	O
amends	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Barter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
to	O
Wife	O
Sarah	B-pers
Cruse	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
his	O
former	O
Wife	O
Sarah	B-pers
Armiger	I-pers
being	O
then	O
alive	O
.	O
Both	O
Marriages	O
were	O
fully	O
proved	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
them	O
on	O
his	O
Trial	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Giles	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Charles	I-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
6	O
Yards	O
of	O
Muslin	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
her	O
Window	O
was	O
broke	O
and	O
a	O
bundle	O
of	O
Muslin	O
taken	O
out	O
about	O
8	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
to	O
the	O
Day	O
but	O
believed	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Reading	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
himself	O
committed	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
held	O
the	O
Door	O
whilst	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
broke	O
the	O
Glass	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Norman	I-pers
in	O
Newtoner	O
's	O
Lane	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
his	O
Share	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
Evidence	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cryer	I-pers
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Hawks	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Gile	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Blackburn	I-pers
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
steal	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
his	O
Wife	O
about	O
7	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
having	O
made	O
his	O
Door	O
fast	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
afterwards	O
,	O
saw	O
a	O
Light	O
in	O
his	O
Bed-Chamber	O
,	O
found	O
his	O
Door	O
broke	O
,	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
a	O
Voice	O
as	O
Men	O
talking	O
above	O
Stairs	O
,	O
ask	O
'd	O
who	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
whereupon	O
came	O
down	O
Stairs	O
immediately	O
,	O
Hawks	O
foremost	O
with	O
a	O
Candle	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
followed	O
them	O
;	O
crying	O
out	O
stop	O
Thief	O
;	O
and	O
was	O
told	O
by	O
a	O
Woman	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
gone	O
down	O
an	O
Alley	O
,	O
he	O
pursued	O
and	O
found	O
Cryer	O
getting	O
over	O
the	O
Wall	O
of	O
the	O
Quakers	O
Burying	O
Ground	O
in	O
Bunhill-Fields	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
full	O
View	O
of	O
them	O
as	O
they	O
came	O
down	O
Stairs	O
by	O
the	O
Light	O
of	O
their	O
own	O
Candle	O
and	O
one	O
which	O
he	O
himself	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sure	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
the	O
same	O
Persons	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
heard	O
somebody	O
cry	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
that	O
Cryer	O
ran	O
down	O
the	O
Alley	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
no	O
Thoroughfare	O
,	O
bidding	O
him	O
make	O
haste	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
would	O
get	O
over	O
the	O
Wall	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Omens	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
Cryer	O
taken	O
getting	O
over	O
the	O
Wall	O
.	O
Hawks	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
a	O
Noise	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Alehouse	O
where	O
Cryer	O
was	O
carried	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
that	O
Cryer	O
wanted	O
somebody	O
to	O
go	O
for	O
his	O
Friends	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
there	O
being	O
willing	O
,	O
he	O
undertook	O
to	O
go	O
for	O
his	O
Wife	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
with	O
her	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
whither	O
he	O
followed	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
at	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
carried	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
;	O
but	O
none	O
appeared	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
called	O
again	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Alehouse	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
Sight	O
of	O
Hawks	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
he	O
knew	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
secured	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Beaul	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Handy	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
in	I-place
Whitchapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
12	O
pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
value	O
24	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
lost	O
12	O
pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
on	O
Saturday	O
in	O
November	O
last	O
;	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
being	O
sick	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
she	O
mist	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Courland	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
himself	O
,	O
committed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
carried	O
the	O
Goods	O
over	O
the	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
6	O
pair	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
Katharine	O
Speed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
6	O
pair	O
to	O
another	O
Person	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Cotterel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
in	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
7	O
pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
half	O
Hundred	O
Weight	O
of	O
Lead	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Roger	B-pers
Walrond	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
December	O
1718	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
lost	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
knew	O
not	O
how	O
many	O
nor	O
when	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Courland	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
himself	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
pawned	O
2	O
pair	O
that	O
Night	O
for	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
sold	O
the	O
other	O
5	O
pair	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
.	O
Roger	B-pers
Walrond	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
several	O
Weights	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
:	O
John	B-pers
Courland	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
himself	O
took	O
a	O
half	O
Hundred	O
Weight	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Daffey	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Mosely	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hampstead	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Johnquit	I-pers
le	I-pers
Peen	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
20	O
Flasks	O
of	O
Claret	O
,	O
4	O
Flasks	O
of	O
Sack	O
,	O
1	O
Brass	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Stockings	O
and	O
200	O
Guineas	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wilcox	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
16	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
,	I-pers
Bacchus	I-pers
,	O
Junior	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
in	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Wheatley	I-pers
,	O
by	O
beating	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Staff	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
Face	O
and	O
Body	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
:	O
whereby	O
he	O
received	O
several	O
Bruises	O
and	O
a	O
Contusion	O
;	O
of	O
which	O
Beating	O
,	O
Bruising	O
and	O
Contusion	O
he	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
January	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Wheatley	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
and	O
her	O
Husband	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
Bed	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
knockt	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
open	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
forced	O
in	O
,	O
knockt	O
down	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
beat	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
Stick	O
,	O
dragg	O
'd	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
down	O
the	O
Stairs	O
:	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
by	O
the	O
Physicians	O
and	O
Surgeons	O
that	O
he	O
died	O
of	O
an	O
ill	O
State	O
of	O
Body	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
no	O
Bruises	O
or	O
Contusion	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
opened	O
;	O
but	O
4	O
large	O
Imposthumations	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
Lungs	O
gone	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Smithers	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Smithurst	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
2	O
Books	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Illidge	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
March	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
loitering	O
about	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
pretending	O
to	O
read	O
a	O
Book	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
those	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
immediately	O
followed	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Man	O
(	O
whom	O
he	O
struck	O
with	O
them	O
on	O
his	O
Breast	O
)	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Grace	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Katharine	I-place
by	I-place
the	I-place
Tower	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Silver	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
23	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cofferon	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
:	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
Fit	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
help	O
her	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
pretending	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
to	O
fetch	O
her	O
something	O
to	O
smell	O
to	O
,	O
laid	O
a	O
Guinea	O
of	O
it	O
over	O
her	O
own	O
Door	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
afterwards	O
found	O
by	O
her	O
Direction	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lockwood	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Logwood	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Christian	B-pers
Hurst	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
;	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
Chain	O
,	O
and	O
Seal	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
:	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Red-Cross-street	O
he	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Hurst	O
,	O
who	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
hand	O
her	O
over	O
the	O
Kennel	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
askt	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
to	O
Logwood	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
where	O
Hurst	O
pickt	O
his	O
Pocket	O
of	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
Man	O
that	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
hearing	O
a	O
Noise	O
of	O
other	O
Men	O
below	O
Stairs	O
was	O
afraid	O
they	O
might	O
murder	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
made	O
many	O
Words	O
;	O
so	O
went	O
away	O
:	O
But	O
being	O
askt	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
Logwood	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
advised	O
to	O
take	O
her	O
up	O
as	O
Landlady	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
both	O
confest	O
(	O
when	O
in	O
Custody	O
)	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
which	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
advance	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
Two	O
other	O
Evidences	O
deposed	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
heard	O
them	O
confess	O
as	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Hurst	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
another	O
Man	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
live	O
in	O
Hand	O
Alley	O
in	O
Golden-Lane	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
an	O
ill	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
against	O
Logwood	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Christian	O
Hurst	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Callicoe	O
Petticoat	O
value	O
12	O
s	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Eagleston	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
:	O
Mary	B-pers
Eagleston	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
lost	O
her	O
Petticoat	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
at	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Compton	I-pers
's	O
who	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
Mountjoy	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
she	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
,	O
Laurence	B-pers
Waldren	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
at	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Humphreys	I-pers
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
Sheets	O
,	O
a	O
Drugget	O
Coat	O
and	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Bodice	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
and	O
Stockings	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Peter	O
Humphreys	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Felony	O
;	O
and	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
that	O
;	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Field	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
at	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
Apron	O
,	O
1	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
2	O
Hair	O
Brooms	O
,	O
and	O
1	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evi	O
dence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Sherwood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
,	O
2	O
Shifts	O
,	O
2	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
John	B-pers
Chaunc	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Lewis	B-pers
Elliot	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White	I-place
Chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indict	O
for	O
feloniously	O
,	O
stealing	O
10	O
Silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Pert	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Leever	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Paul	I-place
at	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
that	O
whereas	O
Otherinton	O
Wrathan	O
was	O
convicted	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
100	O
Yards	O
of	O
Sail	O
Cloth	O
called	O
English	O
Duck	O
,	O
value	O
90	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hide	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
:	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
Richard	O
Leever	O
did	O
receive	O
pieces	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Mandevil	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
having	O
been	O
a	O
stir	O
made	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
10	O
bolts	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Cloth	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
White	O
Horse	O
at	O
Limus	O
;	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
Capt	O
Hide	O
's	O
Cloth	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Marks	O
and	O
Seals	O
were	O
cut	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
Yards	O
wanting	O
in	O
each	O
Bolt	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Maker	O
's	O
mark	O
was	O
left	O
:	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
that	O
were	O
left	O
and	O
had	O
cost	O
him	O
30	O
l.	O
to	O
bring	O
them	O
back	O
from	O
the	O
W	O
but	O
refused	O
to	O
tell	O
by	O
whom	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
had	O
rather	O
suffer	O
himself	O
,	O
than	O
betray	O
his	O
Friend	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Sm	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
April	O
about	O
9	O
or	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
to	O
the	O
Necessary	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
staid	O
him	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
he	O
found	O
4	O
Bolts	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
Lacey	O
bring	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Wrat	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
them	O
both	O
Money	O
part	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Beale	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
there	O
w	O
Smith	O
,	O
confirmed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
staying	O
him	O
from	O
going	O
the	O
Vault	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
giving	O
Lacey	O
and	O
Wratham	O
Mon	O
William	B-pers
Wratham	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prison	O
telling	O
him	O
what	O
a	O
sad	O
thing	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
in	O
buying	O
th	O
things	O
of	O
his	O
Son	O
and	O
not	O
telling	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
:	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
sorry	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
bu	O
Guinea	O
a	O
piece	O
.	O
Another	O
deposed	O
that	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Go	O
were	O
worth	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
piece	O
,	O
someworth	O
more	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Dol	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
himself	O
talking	O
together	O
Bell-Wharf	O
in	O
Shadwell	O
,	O
of	O
buying	O
and	O
selling	O
Run	O
stolen	O
Goods	O
,	O
he	O
advised	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
against	O
it	O
,	O
tel	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
dangerous	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
th	O
was	O
a	O
Fool	O
to	O
advise	O
him	O
against	O
it	O
;	O
for	O
if	O
he	O
Goods	O
before	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
buy	O
them	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
by	O
it	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
that	O
he	O
knowingly	O
bought	O
stoled	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
called	O
the	O
following	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Leever	I-pers
deposed	O
Lacey	O
brought	O
some	O
Sail-Cloth	O
to	O
her	O
Father	O
's	O
House	O
about	O
8	O
Months	O
ago	O
at	O
3	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
askt	O
her	O
Father	O
to	O
buy	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
refusing	O
,	O
Lacey	O
sold	O
it	O
as	O
a	O
Sea-fairing-Man	O
for	O
at	O
21	O
s.	O
a	O
piece	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
Heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
examine	O
some	O
Men	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
Cloth	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
their	O
Master	O
was	O
going	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
Money	O
.	O
He	O
also	O
called	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
askt	O
,	O
acknowledged	O
that	O
he	O
dealt	O
in	O
small	O
Run	O
Goods	O
,	O
like	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
his	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
stolen	O
Goods	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
knew	O
of	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
askt	O
why	O
he	O
stopt	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
from	O
going	O
to	O
his	O
Necessary	O
House	O
,	O
said	O
that	O
a	O
Master	O
of	O
a	O
Ship	O
had	O
some	O
Business	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
at	O
his	O
Back-Door	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cobidge	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pancras	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Thomas	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High-Way	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Stephen	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High-Way	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
8s	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Morris	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
by	O
4	O
Foot	O
Pads	O
about	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
a	O
Clock	O
the	O
Evening	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
past	O
him	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
good	O
Night	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
seizing	O
on	O
his	O
Friend	O
Smith	O
who	O
was	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
back	O
to	O
his	O
Assistance	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
clapt	O
two	O
Pistols	O
to	O
his	O
Breast	O
.	O
Stephen	O
Smith	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
4	O
Men	O
set	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
held	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
his	O
Head	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
8	O
s.	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
beat	O
him	O
sadly	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Reading	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Shaw	O
,	O
Dickinson	O
and	O
himself	O
did	O
the	O
Facts	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
18	O
d.	O
from	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
8	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
held	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
's	O
Nose	O
,	O
whilst	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
took	O
8	O
s.	O
from	O
him	O
:	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
when	O
taken	O
)	O
gave	O
him	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
shoot	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
thereby	O
might	O
make	O
his	O
Escape	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
hath	O
been	O
a	O
Thimble-man	O
,	O
or	O
Cups	O
and	O
Balls	O
Man	O
all	O
his	O
Life	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
in	I-place
Westmister	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
committing	O
a	O
Rape	O
on	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Susannah	B-pers
Gilman	I-pers
on	O
7th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
Susannah	O
Gilman	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mrs	O
Thomasin	O
Jones	O
in	O
Pulteney	B-place
Street	I-place
near	I-place
Golden	I-place
Square	I-place
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
the	O
Night	O
aforesaid	O
so	O
their	O
House	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
;	O
that	O
her	O
Mistress	O
being	O
at	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
's	O
hard	O
by	O
,	O
she	O
sent	O
his	O
Footman	O
to	O
call	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
laid	O
Violent	O
Hands	O
on	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
her	O
from	O
the	O
Parlour	O
into	O
Mistress	O
's	O
Bed	O
Chamber	O
,	O
that	O
in	O
so	O
doing	O
(	O
she	O
having	O
the	O
Candlestick	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
)	O
he	O
burnt	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
struggled	O
with	O
him	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
Breath	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
were	O
none	O
but	O
themselves	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
about	O
20	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
and	O
a	O
Virgin	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
afterwards	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
her	O
Mistress	O
came	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
)	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
on	O
Flote	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
askt	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
cry	O
out	O
when	O
her	O
Mistress	O
and	O
his	O
Servant	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
threarned	O
to	O
kill	O
her	O
If	O
she	O
told	O
her	O
Mistress	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
without	O
her	O
Headclothes	O
when	O
she	O
let	O
her	O
in	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Man	O
went	O
away	O
in	O
3	O
Minutes	O
after	O
her	O
Mistress	O
came	O
.	O
And	O
being	O
askt	O
several-Questions	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
answered	O
as	O
follows	O
:	O
That	O
her	O
Mistress	O
kept	O
a	O
Private	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
none	O
came	O
there	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Gentleman	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
how	O
long	O
it	O
was	O
before	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
for	O
a	O
Warrant	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
never	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
Chambers	O
after	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
never	O
demanded	O
Money	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
Newgate	O
twice	O
:	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
some	O
Money	O
:	O
Being	O
Shewn	O
an	O
Affidavit	O
sworn	O
before	O
a	O
Judge	O
,	O
and	O
signed	O
by	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
her	O
Hand-Writing	O
nor	O
she	O
never	O
was	O
before	O
a	O
Judge	O
:	O
being	O
shown	O
a	O
Release	O
signed	O
by	O
her	O
,	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
her	O
Hand	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
put	O
the	O
first	O
Warrant	O
into	O
the	O
Midwife	O
's	O
Hand	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
her	O
it	O
was	O
tore	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Maid	O
told	O
her	O
after	O
the	O
second	O
Warrant	O
granted	O
that	O
the	O
Justice	O
would	O
send	O
her	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
if	O
she	O
made	O
it	O
up	O
without	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Week	O
before	O
she	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
first	O
Warrant	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
Weeks	O
after	O
she	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
second	O
Warrant	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Jones	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
Sharrard-Street	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Servant	O
came	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
immediately	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
sent	O
him	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
for	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Drink	O
for	O
himself	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
rung	O
,	O
her	O
Door	O
was	O
opened	O
presently	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
setting	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
no	O
Disorder	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
her	O
Maid	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
)	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
had	O
hurt	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
askt	O
her	O
why	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
speak	O
of	O
it	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
:	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
half	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
coming	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
believed	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
two	O
Hours	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
several	O
times	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
before	O
:	O
That	O
she	O
saw	O
some	O
Disorder	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
and	O
Floor	O
too	O
:	O
And	O
being	O
askt	O
how	O
she	O
liv	O
'd	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
kept	O
a	O
House	O
of	O
Lodgers	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
House	O
was	O
all	O
lett	O
now	O
but	O
her	O
back	O
Parlour	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
kept	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
Mary	B-pers
Saunderson	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
3	O
Weeks	O
ago	O
Hannah	B-pers
Baily	I-pers
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
their	O
House	O
to	O
lodge	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sent	O
his	O
Footman	O
and	O
a	O
Cornchandler	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
(	O
Baily	O
)	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
)	O
to	O
Newgate	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
she	O
had	O
swore	O
a	O
Rape	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
a	O
Reputed	O
Bawdy-House	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
lie	O
with	O
any	O
Body	O
there	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
a	O
Clap	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
would	O
sooner	O
lose	O
his	O
Nose	O
than	O
take	O
Physick	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
of	O
St.	O
Giles	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Warrant	O
against	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
from	O
her	O
former	O
Mistress	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Brain	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Servant	O
brought	O
the	O
Warrant	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
a	O
Nobleman	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Jones	O
's	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
told	O
him	O
her	O
Mistress	O
was	O
hard	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
his	O
Servant	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
who	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
two	O
Minutes	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
went	O
down	O
Stairs	O
and	O
staid	O
with	O
his	O
Footman	O
2	O
Hours	O
,	O
made	O
no	O
Complaint	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
very	O
merry	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
2	O
Days	O
after	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
with	O
a	O
Message	O
from	O
her	O
Mistress	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
no	O
Complaint	O
then	O
,	O
neither	O
did	O
he	O
hear	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
till	O
a	O
Month	O
after	O
;	O
that	O
a	O
Woman	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Jones	O
's	O
Maid	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
Mrs	O
,	O
Jones	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
know	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
swore	O
a	O
Rape	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
advised	O
him	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
frequently	O
at	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
House	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
Tavern	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
never	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
molest	O
him	O
till	O
Friday	O
was	O
3	O
Weeks	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Holmes	O
at	O
the	O
Bedford-Head	O
Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
very	O
merry	O
together	O
,	O
but	O
differing	O
at	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
Words	O
arising	O
,	O
he	O
committed	O
him	O
to	O
Newgate	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Habeas	O
Corpas	O
being	O
brought	O
for	O
him	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
and	O
the	O
Justice	O
having	O
Notice	O
to	O
attend	O
the	O
Judge	O
that	O
allowed	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
accordingly	O
did	O
attend	O
;	O
and	O
shewed	O
the	O
Depositions	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Evidence	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
when	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
credibly	O
inform	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Justice	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Jones	O
had	O
frequent	O
Correspondence	O
with	O
her	O
:	O
And	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
Morning	O
last	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
House	O
under	O
the	O
pretence	O
of	O
a	O
Visit	O
,	O
leaving	O
a	O
Constable	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Street	O
with	O
a	O
Warrant	O
of	O
Felony	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
expected	O
Hour	O
in	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
Dennis	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
his	O
Master	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Jones	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
sent	O
him	O
for	O
her	O
Mistress	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
not	O
above	O
100	O
Yards	O
off	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
back	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
two	O
Minutes	O
,	O
sent	O
him	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
for	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
might	O
go	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Ketchen	O
and	O
drink	O
it	O
with	O
her	O
Maid	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
staid	O
two	O
Hours	O
there	O
,	O
made	O
a	O
Fire	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
gave	O
him	O
some	O
Bread	O
and	O
Cheese	O
,	O
was	O
very	O
merry	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
no	O
Complaint	O
.	O
That	O
3	O
Days	O
after	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
and	O
askt	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
went	O
into	O
his	O
Chamber	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
bed	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
a	O
Minute	O
,	O
nor	O
make	O
any	O
Complaint	O
then	O
.	O
That	O
his	O
Master	O
went	O
out	O
in	O
his	O
Chariot	O
as	O
usual	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
frequently	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
the	O
Justice	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Baily	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Jones	O
begg	O
'd	O
of	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
bring	O
her	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
Mrs.	O
Jones	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
what	O
's	O
the	O
Reason	O
you	O
ha	O
n't	O
been	O
here	O
?	O
you	O
must	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
persuaded	O
her	O
to	O
swear	O
a	O
Rape	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
get	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
it	O
her	O
self	O
and	O
get	O
10	O
Guineas	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
asking	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
could	O
pretend	O
to	O
go	O
on	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
having	O
neither	O
Money	O
not	O
Friends	O
,	O
she	O
answered	O
,	O
the	O
Justice	O
would	O
find	O
Money	O
and	O
be	O
her	O
Friend	O
.	O
That	O
Mrs	O
Jones	O
told	O
her	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
that	O
the	O
Justice	O
sent	O
to	O
know	O
why	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
and	O
prosecute	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
should	O
be	O
sent	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
if	O
she	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
saw	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
give	O
up	O
the	O
first	O
Warrant	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
General	O
Release	O
,	O
and	O
beg	O
Pardon	O
for	O
her	O
Imposition	O
,	O
and	O
receive	O
4	O
Guineas	O
.	O
A	O
Release	O
being	O
shewed	O
to	O
her	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
she	O
swore	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
sign	O
.	O
The	O
Release	O
was	O
proved	O
and	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Affidavit	O
before	O
a	O
Judge	O
,	O
wherein	O
she	O
begg	O
'd	O
pardon	O
for	O
her	O
Fault	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Jones	O
put	O
her	O
upon	O
it	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
was	O
read	O
also	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Mackworth	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
drew	O
the	O
Affidavit	O
,	O
read	O
it	O
over	O
to	O
her	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
made	O
it	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Powys	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
4	O
Guineas	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Goosetrey	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
went	O
to	O
Hicks	O
's	O
Hall	O
to	O
be	O
sworn	O
to	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
the	O
Justices	O
ordered	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Grand	O
Jury-men	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
for	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
swear	O
an	O
Indictment	O
for	O
a	O
Rape	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
if	O
her	O
Evidence	O
was	O
not	O
sufficient	O
to	O
find	O
it	O
Billa	O
Vera	O
,	O
to	O
lay	O
it	O
by	O
,	O
till	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
should	O
be	O
Evidence	O
enough	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Holmes	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
Justice	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bedford	O
Head	O
Tavern	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
5	O
Pints	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Words	O
arising	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
him	O
Justice	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
replyed	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
he	O
ever	O
did	O
Justice	O
in	O
his	O
Life	O
.	O
Whereupon	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
Justice	O
he	O
would	O
knock	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
commit	O
him	O
;	O
That	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
and	O
Watchmen	O
and	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
,	O
then	O
made	O
a	O
Mittimus	O
and	O
sent	O
him	O
to	O
Newgate	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
told	O
the	O
Justice	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
it	O
up	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
him	O
his	O
Warrant	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
delivered	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
Justice	O
Acknowledged	O
what	O
Mr.	O
Holmes	O
had	O
swore	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Usage	O
had	O
put	O
him	O
upon	O
his	O
Mettle	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
indeed	O
send	O
him	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
two	O
Affidavits	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
swore	O
to	O
and	O
signed	O
on	O
her	O
Examinations	O
before	O
,	O
wherein	O
she	O
positively	O
charged	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
sign	O
the	O
Release	O
and	O
Affidavit	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Money	O
paid	O
her	O
,	O
saw	O
her	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Mackworth	O
to	O
swear	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
her	O
ask	O
pardon	O
and	O
own	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Jones	O
and	O
her	O
Accomplices	O
had	O
put	O
her	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
never	O
lay	O
with	O
her	O
in	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Willis	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
her	O
Mother	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
but	O
a	O
very	O
indifferent	O
Character	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
but	O
a	O
Girl	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
swore	O
a	O
Rape	O
against	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
hearing	O
of	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
Mother	O
and	O
prevailed	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
a	O
Midwife	O
,	O
who	O
upon	O
searching	O
her	O
,	O
declared	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
an	O
impudent	O
Slut	O
:	O
And	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
owned	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
never	O
lay	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
looking	O
upon	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
Ordered	O
him	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
his	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Gilman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
in	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Box-Iron	O
,	O
20	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
10	O
Half	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Brain	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
1718	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Brain	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
her	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
lost	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
and	O
Box-Iron	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Baily	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
being	O
some	O
difference	O
between	O
Mrs.	O
Moss	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
and	O
consest	O
that	O
she	O
stole	O
the	O
Cup	O
,	O
a	O
Box	O
Iron	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Headclothes	O
from	O
her	O
Mistress	O
Brain	O
,	O
about	O
2	O
Years	O
ago	O
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Cup	O
to	O
sell	O
for	O
her	O
about	O
2	O
Years	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
half	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Mistress	O
's	O
Drawers	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
at	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
a	O
Gold	O
Seal	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Tortoise-shell	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Littleton	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Uncle	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
came	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
complaining	O
of	O
his	O
hard	O
Circumstances	O
he	O
relieved	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
kind	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
abroad	O
all	O
Day	O
together	O
at	O
several	O
places	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
Liquor	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
would	O
see	O
him	O
Home	O
in	O
a	O
Hackney-Coach	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
he	O
mist	O
his	O
Watch	O
;	O
that	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
he	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Martel	O
shewing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
for	O
Sale	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
look	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
opened	O
it	O
and	O
examined	O
all	O
the	O
Marks	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
an	O
Advertisement	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
caused	O
to	O
be	O
printed	O
and	O
distributed	O
among	O
the	O
Watch-makers	O
,	O
describing	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
offering	O
a	O
Reward	O
to	O
any	O
who	O
should	O
stop	O
Watch	O
or	O
Parry	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Martel	O
,	O
withal	O
asking	O
him	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
,	O
who	O
answered	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Martel	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
took	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
brought	O
the	O
Watch	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
saying	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
's	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
13	O
l.	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Tavern	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
a	O
Seal	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
kept	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
but	O
having	O
no	O
occasion	O
for	O
it	O
he	O
would	O
change	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
Ring	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Ring	O
of	O
15	O
s.	O
value	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
House	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
February	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
came	O
Home	O
about	O
10	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
in	O
a	O
Hackney	O
Coach	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
putting	O
his	O
Master	O
to	O
Bed	O
mist	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Master	O
missing	O
it	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
askt	O
him	O
after	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
his	O
Master	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
mist	O
it	O
over	O
Night	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
and	O
enquire	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
saying	O
no	O
Body	O
else	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
Company	O
that	O
Day	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
that	O
Morning	O
to	O
ask	O
how	O
his	O
Master	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
telling	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
concern	O
'd	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
Number	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
would	O
enquire	O
after	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
come	O
again	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
afterward	O
till	O
taken	O
:	O
John	B-pers
James	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
going	O
out	O
and	O
coming	O
home	O
together	O
as	O
before	O
mentioned	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
that	O
he	O
sold	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
and	O
Seal	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Martil	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
;	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
wash	O
'd	O
for	O
Mrs.	O
Mary	B-pers
White	I-pers
(	O
but	O
does	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
she	O
lodges	O
)	O
who	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
on	O
Shrove	O
Monday	O
,	O
and	O
askt	O
if	O
she	O
knew	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
a	O
Shilling	O
to	O
call	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
heard	O
her	O
say	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
promised	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
make	O
him	O
a	O
present	O
:	O
that	O
she	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
has	O
not	O
seen	O
her	O
since	O
:	O
Being	O
shown	O
the	O
Watch	O
and	O
Seal	O
in	O
Court	O
(	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
swore	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Martel	O
)	O
and	O
askt	O
if	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
Watch	O
and	O
Seal	O
Mrs.	O
White	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
Watch	O
again	O
,	O
nor	O
see	O
the	O
Seal	O
:	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
call	O
'd	O
again	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
Mrs.	O
White	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
neither	O
she	O
nor	O
no	O
other	O
Woman	O
had	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
that	O
Day	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
knew	O
he	O
lost	O
it	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
his	O
Watch	O
and	O
Seal	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Martel	O
being	O
call	O
'd	O
again	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Wife	O
was	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
to	O
persuade	O
him	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
only	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
:	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
so	O
piain	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Filewood	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Woodford	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
North	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Hinchman	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Whittle	I-pers
,	O
Jasper	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
Martin	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Dalton	I-pers
,	O
were	O
severally	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
New	O
Act	O
of	O
Parliament	O
for	O
the	O
more	O
effectual	O
Transporting	O
of	O
Felons	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
For	O
that	O
they	O
having	O
been	O
formerly	O
Convicted	O
of	O
divers	O
felonies	O
,	O
and	O
Transported	O
among	O
other	O
Convicts	O
from	O
Newgate	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
had	O
returned	O
into	O
Great	O
Brittain	O
without	O
any	O
lawful	O
Cause	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Bartholomew	I-pers
Earl	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
in	O
Conspiring	O
together	O
to	O
Forge	O
an	O
Affidavit	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Instrument	O
to	O
impose	O
on	O
the	O
Attorney-General	O
to	O
obtain	O
a	O
Noli	O
Prosequi	O
to	O
an	O
Indictment	O
for	O
a	O
Riot	O
,	O
Assault	O
and	O
Battery	O
against	O
Francis	B-pers
Buxton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
procuring	O
a	O
Person	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
;	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
deposed	O
.	O
that	O
Application	O
was	O
made	O
to	O
the	O
Attorney	O
General	O
for	O
a	O
Noli	O
Prosequi	O
;	O
who	O
asking	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
saying	O
he	O
must	O
see	O
him	O
first	O
,	O
Saunders	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
Sick	O
a	O
Bed	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
concerned	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Attorney	O
General	O
said	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
bring	O
an	O
Affidavit	O
and	O
Instrument	O
signed	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
granted	O
;	O
that	O
Saunders	O
brought	O
an	O
Affidavit	O
and	O
Agreement	O
,	O
and	O
obtained	O
a	O
Noli	O
Prosequi	O
thereby	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Instrument	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
shewn	O
him	O
)	O
was	O
none	O
of	O
his	O
signing	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
did	O
sign	O
any	O
for	O
a	O
Noli	O
Prosequi	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
sick	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
told	O
Earl	O
that	O
Saunders	O
was	O
not	O
employed	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
Earl	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
swear	O
a	O
Robbery	O
against	O
him	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
consent	O
to	O
a	O
Noli	O
Presequi	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
Earl	O
and	O
Saunders	O
went	O
together	O
to	O
the	O
Attorney	O
General	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
Warrant	O
.	O
The	O
Attorney	O
General	O
's	O
Warrant	O
for	O
a	O
Noli	O
Prosequi	O
,	O
so	O
