TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
'S	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Dallvery	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
MIDDLSEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
.	O
During	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
the	O
Rt	O
.	O
Honble	O
Sir	O
George	B-pers
Thorold	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
and	O
Baronet	O
,	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
6th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
'S	O
Reign	O
.	O
1720	O
.	O
LONDON	O
Printed	O
for	O
E.	O
Symon	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Pope	O
's	O
Head	O
Alley	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
by	O
M.	O
Jonur	O
,	O
against	O
St.	O
Sepul	O
ure	O
's	O
Back	O
Gate	O
in	O
Gilt	O
Spur	O
Street	O
,	O
near	O
Newgate	O
.	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
'S	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
,	O
ON	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
and	O
Monday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
13th	O
,	O
14th	O
,	O
and	O
16th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
January	O
,	O
1720	O
,	O
In	O
the	O
Seventh	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
'S	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
FRYER	I-pers
,	O
Bar	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	B-pers
Bury	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Powys	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Tracy	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Country	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
Names	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Appleby	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Woodrose	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Clifton	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Partington	I-pers
,	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Faulcon	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Shanks	I-pers
,	O
Joshua	B-pers
Walfree	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Short	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Leapidge	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Boswell	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Goodge	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wotton	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Richmond	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Goddard	I-pers
,	O
Percival	B-pers
Ludgate	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
John	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
2	O
Silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Prior	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
Aldersgate-Street	B-place
,	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
the	O
Night	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
draw	O
his	O
Handkerchiefs	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
laid	O
him	O
on	O
with	O
his	O
Cane	O
,	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
a	O
Pickpocket	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Handkerchiefs	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Burridge	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Handkerchiefs	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
not	O
near	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
stopt	O
but	O
calling	O
no	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
not	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
very	O
positive	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Terry	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Cornwall	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Olave	I-place
Hart-Street	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
5	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Russia	O
Yarn	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
and	I-pers
Richard	I-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
Second	O
time	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
20	O
Ells	O
of	O
Russia	O
Linnen	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Hobday	I-pers
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Bradford	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
employed	O
to	O
House	O
Merchants	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
employed	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
as	O
Porters	O
to	O
assist	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
being	O
informed	O
that	O
Terry	O
had	O
lockt	O
up	O
some	O
Goods	O
in	O
a	O
Cupboard	O
in	O
a	O
House	O
they	O
used	O
,	O
he	O
waited	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
concealed	O
till	O
Terry	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
Mr.	O
Hubday	O
's	O
piece	O
of	O
Linnen	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Cupboard	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
secured	O
him	O
:	O
that	O
Cornwall	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
Room	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Scane	O
of	O
Yarn	O
in	O
his	O
Breeches	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Fortune	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
perceiving	O
Cornwall	O
's	O
Apron	O
to	O
stick	O
out	O
,	O
suspected	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Scane	O
of	O
Yarn	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Breeches	O
.	O
Terry	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Cloth	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
to	O
lay	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
at	O
Night	O
to	O
fetch	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
stopt	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
told	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
enquir	O
'd	O
who	O
it	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
have	O
concealed	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
never	O
did	O
an	O
ill	O
thing	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
Cornwall	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
called	O
none	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Walter	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Peters	I-place
Cheap	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
1	O
Silver	O
Porringer	O
,	O
2	O
Silver	O
Mugs	O
,	O
2	O
Silver	O
Salvers	O
,	O
2	O
Silver	O
Salts	O
,	O
2	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
3	O
Gilt	O
Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Marrow	O
Spoon	O
,	O
6	O
Silver	O
Tea	O
Spoons	O
,	O
Tongs	O
and	O
Strainer	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tobacco	O
Box	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Orange-Strainer	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Candlesticks	O
and	O
Snuffers	O
,	O
3	O
Silver	O
Casters	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cruit-Frame	O
and	O
2	O
Cruit	O
Tops	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Bottle	O
Crain	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Stand	O
,	O
Pap-pan	O
and	O
Pap-spoon	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
with	O
his	O
Family	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
his	O
Servant	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
his	O
Parlour	O
Door	O
and	O
Bouffet	O
were	O
broke	O
open	O
and	O
his	O
Plate	O
gone	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
one	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
where	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Place	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
found	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Spoons	O
(	O
which	O
he	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
)	O
accordingly	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
his	O
Plate	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
Dover	O
in	O
Order	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
France	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
stopt	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
back	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
a	O
Particular	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Box	O
of	O
Plate	O
so	O
stopt	O
,	O
in	O
Writing	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
inspected	O
there	O
,	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
:	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
his	O
Servant	O
formerly	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
then	O
behaved	O
himself	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
had	O
Access	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
afterwards	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
and	O
being	O
askt	O
after	O
what	O
manner	O
he	O
committed	O
it	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
(	O
the	O
Door	O
being	O
open	O
)	O
about	O
4	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
himself	O
under	O
the	O
Cellar	O
Stairs	O
till	O
about	O
12	O
or	O
1	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Parlour-Door	O
,	O
and	O
Bouffet	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Olave	I-place
Silver-street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Velvet	O
Scarfe	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Hood	O
,	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Headclothes	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
a	O
Sattin	O
Mantle	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
7	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Brindley	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
Lodgings	O
the	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
just	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
askt	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Morris	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
answered	O
,	O
Yes	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
Mrs.	O
Morris	O
had	O
recommended	O
her	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
)	O
to	O
her	O
self	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
for	O
a	O
Midwife	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
askt	O
her	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Dish	O
of	O
Coffee	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
not	O
liking	O
that	O
Liquor	O
,	O
she	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
Drink	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
after	O
a	O
little	O
talk	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
her	O
business	O
;	O
that	O
presently	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
her	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
)	O
Grand	O
Daughter	O
by	O
her	O
Name	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
Betty	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
sent	O
Betty	O
to	O
the	O
Black	O
Bull	O
in	O
Wood-street	O
,	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
Mrs.	O
Sarah	O
the	O
Bar-keeper	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
of	O
the	O
Errand	O
robb	O
'd	O
her	O
Lodgings	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
That	O
afterwards	O
going	O
out	O
and	O
taking	O
her	O
Grand-Daughter	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
(	O
her	O
Grand-Daughter	O
)	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
ran	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
took	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Arm	O
and	O
secured	O
her	O
till	O
they	O
got	O
a	O
Constable	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
she	O
perceived	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
Suit	O
of	O
Headclothes	O
on	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Grand-Daughter	O
confirmed	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
farther	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
sure	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
Person	O
that	O
came	O
to	O
their	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
her	O
of	O
the	O
Errand	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Morris	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
Baker	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
's	O
Husband	O
)	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
was	O
Lighterman	O
,	O
and	O
Church-Warden	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
her	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
's	O
)	O
Husband	O
's	O
Countryman	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
take	O
Bread	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
after	O
some	O
Discourse	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
askt	O
her	O
who	O
was	O
her	O
Midwife	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
Child	O
of	O
her	O
14th	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
old	O
Midwife	O
was	O
Dead	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Brindley	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
)	O
was	O
her	O
Midwife	O
,	O
and	O
directed	O
her	O
where	O
she	O
liv	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
called	O
none	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
De	I-pers
Plosh	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
an	O
Iron	O
Tobacco-Box	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
lay	O
asleep	O
on	O
a	O
Butcher	O
's	O
Stall	O
between	O
2	O
and	O
3	O
a	O
Clock	O
the	O
Morning	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
Gloves	O
,	O
Hat	O
and	O
Tobacco-Box	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
off	O
his	O
Booots	O
,	O
which	O
waked	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
his	O
Gloves	O
and	O
Tobacco-Box	O
were	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
-	O
Werrey	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Common	O
Disturber	O
,	O
was	O
making	O
a	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
had	O
threatned	O
to	O
set	O
his	O
Uncle	O
's	O
House	O
on	O
Fire	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
secure	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
threatning	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
search	O
'd	O
him	O
for	O
fear	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
any	O
Pistols	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Box	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
Justice	O
deposed	O
that	O
one	O
Tyler	O
confest	O
before	O
him	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
himself	O
pickt	O
a	O
Man	O
's	O
Pocket	O
on	O
a	O
Butcher	O
's	O
Stall	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-Street	B-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
before	O
him	O
for	O
threatning	O
to	O
set	O
his	O
Uncle	O
's	O
House	O
on	O
Fire	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
kickt	O
the	O
Box	O
before	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
none	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
neither	O
could	O
be	O
give	O
any	O
Account	O
how	O
he	O
lived	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
,	O
a	O
Holland	O
Handkerchief	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Munsoe	I-pers
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
January	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Breeches	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Greening	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
Bishops-gate-Street	B-place
he	O
was	O
told	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
pickt	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Pocket	O
of	O
his	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
5	O
Handkerchiefs	O
about	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
owned	O
the	O
white	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
Marks	O
of	O
it	O
before	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transporation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mildred	I-place
in	I-place
Breadstreet	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Hide	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
3	O
Washing	O
Tubs	O
,	O
4	O
Bouls	O
,	O
a	O
Peck-Measure	O
,	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
a	O
Peck-Measure	O
,	O
5	O
Funnels	O
and	O
2	O
Wooden	O
Platters	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Browning	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
at	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Mag	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Camblet	O
Riding	O
Hood	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Science	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
about	O
a	O
Week	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
Mug	O
was	O
stopt	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
Confest	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
Master	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
being	O
sent	O
for	O
by	O
the	O
Goldsmith	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
owned	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
in	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
29	O
Snuff	O
Boxes	O
,	O
16	O
Tooth-pick-Cases	O
,	O
3	O
Womens	O
Equipages	O
,	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Pearl	O
Tossels	O
,	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Ear	O
Rings	O
,	O
30	O
Rings	O
,	O
12	O
pair	O
of	O
Gold	O
Buttons	O
,	O
8	O
Tweezer-Cases	O
,	O
9	O
pair	O
of	O
Gold	O
Buckles	O
,	O
8	O
Gold	O
Chains	O
,	O
17	O
Gold	O
and	O
Diamond	O
Rings	O
,	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Spurs	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
666	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Deard	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
found	O
his	O
Shop	O
broke	O
open	O
and	O
his	O
Goods	O
gone	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Custody	O
of	O
a	O
Constable	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
a	O
search	O
Warrant	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Lodging	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Shop	O
with	O
an	O
Augre	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
T.	O
Wix	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisner	O
bought	O
the	O
Augre	O
produced	O
,	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Lowen	I-pers
(	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
's	O
Servant	O
)	O
confirmed	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
by	O
the	O
Goldsmith	O
who	O
stopt	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
to	O
Search	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
Chest	O
of	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Mottier	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
sell	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
broken	O
Gold	O
Toys	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
having	O
heard	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
stopt	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
owned	O
them	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wilks	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Buttons	O
which	O
were	O
owned	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
wherein	O
he	O
owned	O
that	O
he	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
in	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
Requests	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
urged	O
that	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
privately	O
stealing	O
,	O
because	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
told	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
more	O
private	O
for	O
that	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
Shop	O
but	O
a	O
Stall	O
:	O
He	O
also	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
confessed	O
also	O
by	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Cranstone	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
at	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
4	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cable	O
value	O
15	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
her	O
Male	O
Bastard	O
Child	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Pain	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
complained	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
ill	O
of	O
the	O
Cholick	O
;	O
that	O
looking	O
about	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Child	O
in	O
the	O
Close-stool	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
no	O
Marks	O
of	O
Violence	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
believed	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
its	O
full	O
Growth	O
.	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
dead	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
thought	O
she	O
had	O
two	O
Months	O
longer	O
to	O
go	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
no	O
Marks	O
of	O
Violence	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
believed	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
Stilborn	O
.	O
-	O
Desbury	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
as	O
dying	O
;	O
helpt	O
her	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Midwife	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
wrap	O
it	O
in	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
Yes	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
Trunk	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
immediately	O
to	O
her	O
Trunk	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
found	O
Childbed	O
Linnen	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Way	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
finding	O
the	O
Childbed	O
Linnen	O
in	O
her	O
Trunk	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Bayley	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Mother	O
sent	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
her	O
Daughter	O
had	O
a	O
violent	O
Pain	O
of	O
the	O
Cholick	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
gentle	O
Purge	O
to	O
ease	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
heard	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
deliver	O
'd	O
of	O
a	O
Child	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Withers	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Savoy	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Pot	O
and	O
Cover	O
,	O
a	O
Brass	O
Sauce-Pan	O
,	O
a	O
Copper	O
Drinking	O
Pot	O
and	O
11	O
Yards	O
of	O
Camblet	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Bostock	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
John	O
Heath	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
but	O
gone	O
from	O
him	O
about	O
4	O
Months	O
,	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Roberts	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Tripp	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
lodged	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
went	O
thither	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
'd	O
all	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Roberts	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
hired	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
losing	O
some	O
small	O
things	O
went	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
her	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
carried	O
some	O
Goods	O
to	O
Tripp	O
's	O
,	O
gave	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
notice	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Tripp	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
as	O
her	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
Brass	O
Pot	O
and	O
Cover	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
for	O
a	O
Shilling	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
called	O
none	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Katharine	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
value	O
40	O
s	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Chain	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
value	O
17	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Ramsey	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
January	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
drinking	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
Home	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
,	O
who	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Drink	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
Door	O
;	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Drink	O
paid	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
took	O
him	O
about	O
the	O
Neck	O
,	O
pull	O
'd	O
him	O
backwards	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
kiss	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
missing	O
his	O
Watch	O
seized	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
who	O
said	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
had	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
told	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
Prosecute	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
his	O
things	O
again	O
;	O
which	O
were	O
indeed	O
brought	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
by	O
what	O
means	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
pickt	O
up	O
a	O
Woman	O
and	O
carried	O
her	O
into	O
a	O
Brandy-Shop	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
threw	O
her	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
into	O
an	O
empty	O
Room	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
together	O
above	O
an	O
Hour	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
called	O
her	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
to	O
fetch	O
them	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Drink	O
and	O
a	O
Candle	O
;	O
that	O
his	O
Breeches	O
were	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
running	O
away	O
he	O
seized	O
upon	O
her	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
own	O
'd	O
his	O
being	O
at	O
the	O
Brandy-Shop	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
paid	O
a	O
Shilling	O
for	O
two	O
quarterns	O
of	O
Brandy	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
searcht	O
and	O
nothing	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Humphrey	B-pers
Angier	I-pers
,	I-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
his	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	O
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Duce	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Rose	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
l.	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Gibbs	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
in	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Diaper	O
Tablecloth	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Mackdonnel	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bridgeman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
in	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Callicoe	O
Gown	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Apron	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Litchfield	I-pers
;	O
and	O
3	O
Suits	O
of	O
Headclothes	O
value	O
6s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Tustin	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
Margaret	O
Litchfield	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
lost	O
her	O
Gown	O
and	O
Apron	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
hung	O
up	O
in	O
her	O
Entry	O
to	O
dry	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Tustin	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
lost	O
3	O
Suits	O
of	O
Headclothes	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Room	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Bostock	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
hold	O
a	O
wet	O
Gown	O
up	O
against	O
the	O
Lamp	O
to	O
look	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
cram	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
acquainted	O
a	O
Chairman	O
(	O
that	O
was	O
just	O
by	O
)	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
secured	O
him	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Headclothes	O
,	O
Gown	O
and	O
Apron	O
in	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
.	O
The	O
Chairman	O
confirmed	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
no	O
where	O
else	O
to	O
put	O
them	O
,	O
thrust	O
them	O
into	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
intended	O
to	O
have	O
them	O
cry	O
'd	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
believing	O
him	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Ingledeau	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
in	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Ann	B-pers
Wall	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Turkey	O
Handkerchief	O
trimm	O
'd	O
with	O
Gold	O
value	O
20s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Wall	I-pers
.	O
Ann	O
Wall	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
in	O
Holbourn	B-place
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
snatcht	O
her	O
Handkerchief	O
off	O
her	O
Neck	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
others	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Boy	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
seized	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Stiles	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
her	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
seized	O
him	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
him	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
when	O
brought	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
Druy-Lane	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
Satisfaction	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
try	O
'd	O
for	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
but	O
hop	O
'd	O
to	O
come	O
off	O
with	O
Transportation	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
much	O
value	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
abroad	O
already	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
two	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
they	O
knew	O
him	O
from	O
his	O
Birth	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Barber	O
and	O
Perriwig	O
Maker	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
Indies	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
home	O
about	O
3	O
Months	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
behaved	O
himself	O
honestly	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
was	O
snatcht	O
off	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Neck	O
without	O
any	O
Violence	O
done	O
to	O
her	O
Person	O
,	O
or	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Bodily	O
Fear	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Melton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Pancras	B-place
in	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
in	O
the	O
Left	O
Pap	O
with	O
a	O
drawn	O
Sword	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
and	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
6	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
for	O
Manslaughter	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
James	B-pers
West	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
Lambs-Conduit-Fields	O
,	O
some	O
Boys	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
fight	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
followed	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
place	O
near	O
the	O
new	O
Burying	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
them	O
strip	O
,	O
take	O
up	O
their	O
Swords	O
,	O
and	O
push	O
at	O
one	O
another	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
wounded	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Right	O
Side	O
,	O
which	O
bled	O
very	O
much	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
shook	O
Hands	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
followed	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
turn	O
'd	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stood	O
ready	O
to	O
receive	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
fought	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
wounded	O
the	O
Deceased	O
in	O
the	O
Left	O
Breast	O
,	O
who	O
died	O
immediately	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Frazer	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
drinking	O
together	O
at	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms	O
in	O
Drury	O
Lane	O
,	O
being	O
about	O
14	O
in	O
Company	O
(	O
Drummers	O
in	O
2	O
several	O
Regiments	O
of	O
the	O
Guards	O
)	O
and	O
that	O
some	O
Words	O
arose	O
about	O
dividing	O
the	O
Money	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
given	O
them	O
for	O
Beating	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Here	O
's	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
who	O
will	O
take	O
it	O
from	O
me	O
?	O
that	O
after	O
other	O
Words	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
's	O
no	O
time	O
like	O
the	O
present	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
never	O
part	O
with	O
it	O
till	O
I	O
see	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
wondering	O
that	O
they	O
staid	O
,	O
went	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
very	O
Bloody	O
;	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
he	O
did	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Defence	O
:	O
that	O
he	O
seized	O
him	O
and	O
broke	O
his	O
Sword	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
no	O
Quarrel	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
were	O
very	O
good	O
Friends	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
dropt	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
said	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Fields	O
he	O
(	O
the	O
Deceased	O
)	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
Pot	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Share	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
they	O
fought	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
,	O
be	O
had	O
fought	O
several	O
Men	O
in	O
that	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
there	O
fight	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
wounded	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
Right	O
Pap	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
at	O
first	O
thought	O
was	O
Mortal	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
followed	O
the	O
Deceased	O
afterwards	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
had	O
done	O
your	O
Business	O
already	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
gave	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
ran	O
on	O
his	O
Sword	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
only	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Candlesticks	O
and	O
a	O
Saveall	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Warburton	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
January	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wharton	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
his	O
Master	O
in	O
his	O
Chamber	O
in	O
Lincolns	B-place
Inn	I-place
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
a	O
Noise	O
as	O
of	O
the	O
fall	O
of	O
Brass	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
askt	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
wanted	O
any	O
Writing	O
Sand	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
he	O
mist	O
the	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
and	O
the	O
Saveall	O
upon	O
her	O
in	O
another	O
Stair-Case	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
never	O
did	O
so	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
two	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
in	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Night-Gown	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
26	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sir	O
Justinian	B-pers
Isham	I-pers
,	O
Bart	O
.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
.	O
a	O
Sword	O
and	O
8	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Whitacre	I-pers
;	O
and	O
14	O
l.	O
8s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
1719	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Whitacre	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
travelling	O
with	O
Sir	O
Justinian	O
Isham	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
Assaulted	O
by	O
3	O
Men	O
near	B-place
Dunstable	I-place
in	I-place
Hertfordshire	I-place
,	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
took	O
Sir	O
Justinian	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Chariot	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
(	O
he	O
believed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
took	O
him	O
out	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
what	O
Money	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
askt	O
for	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
hid	O
under	O
the	O
Seat	O
in	O
the	O
Chariot	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
afterwards	O
found	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
Sir	O
Justinian	O
's	O
Pocket-Book	O
and	O
Key	O
;	O
took	O
the	O
Trunk	O
and	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
break	O
it	O
open	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
gave	O
them	O
the	O
Key	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Trunk	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
a	O
Night-Gown	O
,	O
6	O
Shirts	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Hilted	O
Sword	O
and	O
14	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
when	O
taken	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
Sir	O
Justinian	O
's	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
and	O
Night-Gown	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Evidence	O
's	O
Watch	O
and	O
a	O
Ring	O
for	O
his	O
Share	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
wore	O
the	O
Night-Gown	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Lodging	O
and	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Trunk	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
The	O
Woman	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
he	O
lodged	O
,	O
near	O
Red-Lion-Square	O
in	O
Middlesex	O
;	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Esq	O
;	O
Becket	O
;	O
wore	O
Black	O
Velver	O
,	O
Lace	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
and	O
every	O
thing	O
else	O
answerable	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Osgood	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
Half	O
a	O
Year	O
after	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
he	O
received	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
who	O
owned	O
,	O
that	O
himself	O
,	O
one	O
Smith	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
executed	O
at	O
Maidstone	O
,	O
and	O
Jack	O
-	O
in	O
Ireland	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
for	O
his	O
Footman	O
,	O
committed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
to	O
him	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
all	O
the	O
Particulars	O
,	O
saying	O
it	O
signified	O
nothing	O
,	O
to	O
conceal	O
any	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Evidence	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Butcher	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Boxes	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
20	O
printed	O
Books	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Brass	O
Candlestick	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Phelps	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
January	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Betterton	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
which	O
broke	O
out	O
about	O
7	O
a	O
Clock	O
that	O
Night	O
in	O
Red-Cross-street	O
,	O
going	O
through	O
the	O
Bowling-Alley	B-place
into	I-place
White-Cross-street	I-place
,	O
to	O
call	O
another	O
Watchman	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
two	O
Men	O
parlying	O
in	O
the	O
dark	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
why	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
go	O
off	O
now	O
we	O
have	O
got	O
our	O
Booty	O
?	O
whereupon	O
he	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Alley	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Prisner	O
as	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
with	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Boxes	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Person	O
threw	O
down	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Fire	O
broke	O
out	O
the	O
back-side	O
of	O
his	O
House	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
which	O
were	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
)	O
were	O
his	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
them	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
White-Cross-street	O
with	O
2	O
Boxes	O
,	O
who	O
offer	O
'd	O
him	O
6	O
d.	O
to	O
carry	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
,	O
nor	O
the	O
Man	O
who	O
employed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
follow	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
having	O
no	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Heatley	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Precinct	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Katharines	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
a	O
Clock	O
the	O
Morning	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Barge	O
.	O
even	O
into	O
the	O
Cabbin	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
Ceremony	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
wet	O
,	O
his	O
Master	O
ordered	O
him	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
to	O
rise	O
and	O
make	O
a	O
Fire	O
to	O
dry	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
dried	O
himself	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
)	O
mist	O
his	O
Buckels	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shoes	O
,	O
which	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Barge	O
,	O
stood	O
by	O
the	O
Fire-Place	O
,	O
but	O
were	O
removed	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Body	O
else	O
in	O
the	O
Cabbin	O
;	O
that	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
(	O
having	O
notice	O
of	O
him	O
)	O
they	O
took	O
him	O
at	O
a	O
Musick	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Master	O
)	O
confirmed	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
they	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
owned	O
to	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Buckles	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
sorry	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
his	O
Tryal	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
fell	O
into	O
the	O
Mud	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Thames	O
to	O
wash	O
himself	O
and	O
Clothes	O
,	O
then	O
into	O
the	O
Barge	O
to	O
dry	O
them	O
:	O
That	O
when	O
they	O
took	O
him	O
they	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
must	O
go	O
to	O
Newgate	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
make	O
Satisfaction	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Week	O
's	O
time	O
to	O
raise	O
Money	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
not	O
performing	O
,	O
they	O
brought	O
this	O
Prosecution	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
But	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
nor	O
bring	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
in	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
2	O
Silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Wakeham	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2	O
d.	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
January	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Quart	O
Pot	O
value	O
20	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Griffith	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Constable	O
sent	O
him	O
word	O
that	O
searching	O
for	O
stolen	O
Goods	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
his	O
Pot	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Cellar	O
.	O
The	O
Pot	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
had	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Name	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
writ	O
round	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
swore	O
to	O
by	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
it	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Days	O
before	O
he	O
had	O
notice	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
confirmed	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
farther	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
several	O
other	O
Pots	O
belonging	O
to	O
divers	O
People	O
,	O
some	O
batter	O
'd	O
and	O
others	O
with	O
the	O
Names	O
of	O
the	O
Owners	O
filed	O
out	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
also	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
lent	O
Money	O
on	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Pot	O
to	O
a	O
Woman	O
who	O
promised	O
to	O
redeem	O
it	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
;	O
and	O
called	O
some	O
Persons	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
35	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Buckle	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Girdle	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Simon	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Drawer	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Mallard	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
seek	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
Kent-Street	O
,	O
drunk	O
:	O
that	O
she	O
pull	O
'd	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Rings	O
off	O
her	O
Finger	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
;	O
which	O
they	O
found	O
accordingly	O
:	O
that	O
they	O
brought	O
her	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-Yard	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
no	O
further	O
without	O
a	O
Coach	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Hester	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
at	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Breeches	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Colecroft	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
January	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Breeches	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Shop	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
seen	O
and	O
spoke	O
to	O
,	O
carried	O
them	O
back	O
and	O
hung	O
them	O
up	O
again	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
Antient	O
poor	O
Object	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
declaring	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
forgive	O
her	O
if	O
the	O
Court	O
would	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stiles	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
at	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Guineas	O
,	O
a	O
Half	O
Guinea	O
,	O
a	O
Quarter	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
;	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Roebottom	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
3	O
Women	O
more	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
towards	O
the	O
Evening	O
to	O
borrow	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
took	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
15	O
l.	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Bag	O
in	O
her	O
Drawer	O
,	O
her	O
Key	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Drawer	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
her	O
Money	O
there	O
the	O
Minute	O
before	O
she	O
mist	O
it	O
,	O
having	O
gone	O
to	O
her	O
Bag	O
to	O
change	O
a	O
Half	O
Crown	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
pursued	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
a	O
Half	O
Crown	O
and	O
a	O
Six-Pence	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Ely	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
and	O
owned	O
that	O
the	O
Guinea	O
,	O
Half	O
Crown	O
and	O
Six-Pence	O
were	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Betty	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
gave	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
her	O
Share	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
last	O
Evidence	O
:	O
And	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
3	O
were	O
indicted	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Fact	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
given	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
instead	O
thereof	O
clear	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Robbins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
in	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
committing	O
a	O
Rape	O
on	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Tabor	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
Girl	O
of	O
about	O
7	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
)	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Tabor	I-pers
(	O
the	O
Mother	O
of	O
the	O
Girl	O
)	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
took	O
the	O
Child	O
out	O
with	O
him	O
on	O
Christmas-Eve	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
home	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
uneasy	O
.	O
wriggling	O
her	O
Body	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
askt	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
at	O
her	O
Taylor	O
's	O
sitting	O
on	O
his	O
Shop-board	O
;	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
she	O
complained	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
make	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
smarted	O
sadly	O
;	O
that	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
she	O
complained	O
wose	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
examin	O
'd	O
,	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
put	O
his	O
Finger	O
into	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
she	O
made	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
put	O
the	O
thing	O
with	O
which	O
be	O
made	O
Water	O
,	O
into	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
she	O
made	O
Water	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
Private	O
Parts	O
swell	O
'd	O
and	O
rent	O
downwards	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
Force	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
knew	O
not	O
who	O
did	O
it	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
de	I-pers
Layer	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
the	O
Girl	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
privy	O
Parts	O
very	O
sore	O
and	O
bruised	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Running	O
which	O
continued	O
then	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Penetration	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
forced	O
by	O
a	O
Man	O
.	O
John	B-pers
West	I-pers
and	O
Peter	B-pers
du	I-pers
Hamel	I-pers
(	O
two	O
other	O
Surgeons	O
)	O
confirmed	O
the	O
former	O
Surgeon	O
's	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Opinion	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Tabor	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
to	O
him	O
that	O
the	O
Girl	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
on	O
Christmas-Eve	O
;	O
but	O
denied	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Stall	O
is	O
next	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
Man	O
may	O
work	O
in	O
it	O
and	O
no	O
more	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
's	O
a	O
Flap	O
to	O
shut	O
up	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
well	O
before	O
that	O
Saturday	O
.	O
Another	O
Woman	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
washt	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
Linnen	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
Marks	O
of	O
Hurt	O
before	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
that	O
Day	O
;	O
or	O
that	O
he	O
ever	O
offer	O
'd	O
any	O
thing	O
like	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
following	O
Evidence	O
:	O
John	O
Brown	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
viewed	O
the	O
Child	O
with	O
two	O
other	O
Surgeons	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
Penetration	O
large	O
enough	O
for	O
a	O
Man	O
to	O
make	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
try	O
'd	O
with	O
a	O
Probe	O
,	O
which	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
up	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Running	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
the	O
like	O
Hurt	O
occasion	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
Child	O
's	O
Riding	O
on	O
a	O
Horse	O
.	O
Another	O
Surgeon	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
Child	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
as	O
the	O
former	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Penetration	O
large	O
enough	O
for	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
lacerated	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Probe	O
would	O
not	O
enter	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Tomlins	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Shop	O
is	O
next	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
Publick	O
as	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
body	O
or	O
other	O
always	O
at	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
hard	O
at	O
work	O
that	O
Day	O
for	O
a	O
Tenant	O
of	O
hers	O
to	O
finish	O
his	O
Coat	O
against	O
Christmas-Day	O
,	O
and	O
work	O
till	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
lives	O
over	O
against	O
his	O
Shop	O
.	O
But	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
for	O
her	O
Tenant	O
till	O
after	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
Window	O
to	O
shut	O
up	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
goes	O
out	O
.	O
He	O
also	O
called	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
honest	O
civil	O
Man	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
run	O
after	O
the	O
Girls	O
a	O
little	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Carewehus	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Perjury	O
in	O
making	O
a	O
false	O
Affidavit	O
in	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
to	O
put	O
off	O
a	O
Tryal	O
there	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
at	I-place
Hackney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Woodley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
Mistress	O
sent	O
her	O
to	O
London	O
with	O
a	O
Horse	O
to	O
sell	O
some	O
Goods	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
staid	O
out	O
with	O
the	O
Horse	O
all	O
Night	O
and	O
spent	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
that	O
her	O
Mistress	O
missing	O
the	O
Ring	O
came	O
to	O
Town	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
,	O
charg	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
her	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
Her	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Mountjoy	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
at	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Callimancoe	O
Petticoat	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Eggleston	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Camblet	O
Riding	O
Hood	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Rawford	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
in	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
Pewter	O
Dish	O
,	O
7	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
2	O
Pewter	O
Spoons	O
and	O
a	O
Copper	O
Saucepan	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cullis	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
January	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
with	O
her	O
Mother	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
her	O
Mother	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
afterwards	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
tuckt	O
up	O
in	O
her	O
Petticoats	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
finding	O
the	O
Goods	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
as	O
before	O
related	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
intend	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
Maid	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
malicious	O
Person	O
)	O
Hunt	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
But	O
that	O
Excuse	O
not	O
availing	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Branch	I-pers
of	O
Stanwell	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Black	O
Gelding	O
value	O
8l	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Hosey	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
at	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
committing	O
a	O
Rape	O
on	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
the	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Henry	I-pers
Powell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
coming	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Contrivance	O
to	O
extort	O
Money	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
granted	O
him	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
his	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
on	O
the	O
10th	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silver	O
Headed	O
Cane	O
value	O
20s	O
.	O
and	O
3s	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
with	O
other	O
Constable	O
s	O
to	O
the	O
5	B-place
Bells	I-place
in	I-place
Essex-street	I-place
to	O
take	O
up	O
Saunders	O
with	O
a	O
Scape	O
Warrant	O
;	O
that	O
meeting	O
with	O
Resistance	O
the	O
Cane	O
was	O
mist	O
for	O
the	O
present	O
,	O
and	O
Saunders	O
rescued	O
.	O
It	O
appearing	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Robbery	O
but	O
a	O
Lawful	O
Action	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
granted	O
him	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
his	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
at	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Petticoat	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Travers	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
of	O
Isleworth	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Leaden	O
Cistern	O
value	O
30s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Gumley	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
William	B-pers
Corner	I-pers
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
one	O
Morning	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Wright	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
Cistern	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
afterward	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
askt	O
him	O
himself	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
about	O
9	O
or	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
way	O
,	O
moved	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Garden-Ground	O
,	O
cut	O
it	O
into	O
4	O
pieces	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
into	O
some	O
Water	O
to	O
hide	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
this	O
Evidence	O
discovered	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisosoner	O
's	O
Mother	O
kept	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
waste	O
Pipe	O
of	O
the	O
Cistern	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
then	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Pipe	O
on	O
the	O
Road	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Davis	O
told	O
him	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
accordingly	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
thought	O
he	O
had	O
as	O
much	O
Right	O
to	O
it	O
as	O
Mr.	O
Gumley	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
his	O
Uncle	O
left	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
Uncle	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
John	O
Davis	O
being	O
called	O
again	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
Cistern	O
did	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Uncle	O
Mr.	O
Crosby	O
,	O
who	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Gumly	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guily	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Flewelling	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Coach-seats	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sir	O
Andrew	B-pers
Chadwick	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
January	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Acreman	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
going	O
up	O
Bow-street	B-place
with	O
George	B-pers
Bowers	I-pers
,	O
heard	O
an	O
Oyster-Woman	O
cry	O
out	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
with	O
two	O
Coach-seats	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
dropt	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Kennel	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
George	O
Bowers	O
confirmed	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Chariot	O
waited	O
for	O
him	O
in	O
Essex-street	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Servant	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
Seats	O
were	O
stollen	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Coachman	O
and	O
Footman	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
Seats	O
that	O
were	O
dropt	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
their	O
Master	O
's	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
;	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
nor	O
call	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
taking	O
his	O
Word	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
January	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
fix	O
it	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
value	O
7s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Hind	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
:	O
And	O
the	O
Court	O
order	O
'd	O
the	O
Recognizance	O
of	O
20	O
l.	O
Penalty	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
bound	O
in	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
restreated	O
into	O
the	O
Exchequer	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
in	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Katharine	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
January	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
Servant	O
at	O
the	O
Grey	B-place
Coat	I-place
School	I-place
in	I-place
Westminster	I-place
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
up	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
out	O
Apprentice	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
the	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
Examination	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
People	O
there	O
)	O
and	O
she	O
perceiving	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
ill	O
,	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
her	O
Room	O
and	O
set	O
him	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
her	O
business	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Guineas	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Chest	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
unlockt	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
she	O
left	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
his	O
Youth	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hollingsby	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Marry	I-place
Le	I-place
Bone	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
8	O
Guineas	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
January	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Grant	I-pers
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Court	O
ordered	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Recognizance	O
of	O
40l	O
.	O
Penalty	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
bound	O
into	O
prosecute	O
her	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
restreated	O
into	O
the	O
Exchequer	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
at	I-place
Billingsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
84	O
pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
called	O
Moidores	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
de	I-pers
Basto	I-pers
Corea	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Spigget	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Spiggot	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Cross	I-pers
,	O
having	O
had	O
several	O
Bills	O
of	O
Indictment	O
for	O
Robbing	O
on	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
,	O
found	O
against	O
them	O
by	O
the	O
Grand	O
Jury	O
,	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
to	O
be	O
Arraigned	O
and	O
take	O
their	O
Trials	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
stood	O
Mute	O
,	O
and	O
refused	O
to	O
Plead	O
till	O
they	O
should	O
have	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
Horses	O
,	O
Accoutrements	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
which	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
them	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
Apprehended	O
returned	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
But	O
the	O
Court	O
told	O
them	O
that	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
granted	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
their	O
Satisfaction	O
order	O
'd	O
a	O
Clause	O
in	O
an	O
Act	O
of	O
Parliament	O
made	O
in	O
the	O
4th	O
and	O
5th	O
Years	O
of	O
the	O
Reign	O
of	O
King	O
William	O
and	O
Queen	O
Mary	O
,	O
intituled	O
An	O
Act	O
for	O
Encouraging	O
the	O
Apprehending	O
of	O
Highway	O
Men	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
read	O
unto	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
as	O
follows	O
:	O
`	O
And	O
it	O
is	O
hereby	O
further	O
Enacted	O
,	O
That	O
all	O
and	O
`	O
every	O
Person	O
or	O
Persons	O
who	O
shall	O
so	O
Take	O
,	O
Apprehend	O
,	O
Prosecute	O
,	O
or	O
Committ	O
such	O
Robber	O
or	O
Robbers	O
,	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
further	O
Reward	O
shall	O
have	O
and	O
enjoy	O
to	O
his	O
and	O
their	O
proper	O
use	O
and	O
behoof	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
Furniture	O
and	O
Arms	O
,	O
Money	O
,	O
or	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Robber	O
or	O
Robbers	O
that	O
shall	O
be	O
taken	O
with	O
him	O
or	O
them	O
;	O
Any	O
their	O
Majesties	O
Right	O
or	O
Title	O
,	O
Bodies	O
Politick	O
of	O
Corporate	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
Right	O
or	O
Title	O
thereunto	O
of	O
the	O
Lord	O
of	O
any	O
Manor	O
,	O
Liberty	O
or	O
Franchise	O
,	O
or	O
of	O
him	O
or	O
them	O
Lending	O
or	O
Letting	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
Hire	O
to	O
any	O
such	O
Robber	O
or	O
Robbers	O
in	O
any	O
wise	O
notwithstanding	O
.	O
Provided	O
always	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
Clause	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
thing	O
therein	O
contained	O
shall	O
not	O
be	O
Construed	O
to	O
Extend	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
the	O
Right	O
of	O
any	O
Person	O
or	O
Persons	O
to	O
such	O
Horses	O
,	O
Furniture	O
and	O
Arms	O
,	O
Money	O
or	O
other	O
Goods	O
from	O
whom	O
the	O
same	O
were	O
before	O
feloniously	O
taken	O
.	O
But	O
they	O
still	O
refusing	O
to	O
plead	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
acquainted	O
them	O
with	O
the	O
Ill	O
Consequences	O
of	O
their	O
Refusal	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
a	O
heavy	O
Judgement	O
they	O
would	O
draw	O
down	O
upon	O
themselves	O
if	O
they	O
persisted	O
in	O
their	O
Obstinacy	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
more	O
effectually	O
to	O
convince	O
them	O
of	O
their	O
Folly	O
and	O
Error	O
,	O
ordered	O
the	O
Judgement	O
to	O
be	O
read	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
if	O
they	O
continued	O
Mute	O
must	O
be	O
Pronounced	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
in	O
Execution	O
,	O
which	O
Judgment	O
was	O
to	O
the	O
Effect	O
following	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
shall	O
be	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Prison	O
from	O
whence	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
into	O
a	O
mean	O
House	O
,	O
Stopped	O
from	O
Light	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
shall	O
be	O
laid	O
upon	O
the	O
bare	O
Ground	O
without	O
any	O
Litter	O
,	O
Straw	O
or	O
other	O
Covering	O
,	O
and	O
without	O
any	O
Garment	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
saving	O
something	O
to	O
cover	O
his	O
Privy	O
Members	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
shall	O
lie	O
upon	O
his	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Head	O
shall	O
be	O
covered	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Feet	O
bare	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
`	O
Arms	O
shall	O
be	O
drawn	O
with	O
a	O
Cord	O
to	O
one	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Arm	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Legs	O
shall	O
be	O
used	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
manner	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
upon	O
his	O
Body	O
shall	O
be	O
laid	O
so	O
much	O
Iron	O
and	O
Stone	O
as	O
he	O
can	O
bear	O
,	O
and	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
first	O
Day	O
after	O
he	O
shall	O
have	O
three	O
Morsels	O
of	O
Barley	O
Bread	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
second	O
Day	O
he	O
shall	O
drink	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
he	O
can	O
three	O
times	O
of	O
the	O
Wa	O
`	O
ter	O
which	O
is	O
next	O
the	O
Prison	O
Door	O
,	O
saving	O
running	O
Water	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
Bread	O
:	O
and	O
this	O
shall	O
be	O
his	O
Diet	O
until	O
be	O
die	O
.	O
And	O
he	O
against	O
whom	O
this	O
Judgment	O
shall	O
be	O
given	O
,	O
forfeits	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
his	O
Goods	O
.	O
All	O
this	O
having	O
no	O
Effect	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Executioner	O
was	O
called	O
and	O
ordered	O
to	O
tye	O
their	O
Thumbs	O
,	O
as	O
usual	O
in	O
such	O
Cases	O
;	O
but	O
all	O
being	O
in	O
vain	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
still	O
peremptorily	O
refusing	O
,	O
and	O
declaring	O
that	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
Plead	O
notwithstanding	O
all	O
the	O
Admonition	O
that	O
could	O
be	O
given	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
pass	O
Sentence	O
against	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
prest	O
to	O
Death	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Law	O
directs	O
.	O
Whereupon	O
they	O
were	O
carried	O
back	O
to	O
Newgate	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
undergo	O
that	O
Judgment	O
the	O
Law	O
had	O
inflicted	O
on	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Press	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Phillips	O
alias	O
Cross	O
desired	O
to	O
be	O
carried	O
again	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
would	O
Plead	O
;	O
and	O
Spiggot	O
continuing	O
still	O
Resolute	O
,	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
Press	O
according	O
to	O
his	O
Sentence	O
,	O
where	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
he	O
also	O
desired	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
again	O
,	O
to	O
Plead	O
which	O
being	O
Granted	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
indicted	O
by	O
the	O
Names	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Spigget	I-pers
alias	O
Spiggot	O
and	O
Thomas	O
Philips	O
alias	O
Cross	O
,	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fearand	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
a	O
Holland	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
a	O
Scarlet	O
Riding-Hood	O
lined	O
with	O
Silk	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
200l	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
again	O
indicted	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Heater	I-pers
;	O
Spiggot	O
and	O
Phillips	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
5	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
Turner	O
,	O
and	O
1	O
Box	O
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
12	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Lace	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
2	O
Cambrick	O
Bosoms	O
.	O
2	O
Lawn	O
,	O
Turnovers	O
,	O
2	O
Muslin	O
Turnovers	O
,	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
12	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Neal	B-pers
Sheldon	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
Hater	O
as	O
Accessory	O
in	O
Harbouring	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
receiving	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Monmouth	O
with	O
his	O
Pack-Horses	O
,	O
between	O
Brentford	O
and	O
Smallberry-Green	O
,	O
he	O
observed	O
Phillips	O
to	O
follow	O
and	O
watch	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
Bishops-Grove	B-place
on	I-place
Hounslow-Heath	I-place
,	O
Spiggot	O
,	O
Phillips	O
and	O
another	O
rode	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
Spiggot	O
clapt	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
his	O
Breast	O
,	O
bid	O
him	O
stand	O
,	O
took	O
his	O
Watch	O
and	O
5	O
l.	O
from	O
him	O
and	O
said	O
if	O
he	O
wou	O
'd	O
not	O
tell	O
him	O
what	O
Horse	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
on	O
they	O
would	O
kill	O
them	O
all	O
.	O
Phillips	O
stopt	O
the	O
Ostler	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Pack-Horses	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Person	O
secur	O
'd	O
his	O
Man	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
above	O
200	O
l.	O
in	O
all	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
Spiggot	O
and	O
Phillips	O
were	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
who	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
Spiggot	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Years	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
in	O
Monmouth	O
Goal	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
deposed	O
.	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
November	O
about	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
by	O
5	O
Men	O
,	O
4	O
of	O
them	O
on	O
Horseback	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
on	O
Foot	O
,	O
near	O
Tyburn	B-place
;	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
Mr.	O
Sheldon	O
's	O
Box	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Waggon	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
following	O
of	O
them	O
they	O
knockt	O
him	O
down	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
his	O
Waggon	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
took	O
nothing	O
else	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
a	O
Mare	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
masqued	O
and	O
disguised	O
.	O
Neal	B-pers
Sheldon	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
October	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
Buckinghamshire	O
,	O
and	O
thinking	O
his	O
Portmantua	O
too	O
heavy	O
for	O
his	O
Man	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
it	O
up	O
John	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
the	O
Wendover	O
Carrier	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Perriwig	O
he	O
had	O
then	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
was	O
his	O
Perriwig	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Box	O
(	O
or	O
Portmanteau	O
)	O
which	O
he	O
deliver	O
'd	O
to	O
Turner	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bryan	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Merrit	O
to	O
Search	O
Spiggot	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
found	O
the	O
Wig	O
which	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Merrit	O
Confirmed	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
and	O
farther	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
found	O
several	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
some	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Portsmouth	O
Waggon	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
taken	O
from	O
Persons	O
under	O
Tybourn	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Plummer	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Wig	O
produced	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Sheldon	O
's	O
Wig	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
it	O
well	O
,	O
having	O
altered	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Merrit	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Watkins	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
ruin	O
'd	O
;	O
that	O
3	O
Highway	O
Men	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
on	O
Hounslow-Heath	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
Watch	O
,	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pack-Horse	O
from	O
him	O
:	O
that	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
enquiring	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
sound	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
hired	O
Horses	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
the	O
Person	O
to	O
stop	O
them	O
if	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
Hire	O
any	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
reward	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
dogg	O
'd	O
Heater	O
with	O
the	O
Horses	O
from	O
Finsbury	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
George	O
in	O
Long-Acre	O
,	O
and	O
thence	O
to	O
the	O
Broadway	O
in	O
Westminster	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
(	O
with	O
the	O
others	O
that	O
took	O
them	O
)	O
planted	O
themselves	O
in	O
a	O
House	O
over	O
against	O
the	O
Inn	O
where	O
their	O
Horses	O
were	O
in	O
Westminster	O
;	O
but	O
after	O
some	O
Consultstion	O
they	O
believing	O
Mr.	O
Rowlet	O
the	O
Inn-Keeper	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
and	O
acquainted	O
him	O
with	O
their	O
Business	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
them	O
they	O
should	O
be	O
welcome	O
to	O
set	O
up	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
assist	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
Heater	O
was	O
the	O
Porter	O
who	O
brought	O
the	O
Horses	O
and	O
put	O
Sacks	O
under	O
the	O
Saddles	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
about	O
10	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Stable	O
,	O
where	O
Mr.	O
Rowlet	O
was	O
before	O
by	O
Appointment	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
followed	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
:	O
that	O
Spiggot	O
had	O
the	O
Landlord	O
Rowlet	O
down	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
Assistance	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Rowlet	I-pers
confirmed	O
Heater	O
's	O
bringing	O
the	O
Horses	O
to	O
his	O
Inn	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
his	O
Stable	O
,	O
and	O
farther	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
Mr.	O
Bryan	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Stable	O
Phillips	O
flash	O
'd	O
a	O
Pistol	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
followed	O
Spiggot	O
,	O
threw	O
up	O
his	O
Heels	O
and	O
Scuffled	O
with	O
him	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
;	O
that	O
Spiggot	O
shot	O
him	O
through	O
the	O
Left	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
offer	O
'd	O
him	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
off	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hill	O
(	O
the	O
Constable	O
)	O
deposed	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Merrit	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Recorder	O
's	O
Warrant	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Burton	O
's	O
then	O
over	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Rowlet	O
's	O
;	O
that	O
about	O
8	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
Lindsey	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
were	O
for	O
securing	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
others	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
that	O
would	O
prevent	O
their	O
taking	O
the	O
others	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
agreed	O
to	O
stay	O
till	O
they	O
could	O
meet	O
with	O
them	O
together	O
;	O
that	O
about	O
10	O
all	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
came	O
in	O
together	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Stable	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
followed	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
Phillips	O
snapt	O
a	O
Musquetoon	O
loaded	O
with	O
3	O
Bullets	O
at	O
him	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
but	O
it	O
flash	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Pan	O
only	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bryan	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Merri	O
to	O
Finsbury	O
,	O
and	O
dogg	O
'd	O
Heater	O
with	O
the	O
Horses	O
to	O
Westminster	O
;	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
Inn	O
and	O
being	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
Stable	O
;	O
that	O
Spiggot	O
flash	O
'd	O
a	O
Pistol	O
at	O
him	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
and	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
seeing	O
Mr.	O
Rowles	O
wounded	O
and	O
upon	O
Spiggot	O
,	O
whose	O
Sword	O
was	O
half	O
drawn	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
with	O
a	O
design	O
to	O
stick	O
Spiggot	O
,	O
but	O
instead	O
of	O
doing	O
so	O
,	O
ran	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
Butchers	O
Leg	O
:	O
And	O
that	O
Spiggot	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
kill	O
a	O
Thousand	O
before	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
taken	O
.	O
Murrel	O
(	O
the	O
Boy	O
who	O
dogg	O
'd	O
Heater	O
and	O
the	O
Horses	O
from	O
Finsbury	O
to	O
Long-Acre	O
with	O
two	O
Horses	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
took	O
another	O
and	O
carryed	O
them	O
to	O
Westminster	O
)	O
confirmed	O
the	O
former	O
Evidences	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Lindsey	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Spiggot	O
,	O
Pbillips	O
,	O
Coltis	O
and	O
Tyson	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Box	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Heater	O
used	O
to	O
hire	O
Horses	O
and	O
carry	O
them	O
backward	O
and	O
forward	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
but	O
not	O
for	O
this	O
Robbery	O
:	O
that	O
he	O
(	O
Heater	O
)	O
received	O
some	O
Buttons	O
and	O
Mohair	O
which	O
he	O
knew	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
not	O
mentioned	O
in	O
this	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
Spiggot	O
bought	O
a	O
Horse	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
then	O
Heater	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
he	O
denied	O
that	O
he	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
Patrick	B-pers
Deveny	I-pers
confirmed	O
Burton	O
's	O
Evidence	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Merrit	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Recorder	O
's	O
Warrant	O
to	O
execute	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
a	O
Blunderbuss	O
out	O
of	O
Phillip	O
's	O
Hand	O
,	O
who	O
flasht	O
a	O
Pistol	O
at	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
off	O
;	O
that	O
Spiggot	O
fired	O
2	O
Pistols	O
and	O
Wounded	O
Mr.	O
Rowlet	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Leaton	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Spiggot	O
,	O
Phillips	O
and	O
Lindsey	O
came	O
to	O
take	O
Horse	O
in	O
Westminster	O
,	O
that	O
Heater	O
came	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
Phillips	O
flasht	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
but	O
Lindsey	O
surrender	O
'd	O
himself	O
to	O
this	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Autbony	O
Merrit	O
deposed	O
that	O
Heater	O
has	O
had	O
Phillips	O
's	O
Horse	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
to	O
fetch	O
Sacks	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
under	O
the	O
Saddles	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
the	O
Goods	O
sold	O
from	O
his	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
Spiggot	O
and	O
Phillips	O
,	O
both	O
declared	O
that	O
Heater	O
was	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
only	O
acted	O
as	O
a	O
Porter	O
in	O
fetching	O
and	O
carrying	O
their	O
Horses	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
against	O
Heater	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Spiggot	O
,	O
and	O
Phillips	O
alias	O
Cross	O
Guilty	O
of	O
these	O
Indictments	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
also	O
several	O
other	O
Indictments	O
found	O
against	O
them	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Spigget	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Spiggot	I-pers
was	O
again	O
Indicted	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Bourroughs	I-pers
of	O
Finchley	B-place
,	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Charles	B-pers
Sybbald	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
.	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
15	O
Guineas	O
and	O
10	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Lindsey	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
himself	O
met	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
his	O
Man	O
on	O
Finchley	B-place
Common	I-place
about	O
Bartholemewtide	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
Robb	O
'd	O
him	O
of	O
a	O
Purse	O
of	O
Guineas	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
but	O
of	O
6	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
that	O
Spiggot	O
took	O
the	O
Purse	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
his	O
Man	O
rode	O
one	O
on	O
a	O
White	O
Horse	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
on	O
a	O
Grey	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Sybbold	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
assaulted	O
on	O
Finchley	O
Common	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
by	O
Three	O
Men	O
on	O
Horseback	O
;	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
presented	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
him	O
on	O
his	O
Right	O
another	O
of	O
them	O
did	O
the	O
same	O
on	O
his	O
Left	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
third	O
secur	O
'd	O
his	O
Man	O
.	O
That	O
Lindsey	O
took	O
the	O
Bridle	O
of	O
his	O
Horse	O
and	O
turned	O
him	O
loose	O
,	O
that	O
Burroughs	O
had	O
a	O
long	O
Wig	O
with	O
the	O
ends	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Mouth	O
,	O
and	O
Spiggot	O
's	O
Cape	O
was	O
button	O
'd	O
up	O
about	O
his	O
Chin	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
rifled	O
him	O
,	O
one	O
began	O
at	O
his	O
Head	O
another	O
at	O
his	O
Middle	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
downwards	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
15	O
Guineas	O
,	O
some	O
Silver	O
and	O
some	O
Writings	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
were	O
tall	O
Men	O
like	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
Swear	O
to	O
any	O
but	O
Lindsay	O
,	O
who	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
plainer	O
view	O
of	O
and	O
remember	O
'd	O
his	O
Voice	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Man	O
and	O
himself	O
were	O
on	O
a	O
Grey	O
and	O
a	O
White	O
Horse	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
said	O
they	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
And	O
Burroughs	O
's	O
Brother	O
deposed	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Lindsey	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
his	O
Brother	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
with	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
come	O
to	O
Town	O
Raving	O
Mad	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
home	O
to	O
his	O
Mothers	O
for	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
have	O
Men	O
to	O
sit	O
up	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
him	O
into	O
Bethlehem	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
ever	O
since	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
's	O
Day	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Tompkins	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
14	O
lb	O
of	O
Cocoa-Nuts	O
,	O
20	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Ale	O
and	O
40	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Benning	I-pers
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
5	O
Guineas	O
,	O
80	O
Pound	O
of	O
Cocoa-Nuts	O
,	O
10	O
Pound	O
of	O
Chocolate	O
,	O
some	O
Coffee	O
and	O
12	O
Flasks	O
of	O
Florence	O
Wine	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
New	O
Act	O
of	O
Parliament	O
for	O
the	O
more	O
effectual	O
Transporting	O
of	O
Felons	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
formerly	O
convicted	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
Transported	O
among	O
other	O
Convicts	O
from	O
Newgate	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
had	O
returned	O
into	O
the	O
Kingdom	O
of	O
Great	O
.	O
Brittain	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
lawful	O
Cause	O
:	O
which	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
in	O
Assaulting	O
Robert	B-pers
Sandford	I-pers
,	O
and	O
striking	O
him	O
over	O
the	O
Right	O
Wrist	O
with	O
a	O
Handspike	O
,	O
which	O
lamed	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
Week	O
or	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
rents	O
some	O
Ground	O
and	O
Warehouses	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
by	O
Fleet-Ditch	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Defendant	O
Johnson	O
erected	O
a	O
Post	O
or	O
Crain	O
on	O
his	O
Ground	O
to	O
hoist	O
Timber	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Ditch	O
:	O
that	O
he	O
sent	O
his	O
Man	O
to	O
tell	O
him	O
he	O
must	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
afterwards	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
his	O
Man	O
to	O
cut	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Defendant	O
Johnson	O
took	O
a	O
Handspike	O
and	O
push	O
'd	O
at	O
his	O
Face	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
put	O
it	O
by	O
with	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
so	O
doing	O
push	O
'd	O
the	O
Defendant	O
on	O
the	O
Breast	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Defendant	O
lifted	O
up	O
the	O
Handspike	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
him	O
over	O
the	O
Wrist	O
,	O
and	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
would	O
lose	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
his	O
Right	O
Hand	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutors	O
Man	O
confirmed	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
5	O
Evidences	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
Defendant	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
strike	O
Mr.	O
Sandford	O
before	O
he	O
struck	O
Johnson	O
on	O
the	O
Breast	O
with	O
his	O
Hand	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
by	O
two	O
positive	O
Evidences	O
about	O
what	O
the	O
negative	O
Evidences	O
called	O
the	O
Blow	O
on	O
the	O
Defendant	O
's	O
Breast	O
,	O
was	O
only	O
Mr.	O
Sandford	O
's	O
putting	O
of	O
the	O
Handspike	O
from	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Fined	O
10	O
Marks	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Coste	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgement	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
7.	O
William	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
Themas	O
Butler	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Spigget	I-pers
alias	O
Spiggot	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
alias	O
Cross	O
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Burroughs	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
2.	O
James	B-pers
Melton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Browning	I-pers
,	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
,	O
19	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Terry	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Cornwall	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
de	I-pers
Plosh	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bridgeman	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Ingledeau	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Butcher	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Shephard	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stiles	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
alias	O
Richardson	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Rawford	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Flewelling	I-pers
,	O
Michael	O
Hall	O
,	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Withers	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Heatley	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
,	O
1.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
for	O
his	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
was	O
fined	O
10	O
Marks	O
Newly	O
Printed	O
for	O
Eman	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
in	O
Pater-noster-Row	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
An	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Life	O
and	O
Death	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
Reverend	O
Mr.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Henry	I-pers
,	O
by	O
the	O
Reverend	O
Mr.	O
Tong	O
.	O
The	O
Second	O
Edition	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
The	O
Doctrine	O
of	O
the	O
Blessed	O
Trinity	O
Stated	O
and	O
Defended	O
by	O
the	O
Reverend	O
Mr.	O
Tong	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Robinson	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Reynoldss	O
.	O
The	O
Second	O
Edition	O
price	O
1s	O
6d	O
..	O
3.Memoires	O
of	O
the	O
Life	O
of	O
the	O
Reverend	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fister	I-pers
,	O
A.	O
M.	O
and	O
sometimes	O
fellow	O
of	O
Pembroke	O
College	O
in	O
Oxford	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
Funeral	O
Sermon	O
by	O
the	O
Reverend	O
Mr.	O
Charles	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
,	O
Price	O
Bound	O
6	O
d.	O
4	O
.	O
Hymns	O
sacred	O
to	O
the	O
Lord	O
's	O
Table	O
,	O
Collected	O
and	O
Methodised	O
by	O
the	O
Reverend	O
Mr.	O
Charles	O
Owen	O
.	O
Price	O
pound	O
6	O
d.	O
5	O
.	O
Plain-Dealing	O
.	O
or	O
Seperation	O
without	O
Schism	O
and	O
Schism	O
without	O
Seperation	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Reverend	O
Mr.	O
Charles	O
Owen	O
.	O
The	O
Seventh	O
Edition	O
price	O
,	O
6	O
d.	O
6	O
.	O
Observations	O
on	O
sudden	O
Death	O
,	O
Occasion	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
late	O
frequent	O
Instances	O
of	O
it	O
both	O
in	O
the	O
City	O
and	O
Country	O
by	O
the	O
Reverend	O
Mr.	O
Grosvener	O
.	O
Price	O
6d	O
.	O
7	O
.	O
Past	O
Deliverances	O
and	O
present	O
Calamities	O
Improv	O
'd	O
in	O
a	O
Sermon	O
preach	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Reverend	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
.	O
Price	O
.	O
3d	O
.	O
LONDON	O
,	O
Printed	O
for	O
Eman	O
.	O
Matthews	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
in	O
Pater-noster-Row	O
;	O
by	O
M.	O
Jenour	O
against	O
St.	O
Sepulchres	O
Back-Gate	O
in	O
Gilt-Spur-Street	O
near	O
Newgate	O
;	O
and	O
Sold	O
by	O
J.	O
Roberts	O
in	O
Warwick-Lane	O
.	O
Where	O
Advertisements	O
are	O
taken	O
in	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
3	O
d	O
.	O
)	O
