TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bayly	O
,	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
11th	O
,	O
12th	O
,	O
13th	O
and	O
14th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
,	O
1721	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Eighth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
FRYER	I-pers
,	O
Bart	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
Pratt	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Country	O
of	O
Middleses	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
Names	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
London	O
Jury	O
John	B-pers
Elliston	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Hodgson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hampston	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Partington	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
Georgs	B-pers
Leapidge	I-pers
,	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Jackman	I-pers
,	O
Hezekiah	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
Michael	B-pers
Christmas	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Barsby	I-pers
,	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cliff	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hargrave	I-pers
,	O
Abraham	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Ludby	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Baldwin	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Purcival	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Ambler	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Stibbs	I-pers
,	O
Alexander	B-pers
Kilgower	I-pers
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Keene	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	I-pers
(	I-pers
commonly	I-pers
called	I-pers
Half-Hang	I-pers
'd	I-pers
Smith	I-pers
)	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
in	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
and	I-pers
William	I-pers
Loveday	I-pers
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
Steal	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Haines	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
beating	O
his	O
Rounds	O
in	O
Mincing-Lane	B-place
between	O
Four	O
and	O
Five	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
Light	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
up	O
his	O
Heels	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
8	O
Picklock	O
Keys	O
,	O
a	O
Tinder-Box	O
,	O
Flint	O
,	O
Steel	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
confirmed	O
the	O
finding	O
the	O
Picklock	O
Keys	O
,	O
Tinder-Box	O
,	O
etc	O
.	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Curtis	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
lockt	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
safe	O
over	O
Night	O
,	O
both	O
stocklock	O
and	O
Padlock	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
found	O
it	O
open	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
and	O
called	O
James	B-pers
White	I-pers
to	O
discredit	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Haines	I-pers
;	O
but	O
he	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
neither	O
Good	O
nor	O
hurt	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
also	O
called	O
some	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
they	O
knew	O
no	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
bring	O
fully	O
proved	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Notorious	O
Offender	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Fined	O
40	O
Marks	O
,	O
to	O
suffer	O
3	O
Years	O
Imprisonment	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
find	O
security	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
behaviour	O
for	O
3	O
Years	O
after	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Lyon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Peters	I-place
Cheap	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
Ell	O
of	O
Silk	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
5	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cambrick	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Davenport	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Davenport	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
their	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
brought	O
home	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
Silk	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
remarkable	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
she	O
swore	O
to	O
in	O
Court	O
)	O
and	O
about	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
after	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
offer	O
it	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Shudal	O
behind	O
,	O
St.	O
Clements	O
Church	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
she	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
brought	O
in	O
the	O
5	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cambrick	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
it	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
out	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
by	O
6	O
a	O
Clock	O
;	O
and	O
had	O
since	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
pay	O
3	O
l.	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Davenport	O
Senior	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
Cambrick	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
over	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
up	O
Stairs	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
sent	O
one	O
to	O
offer	O
3	O
l.	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Shudal	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
offer	O
'd	O
the	O
Silk	O
to	O
her	O
for	O
7	O
s.	O
Alices	O
Golding	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sold	O
the	O
Silk	O
to	O
her	O
for	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Remnant	O
;	O
and	O
was	O
sure	O
the	O
Silk	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
she	O
bought	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
bought	O
the	O
Silk	O
of	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
(	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
)	O
and	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Drummer	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Gregory	I-place
by	I-place
St.	I-place
Paul	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
dozen	O
of	O
Buttons	O
set	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
value	O
36	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Valentine	B-pers
Grimstead	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
keeps	O
a	O
Toy-Shop	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Church-yard	I-place
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Glass-Case	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
without	O
his	O
Shop	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Styrrup	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Boy	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
whereupon	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
he	O
dropt	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
Boy	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drop	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Warminger	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
9	O
Bowls	O
value	O
31	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
and	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
Bowls	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
De	I-pers
Costa	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Bowling-House	O
at	O
Islington	B-place
;	O
that	O
he	O
advertised	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
News	O
,	O
telling	O
their	O
Marks	O
and	O
offering	O
a	O
Guinea	O
Reward	O
:	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Storier	O
stopt	O
the	O
prisoner	O
offering	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
him	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
before	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
hat	O
he	O
stole	O
them	O
;	O
saying	O
,	O
Poverty	O
made	O
him	O
do	O
it	O
;	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Storier	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
offered	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
Bowls	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
perceiving	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
were	O
advertised	O
,	O
stopt	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Harriot	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
covered	O
over	O
with	O
Nettles	O
;	O
but	O
called	O
none	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
nor	O
any	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
taking	O
his	O
Word	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rice	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Christ	B-place
's	I-place
Church	I-place
Parish	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
6	O
Yards	O
of	O
Bone-Lace	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Elson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
and	O
cheapned	O
Lace	O
;	O
took	O
1	O
piece	O
,	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Bosom	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
seen	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
was	O
followed	O
and	O
apprehended	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Elson	O
was	O
positive	O
she	O
saw	O
him	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Bosom	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
30	O
Pound	O
Weight	O
of	O
Cotton	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Tranter	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
cut	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
2	O
Bags	O
at	O
2	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
the	O
Watchman	O
(	O
Mr.	O
Burlington	O
)	O
with	O
the	O
last	O
parcel	O
in	O
a	O
Blanket	O
upon	O
her	O
Head	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
his	O
Rounds	O
about	O
3	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
She	O
confest	O
her	O
taking	O
the	O
last	O
parcel	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
first	O
was	O
found	O
where	O
she	O
liv	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Riches	I-pers
.	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ethelburga	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
6	O
Yards	O
of	O
Broadcloth	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Jackson	O
had	O
the	O
Cloth	O
to	O
Dye	O
for	O
the	O
East-India-Company	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
cut	O
off	O
6	O
Yards	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
disposed	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
in	O
offering	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
50	O
Guineas	O
to	O
stop	O
a	O
Prosecution	O
against	O
Mr.	O
Parker	O
:	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
granted	O
him	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
and	I-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
his	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
alias	I-pers
,	I-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
Reeve	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	O
his	O
Wife	O
alias	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Reeve	O
Spinster	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
in	O
Counterfeiting	O
the	O
current	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
:	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Bryan	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Perjury	O
in	O
the	O
Tryal	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
for	O
Subornation	O
of	O
Evidence	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Subornation	O
the	O
said	O
Robert	O
Parker	O
was	O
Convicted	O
in	O
Guild-Hall	B-place
the	O
6th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
:	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
Richard	B-pers
Bryan	I-pers
did	O
there	O
swear	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Robert	O
Parker	O
and	O
himself	O
did	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
October	O
1719.	O
walk	O
together	O
from	O
the	O
Cock	O
Alehouse	O
on	O
Ludgate-Hill	O
to	O
the	O
Crown	O
at	O
Ware	O
in	O
Herefordshire	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
Return	O
till	O
the	O
17th	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
all	O
that	O
while	O
together	O
;	O
which	O
if	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Robert	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
could	O
not	O
have	O
been	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Subornation	O
of	O
Evidence	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
charged	O
with	O
.	O
But	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
Richard	B-pers
Bryan	I-pers
being	O
Cross-examined	O
,	O
was	O
then	O
detcted	O
;	O
and	O
now	O
on	O
his	O
Tryal	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
drinking	O
on	O
the	O
said	O
16th	O
of	O
June	O
with	O
Ballance	O
Parker	O
at	O
the	O
Cock	O
Alehouse	O
on	O
Ludgate-Hill	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Fined	O
20	O
Marks	O
,	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
at	O
King-street	O
end	O
,	O
and	O
Suffer	O
6	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
Charlotta	B-pers
Broom	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Felony	O
in	O
taking	O
to	O
Husband	O
Joseph	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
her	O
first	O
Husband	O
Edward	B-pers
Hathaway	I-pers
being	O
then	O
alive	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
first	O
Marriage	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Printed	O
Paper	O
,	O
called	O
a	O
Brunswick	O
Lottery	O
Ticker	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
1720	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Frances	B-pers
Matcalf	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
20	O
s.	O
7	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Frances	O
Mettalf	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
suits	O
of	O
Muslin	O
Pinners	O
,	O
etc	O
.	O
value	O
13	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Girl	I-pers
.	O
It	O
fully	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
at	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
5	O
Leather	O
Stools	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Egg	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
1	O
Bed	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
1	O
Quilt	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Rammidge	I-pers
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
Daniel	O
Egg	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
charge	O
of	O
the	B-place
Ship	I-place
called	I-place
The	I-place
Royal	I-place
Exchange	I-place
,	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Ship	O
broke	O
open	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
gone	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
found	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Rammidge	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Bed	O
and	O
Quilt	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Ship	O
called	O
The	O
Three	O
Johns	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
:	O
The	O
finding	O
the	O
Goods	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
was	O
confirmed	O
by	O
another	O
Evidence	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Shipmate	O
brought	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
him	O
desiring	O
him	O
to	O
keep	O
them	O
for	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
return	O
'd	O
from	O
Sea	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
honestly	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
Indictment	O
,	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Hinds	I-pers
and	O
Francis	B-pers
Coudil	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
at	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Ducks	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
2	O
Geese	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
1	O
Cock	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Walter	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Poultry	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Root	O
the	O
Night	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Risdel	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
himself	O
workt	O
at	O
Tile-making	O
at	O
Islington	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Night	O
aforesaid	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
brought	O
down	O
2	O
Geese	O
and	O
2	O
Ducks	O
into	O
the	O
Kill-Pit	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
asking	O
them	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
show	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
them	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
took	O
the	O
Cockerel	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
back	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Ealing	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Collet	B-pers
Mawhood	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High	O
way	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
with	O
a	O
blue	O
Stone	O
in	O
it	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
by	O
2	O
Highwaymen	O
of	O
his	O
Money	O
and	O
Ring	O
near	O
Hanwell	B-place
Heath	I-place
about	O
5	O
a	O
Clock	O
the	O
afternoon	O
aforesaid	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
That	O
having	O
a	O
great	O
value	O
for	O
the	O
Ring	O
for	O
the	O
sake	O
of	O
the	O
Friend	O
who	O
left	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
begg	O
'd	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
promising	O
them	O
any	O
Consideration	O
,	O
telling	O
them	O
his	O
Name	O
and	O
where	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
;	O
that	O
Hawes	O
returned	O
him	O
his	O
Ring	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Ring	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
Ring	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Hawes	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
himself	O
committed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
restored	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
his	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
again	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
hired	O
their	O
Horses	O
in	O
Bedfordbury	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
committed	O
11	O
Robberies	O
in	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Hawes	O
sent	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
himself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
this	O
Robbery	O
and	O
discover	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Ring	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
begg	O
'd	O
hard	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
Ring	O
again	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
refused	O
to	O
give	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
that	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
the	O
Chief	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Wife	O
brought	O
the	O
Ring	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
Prison	O
,	O
being	O
arrested	O
for	O
Debt	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Hawes	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
lye	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
very	O
full	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Mitchell	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Mitcheller	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
at	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Feather	O
Bolsters	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Kendrick	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodged	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Watchman	O
(	O
Atlee	O
)	O
about	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
at	O
last	O
confest	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
who	O
being	O
sent	O
for	O
came	O
and	O
owned	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
his	O
Trial	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
Man	O
gave	O
him	O
6	O
d.	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
into	O
Southwark	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Courtney	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Fillet	I-pers
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
silver	O
Chain	O
,	O
4	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Gold	O
Dust	O
,	O
2	O
Hand	O
Vices	O
,	O
a	O
Rule	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Nicholas	O
and	O
Peter	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
.	O
He	O
was	O
Second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Else	I-pers
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
an	O
Instrument	O
called	O
a	O
Bassoon	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Samuel	O
Else	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
a	O
square	O
of	O
Glass	O
being	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Sash	O
it	O
was	O
pasted	O
over	O
with	O
Paper	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
broke	O
and	O
the	O
Sash	O
lifted	O
up	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
gone	O
:	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Woodward	O
the	O
Constable	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
his	O
Goods	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Woodward	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Higgins	I-pers
stole	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
Higgins	O
going	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
was	O
stopt	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
made	O
himself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
and	O
discover	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
that	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
both	O
Indictments	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
swore	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Jakeman	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Hand-vices	O
,	O
and	O
verily	O
believed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Higgins	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
himself	O
were	O
drinking	O
at	O
a	O
Brandy-Shop	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
askt	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Ellis	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
helpt	O
him	O
over	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
broke	O
the	O
Paper	O
of	O
the	O
Sash	O
,	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
what	O
he	O
thought	O
fit	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sold	O
them	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
one	O
Buxon	O
and	O
himself	O
committed	O
the	O
other	O
Fact	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
himself	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Window	O
whilst	O
Buxon	O
stood	O
at	O
some	O
distance	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
any	O
Body	O
came	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
notice	O
by	O
crying	O
Tommy	O
;	O
that	O
turning	O
the	O
Pin	O
,	O
the	O
Key	O
fell	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
down	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
broke	O
the	O
Glass	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Instrument	O
out	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
disturbed	O
could	O
get	O
nothing	O
else	O
Samuel	O
Else	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Glass	O
was	O
broke	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
Instrument	O
and	O
a	O
Leaden	O
Inkhorn	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
and	O
owned	O
his	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Higgins	O
made	O
him	O
drunk	O
with	O
Geneva	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Father	O
and	O
Mother	O
were	O
very	O
honest	O
,	O
as	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
formerly	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
lately	O
fallen	O
into	O
ill	O
company	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Cannor	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Conner	I-pers
of	O
Isleworth	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
40	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Draper	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Harvis	I-pers
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Harvis	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
were	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Bed-Chamber	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
taken	O
at	O
London	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
36	O
s.	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Marlow	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
paid	O
his	O
Wife	O
some	O
Money	O
he	O
had	O
borrowed	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
for	O
London	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
coming	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
followed	O
him	O
to	O
London	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
36	O
s.	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
of	O
James	O
Draper	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lent	O
him	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
Stockings	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
for	O
a	O
service	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
brought	O
this	O
Indictment	O
against	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
sake	O
of	O
the	O
reward	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hampstead	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Salts	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Pepper	O
Box	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Saywell	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Usquehaugh	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Oxford-Ale	O
value	O
8	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Flannel	O
Wastcoat	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Baily	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Dillington	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
9	O
Muslin	O
Turnovers	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Pearce	I-pers
;	O
2	O
Neckcloths	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
;	O
a	O
Neckcloth	O
and	O
a	O
Shift	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Greenhall	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Reddish	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
washt	O
for	O
Mrs.	O
Greenhall	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Reddish	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
challenged	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
confest	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Ball	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
accordingly	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Ball	O
also	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
had	O
used	O
his	O
House	O
3	O
Years	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
her	O
for	O
and	O
honest	O
Woman	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Greenall	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
entrusted	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
found	O
her	O
honest	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
at	I-place
Islington	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Brass	O
Candle-sticks	O
values	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hollis	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Plat	O
of	O
Drink	O
smoakt	O
his	O
Pipe	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
Mrs.	O
Hollis	O
was	O
gone	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Candlesticks	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
was	O
immediately	O
followed	O
,	O
and	O
overtaken	O
with	O
them	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
fell	O
on	O
his	O
Knees	O
and	O
begg	O
'd	O
Pardon	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
also	O
owned	O
it	O
on	O
his	O
Trial	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Elliot	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
at	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
2	O
Gowns	O
and	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
1	O
Silk	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
1	O
Diaper	O
Table	O
cloth	O
,	O
18	O
Diaper	O
Napkins	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
Cooper	O
.	O
The	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
was	O
fully	O
proved	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Peak	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
8	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Emmerton	I-pers
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
another	O
Soldier	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
to	O
drink	O
Geneva	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
person	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
set	O
by	O
him	O
and	O
pickt	O
his	O
Pocket	O
of	O
8	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Soldier	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
(	O
a	O
Chandler	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
sells	O
several	O
odd	O
things	O
)	O
very	O
drunk	O
,	O
swore	O
bitterly	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
some	O
Geneva	O
;	O
that	O
at	O
last	O
she	O
let	O
them	O
have	O
2	O
quarterns	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
her	O
Apples	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Basket	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
without	O
paying	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
Half-penny	O
Loaf	O
and	O
hid	O
it	O
under	O
his	O
Breech	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
beat	O
her	O
and	O
used	O
her	O
barbarously	O
,	O
insomuch	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
who	O
let	O
her	O
Blood	O
and	O
put	O
a	O
Searcloth	O
to	O
her	O
Side	O
;	O
and	O
called	O
several	O
who	O
proved	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
said	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
farther	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
not	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
but	O
a	O
Halfpenny	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
her	O
Shop	O
.	O
The	O
Justice	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
when	O
before	O
him	O
owned	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Apples	O
,	O
and	O
beat	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
her	O
a	O
Crown	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
Peace	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
White	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Silk	O
Petticoats	O
25	O
s.	O
a	O
Silk	O
Cloak	O
,	O
a	O
Velvet	O
Scarf	O
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
6	O
Guineas	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Packer	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
their	O
Rooms	O
were	O
next	O
to	O
one	O
another	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
about	O
a	O
Month	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
missing	O
her	O
Goods	O
,	O
examined	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
denied	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
made	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
fetch	O
her	O
Husband	O
to	O
vindicate	O
her	O
.	O
That	O
their	O
Box	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
their	O
Trunk	O
open	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
gone	O
,	O
most	O
of	O
which	O
they	O
found	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
searching	O
after	O
her	O
they	O
found	O
her	O
lockt	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Closet	O
in	O
a	O
Garret	O
in	O
Wild-Street	O
.	O
Her	O
Pawning	O
the	O
Goods	O
was	O
proved	O
by	O
the	O
several	O
Pawnbrokers	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pledged	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Door	O
and	O
Trunk	O
were	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
intended	O
to	O
restore	O
them	O
:	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
first	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Emanuel	B-pers
Giles	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
at	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dikes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
at	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Charles	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Pen-knife	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
a	O
Steal	O
Seal	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
8	O
d.	O
1/2	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
from	O
London	O
he	O
was	O
stopt	O
by	O
Issac	O
Drew	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
clapt	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
his	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
stand	O
quietly	O
he	O
would	O
shoot	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
Seal	O
,	O
and	O
Pen-knife	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
clapt	O
the	O
Pistol	O
to	O
his	O
Breast	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
plain	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
a	O
fine	O
Star-Light	O
Night	O
.	O
Issac	O
Drew	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisner	O
and	O
himself	O
stopt	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
took	O
the	O
Seal	O
,	O
Pen-Knife	O
and	O
Eightpence	O
Halfpenny	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
conceal	O
'd	O
from	O
him	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
and	O
sunk	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
clapt	O
the	O
Pistol	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Breast	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
informed	O
that	O
Dikes	O
and	O
Drew	O
went	O
on	O
the	O
Footpad	O
,	O
dog	O
'd	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
together	O
;	O
that	O
Dikes	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
could	O
make	O
a	O
Discovery	O
against	O
Drew	O
of	O
some	O
Trifles	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
great	O
Sums	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
an	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
elsewhere	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Sister	O
sent	O
for	O
her	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
askt	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Friday	O
or	O
Saturday	O
before	O
Bartholomewtide	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
she	O
differ	O
'd	O
widely	O
in	O
point	O
of	O
time	O
.	O
He	O
also	O
called	O
some	O
to	O
discredit	O
Drew	O
's	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
Hang	O
a	O
Hundred	O
before	O
be	O
would	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
himself	O
.	O
He	O
also	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Morgan	B-pers
Oxton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Finchley	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
4	O
Weather	O
Sheep	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Rotheram	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Calf	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Melchior	B-pers
Acres	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Vernham	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
and	O
left	O
his	O
Watch	O
hanging	O
up	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
Back	O
he	O
mist	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
told	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Man	O
found	O
out	O
where	O
it	O
it	O
was	O
pawned	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Griffiths	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
keeping	O
a	O
Cook	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
brought	O
a	O
Watch	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
telling	O
her	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
Trouble	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
pawn	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
for	O
40	O
s.	O
for	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
Red	O
Coat	O
might	O
be	O
scrupled	O
:	O
that	O
she	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
for	O
30	O
s.	O
The	O
Watch	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
Pawn	O
Broker	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Kendrick	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
no	O
body	O
came	O
near	O
the	O
Watch	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
Woman	O
in	O
Monmouth-street	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
in	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
5	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Thread	O
value	O
11	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
Stuft	O
Wastcoats	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Crowden	I-pers
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
lockt	O
the	O
Doors	O
of	O
his	O
Closet	O
and	O
Room	O
,	O
but	O
left	O
the	O
Keys	O
in	O
and	O
did	O
but	O
step	O
into	O
the	O
next	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Leach	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
hearing	O
somebody	O
go	O
along	O
the	O
Entry	O
,	O
followed	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Thread	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
in	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
James	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
in	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Riding-Hood	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hilton	I-pers
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Popler	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Poplinton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Porridge-pot	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
North	I-pers
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
she	O
stole	O
the	O
Pot	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
in	O
Jewin-Street	O
but	O
enquiring	O
of	O
that	O
Person	O
,	O
he	O
declared	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
buy	O
it	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
nor	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Jury	O
looking	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
poor	O
crasy	O
Creature	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
the	O
said	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Aucott	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Chelsea	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
her	O
Male	O
Infant	O
Child	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
Second	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Churchill	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
examining	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
Miscarried	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Child	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Trunk	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
this	O
Evidence	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
alone	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Child	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
full	O
Growth	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
saw	O
no	O
Marks	O
of	O
Violence	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Price	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
Order	O
,	O
acquainted	O
her	O
Mistress	O
,	O
who	O
sent	O
her	O
for	O
Mrs.	O
Churchill	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
Evidence	O
went	O
to	O
London	O
about	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
deliver	O
'd	O
between	O
4	O
and	O
5.	O
that	O
they	O
found	O
some	O
Linnen	O
in	O
her	O
Trunk	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
of	O
a	O
sudden	O
when	O
no	O
Body	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
but	O
her	O
self	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
made	O
Provision	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Churchill	O
confirmed	O
the	O
finding	O
the	O
Linnen	O
in	O
her	O
Trunk	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Greenwell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.Sepulchres	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tobacco-box	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ashbyshaw	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
Sufficient	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Bunn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Purse	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
9	O
Guineas	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
Of	O
Allhallows	B-place
Barkin	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Leather	O
Trunk	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
3	O
Camblet	O
Ridinghoods	O
value	O
6l	O
.	O
5	O
pair	O
of	O
Mens	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
1000	O
Pins	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Du-Guard	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Slow	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5	O
th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bartholomew	I-place
the	I-place
Less	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
half	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
Holland	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
suit	O
of	O
Headclothes	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
4	O
l.	O
6	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
number	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Brittain	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
Brittain	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
.	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prose	O
cutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
who	O
missing	O
his	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Breeches	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
one	O
Night	O
rose	O
out	O
of	O
Bed	O
and	O
told	O
it	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
mist	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
;	O
and	O
acquainting	O
his	O
Wife	O
therewith	O
the	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
dropt	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
about	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
finding	O
it	O
there	O
,	O
lockt	O
into	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Box	O
wheresthe	O
sound	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
wrapt	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Holland	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
cut	O
off	O
from	O
a	O
piece	O
her	O
Mistress	O
had	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
acquainted	O
her	O
Husband	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
who	O
lookt	O
in	O
a	O
Bag	O
of	O
Money	O
he	O
had	O
by	O
him	O
of	O
above	O
60	O
l.	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
told	O
over	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
and	O
mist	O
that	O
Sum	O
,	O
whereupon	O
they	O
called	O
in	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Neighbours	O
and	O
charged	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
who	O
confessed	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Box	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Master	O
's	O
Bag	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Bosom	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
13	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
saying	O
it	O
was	O
their	O
Money	O
.	O
Her	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Allchorn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Allhallows	B-place
Barkin	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
80	O
Pound	O
Weight	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Tobias	B-pers
Bowles	I-pers
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
near	O
100	O
Hogsheads	O
upon	O
the	O
Key	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Coopers	O
employed	O
,	O
who	O
when	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
Dinner	O
took	O
some	O
Tobacco	O
off	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Barrel	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
His	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Currey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Magnus	I-place
the	I-place
Martyr	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Underwood	I-pers
,	O
by	O
throwing	O
him	O
from	O
the	O
Deck	O
of	O
a	O
Ship	O
into	O
the	O
River	O
of	O
Thames	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
on	O
the	O
Deck	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
were	O
in	O
their	O
Cabbins	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
the	O
Mare	O
of	O
the	O
Ship	O
)	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
up	O
again	O
with	O
his	O
Coat	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
askt	O
him	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
what	O
Noise	O
that	O
was	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
Boys	O
and	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Officers	O
made	O
it	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
before	O
the	O
Mast	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
refusing	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
to	O
beat	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
,	O
though	O
lame	O
in	O
one	O
Arm	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
Cornish	O
Man	O
,	O
threw	O
him	O
down	O
several	O
times	O
and	O
had	O
so	O
far	O
the	O
Advantage	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
enough	O
,	O
and	O
promised	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
alone	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
he	O
followed	O
him	O
again	O
round	O
the	O
Mast	O
and	O
the	O
Capstearn	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
coming	O
up	O
would	O
have	O
prevented	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
following	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
Scuffled	O
upon	O
the	O
Deck	O
and	O
fell	O
over-board	O
together	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
Rope	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
Deceased	O
.	O
Edmund	B-pers
Makepeace	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
had	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
down	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
him	O
get	O
up	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
hearing	O
the	O
Disturbance	O
laid	O
his	O
Hand	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Breast	O
and	O
reasoned	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
beat	O
him	O
too	O
,	O
so	O
fell	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
had	O
several	O
Falls	O
on	O
the	O
Deck	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
both	O
fell	O
over	O
the	O
Gunnel	O
together	O
:	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
thrown	O
over	O
by	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
pull	O
'd	O
him	O
in	O
twice	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Doddington	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
particularly	O
their	O
falling	O
over	O
together	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Broadway	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
Hold	O
stowing	O
a	O
Pipe	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
the	O
would	O
strike	O
a	O
Crow	O
through	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
cut	O
his	O
Throat	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
:	O
and	O
being	O
asked	O
how	O
long	O
ago	O
that	O
was	O
,	O
answered	O
,	O
at	O
Port	O
,	O
6	O
Weeks	O
before	O
this	O
happen	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
fighting	O
then	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
weary	O
with	O
,	O
unlading	O
several	O
Wines	O
,	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
Cabbin	O
asleep	O
;	O
but	O
hearing	O
a	O
Noise	O
got	O
up	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
Ship	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
the	O
charge	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
finding	O
Matthews	O
on	O
the	O
Deck	O
and	O
Suspecting	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
Disturbance	O
,	O
he	O
order	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
before	O
the	O
Mast	O
,	O
(	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Fore-Mast-Man	O
)	O
which	O
he	O
refusing	O
,	O
he	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
force	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
having	O
no	O
Shoes	O
on	O
,	O
Matthews	O
stampt	O
on	O
his	O
Toes	O
and	O
threw	O
him	O
down	O
several	O
times	O
:	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
assaulted	O
him	O
also	O
;	O
beat	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
him	O
over-board	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
after	O
himself	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
swim	O
,	O
so	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
bottom	O
;	O
yet	O
by	O
the	O
Providence	O
of	O
God	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
;	O
though	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
who	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
swim	O
over	O
him	O
,	O
was	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
.	O
And	O
called	O
the	O
following	O
Evidence	O
to	O
the	O
Fact	O
and	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Winch	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
help	O
'd	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Ship	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
stop	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
by	O
the	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
both	O
fell	O
over	O
.	O
Capt	B-pers
Tyson	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Mate	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
himself	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
askt	O
,	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
did	O
his	O
Duty	O
also	O
.	O
Capt	B-pers
Sarjeant	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
his	O
Duty	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
Civil	O
Man	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
his	O
Boatswain	O
,	O
a	O
very	O
quarrelsome	O
Man	O
,	O
laid	O
violent	O
Hands	O
of	O
him	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
pull	O
'd	O
our	O
4	O
of	O
his	O
Teeth	O
,	O
and	O
followed	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
Cabbin	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
also	O
Assaulted	O
his	O
Mate	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
.	O
Capt	O
.	O
Testard	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Second	O
Mate	O
,	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
and	O
another	O
going	O
to	O
play	O
at	O
Drafts	O
on	O
a	O
Sunday	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
them	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
Assaulted	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
afterterwards	O
took	O
a	O
Boat-Hook	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
stick	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
's	O
)	O
Back	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
threw	O
him	O
over-board	O
,	O
and	O
hald	O
in	O
all	O
the	O
Ropes	O
to	O
prevent	O
his	O
coming	O
on	O
Board	O
again	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
forc	O
'd	O
to	O
swim	O
to	O
another	O
Ship	O
at	O
some	O
distance	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
return	O
'd	O
he	O
struck	O
his	O
Knife	O
into	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
hinder	O
his	O
coming	O
on	O
Board	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Tyler	I-pers
,	O
by	O
striking	O
,	O
kicking	O
,	O
and	O
bruising	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
Neck	O
,	O
Breast	O
,	O
Stomach	O
,	O
Belly	O
and	O
Privy	O
Parts	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
last	O
:	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Month	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
Manslaughter	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Foot	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Timber	O
.	O
and	O
ordered	O
the	O
Deceased	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
measure	O
it	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
Yard	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
Deceased	O
for	O
a	O
little	O
Money	O
he	O
owed	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
pusht	O
at	O
one	O
another	O
,	O
fell	O
to	O
fighting	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
threw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
himself	O
,	O
got	O
off	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
went	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
complained	O
greatly	O
of	O
his	O
Hurt	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Dram	O
.	O
And	O
being	O
examined	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
received	O
same	O
Hurt	O
formerly	O
by	O
lifting	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Timber	O
,	O
which	O
occasion	O
'd	O
the	O
running	O
of	O
the	O
Reins	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
make	O
Water	O
.	O
That	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Stump	O
of	O
a	O
Post	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
fighting	O
:	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
kick	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
nor	O
stamp	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
fall	O
on	O
the	O
stump	O
for	O
ought	O
he	O
knew	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
after	O
Mr	O
.	O
Foot	O
had	O
given	O
the	O
Deceased	O
a	O
Dram	O
(	O
she	O
held	O
him	O
up	O
)	O
he	O
vomitted	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Blood	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
lookt	O
in	O
his	O
Face	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
not	O
Dead	O
yet	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
your	O
Wife	O
you	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
I	O
had	O
kill	O
'd	O
you	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Lamb	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
askt	O
for	O
Mrs.	O
Tyler	O
.	O
askt	O
her	O
if	O
her	O
Husband	O
was	O
come	O
home	O
;	O
who	O
answering	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
it	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
have	O
kill	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
will	O
never	O
come	O
home	O
more	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
seemed	O
pretty	O
well	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
following	O
about	O
6	O
a	O
Clock	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
complained	O
of	O
his	O
Belly	O
and	O
Privy	O
Parts	O
.	O
Mrs	O
Tyler	O
confirmed	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
farther	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
said	O
Thomas	O
Hill	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
askt	O
,	O
said	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
had	O
some	O
Mischance	O
formerly	O
but	O
was	O
pretty	O
well	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
able	O
to	O
work	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bishop	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
helpt	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
Deceased	O
home	O
;	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
;	O
that	O
one	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
some	O
Words	O
and	O
kickt	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Belly	O
,	O
which	O
occasioned	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
reacht	O
and	O
brought	O
up	O
Blood	O
and	O
Water	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Burton	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
several	O
Tumours	O
on	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Body	O
,	O
a	O
great	O
one	O
upon	O
the	O
Scrotum	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Mortification	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
his	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
by	O
some	O
Injury	O
lately	O
received	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
and	O
he	O
were	O
Sawyers	O
and	O
workt	O
together	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
got	O
a	O
strain	O
by	O
lifting	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Timber	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
work	O
a-Top	O
but	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
a-Top	O
.	O
and	O
used	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
make	O
Water	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
times	O
in	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
cry	O
out	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
lent	O
the	O
Deceased	O
a	O
little	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
in	O
great	O
Straits	O
went	O
to	O
ask	O
it	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
pusht	O
him	O
,	O
beat	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
he	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
being	O
then	O
very	O
drunk	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
pusht	O
and	O
struck	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
several	O
times	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
fell	O
down	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
fell	O
with	O
his	O
Belly	O
on	O
the	O
Post	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
kick	O
the	O
Deceased	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Hussey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
;	O
Cole	O
adding	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
twice	O
to	O
fight	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
refused	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
put	O
it	O
off	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Deceased	O
got	O
him	O
up	O
against	O
a	O
Wall	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
defended	O
himself	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
with	O
his	O
open	O
Hand	O
,	O
(	O
being	O
drunk	O
)	O
that	O
he	O
(	O
Cole	O
)	O
followed	O
the	O
Deceased	O
into	O
a	O
Coach-House	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
complained	O
much	O
,	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
fell	O
against	O
a	O
Post	O
,	O
had	O
hurt	O
his	O
Belly	O
,	O
and	O
believed	O
he	O
had	O
moved	O
the	O
Cause	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
ill	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
an	O
Orderly	O
quiet	O
Man	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Olave	I-place
in	I-place
Southwark	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Boat-Hook	O
near	O
the	O
Left	O
Hip	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Length	O
of	O
One	O
Inch	O
and	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
One	O
Inch	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22nd	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
;	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
Vintrey	I-place
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
his	O
Hitcher	O
against	O
the	O
Deceased	O
upon	O
the	O
Thames	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
and	O
shewed	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
stabb	O
'd	O
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Bradford	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
Deceased	O
to	O
Pepper-Alley	O
to	O
seek	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
shewed	O
him	O
his	O
Wound	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
wisht	O
he	O
had	O
struck	O
his	O
Staff	O
in	O
his	O
Heart	O
's	O
Blood	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
ran	O
against	O
his	O
Boat	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
the	O
Deceased	O
(	O
her	O
Kinsman	O
)	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
wounded	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
Bridge	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Tide	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
going	O
Cross	O
to	O
come	O
through	O
against	O
the	O
Tide	O
,	O
their	O
Boat-Heads	O
met	O
:	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
he	O
had	O
staved	O
his	O
(	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
)	O
Boat	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Number	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
got	O
clear	O
and	O
stabb	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
in	O
his	O
Agony	O
,	O
Cry	O
'd	O
,	O
this	O
Rogue	O
has	O
Murder	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
fear	O
'd	O
it	O
would	O
kill	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
prosecute	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
thought	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
Rest	O
.	O
That	O
when	O
she	O
apprehended	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Defence	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Deceased	O
struck	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
Fist	O
and	O
Scull	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
asking	O
him	O
why	O
he	O
wisht	O
his	O
Staff	O
in	O
his	O
Heart	O
's	O
Blood	O
;	O
he	O
answered	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
Passion	O
:	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Dying	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Let	O
him	O
Die	O
and	O
be	O
D	O
-	O
nd	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
die	O
quietly	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
declared	O
on	O
his	O
Death-Bed	O
before	O
receiving	O
the	O
Sacrament	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Bodily	O
Health	O
,	O
had	O
no	O
Pains	O
or	O
Aches	O
about	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
him	O
that	O
Wound	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
strike	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
his	O
Scull	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
with	O
his	O
Fist	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Miller	O
confirmed	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
askt	O
her	O
Husband	O
if	O
he	O
forgave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
who	O
answered	O
,	O
that	O
in	O
one	O
respect	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
but	O
Blood	O
for	O
Blood	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
Rowing	O
cross	O
from	O
Billinsgate	O
to	O
hale	O
through	O
Bridge	O
the	O
Deceased	O
fell	O
a	O
Broad-side	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Boat	O
in	O
the	O
Eddy	O
,	O
carried	O
him	O
down	O
a	O
great	O
way	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
Son	O
of	O
a	O
Bitch	O
,	O
struck	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
Fist	O
,	O
afterward	O
with	O
his	O
Scull	O
and	O
hurt	O
his	O
Arm	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
followed	O
him	O
to	O
Pepper	O
Alley	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
satisfied	O
with	O
fighting	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Wheatley	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
set	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
through	O
Bridge	O
,	O
who	O
shewed	O
him	O
his	O
Arm	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Skin	O
was	O
rased	O
and	O
a	O
Bruise	O
,	O
which	O
looks	O
as	O
fresh	O
done	O
by	O
a	O
stroak	O
with	O
a	O
Scull	O
or	O
Staff	O
.	O
The	O
Surgeon	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
not	O
above	O
Half	O
an	O
Inch	O
deep	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
look	O
upon	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
Mortal	O
without	O
an	O
ill	O
State	O
of	O
Body	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
laid	O
it	O
open	O
lower	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
appeared	O
to	O
him	O
no	O
Danger	O
,	O
no	O
Mortification	O
:	O
that	O
he	O
opened	O
him	O
after	O
his	O
Decease	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
every	O
thing	O
within	O
the	O
Abdomen	O
well	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Thorax	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Matter	O
spun	O
out	O
.	O
about	O
5	O
Pints	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
believed	O
was	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
;	O
though	O
not	O
occasion	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Wound	O
,	O
neither	O
could	O
he	O
tell	O
from	O
what	O
Cause	O
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Goodby	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
Pepper-Alley	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
came	O
thither	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
see	O
what	O
you	O
have	O
done	O
,	O
pulling	O
up	O
his	O
Shirt	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
see	O
what	O
you	O
have	O
done	O
,	O
shewing	O
his	O
Arm	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hicks	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Deceased	O
say	O
that	O
he	O
struck	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
Check	O
with	O
his	O
Hand	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Arm	O
bloody	O
,	O
as	O
just	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
believed	O
that	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
done	O
by	O
setting	O
his	O
Boat	O
through	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Eales	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
challenged	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ashore	O
to	O
fight	O
him	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
deposed	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Crow	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
in	I-place
Whitchapel	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Douglas	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
William	O
Crow	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
driving	O
an	O
empty	O
Cart	O
with	O
4	O
Horses	O
the	O
Fore-Horse	O
did	O
strike	O
and	O
throw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
to	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
near	O
Wheel	O
of	O
the	O
Cart	O
ran	O
over	O
the	O
Small	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Back	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
instantly	O
died	O
:	O
And	O
James	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
for	O
Aiding	O
and	O
Abetting	O
him	O
therein	O
.	O
William	O
Crow	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
Manslaughter	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
looking	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Window	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
the	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
Cart	O
or	O
Waggon	O
drive	O
very	O
furiously	O
along	O
,	O
he	O
lookt	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
Woman	O
with	O
a	O
Child	O
in	O
her	O
Arms	O
,	O
the	O
Fore-House	O
struck	O
the	O
Woman	O
down	O
and	O
the	O
Child	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Wheel	O
ran	O
over	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
who	O
never	O
spoke	O
after	O
:	O
that	O
both	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Cart	O
,	O
and	O
drove	O
as	O
hard	O
as	O
they	O
could	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Widger	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
just	O
by	O
when	O
the	O
Fore-Horse	O
beat	O
the	O
Deceased	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Child	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Arms	O
:	O
That	O
the	O
Cart	O
was	O
drawn	O
by	O
4	O
Horses	O
,	O
and	O
both	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
the	O
Cart	O
,	O
who	O
drove	O
violently	O
:	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
past	O
2	O
Carts	O
that	O
were	O
standing	O
still	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
run	O
over	O
by	O
this	O
Brick-Cart	O
:	O
and	O
being	O
askt	O
whether	O
the	O
Pisoners	O
did	O
not	O
stop	O
their	O
Cart	O
and	O
jump	O
down	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
answered	O
,	O
that	O
neither	O
of	O
them	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
nor	O
stopt	O
their	O
Horses	O
,	O
but	O
whipt	O
them	O
and	O
drove	O
away	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
they	O
could	O
,	O
without	O
taking	O
any	O
manner	O
of	O
Care	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lisle	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
adding	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
60	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Drayman	O
whipt	O
their	O
Horses	O
,	O
which	O
set	O
them	O
on	O
a	O
Gallop	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
stop	O
them	O
.	O
But	O
they	O
were	O
told	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
an	O
unlawful	O
Act	O
,	O
by	O
riding	O
in	O
their	O
Cart	O
in	O
a	O
publick	O
Road	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
prohibited	O
by	O
Law	O
,	O
and	O
ought	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
leading	O
their	O
Horses	O
,	O
which	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
done	O
(	O
as	O
was	O
their	O
Duty	O
)	O
would	O
have	O
prevented	O
this	O
Mischief	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Scott	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
crow	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
Cart	O
;	O
that	O
Browne	O
was	O
his	O
Father	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
Crow	O
to	O
unload	O
the	O
Bricks	O
;	O
but	O
Crow	O
had	O
the	O
Whip	O
.	O
And	O
being	O
askt	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Father	O
and	O
himself	O
were	O
Partners	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
of	O
them	O
honest	O
civil	O
Men	O
.	O
Another	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Crow	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
2	O
Years	O
as	O
a	O
Carter	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Servant	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
Browne	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Crow	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Field	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
in	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
a	O
Muslin	O
Hood	O
,	O
a	O
Riding-Hood	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
9	O
l.	O
the	O
Good	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Autherley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
of	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
9	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	O
Autherley	O
:	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
her	O
Room	O
at	O
9	O
a	O
Clock	O
that	O
Morning	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
before	O
Eleven	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
found	O
her	O
Door	O
open	O
and	O
her	O
Goods	O
gone	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
found	O
her	O
Goods	O
in	O
Mackain	O
's	O
Shop	O
in	O
Field-Lane	O
;	O
who	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
.	O
Katherine	B-pers
Mackain	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
bought	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	O
Harris	O
(	O
who	O
went	O
about	O
the	O
Streets	O
with	O
Earthen	O
Ware	O
)	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
51	O
s.	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Harris	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Field	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Merrick	I-pers
and	O
her	O
self	O
committed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
who	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
of	O
a	O
pretty	O
Ken	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
could	O
touch	O
,	O
for	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
up	O
with	O
her	O
Punch-Bowl	O
,	O
none	O
would	O
suspect	O
her	O
:	O
that	O
he	O
slipt	O
up	O
first	O
,	O
she	O
followed	O
with	O
the	O
Punch-Bowl	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
to	O
cover	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
Merrick	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
to	O
watch	O
:	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
with	O
a	O
Picklock-Key	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
put	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
small	O
Bag	O
,	O
and	O
ty	O
'd	O
the	O
rest	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
large	O
Blue	O
Apron	O
of	O
hers	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
down	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
carried	O
the	O
Bundle	O
down	O
on	O
her	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
Merrick	O
:	O
That	O
she	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
carried	O
them	O
directly	O
to	O
Mackain	O
's	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
for	O
51	O
s.	O
whilst	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Merrick	O
waited	O
at	O
the	O
Salutation	O
Tavern	O
for	O
her	O
Return	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
they	O
left	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Wife	O
behind	O
at	O
Westminster	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Grantland	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
a	O
Search	O
Warrant	O
for	O
Elizabeth	O
Harris	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
Charterhouse-Lane	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
carried	O
her	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
made	O
her	O
self	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
this	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
Harris	O
swore	O
against	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
Malice	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
to	O
save	O
her	O
own	O
Life	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
,	O
and	O
hang	O
'd	O
her	O
Husband	O
about	O
a	O
Year	O
ago	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
Shadwell	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
;	O
and	O
called	O
the	O
following	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
his	O
Defence	O
.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Field	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
his	O
Brother	O
)	O
was	O
at	O
their	O
House	O
in	O
SunTavern-Fields	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
own	O
in	O
Chambers-Street	O
,	O
all	O
that	O
Day	O
,	O
too	O
and	O
fro	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
about	O
8	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
delighting	O
in	O
Ringing	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
the	O
Bells	O
Chime	O
,	O
askt	O
him	O
if	O
it	O
were	O
any	O
Holyday	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
reply	O
'd	O
no	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Fast-Day	O
for	O
the	O
Martyrdom	O
of	O
K.	O
Charles	O
I	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
Harris	O
threatned	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Field	I-pers
(	O
the	O
Father	O
)	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
their	O
House	O
at	O
8	O
a	O
Clock	O
that	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
till	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
then	O
went	O
with	O
his	O
Brother	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
House	O
:	O
that	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
is	O
a	O
Shoe-maker	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Sons	O
works	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
That	O
Harris	O
threatned	O
to	O
Mob	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Windows	O
were	O
broke	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
left	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
an	O
ill	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
leave	O
her	O
old	O
Courses	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
took	O
him	O
home	O
to	O
prevent	O
the	O
Gang	O
following	O
him	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
Harris	O
say	O
(	O
when	O
her	O
Husband	O
was	O
condemn	O
'd	O
)	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
stick	O
or	O
poison	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
if	O
she	O
could	O
get	O
into	O
his	O
Company	O
.	O
Other	O
Evidences	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Father	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Man	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
liv	O
'd	O
a	O
regular	O
Life	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
left	O
that	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Town	O
,	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
matter	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
Evidence	O
that	O
affected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
but	O
Harris	O
's	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
Entring	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Day	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Gold	O
Chain	O
and	O
Locket	O
,	O
2	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
and	O
44	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
James	O
Day	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
and	O
three	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
fourth	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Ridinghood	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Hood	O
,	O
2	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
,	O
2	O
Holland	O
Shifts	O
,	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
Pinners	O
,	O
a	O
Carbine-Belt	O
,	O
a	O
Housing	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Williams	B-pers
Russ	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Ham	I-pers
:	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
other	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
than	O
that	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
these	O
3	O
Indictments	O
also	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Trantrum	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ethelburga	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Jacob	B-pers
De	I-pers
Villa	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
2	O
Gowns	O
and	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
Guineas	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hammond	I-pers
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
Plate	O
,	O
Linnen	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
value	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
and	O
Camblet	O
Riding-Hood	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
fourth	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Randolph	B-pers
Walstead	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
his	O
Goods	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Storey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	O
Mary	O
in	O
Whitechapel	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Edmand	B-pers
Juby	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
20	O
Hats	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Trantrum	I-pers
and	O
Philip	B-pers
Storey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
in	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
together	O
with	O
Christian	B-pers
Leonard	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Pepper	O
Box	O
,	O
Strainer	O
,	O
and	O
Tongs	O
,	O
200	O
Yards	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
20	O
Turnovers	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Coverly	I-pers
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
Trantrum	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
again	O
indicted	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botoplh	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Gascoign	I-pers
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
they	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
again	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Nicholson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
his	O
Goods	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
they	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
again	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hadduck	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
stealing	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
Trantrum	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
again	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
her	O
Goods	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
Trantrum	O
plead	O
Guilty	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
again	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Omans	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
his	O
Goods	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
they	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Hogg	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Felony	O
:	O
that	O
whereas	O
William	B-pers
Spiggot	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
did	O
Assault	O
John	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
(	O
the	O
Monmouth	O
Carrier	O
)	O
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
a	O
Holland	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
3	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
2	O
Turkish	O
Habbits	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
200	O
l.	O
for	O
which	O
Felony	O
and	O
Robbery	O
they	O
were	O
Convicted	O
at	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
at	O
the	O
Sessions	O
held	O
there	O
last	O
January	O
:	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
James	O
Hogg	O
did	O
receive	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
in	O
receiving	O
Goods	O
stole	O
from	O
Doraohy	O
Crisp	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Watkins	O
's	O
Watch	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Pocket	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Chain	O
and	O
Seal	O
were	O
changed	O
:	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
carried	O
the	O
Shoes	O
,	O
Stays	O
,	O
Gown	O
,	O
2	O
Turkish	O
Habits	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
to	O
Judith	B-pers
Clifford	I-pers
's	O
to	O
sell	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
disposed	O
of	O
several	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
but	O
finding	O
an	O
Advertisement	O
describing	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
sent	O
the	O
rest	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
by	O
his	O
Order	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Watch	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Cotterel	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
his	O
Wife	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
Katherine	B-pers
Cotterel	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
left	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
with	O
her	O
Husband	O
to	O
sell	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
10	O
Years	O
,	O
for	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
Marks	O
it	O
had	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
very	O
well	O
describe	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
Tompion	O
's	O
Make	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
knew	O
the	O
Chain	O
and	O
Seal	O
very	O
well	O
:	O
but	O
the	O
Watch	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
Burges	O
's	O
Make	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Downws	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Tilley	O
deposed	O
they	O
knew	O
it	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
by	O
what	O
they	O
had	O
done	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
particularly	O
the	O
Verge	O
and	O
Balance	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Watkins	O
has	O
had	O
it	O
3	O
Years	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Watkins	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
it	O
well	O
,	O
had	O
had	O
it	O
5	O
Years	O
.	O
He	O
also	O
called	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
invalidate	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
Judith	B-pers
Clifford	I-pers
and	O
her	O
Daughter	O
;	O
but	O
in	O
vain	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
committed	O
before	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
July	O
the	O
Court	O
respited	O
his	O
Judgment	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Garment	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Parrin	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ashworth	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Heyford	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
in	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Nusance	O
,	O
in	O
throwing	O
Blood	O
and	O
Excrements	O
of	O
Beasts	O
into	O
the	O
Streets	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
they	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
Fined	O
40	O
s.	O
each	O
.	O
The	O
Tryal	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Mist	I-pers
the	O
Printer	O
was	O
put	O
off	O
till	O
next	O
Sessions	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
several	O
Affidavits	O
made	O
and	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
ill	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Bed	O
and	O
Room	O
into	O
the	O
Air	O
without	O
manifest	O
Danger	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
.	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
's	O
Tryal	O
was	O
also	O
put	O
off	O
till	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
6.	O
John	B-pers
Trantrum	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Courtney	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Dikes	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Philip	B-pers
Storey	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
7.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Curry	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	O
Hill	O
,	O
Williams	O
Palmer	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
alias	O
Lyon	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Crow	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Kelley	I-pers
,	O
the	O
two	O
last	O
formerly	O
Convicted	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
,	O
16.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Drummer	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Warminger	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rice	I-pers
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Riches	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Cannor	I-pers
alias	O
Connor	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
alias	O
Dissington	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
alias	O
White	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Calf	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Hind	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Coudil	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
alias	O
Michener	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
James	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
,	O
a.	O
Charles	B-pers
Allchorn	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Katharine	O
Baker	O
,	O
the	O
last	O
formerly	O
Convicted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
(	O
commonly	O
called	O
Half-hang	O
'd	O
Smith	O
)	O
was	O
Fined	O
40	O
Marks	O
,	O
to	O
suffer	O
3	O
Years	O
Imprisonment	O
and	O
find	O
Security	O
for	O
3	O
Years	O
after	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Bryan	I-pers
,	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
against	O
King-Street	O
End	O
,	O
Fined	O
20	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
suffer	O
6	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
Dianah	O
Cole	O
,	O
formerly	O
Convicted	O
of	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
in	O
receiving	O
stolen	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
consideration	O
of	O
her	O
Poverty	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
several	O
Months	O
imprison	O
'd	O
,	O
was	O
Fined	O
5	O
Marks	O
only	O
.	O
