TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
'S	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
.	O
During	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
the	O
Rt	O
.	O
Honble	O
Sir	O
Gerard	O
Conyers	O
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
9th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
1723	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
Humfreys	O
,	O
in	O
Bartholomew	O
Lane	O
,	O
behind	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
;	O
and	O
E.	O
Symon	O
,	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Pope	O
's	O
Head	O
Alley	O
Cornhill	O
.	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice	O
Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
5th	O
,	O
6th	O
,	O
and	O
7th	O
,	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
December	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Ninth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
GERARD	B-pers
CONYERS	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
King	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Aires	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
,	O
Esquire	O
,	O
Deputy-Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
JURORS	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
The	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wicks	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
Tho	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Ventridge	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Dutton	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Silver	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Levet	I-pers
,	O
Ambrose	B-pers
Rule	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Dolliff	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Wudger	I-pers
,	O
Tho	B-pers
Stebbin	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Fairchild	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Whitehurst	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Salisbury	I-pers
,	O
Cornelius	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
Allen	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
Percival	B-pers
Ludgate	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Passewater	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Percival	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hyde	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolph	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
English	O
Common-Prayer	O
Books	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Parish	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Books	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
suppos	O
'd	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
of	O
a	O
Burial	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
said	O
Church	O
;	O
that	O
having	O
advertis	O
'd	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
publick	O
News	O
,	O
Information	O
being	O
given	O
where	O
the	O
Books	O
were	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
accordingly	O
,	O
in	O
Rag	O
Fair	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
.	O
R.	O
Armstrong	O
,	O
a	O
Dealer	O
in	O
Old	O
Clothes	O
,	O
Etc	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Stealing	O
of	O
the	O
Books	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
another	O
Woman	O
in	O
Rag	O
Fair	O
for	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
Armstrong	O
for	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Lothbury	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Flock	O
Bed	O
,	O
Bolster	O
and	O
Rug	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Burroughs	I-pers
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
being	O
Car-Men	O
,	O
were	O
removing	O
Goods	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
from	O
the	O
Cart	O
to	O
carry	O
in	O
some	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Bed	O
upon	O
their	O
return	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
off	O
from	O
the	O
Cart	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
running	O
in	O
search	O
after	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
holding	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Arms	O
against	O
a	O
Wall	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
coming	O
a	O
long	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
fling	O
it	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
Dirt	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
holding	O
it	O
while	O
some	O
Body	O
came	O
to	O
own	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Excuse	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Barthia	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Horse-Man	O
's	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Distiller	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
some	O
strong	O
Waters	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
her	O
Money	O
was	O
changing	O
took	O
the	O
Coat	O
off	O
from	O
the	O
Rails	O
of	O
a	O
Stair-Case	O
where	O
it	O
being	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
her	O
Apron	O
was	O
carrying	O
it	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
discovered	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Coat	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
her	O
taking	O
the	O
Coat	O
,	O
or	O
ever	O
having	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
Apron	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
being	O
positively	O
sworn	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
Ten	O
pence	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Pollet	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
New	I-place
Fish-Street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Sarah	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
fear	O
of	O
her	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Callico	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Judith	B-pers
Field	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
Street	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
on	O
her	O
Head	O
,	O
two	O
Men	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Blow	O
on	O
the	O
Leg	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
her	O
stagger	O
against	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
instant	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Things	O
off	O
her	O
Head	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
Monument-Yard	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
recovering	O
her	O
Surprize	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
crying	O
,	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
.	O
Other	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
hearing	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
,	O
they	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Monument-Yard	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
saw	O
him	O
fling	O
the	O
Bundle	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
one	O
took	O
up	O
while	O
another	O
secur	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
going	O
along	O
upon	O
Fishstreet-hill	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
Woman	O
stumble	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
Bundle	O
,	O
but	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
stealing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
the	O
Assault	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Edmund	B-pers
Neal	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Pincher	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
and	O
robbing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
the	O
said	O
Joseph	O
Dormy	O
a	O
Linnen-Cap	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
Pence	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
Pence	O
3	O
Farthings	O
in	O
Copper	O
Money	O
.	O
Joseph	O
Dormy	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
going	O
by	O
the	O
Haberdashers	B-place
Almshouses	I-place
at	I-place
Hoxton	I-place
,	O
about	O
9	O
a-Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
of	O
the	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
by	O
Pincher	O
,	O
and	O
rifled	O
by	O
Edmund	B-pers
Neal	I-pers
,	O
who	O
roll	O
'd	O
him	O
about	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
tore	O
his	O
Breeches	O
to	O
Pieces	O
in	O
searching	O
his	O
Pockets	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
3	O
Pence	O
3	O
Farthings	O
in	O
Copper	O
Money	O
.	O
His	O
Wife	O
confirm	O
'd	O
what	O
her	O
Husband	O
had	O
said	O
,	O
adding	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
going	O
a	O
little	O
Way	O
before	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
beating	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
turn	O
'd	O
back	O
and	O
begg	O
'd	O
of	O
them	O
not	O
to	O
beat	O
and	O
abuse	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
very	O
antient	O
;	O
that	O
thereupon	O
Neal	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
her	O
down	O
,	O
calling	O
her	O
Bitch	O
,	O
threatning	O
to	O
murder	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
made	O
any	O
Noise	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
refrain	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
beat	O
and	O
abus	O
'd	O
her	O
mercilessly	O
,	O
beat	O
out	O
two	O
of	O
her	O
Teeth	O
,	O
wounded	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
bled	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
almost	O
kill	O
her	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
the	O
more	O
she	O
cry	O
'd	O
for	O
Mercy	O
,	O
the	O
more	O
they	O
beat	O
and	O
abus	O
'd	O
her	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Bays	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
about	O
9	O
a-Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
hearing	O
a	O
Cry	O
of	O
Murder	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
a	O
Head-borough	O
,	O
ran	O
out	O
to	O
be	O
assisting	O
to	O
the	O
distressed	O
,	O
having	O
with	O
him	O
two	O
Dogs	O
:	O
That	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
,	O
the	O
Old	O
Man	O
was	O
but	O
just	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
very	O
much	O
abus	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
bloody	O
Condition	O
;	O
that	O
inquiring	O
which	O
Way	O
the	O
Rogues	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
the	O
Old	O
Man	O
pointed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
pursu	O
'd	O
with	O
his	O
Dogs	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
taken	O
into	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
Pincher	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
feigning	O
himself	O
to	O
be	O
drunk	O
;	O
that	O
other	O
Persons	O
also	O
being	O
come	O
to	O
his	O
Assistance	O
,	O
they	O
bid	O
Pincher	O
rise	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
not	O
doing	O
so	O
,	O
they	O
attempted	O
to	O
help	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
rise	O
,	O
bidding	O
them	O
let	O
him	O
alone	O
,	O
telling	O
them	O
he	O
was	O
choaked	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
strangled	O
,	O
asking	O
them	O
if	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
rob	O
him	O
,	O
bidding	O
them	O
take	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
abuse	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
Time	O
Edward	B-pers
Neal	I-pers
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
having	O
got	O
Pincher	O
up	O
,	O
they	O
tax	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Robbery	O
committed	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
Neal	O
told	O
them	O
he	O
knew	O
Pincher	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
honest	O
Fellow	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
believe	O
be	O
would	O
do	O
any	O
such	O
Fact	O
.	O
That	O
upon	O
this	O
Bays	O
being	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
suspected	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Companion	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
secur	O
'd	O
him	O
also	O
.	O
The	O
Old	O
Man	O
swore	O
positively	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
the	O
Persons	O
who	O
had	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
had	O
a	O
full	O
View	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
a	O
bright	O
Moonshine	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Cap	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
New	O
Prison	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Edmund	B-pers
Neal	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Pincher	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
a	O
Second	O
Time	O
for	O
assaulting	O
and	O
robbing	O
Solomon	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
said	O
13th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Steel-Box	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
Pence	O
,	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
Pence	O
,	O
a	O
Tinder-Box	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
Pence	O
,	O
two	O
Half-Pence	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Farthings	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
expecting	O
to	O
have	O
receiv	O
'd	O
40	O
or	O
50	O
Shillings	O
;	O
that	O
going	O
home	O
by	O
Hoxton	B-place
,	O
three	O
Men	O
jumped	O
over	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
Pincher	O
darted	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
into	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
them	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
,	O
desir	O
'd	O
them	O
not	O
to	O
abuse	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
rifled	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
the	O
Things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
:	O
And	O
that	O
Neal	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
rifling	O
,	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Slap	O
on	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
bidding	O
him	O
turn	O
his	O
Head	O
another	O
Way	O
from	O
looking	O
on	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
desired	O
them	O
not	O
to	O
hurt	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
concern	O
himself	O
about	O
them	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
afterwards	O
to	O
the	O
Hampshire	O
Hog	O
at	O
Hoxton	O
,	O
where	O
finding	O
John	B-pers
Dickman	I-pers
he	O
told	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
serv	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
supposing	O
the	O
Persons	O
who	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
would	O
rob	O
thereabouts	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
they	O
both	O
went	O
out	O
in	O
Search	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
the	O
Outcry	O
of	O
Murther	O
,	O
made	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Dormy	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
and	O
assisted	O
at	O
the	O
apprehending	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
being	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Things	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dickman	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
going	O
to	O
drink	O
at	O
the	O
Hampshire	O
Hog	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Nichols	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
set	O
upon	O
by	O
3	O
Villains	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
;	O
whereupon	O
they	O
resolv	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
Search	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
the	O
outcry	O
of	O
Murther	O
,	O
pursu	O
'd	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
Field	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
as	O
has	O
been	O
before	O
related	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
hearing	O
the	O
Cry	O
of	O
Murder	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Mrs.	O
Dorny	O
just	O
got	O
up	O
from	O
the	O
Ground	O
all	O
bloody	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
Persons	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
also	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
Neal	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
pretending	O
to	O
vindicate	O
Pincher	O
's	O
Innocency	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
knew	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
honest	O
Fellow	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
after	O
Nichols	O
's	O
Goods	O
had	O
been	O
found	O
in	O
Pincher	O
's	O
Pocket	O
,	O
Neal	O
acknowledg	O
'd	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
Dorny	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
Nichols	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
Person	O
concern	O
'd	O
with	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
;	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
together	O
at	O
the	O
Yorkshire	O
Gray	O
in	O
Old-Street	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
they	O
agreed	O
to	O
go	O
a	O
robbing	O
together	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Bays	O
,	O
Mathew	B-pers
Longworth	I-pers
,	O
Tho	B-pers
Bowler	I-pers
,	O
and	O
other	O
Evidences	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
both	O
pleaded	O
Ignorance	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
positively	O
deny	O
'd	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Player	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
80	O
Beaver-Skins	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
Pound	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	B-place
Ship	I-place
called	I-place
the	I-place
Mary	I-place
Frigate	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Master	O
of	O
the	O
Ship	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
no	O
Persons	O
,	O
Officers	O
of	O
the	O
Ship	O
or	O
Sailors	O
,	O
were	O
permitted	O
to	O
bring	O
any	O
Skins	O
,	O
or	O
other	O
Commodities	O
the	O
Company	O
traded	O
in	O
,	O
upon	O
their	O
own	O
Account	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
80	O
Beaver	O
Skins	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Hold	O
of	O
the	O
Ship	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
attempted	O
to	O
be	O
carried	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Ship	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
been	O
stopp	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Hudson's-Bay	O
Company	O
's	O
Porter	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
upon	O
the	O
Information	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Sailors	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Skins	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Cabbin	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Number	O
of	O
30	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
had	O
the	O
Company	O
's	O
Mark	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Skins	O
put	O
into	O
a	O
Bag	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
as	O
he	O
thought	O
to	O
be	O
carried	O
away	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Waterman	O
was	O
sent	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
his	O
Landlady	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Bellinger	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
Bag	O
to	O
carry	O
some	O
Things	O
ashore	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
brought	O
him	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
put	O
Skins	O
into	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
were	O
taken	O
by	O
the	O
Company	O
's	O
Porter	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Barrington	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
fill	O
the	O
Bag	O
with	O
Skins	O
,	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
hand	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Company	O
's	O
Porter	O
stop	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
found	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
Bag	O
of	O
Skins	O
wanting	O
of	O
the	O
Company	O
's	O
Cargo	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Invoice	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
there	O
were	O
found	O
15	O
Skins	O
in	O
the	O
Cabbin	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
between	O
Decks	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
put	O
Skins	O
into	O
the	O
Bag	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
ashore	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
30	O
Skins	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Bag	O
,	O
30	O
loose	O
in	O
his	O
Cabbin	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
more	O
found	O
loose	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
up	O
the	O
Number	O
of	O
80	O
,	O
the	O
Number	O
of	O
Skins	O
commonly	O
put	O
into	O
a	O
Bundle	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
upon	O
a	O
full	O
Hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Pottage	O
Pot	O
and	O
Cover	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Hawthorn	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	O
Hawthorn	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
into	O
her	O
Wash-House	O
in	O
her	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Pot	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
seeing	O
her	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Pot	O
set	O
against	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Cover	O
lying	O
at	O
a	O
distance	O
.	O
That	O
enquiring	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
what	O
Business	O
she	O
had	O
there	O
?	O
She	O
pretended	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
a	O
Necessary	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
pretended	O
to	O
inquire	O
for	O
a	O
Dyer	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
upon	O
a	O
full	O
Hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Henry	I-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
6	O
Blankets	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
2	O
Quilts	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
2	O
Looking-Glasses	O
,	O
value	O
45	O
s.	O
2	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
2	O
Curtains	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
2	O
Sconces	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Lewis	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Lewis	O
Baker	O
,	O
the	O
22	O
d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
two	O
Women	O
having	O
taken	O
a	O
Lodging	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
with	O
them	O
the	O
first	O
Night	O
,	O
lighting	O
them	O
with	O
a	O
Candle	O
in	O
a	O
Lanthorn	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
about	O
5	O
a-Clock	O
,	O
she	O
hearing	O
a	O
Noise	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
to	O
a	O
Nurse	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
getting	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Bed	O
,	O
went	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Street-Door	O
open	O
,	O
her	O
Goods	O
and	O
her	O
new	O
Lodgers	O
gone	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cheshire	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
her	O
Mistress	O
having	O
let	O
the	O
Lodging	O
to	O
the	O
two	O
Women	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
as	O
was	O
before	O
depos	O
'd	O
:	O
That	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
Women	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Mr.	O
William	O
,	O
Pray	O
walk	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
up	O
in	O
to	O
their	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Dram	O
,	O
asking	O
him	O
,	O
If	O
his	O
Master	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
bring	O
their	O
Things	O
.	O
He	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
Yes	O
,	O
no	O
doubt	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
bring	O
them	O
.	O
That	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
pretended	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
whether	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
or	O
did	O
stay	O
all	O
Night	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
certain	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
suspect	O
the	O
latter	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
hovering	O
about	O
,	O
or	O
passing	O
by	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
crying	O
out	O
to	O
stop	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
seized	O
by	O
one	O
that	O
passed	O
by	O
.	O
That	O
when	O
the	O
Constable	O
came	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
own	O
.	O
he	O
lighted	O
the	O
Women	O
thither	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
them	O
:	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
carry	O
them	O
where	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
took	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
about	O
with	O
him	O
from	O
place	O
to	O
place	O
,	O
but	O
were	O
not	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Violet	I-pers
,	O
another	O
Evidence	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
directed	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Stokes	O
,	O
who	O
would	O
carry	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Violet	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
a	O
Women	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
buy	O
Goods	O
,	O
telling	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Aunt	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
left	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
Women	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
more	O
Relations	O
,	O
were	O
to	O
bury	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
the	O
Goods	O
for	O
that	O
purpose	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
bought	O
the	O
Goods	O
for	O
five	O
Pounds	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
having	O
reason	O
afterwards	O
to	O
suspect	O
they	O
were	O
stolen	O
,	O
made	O
diligent	O
Enquiry	O
after	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
had	O
lost	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
by	O
Stoke	O
's	O
Direction	O
find	O
Mrs.	O
Baker	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
her	O
have	O
her	O
Goods	O
again	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
also	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Women	O
which	O
had	O
taken	O
Mrs.	O
Baker	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
was	O
,	O
or	O
did	O
pass	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
his	O
sister	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
carried	O
and	O
sold	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
,	O
after	O
having	O
heard	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
and	O
Susanna	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
l.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Rainbow	I-pers
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
Sarah	O
Rainbow	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Chapel	I-place
,	O
and	O
after	O
Evening	O
Sermon	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Chapel	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
Lame	O
took	O
hold	O
by	O
the	O
Chair-Man	O
to	O
help	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
Chair	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
mean	O
while	O
she	O
felt	O
something	O
press	O
against	O
her	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
clapping	O
her	O
Hand	O
to	O
feel	O
for	O
her	O
Watch	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
Sarah	O
Fox	O
was	O
standing	O
just	O
by	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
laying	O
her	O
Hand	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
have	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
saw	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
glitter	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
put	O
behind	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Susanna	O
Jones	O
,	O
stood	O
behind	O
Sarah	O
Fox	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
they	O
were	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
search	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Vestry	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
found	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
and	O
Sarah	O
Fox	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Persons	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Child	O
's	O
Coat	O
Maker	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
industrious	O
Woman	O
in	O
her	O
Calling	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
Mr.	O
Worcester	O
,	O
the	O
late	O
High	O
Constable	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
several	O
Times	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Searches	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
Persons	O
of	O
ill	O
Repute	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
,	O
upon	O
due	O
Hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
And	O
nothing	O
appearing	O
against	O
Susannah	O
Jones	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Highgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
8	O
Pound	O
about	O
two	O
Years	O
since	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Joseph	O
Townsend	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
,	O
at	O
several	O
Times	O
,	O
lost	O
several	O
Sums	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
Carpenter	O
by	O
his	O
Trade	O
,	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
mend	O
a	O
Drawer	O
in	O
a	O
Compting-House	O
.	O
That	O
20	O
s.	O
were	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
Drawer	O
to	O
make	O
an	O
Experiment	O
of	O
his	O
Honesty	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Drawer	O
lock	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
Compting-House	O
by	O
himself	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Drawer	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
3	O
s.	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
carried	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
did	O
confess	O
the	O
Facts	O
.	O
His	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Stapler	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
;	O
Stapler	O
and	O
Nichols	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Looking	O
Glasses	O
,	O
value	O
22	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sparrow	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	O
Jones	O
for	O
receiving	O
them	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Bridget	B-pers
Sparrow	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
lost	O
the	O
Glass	O
;	O
that	O
having	O
stept	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
,	O
leaving	O
a	O
young	O
Child	O
in	O
the	O
Cradle	O
,	O
the	O
Glass	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Packer	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
two	O
Women	O
came	O
to	O
sell	O
her	O
two	O
Looking	O
Glasses	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
fetch	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
Pawn	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
for	O
16	O
s.	O
Susan	B-pers
Stapler	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
him	O
gone	O
out	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
;	O
that	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
Glasses	O
,	O
and	O
hid	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Cole-Hole	O
;	O
saying	O
,	O
His	O
Grandmother	O
was	O
sick	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
she	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Broker	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
afterwards	O
Nichols	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
stolen	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
a	O
Court	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	B-place
,	O
which	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
Nichols	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Stapler	I-pers
also	O
call	O
'd	O
some	O
Persons	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
,	O
upon	O
hearing	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
acquitted	O
Jeremiah	O
Stapler	O
and	O
Ann	O
Jones	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Thomas	O
Nichols	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Nut	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Manning	I-pers
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
Joseph	O
Manning	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
keeping	O
a	O
Chandler	O
's	O
Shop	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Ring	O
in	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
Coat	O
Pocket	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Ring	O
was	O
afterwards	O
produc	O
'd	O
by	O
Mary	B-pers
Mark	I-pers
her	O
Cousin	O
.	O
Mary	O
Mark	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Ring	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Herrick	I-pers
a	O
Cook	O
Woman	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
Sarah	B-pers
Nutt	I-pers
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
lent	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
Sarah	O
Nut	O
might	O
pay	O
the	O
Cook	O
Woman	B-pers
a	O
Shilling	O
she	O
ow	O
'd	O
her	O
for	O
Victnals	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
some	O
more	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Herrick	I-pers
confirm	O
'd	O
what	O
the	O
last	O
Evidence	O
had	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
own	O
'd	O
when	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
stirring	O
the	O
Fire	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Vedas	I-place
,	I-place
alias	I-place
Foster-Lane	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Buckle	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hutchins	I-pers
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
December	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
broken	O
his	O
Show-Glass	O
with	O
his	O
Elbow	O
,	O
put	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Buckle	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
apprehended	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Buckle	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fryer	I-pers
,	O
That	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
done	O
by	O
him	O
and	O
one	O
Welchman	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
the	O
other	O
Buckle	O
.	O
His	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
only	O
said	O
,	O
The	O
Glass	O
was	O
broke	O
before	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Stephen	I-place
Colemanstreet	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
73	O
Horse-Shoes	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
Pound	O
of	O
Iron	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dart	I-pers
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Dart	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
had	O
lost	O
Horse-Shoes	O
at	O
Times	O
,	O
about	O
70	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Iron	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Simpson	O
's	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Simpson	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
in	O
Colemanstreet	O
,	O
of	O
one	O
Charles	B-pers
Mainard	I-pers
,	O
who	O
owing	O
him	O
Money	O
for	O
Service	O
,	O
gave	O
him	O
them	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
to	O
pay	O
himself	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
the	O
same	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
deny	O
'd	O
by	O
Charles	B-pers
Mainard	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Lynch	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Morrice	B-pers
Lynch	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Woolchurch	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
s.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
4	O
Shirts	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Arthur	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Arthur	O
Green	O
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
this	O
Indictment	O
Morrice	O
Lynch	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
having	O
the	O
Things	O
in	O
a	O
Bag	O
hanging	O
over	O
his	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
he	O
inquir	O
'd	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
the	O
Way	O
to	O
Smithfield	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
thither	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
shew	O
him	O
the	O
Way	O
;	O
that	O
going	O
along	O
together	O
,	O
one	O
step	O
'd	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
behind	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Things	O
from	O
him	O
:	O
That	O
Charles	O
Lynch	O
took	O
the	O
Things	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
Morrice	O
Lynch	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
coming	O
over	O
Tower-hill	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Way	O
to	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
carry	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Bridget	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
William	O
Hall	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Feather-beds	O
,	O
2	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Susannah	B-pers
Norgate	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	O
Norgate	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
her	O
Lodger	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
being	O
arrested	O
,	O
wanted	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
her	O
Door	O
,	O
bidding	O
her	O
take	O
a	O
Looking-Glass	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
as	O
many	O
as	O
would	O
raise	O
her	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
d.	O
to	O
pay	O
her	O
Charges	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
strip	O
'd	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
she	O
had	O
Mrs.	O
Norgate	O
's	O
Order	O
for	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Bridget	O
Hall	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
Second	O
Time	O
for	O
defrauding	O
Walter	B-pers
Benson	I-pers
of	O
7	O
l.	O
13	O
s	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
Goods	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
stolen	O
from	O
one	O
Capt	O
.	O
Hyde	O
,	O
in	O
Scotland-Yard	O
,	O
whom	O
she	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
serve	O
in	O
working	O
Chocolate	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
sent	O
by	O
Madam	O
Hyde	O
,	O
to	O
desire	O
him	O
to	O
lend	O
Money	O
on	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
7	O
l.	O
13	O
s.	O
was	O
lent	O
upon	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Captain	O
Hyde	O
had	O
fetch	O
'd	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
without	O
paying	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
saying	O
they	O
were	O
stolen	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
sent	O
by	O
him	O
or	O
his	O
Wife	O
to	O
be	O
pawn	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
her	O
by	O
Capt	O
.	O
Hyde	O
's	O
Maid	O
to	O
be	O
pawn	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
also	O
carried	O
the	O
Goods	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
None	O
of	O
Capt	O
.	O
Hyde	O
's	O
Family	O
appearing	O
to	O
contradict	O
this	O
Plea	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Flint	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Hornsey	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Linnen	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Bun	I-pers
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
hanging	O
on	O
an	O
Hedge	O
to	O
dry	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
them	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
thereupon	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
he	O
flung	O
the	O
Linnen	O
over	O
a	O
Gate	O
,	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
hid	O
himself	O
from	O
the	O
Pursuers	O
under	O
a	O
Hedge	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
having	O
the	O
Linnen	O
,	O
and	O
pleaded	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
apprehensive	O
of	O
being	O
arrested	O
,	O
and	O
supposing	O
the	O
Pursuers	O
to	O
be	O
Bailiffs	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Richmond	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
Value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Burnham	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
December	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
having	O
Coals	O
in	O
a	O
Cellar	O
of	O
an	O
House	O
separate	O
from	O
his	O
Dwelling-house	O
,	O
going	O
to	O
measure	O
some	O
Coals	O
in	O
his	O
Cellar	O
,	O
about	O
10	O
or	O
11	O
aClock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
asleep	O
in	O
his	O
Cellar	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
kept	O
fast	O
lock	O
'd	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
Key	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
he	O
suppos	O
'd	O
she	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
ran	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
he	O
pursu	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
having	O
shut	O
a	O
Door	O
which	O
stopt	O
his	O
Pursuit	O
,	O
he	O
afterwards	O
found	O
her	O
hid	O
under	O
a	O
Lodger	O
's	O
Bed	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
also	O
Goods	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
in	O
that	O
House	O
,	O
examin	O
'd	O
a	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
several	O
Goods	O
missing	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
afterwards	O
found	O
at	O
a	O
Pawn-broker	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
However	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Hayes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
Value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
December	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
her	O
Shop	O
to	O
cheapen	O
Stocking	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
,	O
Stockings	O
that	O
hung	O
up	O
for	O
a	O
Show	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
calling	O
out	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
stop	O
'd	O
.	O
Other	O
Evidences	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
stopp	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Stockings	O
were	O
drop	O
'd	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
just	O
by	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
ever	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Floyd	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
29	O
Pair	O
of	O
Scissors	O
,	O
value	O
39	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ralph	B-pers
Mansel	I-pers
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Clemenson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Clemenson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
a-Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
her	O
at	O
a	O
Tavern	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
her	O
Lodging	O
in	O
Cross	B-place
Lane	I-place
:	O
That	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
,	O
he	O
clap	O
'd	O
his	O
Hand	O
upon	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
that	O
his	O
Goods	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
back	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Lodging	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Cellar	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
readily	O
find	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
they	O
did	O
find	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Constable	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
about	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
about	O
3	O
l.	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
readily	O
find	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
but	O
were	O
first	O
let	O
into	O
a	O
Cellar	O
belonging	O
to	O
a	O
Bricklayer	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
Woman	O
out	O
at	O
a	O
Window	O
pointing	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Cellar	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
gotten	O
Entrance	O
,	O
demanded	O
the	O
Scissors	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
readily	O
acknowledg	O
'd	O
they	O
were	O
there	O
,	O
saying	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
drop	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
off	O
the	O
Floor	O
,	O
and	O
readily	O
deliver	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Gates	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Peter	I-pers
Gates	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Hempen	O
Sacks	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
O	I-pers
Brian	I-pers
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Sacks	O
were	O
lost	O
from	O
Low	B-place
Layton	I-place
,	O
being	O
fill	O
'd	O
with	O
Potatoes	O
in	O
the	O
Field	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Potatoes	O
were	O
turn	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Sacks	O
carried	O
away	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
offer	O
them	O
to	O
Sale	O
for	O
a	O
Shilling	O
,	O
be	O
suspected	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
,	O
sent	O
Notice	O
of	O
the	O
Sacks	O
to	O
Stocks	O
Market	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Sacks	O
thrust	O
between	O
a	O
Post	O
and	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
at	O
George-yard	O
Gate	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	I-pers
Spinster	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
Burchley	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
(	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
house	O
)	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
September	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Bodkin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
Half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
25	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Morgan	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
being	O
just	O
then	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Relation	O
's	O
House	O
to	O
lodge	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
drank	O
Part	O
of	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Quarterns	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
about	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
a-Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
see	O
after	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Countrymen	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
himself	O
not	O
well	O
,	O
was	O
going	O
back	O
again	O
to	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
but	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Way	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
wandring	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
inquir	O
'd	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
directed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
there	O
be	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Money	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Melly	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
both	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Vine	B-place
Tavern	I-place
in	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
show	O
'd	O
a	O
Box	O
,	O
had	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Mountain	O
Wine	O
with	O
Sack	O
,	O
and	O
Bread	O
and	O
Cheese	O
.	O
That	O
there	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
very	O
sweet	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
putting	O
his	O
Hand	O
round	O
her	O
Neck	O
.	O
That	O
having	O
drank	O
the	O
Wine	O
,	O
they	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
14	O
Peace	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
put	O
her	O
Hand	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Pocket	O
,	O
took	O
out	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
Change	O
was	O
brought	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
willing	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
Transactions	O
,	O
look	O
'd	O
through	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
put	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Money	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
ask	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
his	O
Money	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
also	O
see	O
her	O
put	O
another	O
Peice	O
of	O
Money	O
into	O
her	O
Bosom	O
,	O
and	O
something	O
into	O
her	O
Mouth	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
seeing	O
this	O
,	O
told	O
the	O
Old	O
Man	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Money	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
being	O
very	O
drunk	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
his	O
Relation	O
,	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
not	O
ready	O
to	O
shew	O
any	O
Mistrust	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Company	O
,	O
but	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Drawer	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Melly	I-pers
,	O
swore	O
this	O
against	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
Spite	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
had	O
once	O
hindred	O
him	O
from	O
having	O
6	O
Pence	O
given	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Indictment	O
was	O
Laid	O
for	O
stealing	O
privately	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Evidence	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
not	O
without	O
his	O
Knowledge	O
,	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Harriot	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hounslow	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Black	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
His	B-pers
Royal	I-pers
Highness	I-pers
George	I-pers
Prince	I-pers
of	I-pers
Wales	I-pers
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Horse	O
was	O
turn	O
'd	O
out	O
to	O
Grass	O
about	O
4	O
a-Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Horse	O
was	O
missing	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
about	O
6	O
a-Clock	O
.	O
Will	B-pers
Feathers	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
ferryman	O
brought	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Horse	O
over	O
the	O
Water	O
from	O
Cue	O
,	O
betwixt	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
a-Clock	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Hounslow	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
taking	O
Notice	O
of	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Horse	O
,	O
inquir	O
'd	O
whose	O
it	O
was	O
?	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Horse	O
.	O
one	O
Mr.	B-pers
Ewers	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
and	O
Farmer	O
at	O
Kingston	O
;	O
that	O
his	O
Master	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Red	O
Lion	O
at	O
Hounslow	O
,	O
had	O
sold	O
a	O
Pad	O
Nag	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
that	O
Horse	O
to	O
fetch	O
his	O
Master	O
home	O
;	O
that	O
thereupon	O
he	O
considering	O
the	O
Improbableness	O
of	O
the	O
Story	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
should	O
from	O
Kingston	O
thither	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Hounslow	O
,	O
suspected	O
therefore	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
ride	O
behind	O
him	O
;	O
or	O
that	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
at	O
Hounslow	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
thither	O
:	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
let	O
him	O
ride	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
discoursing	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
him	O
to	O
vary	O
in	O
his	O
Story	O
,	O
suspected	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
Hounslow	O
,	O
and	O
near	O
the	O
Inn	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bid	O
him	O
get	O
down	O
,	O
because	O
if	O
his	O
Master	O
should	O
see	O
him	O
upon	O
the	O
Horse	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
angry	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
get	O
down	O
till	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Red	O
Lion	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
he	O
inquir	O
'd	O
For	O
his	O
Master	O
Mr.	O
Ewers	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
such	O
Person	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
not	O
did	O
they	O
know	O
any	O
such	O
Person	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
If	O
Mr.	O
Ewers	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Lord	O
Bartlet	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
Cranford	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
should	O
find	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
for	O
going	O
away	O
very	O
abruptly	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
ordered	O
them	O
to	O
set	O
the	O
Horse	O
in	O
the	O
Stable	O
and	O
did	O
secure	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
after	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
did	O
own	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Horse	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
waste	O
Grounds	O
near	O
Richmond	B-place
.	O
The	O
Park	O
Keepers	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Horse	O
did	O
belong	O
to	O
his	O
Royal	O
Highness	O
the	O
Prince	O
of	O
Wales	O
.	O
The	O
former	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Horse	O
's	O
Tail	O
had	O
been	O
very	O
dexterously	O
and	O
neatly	O
plaited	O
,	O
as	O
ever	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
having	O
ty	O
'd	O
the	O
Horse	O
the	O
mean	O
while	O
to	O
a	O
Gate	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
only	O
took	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
being	O
an	O
old	O
Man	O
,	O
to	O
ride	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
Cranford	O
,	O
to	O
fetch	O
his	O
Clothes	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
there	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
work	O
there	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
giving	O
Credit	O
to	O
his	O
Story	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Packer	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
Black	I-place
Fryars	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
1	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
December	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
and	O
another	O
Friend	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Drink	O
and	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Geneva	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
also	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
felt	O
her	O
Hand	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
and	O
clapp	O
'd	O
hold	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
got	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
slipp	O
'd	O
the	O
Money	O
into	O
her	O
other	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
open	O
'd	O
her	O
Hand	O
to	O
show	O
him	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
any	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
said	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
pull	O
'd	O
her	O
cross	O
a	O
Table	O
to	O
kiss	O
her	O
and	O
tore	O
her	O
Headcloths	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
,	O
upon	O
hearing	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
,	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Arthur	B-pers
Hullerton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Woman	O
's	O
Jumps	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Adam	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
the	O
third	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Walker	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
her	O
Shop	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Jumps	O
drawn	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
Window	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
to	O
stop	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
threw	O
down	O
the	O
Jumps	O
and	O
was	O
apprehended	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
his	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
He	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
bare	O
denial	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Abigail	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Nelson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White	I-place
Chapel	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bag	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
9	O
Guineas	O
in	O
Gold	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Gorge	B-pers
Boller	I-pers
the	O
24th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
went	O
along	O
White	O
Chapel	O
he	O
was	O
eating	O
a	O
Pennyworth	O
of	O
Oysters	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
some	O
Oysters	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
overtook	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
an	O
Ale-House	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	B-place
of	I-place
the	I-place
Rose	I-place
in	I-place
Catherine	I-place
Wheel	I-place
Alley	I-place
,	O
that	O
there	O
they	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
a	O
Hot-pot	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
his	O
Pocket	O
had	O
been	O
pick	O
'd	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
before	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
a	O
Hand	O
at	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
thought	O
,	O
Abigail	O
Green	O
's	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
apprehend	O
his	O
Pocket	O
was	O
pick	O
'd	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
shut	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Watch	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
having	O
his	O
Money	O
and	O
were	O
search	O
'd	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Bag	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Chimney	O
Corner	O
empty	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-House	O
,	O
5	O
Guineas	O
were	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
After	O
a	O
full	O
Hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cleg	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Marrying	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Mary	I-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
a	O
former	O
Wife	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
de	I-pers
Fille	I-pers
,	O
being	O
alive	O
;	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
Evidence	O
sufficient	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hargrave	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolph	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
marrying	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
his	O
former	O
Wife	O
being	O
alive	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
marrying	O
Mary	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Abbot	I-pers
,	O
his	O
former	O
Wife	O
,	O
being	O
alive	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Roger	B-pers
Lansdown	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sack	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
three	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Oats	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
from	O
Francis	B-pers
Chartres	I-pers
,	O
Esquire	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Body	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Vincent	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Vincent	I-pers
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
,	O
whereas	O
James	B-pers
Appleby	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Appleton	I-pers
was	O
convicted	O
of	O
Breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Alice	B-pers
Marchand	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
six	O
Guineas	O
,	O
a	O
Jacobus	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
Goods	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
receive	O
them	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
James	O
Appleton	O
,	O
executed	O
for	O
that	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
himself	O
,	O
having	O
committed	O
the	O
Robbery	O
in	O
Mrs.	O
Marchand	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
did	O
carry	O
the	O
Trunk	O
into	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Yard	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
they	O
opened	O
the	O
Trunk	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
taking	O
out	O
some	O
Money	O
.	O
James	O
Appleton	O
gave	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Eleanor	O
Vincent	O
,	O
a	O
Crown	O
piece	O
for	O
her	O
Civility	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
also	O
left	O
with	O
her	O
two	O
Suits	O
of	O
Headcloths	O
,	O
which	O
James	O
Appleton	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
fetch	O
'd	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
also	O
pawn	O
to	O
her	O
a	O
Rose	B-pers
Ring	I-pers
set	O
with	O
Bristol	O
Stones	O
for	O
a	O
Crown	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
it	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Trunk	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Vincent	I-pers
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
did	O
receive	O
5	O
s.	O
of	O
James	O
Appleton	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
part	O
of	O
11	O
s.	O
that	O
James	O
Appleton	O
owed	O
her	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
other	O
Evidence	O
who	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
corrobate	O
that	O
of	O
Richer	O
Jones	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Court	O
ordered	O
the	O
Recognizance	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
Evidences	O
,	O
and	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Ennis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
two	O
Camblet	O
Coats	O
,	O
a	O
Wast-Coat	O
,	O
and	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
from	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
carrying	O
the	O
Goods	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
also	O
,	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
had	O
the	O
Wig	O
on	O
his	O
Head	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Wig	O
was	O
given	O
him	O
by	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
giving	O
Credit	O
to	O
his	O
Plea	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Riding	O
Hoods	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Hambleton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Newmarsh	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sheet	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Looking-Glass	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Blanket	O
,	O
a	O
Table-Cloth	O
,	O
Napkin	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lowther	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
hired	O
a	O
Lodging	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
away	O
about	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
before	O
her	O
Companion	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
wanting	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
not	O
Evidence	O
sufficient	O
to	O
fix	O
the	O
Goods	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
felonious	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
and	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Batholomew	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Clothes	O
were	O
taken	O
off	O
his	O
Bed	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
directed	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
had	O
bought	O
his	O
Wastcoat	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
pleaded	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
her	O
Husband	O
's	O
Brother	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
came	O
Home	O
together	O
very	O
drunk	O
,	O
making	O
a	O
great	O
Noise	O
and	O
Disturbance	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
for	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
their	O
Cloths	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
Money	O
rais	O
'd	O
to	O
buy	O
more	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
a	O
young	O
Woman	O
a	O
full	O
Pot	O
of	O
Drink	O
to	O
sell	O
his	O
Clothes	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Enfield	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Mares	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
One	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
going	O
upon	O
the	O
Common	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
a	O
stray	O
'd	O
Horse	O
,	O
saw	O
two	O
Mares	O
feeding	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
hid	O
in	O
a	O
Bush	O
near	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
,	O
describing	O
a	O
Horse	O
he	O
wanted	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
them	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Bottom	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
fetch	O
them	O
Mares	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Hertford	O
Fair	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
supposing	O
they	O
were	O
Strays	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
thought	O
to	O
have	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Pound	O
till	O
they	O
should	O
be	O
inquir	O
'd	O
after	O
by	O
the	O
Owner	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
about	O
to	O
drive	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
saddled	O
one	O
and	O
bridled	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
secur	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
own	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
prov	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
own	O
Mares	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Elias	B-pers
Spinnet	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Iron	O
Racks	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Balladine	I-pers
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
a	O
Robbing	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
told	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
there	O
were	O
such	O
Things	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bid	O
him	O
fetch	O
them	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
sell	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
for	O
20	O
d.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
They	O
saw	O
such	O
Things	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Hands	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
Chapman	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
several	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Burroughs	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
7	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
16	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Clogs	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Waller	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Woodroffe	I-pers
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
he	O
were	O
Lodgers	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
;	O
that	O
while	O
his	O
Wife	O
went	O
for	O
a	O
little	O
new	O
Milk	O
for	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
into	O
his	O
Room	O
,	O
broke	O
open	O
some	O
Drawers	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
depos	O
'd	O
as	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
,	O
Whether	O
she	O
lock	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
her	O
Room	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
back	O
she	O
heard	O
the	O
Child	O
cry	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Voice	O
,	O
saying	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
Do	O
n't	O
cry	O
,	O
Mamma	O
's	O
coming	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
her	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
afterwards	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Drawer	O
to	O
look	O
a	O
Cap	O
for	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
her	O
Money	O
,	O
Shoes	O
and	O
Clogs	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
found	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
own	O
Knives	O
in	O
the	O
Drawer	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
broken	O
the	O
Drawer	O
open	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
afterwards	O
confess	O
'd	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
4	O
Guineas	O
,	O
some	O
Silver	O
and	O
a	O
Counter	O
.	O
That	O
upon	O
this	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
some	O
Time	O
before	O
they	O
found	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
length	O
she	O
was	O
apprehended	O
in	O
Rag	O
Fair	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
having	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
before	O
Witness	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hutton	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
several	O
Blows	O
and	O
Bruises	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
Face	O
,	O
Breast	O
,	O
Ect	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Blows	O
and	O
Bruises	O
he	O
languish	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Month	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Purvys	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Joseph	O
Hutton	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
with	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
more	O
Men	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
Master	O
's	O
House	O
to	O
drink	O
about	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
a	O
Clock	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
That	O
Michael	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
came	O
in	O
about	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Drink	O
.	O
That	O
Michael	O
Young	O
knowing	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
drank	O
Punch	O
together	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
two	O
Shilling	O
Bowl	O
,	O
and	O
Michael	O
Young	O
bid	O
them	O
make	O
it	O
a	O
half	O
Crown	O
Bowl	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
paid	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
pay	O
any	O
Thing	O
toward	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
challenged	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
fight	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
Joseph	O
Hutton	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Company	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
Michael	O
Young	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
with	O
him	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
Men	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
stay	O
'd	O
out	O
better	O
than	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
both	O
of	O
them	O
very	O
bloodyThat	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
they	O
wash	O
'd	O
themselves	O
,	O
and	O
Joseph	O
Hutton	O
said	O
to	O
Michael	O
Young	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
there	O
will	O
no	O
further	O
Trouble	O
come	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
Michael	O
Young	O
said	O
,	O
None	O
should	O
come	O
on	O
his	O
part	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
said	O
,	O
None	O
should	O
on	O
his	O
part	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
shook	O
Hands	O
and	O
were	O
Friends	O
.	O
Landry	O
Dawson	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
purpose	O
,	O
adding	O
.	O
That	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
deny	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
pay	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
high	O
Words	O
arising	O
,	O
he	O
challeng	O
'd	O
to	O
fight	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Company	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
said	O
,	O
He	O
should	O
not	O
fight	O
with	O
that	O
Person	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
an	O
equal	O
Match	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
challeng	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
Best	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
Company	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
If	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
bent	O
on	O
fighting	O
,	O
himself	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Doors	O
of	O
fight	O
,	O
but	O
Michael	B-pers
Young	I-pers
would	O
not	O
fight	O
without	O
having	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
Friends	O
present	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
ran	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Water	O
side	O
and	O
brought	O
several	O
Men	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
into	O
the	O
Fields	O
and	O
fought	O
fairly	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
had	O
done	O
shook	O
Hands	O
and	O
parted	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
purpose	O
,	O
adding	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Flip	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Company	O
having	O
drank	O
part	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
paid	O
,	O
did	O
refuse	O
to	O
pay	O
part	O
towards	O
the	O
Punch	O
,	O
that	O
thence	O
the	O
Quarrel	O
arose	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
fought	O
fairly	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
Friends	O
again	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
other	O
Evidences	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
purpose	O
,	O
who	O
all	O
swore	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Cartwright	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
be	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
about	O
12	O
Hours	O
before	O
he	O
dy	O
'd	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
He	O
and	O
Michael	O
Young	O
had	O
fought	O
together	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
15	O
Falls	O
given	O
between	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
Michael	O
Young	O
12	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Michael	O
Young	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
enough	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
having	O
done	O
Michael	O
Young	O
came	O
upon	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
slung	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
knee	O
'd	O
him	O
very	O
much	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
enough	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
had	O
he	O
struck	O
two	O
Blows	O
more	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
purpose	O
,	O
adding	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
after	O
relating	O
this	O
Matter	O
,	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
O	O
Michael	O
Young	O
!	O
O	O
Michael	O
Young	O
!	O
A	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
him	O
labouring	O
with	O
a	O
Shortness	O
of	O
Breath	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Fever	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Appearance	O
of	O
a	O
Contusion	O
upon	O
his	O
Stomach	O
;	O
that	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
upon	O
opening	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
Large	O
Collection	O
of	O
Matter	O
between	O
the	O
Pleura	O
and	O
Diaphragma	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
he	O
dy	O
'd	O
of	O
the	O
Bruises	O
.	O
Another	O
Surgeon	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
,	O
at	O
opening	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
perceive	O
any	O
outward	O
Wound	O
or	O
Discoloration	O
of	O
the	O
Stomach	O
,	O
nor	O
apparent	O
Bruise	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
black	O
Eye	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
turning	O
up	O
the	O
Sternum	O
,	O
did	O
find	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
corrupted	O
Matter	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
suppos	O
'd	O
might	O
proceed	O
from	O
the	O
Rupture	O
of	O
some	O
Vessels	O
by	O
some	O
violent	O
Straining	O
,	O
or	O
by	O
a	O
Fall	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
many	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
peaceable	O
Person	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
known	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
of	O
a	O
quarrelsom	O
Disposition	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
,	O
after	O
a	O
full	O
Hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
,	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Hutchinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Lime-House	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
with	O
Jacob	B-pers
Fish	I-pers
and	O
Ephraim	B-pers
Lisle	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
four	O
Hundred	O
Pounds	O
of	O
Hemp	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Withers	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Withers	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
having	O
four	O
Lighters	O
of	O
Hemp	O
brought	O
to	O
Battle	O
Bridge	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Thompson	O
's	O
Granary	O
at	O
Deptford	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Bundles	O
loose	O
,	O
and	O
ordering	O
his	O
Servant	O
to	O
weigh	O
one	O
Bundle	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Hundred	O
and	O
a	O
Half	O
wanting	O
;	O
but	O
some	O
other	O
Bundles	O
being	O
shipp	O
'd	O
off	O
,	O
he	O
know	O
not	O
what	O
more	O
was	O
wanting	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
himself	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Hutchison	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
to	O
fetch	O
Mr.	O
Wither	O
's	O
Hemp	O
;	O
that	O
Hutchison	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
Jacob	B-pers
Fish	I-pers
had	O
inform	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
That	O
Atkins	O
would	O
take	O
Hemp	O
;	O
that	O
accordingly	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
had	O
brought	O
the	O
Lighters	O
to	O
Lime-house	B-place
,	O
within	O
two	O
Ships	O
length	O
of	O
Atkin	O
's	O
Back-Door	O
.	O
Hutchinson	O
,	O
Fish	O
,	O
and	O
himself	O
,	O
fill'ed	O
two	O
Bags	O
of	O
Hemp	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
Atkins	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
at	O
his	O
Back-Door	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Hemp	O
was	O
about	O
five	O
Hundred	O
Weight	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
14	O
s.	O
a	O
Hundred	O
Weight	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
17	O
s.	O
a	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Expences	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
Persons	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
.	O
Several	O
appear	O
'd	O
for	O
Hutchinson	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
as	O
an	O
Honest	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
who	O
constantly	O
frequented	O
the	O
Church	O
.	O
Others	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Atkin	O
's	O
Character	O
,	O
who	O
also	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
an	O
Honest	O
Man	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
stop	O
stolen	O
Goods	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
the	O
right	O
Owners	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
heard	O
him	O
charge	O
his	O
Daughter	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Absence	O
to	O
take	O
Care	O
not	O
to	O
buy	O
any	O
such	O
.	O
But	O
in	O
Contradiction	O
to	O
this	O
,	O
one	O
Evidence	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
He	O
had	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1714	O
,	O
prosecuted	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
Fact	O
of	O
the	O
like	O
Nature	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
James	O
Hutchinson	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
Second	O
Time	O
with	O
Jacob	O
Fish	O
,	O
and	O
Ephraim	O
Lisle	O
,	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
for	O
felonionsly	O
stealing	O
4	O
Hundred	O
weight	O
of	O
Hemp	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rawlins	I-pers
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
And	O
Edward	O
Atkins	O
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Abrams	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
Mr	O
Rawlins	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
He	O
order	O
'd	O
his	O
Porter	O
to	O
employ	O
a	O
Lighterman	O
,	O
to	O
bring	O
him	O
up	O
40	O
Bundles	O
of	O
Hemp	O
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
wanted	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
Hundred	O
Weight	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Hutchinson	I-pers
,	O
Jacob	B-pers
Fish	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ephraim	B-pers
Lisle	I-pers
,	O
having	O
fetch	O
'd	O
up	O
a	O
Lighter	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Rawlin	O
's	O
Hemp	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
over	O
against	O
the	O
Back	O
Door	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
at	O
Limehouse	B-place
,	O
about	O
2	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
Hutchinson	O
and	O
Lisle	O
fill	O
'd	O
the	O
first	O
Bag	O
,	O
which	O
weigh	O
'd	O
2	O
Hundred	O
weight	O
;	O
that	O
himself	O
and	O
Fish	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Atkins	O
's	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
second	O
Bag	O
weigh	O
'd	O
1	O
Hundred	O
weight	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
third	O
Bag	O
1	O
Hundred	O
weight	O
,	O
3	O
Quarters	O
,	O
and	O
14	O
Pounds	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Atkins	O
paid	O
them	O
for	O
it	O
3	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
James	B-pers
Tow	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Abram	O
's	O
Rope-Walk	O
,	O
Edward	O
,	O
Atkins	O
came	O
and	O
talk	O
'd	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Abrams	O
in	O
the	O
Walk	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
with	O
a	O
Bag	O
to	O
Atkins	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
fetch	O
6	O
Parcels	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
The	O
Information	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
wherein	O
James	O
Hutchinson	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
stealing	O
and	O
selling	O
the	O
Hemp	O
to	O
Atkins	O
,	O
and	O
Atkins	O
the	O
buying	O
the	O
Hemp	O
of	O
Woodward	O
and	O
Fish	O
,	O
at	O
14	O
s.	O
the	O
Hundred	O
weight	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Abrams	O
the	O
buying	O
of	O
4	O
Hundred	O
weight	O
of	O
Hemp	O
of	O
Atkins	O
,	O
at	O
21	O
s.	O
the	O
Hundred	O
weight	O
.	O
Hutchinson	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Rawlins	O
had	O
made	O
him	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
know	O
not	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
when	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
Information	O
.	O
And	O
Mr.	O
Abraham	O
call	O
'd	O
Two	O
Master	O
Rope-Makers	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
if	O
all	O
the	O
Hemp	O
was	O
like	O
that	O
Pair	O
of	O
it	O
they	O
had	O
seen	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Abram	O
's	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
to	O
the	O
full	O
Value	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
more	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Wintesses	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
them	O
generally	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
full	O
against	O
Hutchinson	O
and	O
Atkins	O
,	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
And	O
Acquitted	O
Abrams	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Greg	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Greg	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
That	O
whereas	O
William	B-pers
Rudgate	I-pers
had	O
been	O
convicted	O
of	O
stealing	O
3	O
Bobbins	O
of	O
Balladine	O
Silk	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Crush	I-pers
,	O
she	O
did	O
receive	O
them	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
William	B-pers
Rudgate	I-pers
coming	O
to	O
inquire	O
for	O
Work	O
,	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Bobbins	O
of	O
Silk	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
That	O
when	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
apprehend	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
her	O
Husband	O
told	O
them	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Greenwich	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
searching	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
her	O
conceal	O
'd	O
in	O
a	O
Back-Yard	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Rudgate	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
had	O
had	O
frequent	O
Dealings	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Years	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
6	O
Bobbins	O
of	O
Silk	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Gering	O
's	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
2	O
s.	O
That	O
she	O
knew	O
the	O
Silk	O
was	O
stolen	O
,	O
knowing	O
in	O
what	O
Shops	O
he	O
worked	O
;	O
and	O
consequently	O
how	O
he	O
must	O
come	O
by	O
them	O
:	O
That	O
she	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
turn	O
off	O
the	O
Silk	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
empty	O
Bobbins	O
again	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
the	O
Ruin	O
of	O
him	O
and	O
his	O
Family	O
,	O
in	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
sometimes	O
come	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
tell	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
to	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
must	O
get	O
her	O
some	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
knew	O
could	O
be	O
no	O
other	O
Way	O
but	O
by	O
stealing	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gering	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
There	O
were	O
2	O
Bobbins	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Crush	O
's	O
Mark	O
,	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
some	O
Silk	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Crush	O
affirmed	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Silk	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Dole	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
in	O
searching	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
a	O
great	O
Number	O
of	O
Bobbins	O
were	O
found	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Marks	O
of	O
divers	O
Silk-Throwers	O
;	O
whereas	O
they	O
were	O
always	O
so	O
careful	O
of	O
keeping	O
their	O
Bobbins	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
at	O
any	O
Time	O
they	O
grew	O
unfit	O
for	O
use	O
they	O
either	O
burnt	O
them	O
,	O
or	O
cut	O
out	O
their	O
Marks	O
:	O
Or	O
if	O
a	O
Person	O
dy	O
'd	O
and	O
his	O
Bobbins	O
were	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
,	O
the	O
Buyer	O
immediately	O
put	O
on	O
them	O
his	O
own	O
Mark	O
.	O
And	O
also	O
in	O
a	O
Garret	O
over	O
another	O
House	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
a	O
private	O
Throwing-Mill	O
for	O
Silk	O
,	O
that	O
carried	O
40	O
Spindles	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
an	O
unlawful	O
Mill	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
Silk	O
on	O
the	O
Bobbins	O
upon	O
the	O
Mill	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
no	O
Person	O
of	O
a	O
Silk	O
Thrower	O
,	O
might	O
imploy	O
any	O
such	O
Mill	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
Penalty	O
of	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Month	O
.	O
Several	O
other	O
Evidences	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
:	O
And	O
also	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
6	O
Bobbins	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Gering	O
's	O
,	O
with	O
Silk	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
And	O
Mr.	O
Powel	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
did	O
lend	O
Rudgate	O
2	O
s.	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
produc	O
'd	O
an	O
Evidence	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
had	O
at	O
one	O
Time	O
sold	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
9	O
Dozen	O
of	O
old	O
Bobbins	O
:	O
And	O
another	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
Rudgate	O
had	O
brought	O
empty	O
Bobbins	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
did	O
see	O
Rudgate	O
at	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
being	O
arrested	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
lend	O
him	O
2	O
Shillings	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
she	O
afterwards	O
seeing	O
the	O
6	O
Bobbins	O
of	O
Silk	O
(	O
which	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
Mr.	O
Gearing	O
's	O
)	O
in	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
was	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
pleaded	O
she	O
us	O
'd	O
the	O
Mill	O
in	O
her	O
Business	O
,	O
she	O
dealing	O
in	O
Waste	O
,	O
Silk	O
,	O
for	O
making	O
Ferrets	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
in	O
the	O
Silk	O
Stocking	O
Trade	O
.	O
She	O
call	O
'd	O
some	O
Persons	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Wootton	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Beal	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Motherby	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Hornby	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
upon	O
the	O
Statute	O
made	O
in	O
the	O
Fourth	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
Reign	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
King	O
George	O
,	O
intituled	O
,	O
An	O
Act	O
for	O
the	O
Further	O
preventing	O
Robbery	O
,	O
Burglary	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Felonies	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
the	O
more	O
effectual	O
Transportation	O
of	O
Felons	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
That	O
whereas	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
feloniously	O
stolen	O
from	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Alexander	B-pers
Hatchet	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
a	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
a	O
Rose	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
did	O
take	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hatcbet	I-pers
,	O
6	O
Guineas	O
for	O
helping	O
her	O
to	O
Two	O
Gold	O
Chains	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
and	O
19	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
stolen	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
apprehend	O
,	O
or	O
cause	O
to	O
be	O
apprehended	O
the	O
Felon	O
who	O
stole	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Statute	O
in	O
that	O
Case	O
directs	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Hatchet	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Wootton	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
Beal	I-pers
,	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
That	O
if	O
she	O
and	O
her	O
Partner	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
since	O
deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
would	O
give	O
them	O
6	O
Guineas	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
help	O
her	O
to	O
2	O
Gold	O
Chains	O
,	O
19	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
again	O
,	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
would	O
produce	O
the	O
Felon	O
that	O
stole	O
them	O
:	O
That	O
she	O
and	O
her	O
Partner	O
consented	O
to	O
the	O
Proposal	O
,	O
and	O
acquainted	O
a	O
Friend	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Sunderland	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Sun	B-place
Tavern	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Clare-Market	I-place
,	O
where	O
the	O
Goods	O
before-mentioned	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Person	O
who	O
personated	O
the	O
Thief	O
were	O
produc	O
'd	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Sunderland	O
depos	O
'd	O
That	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
he	O
can	O
remember	O
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Hornby	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
Beal	I-pers
being	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Hatchet	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
to	O
a	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Clare-Market	O
,	O
he	O
thinks	O
the	O
Sun	O
Tavern	O
,	O
upon	O
their	O
Promise	O
for	O
the	O
Reward	O
of	O
6	O
Guineas	O
,	O
to	O
produce	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
stole	O
them	O
.	O
That	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Tavern	O
,	O
they	O
inquir	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
Hornby	O
and	O
Beal	O
went	O
from	O
the	O
Tavern	O
,	O
while	O
Mrs.	O
Hatchet	O
and	O
he	O
staid	O
there	O
,	O
to	O
fetch	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
about	O
an	O
Hour	O
and	O
half	O
they	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
bring	O
him	O
up	O
with	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
Hornby	O
and	O
Beal	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Wootton	I-pers
came	O
in	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
both	O
Beal	O
and	O
Wootton	O
insisted	O
upon	O
having	O
Releases	O
drawn	O
,	O
and	O
Hornby	O
upon	O
their	O
paying	O
the	O
6	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Reward	O
;	O
that	O
Wootton	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
the	O
Releases	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Scrivener	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Hatchet	O
and	O
Sunderland	O
,	O
demanding	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
Person	O
who	O
stole	O
them	O
,	O
before	O
they	O
paid	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Motherby	I-pers
was	O
brought	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
large	O
black	O
Coat	O
,	O
big	O
enough	O
to	O
hold	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
but	O
a	O
slender	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
very	O
large	O
Hat	O
on	O
his	O
Head	O
.	O
That	O
this	O
Charles	O
,	O
Motherby	O
took	O
upon	O
himself	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
produc	O
'd	O
the	O
Bag	O
wherein	O
the	O
Things	O
had	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
and	O
19	O
Rings	O
,	O
2	O
Gold	O
Chains	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
.	O
That	O
these	O
Things	O
being	O
produc	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
6	O
Guineas	O
were	O
laid	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
up	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Hornby	I-pers
:	O
And	O
that	O
asking	O
Motherby	O
,	O
who	O
produc	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Thief	O
,	O
his	O
Name	O
and	O
Occupation	O
,	O
Motherby	O
told	O
him	O
his	O
Name	O
was	O
Peter	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Sawyer	O
in	O
Westminster	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
suspecting	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
told	O
him	O
true	O
,	O
bid	O
Motherby	O
let	O
him	O
see	O
his	O
Hand	O
;	O
which	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
Motherby	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
Person	O
he	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
(	O
Mr.	O
Sunderland	O
)	O
himself	O
being	O
a	O
Sawyer	O
,	O
was	O
well	O
satisfy	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
that	O
Business	O
,	O
but	O
some	O
Taylor	O
,	O
Barber	O
,	O
or	O
Garreteer	O
.	O
That	O
his	O
Suspicion	O
belong	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Hatchet	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Man	O
very	O
different	O
in	O
Person	O
from	O
Charles	B-pers
Motherby	I-pers
,	O
he	O
talk	O
'd	O
sharply	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
threatning	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
confess	O
the	O
Truth	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
sent	O
to	O
Newgate	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
Mothorby	O
begg	O
'd	O
for	O
Favour	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Perriwig-maker	O
in	O
Golden	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
was	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Dawes	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Sawyer	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Roher	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Charles	B-pers
Motherby	I-pers
came	O
to	O
him	O
the	O
latter	O
End	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
the	O
Day	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
well	O
remember	O
,	O
but	O
thought	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
the	O
26th	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
3	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Diamond	O
Rings	O
,	O
desiring	O
him	O
to	O
tell	O
him	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
value	O
the	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Friend	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
a	O
Jeweller	O
,	O
coming	O
in	O
,	O
did	O
value	O
the	O
Diamond	O
Rings	O
,	O
at	O
13	O
s.	O
the	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
thinks	O
;	O
that	O
himself	O
not	O
pretending	O
to	O
Skill	O
in	O
Watches	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
left	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
valued	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
an	O
Advertisement	O
publish	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Goldsmith	O
's	O
Company	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
wherein	O
be	O
found	O
the	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
described	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
thereupon	O
he	O
carried	O
the	O
Watch	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Carter	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Hatchet	O
.	O
Other	O
Evidences	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
Charles	B-pers
Motherby	I-pers
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dawes	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Sawyer	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
said	O
to	O
have	O
stolen	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Edward	B-pers
Wootton	I-pers
was	O
Brother	O
to	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
Dawes	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
Defence	O
consisted	O
chiefly	O
in	O
Three	O
Things	O
.	O
First	O
,	O
In	O
supporting	O
their	O
Reputation	O
.	O
Secondly	O
,	O
in	O
charging	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
with	O
a	O
Design	O
of	O
extorting	O
Money	O
from	O
them	O
.	O
And	O
thirdly	O
,	O
In	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
show	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
conform	O
'd	O
themselves	O
to	O
the	O
Statute	O
in	O
that	O
Case	O
made	O
and	O
provided	O
.	O
Wootton	O
and	O
Beal	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
them	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
both	O
as	O
to	O
their	O
Industry	O
in	O
their	O
Callings	O
,	O
Wootton	O
being	O
a	O
Frame-maker	O
,	O
and	O
Beal	O
a	O
Carver	O
;	O
and	O
Motherby	O
also	O
call	O
'd	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
And	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
would	O
have	O
extorted	O
Money	O
from	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
call	O
'd	O
Robert	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Brother	O
of	O
Wootton	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Mrs.	O
Hatchet	O
would	O
have	O
compounded	O
the	O
Matter	O
for	O
15	O
l.	O
But	O
their	O
Evidence	O
being	O
attended	O
with	O
some	O
seeming	O
Improbabilities	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
deny	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
it	O
gain	O
'd	O
but	O
little	O
Credit	O
.	O
The	O
Third	O
Part	O
of	O
their	O
Defence	O
related	O
chiefly	O
to	O
Wootton	O
,	O
Beal	O
,	O
and	O
Hornby	O
,	O
who	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
infer	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
had	O
comply	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Statute	O
,	O
in	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
apprehended	O
Charles	B-pers
Motherby	I-pers
,	O
whom	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
took	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
all	O
the	O
Thief	O
they	O
knew	O
;	O
urging	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
a	O
great	O
Expence	O
in	O
apprehending	O
and	O
fetching	O
him	O
60	O
or	O
70	O
Miles	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
.	O
In	O
answer	O
to	O
this	O
the	O
Statute	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
read	O
to	O
them	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
for	O
their	O
Satisfaction	O
how	O
well	O
they	O
had	O
conform	O
'd	O
themselves	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
read	O
accordingly	O
.	O
Upon	O
a	O
full	O
Hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
all	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
The	O
trials	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Sentence	O
as	O
followeth	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
3.	O
Edmund	B-pers
Neal	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Pincher	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Nutt	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Harriot	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Burroughs	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
2.	O
Robert	B-pers
Marsb	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Michael	B-pers
Young	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
,	O
25.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hyde	I-pers
,	O
David	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Pollet	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
Morris	B-pers
Lynch	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Lynch	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Richmond	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Hutchinson	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Wootton	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Beal	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Motherby	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hornby	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Hardiman	I-pers
Barthia	I-pers
Fisher	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Flint	I-pers
,	O
Elias	B-pers
Spinnet	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Hayes	I-pers
,	O
Arthur	B-pers
Fullerton	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Ennis	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
Stephen	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
Peter	O
,	O
alias	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gates	I-pers
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
I.	O
Cartonche	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
The	O
Robbers	O
.	O
A	O
Comedy	O
.	O
As	O
it	O
was	O
acted	O
many	O
Times	O
with	O
great	O
Applause	O
at	O
Paris	O
.	O
By	O
Mons	O
.	O
la	O
Grand	O
,	O
Comedian	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
II	O
.	O
The	O
Life	O
and	O
Actions	O
of	O
Lewis	B-pers
Deminique	I-pers
Cartouche	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
broke	O
alive	O
upon	O
the	O
Wheel	O
at	O
Paris	O
.	O
Nov.	O
28	O
,	O
1721	O
.	O
N.	O
S.	O
relating	O
at	O
large	O
his	O
remarkable	O
Adventures	O
,	O
desperate	O
Enterprizes	O
,	O
and	O
various	O
Escapes	O
:	O
With	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
his	O
Behaviour	O
under	O
Sentence	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
Scaffold	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Manner	O
of	O
his	O
Execution	O
.	O
The	O
Second	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
III	O
.	O
The	O
Tryal	O
at	O
large	O
of	O
Patrick	B-pers
Hurly	I-pers
,	O
for	O
Perjury	O
and	O
a	O
Cheat	O
:	O
With	O
the	O
learned	O
Arguments	O
of	O
the	O
Council	O
on	O
both	O
Sides	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
All	O
Sold	O
by	O
J.	O
Roberts	O
,	O
in	O
Warwick	O
Lane	O
.	O
A	O
Water	O
that	O
perfectly	O
cures	O
the	O
Itch	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
Itching	O
Humour	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
,	O
without	O
Necessary	O
of	O
Purging	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
dangerous	O
Use	O
of	O
Mercury	O
,	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
only	O
is	O
prepared	O
and	O
sold	O
,	O
by	O
A	O
.	O
Downing	O
,	O
Chymist	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
and	O
Ball	O
,	O
in	O
George	O
Court	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
John	O
's	O
Lane	O
,	O
by	O
Hicks	O
's	O
Hall	O
,	O
near	O
West-Smithfield	O
.	O
Where	O
also	O
may	O
be	O
bad	O
,	O
the	O
best	O
Spirits	O
of	O
Scurvy-Grass	O
,	O
by	O
Wholesale	O
or	O
Retale	O
,	O
at	O
8	O
d.	O
a	O
Bottle	O
.	O
A	O
most	O
effectual	O
Remedy	O
for	O
the	O
violent	O
Pain	O
in	O
the	O
Teeth	O
,	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
Also	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Remedy	O
for	O
the	O
Teeth	O
,	O
and	O
clearing	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
Humfreys	O
,	O
in	O
Bartholemew-lane	O
,	O
behind	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
;	O
and	O
E.	O
Symon	O
,	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Pope	O
's	O
Head	O
Alley	O
,	O
Cornhill	O
:	O
And	O
Sold	O
by	O
J.	O
Roberts	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Oxford-Arms	O
,	O
Warwick-Lane	O
,	O
1722	O
.	O
Where	O
Advertisements	O
atc	O
taken	O
in	O
Price	O
Three	O
Pence	O
.	O
