TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
NEWGATE	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
:	O
ON	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
,	O
Monday	O
,	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
and	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
7th	O
,	O
8th	O
,	O
10th	O
,	O
11th	O
,	O
and	O
12th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
1722.	O
in	O
the	O
Ninth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
M	O
A	O
J	O
E	O
S	O
T	O
Y	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
STEWART	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Fortescue	O
;	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
;	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
Country	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Nap	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barns	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Stockhall	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hoyle	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Berisford	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Crease	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Todd	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Harford	I-pers
,	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Holloway	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hinton	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Apply	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Burkett	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Corbett	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Jackman	I-pers
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
Arthur	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Hutchins	I-pers
,	O
Marmaduke	B-pers
Bramly	I-pers
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Hulman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
brown	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Sayer	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
(	O
by	O
information	O
from	O
Sir	O
Francis	B-pers
Forbes	I-pers
Clerk	O
)	O
found	O
his	O
Horse	O
at	O
the	O
Py	O
'd	O
Bull	O
and	O
Gate	O
in	O
West-Smithfield	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Horse	O
for	O
3	O
l.	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
afterwards	O
confest	O
he	O
stole	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Barbara	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Dukes	I-place
Place	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Abrams	I-pers
,	O
3	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
missed	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
being	O
examin	O
'd	O
,	O
confest	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Oxer	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Oxly	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Thomas	I-pers
Hudson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Bassishaw	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Testard	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
2	O
Silver	O
Salvers	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
l.	O
14	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23rd	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
8	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Boussetts	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Plate	O
;	O
and	O
was	O
apprehended	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
He	O
said	O
little	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
his	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Rebeccah	B-pers
Farmer	I-pers
,	O
8	O
pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Gloves	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
pawn	O
out	O
of	O
meer	O
necessity	O
,	O
intending	O
to	O
fetch'em	O
home	O
again	O
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
Widdow	O
,	O
of	O
St.	O
Dunstan	O
in	O
the	O
West	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
her	O
Female	O
Bastard	O
Instant	O
,	O
by	O
willfully	O
throwing	O
it	O
(	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
born	O
alive	O
)	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
of	O
Ease	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
smother	O
'd	O
and	O
instantly	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hope	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
suspecting	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
lodg	O
'd	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
Year	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
she	O
tax	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
who	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Tympany	O
she	O
had	O
had	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
Years	O
,	O
having	O
got	O
cold	O
in	O
her	O
Lying-in	O
.	O
The	O
Sunday	O
following	O
she	O
went	O
quite	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
after	O
there	O
being	O
occasion	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
Necessary	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
found	O
by	O
Robert	B-pers
Sanders	I-pers
,	O
who	O
confirm	O
'd	O
that	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
succeeding	O
Saturday	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
-	O
Cooper	O
,	O
the	O
Midwife	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
viewing	O
the	O
dead	O
Infant	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Female	O
,	O
and	O
full	O
grown	O
;	O
and	O
asking	O
the	O
prisoner	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
provided	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
No	O
indeed	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Cooper	O
,	O
I	O
've	O
provided	O
nothing	O
;	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
a	O
lie	O
for	O
the	O
world	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Nicholas	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Wisher	I-pers
,	O
2	O
Jacobus	O
's	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
2	O
half	O
Carolus	O
's	O
value	O
23	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
Daniel	O
Wisher	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
mist	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
examin	O
'd	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
In	O
his	O
Defence	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
drawn	O
into	O
the	O
These	O
by	O
two	O
young	O
Men	O
of	O
his	O
Acquaintance	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Beasly	I-pers
,	O
10	O
Yards	O
of	O
Sprig	O
'd	O
Callico	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
21	O
st.	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
a	O
Soldier	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
give'em	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
dropt	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
secured	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Bristow	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Blue-Coats	O
belonging	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
.	O
In	O
his	O
Defence	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
after	O
the	O
Rogue	O
,	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
still	O
pursued	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
but	O
was	O
prevented	O
by	O
the	O
young	O
Man	O
that	O
stopt	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Matth.ias	B-pers
Brinsden	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
Blackfriars	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Hannah	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
her	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
under	O
the	O
Left	O
Pap	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
1	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
depth	O
of	O
6	O
Inches	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Wound	O
she	O
instantly	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Brinsdon	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
her	O
Mother	O
(	O
the	O
Deseas	O
'd	O
)	O
sitting	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
suckling	O
her	O
Child	O
,	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
Father	O
(	O
the	O
prisoner	O
)	O
what	O
she	O
should	O
have	O
for	O
Supper	O
?	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
Bread	O
and	O
Cheese	O
,	O
ca	O
n't	O
you	O
eat	O
that	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
the	O
Children	O
?	O
No	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
want	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
Meat	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
Money	O
to	O
buy	O
you	O
any	O
says	O
he	O
.	O
You	O
know	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
,	O
but	O
little	O
to	O
day	O
.	O
D	O
...	O
n	O
ye	O
,	O
ye	O
Bitch	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
stick	O
ye	O
the	O
next	O
Word	O
that	O
ye	O
speak	O
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
again	O
askt	O
for	O
Meat	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pushed	O
her	O
back	O
with	O
his	O
Left	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
stab	O
'd	O
her	O
under	O
the	O
Breast	O
with	O
the	O
Knife	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
Right	O
Hand	O
.	O
This	O
Evidence	O
seeing	O
the	O
Blood	O
flow	O
so	O
fast	O
from	O
her	O
Mother	O
,	O
ran	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Child	O
from	O
her	O
Breast	O
;	O
and	O
her	O
elder	O
Sister	O
Betty	O
,	O
crying	O
,	O
Lord	O
Father	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
murder	O
'd	O
my	O
Mother	O
!	O
he	O
swore	O
,	O
D	O
...	O
n	O
,	O
ye	O
Bitches	O
,	O
hold	O
your	O
Tongues	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
'll	O
stick	O
you	O
too	O
.	O
And	O
then	O
putting	O
the	O
Knife	O
into	O
his	O
Mouth	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
this	O
Evidence	O
for	O
Sugar	O
and	O
Basilicon	O
;	O
which	O
having	O
applie	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Wound	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
dy	O
'd	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
two	O
days	O
after	O
,	O
by	O
means	O
of	O
a	O
Letter	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Horn	O
in	O
Bridewell	O
Precinct	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
bed	O
at	O
(	O
or	O
near	O
)	O
Mr.	O
Keys	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
Barbers	O
at	O
Shadwell	O
Dock	O
.	O
The	O
Surgeon	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
mortal	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
could	O
perceive	O
no	O
motion	O
of	O
her	O
Pulse	O
.	O
Several	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
Neighbours	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
Girl	O
's	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
ill	O
Husband	O
,	O
often	O
abusing	O
and	O
beating	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
using	O
her	O
barbarously	O
upon	O
the	O
least	O
provocation	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
upon	O
his	O
Wife	O
's	O
asking	O
for	O
Meat	O
for	O
Supper	O
,	O
he	O
deny	O
'd	O
her	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
have	O
it	O
here	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
go	O
out	O
and	O
get	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
stay	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
cutting	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Bread	O
's	O
for	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Children	O
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
being	O
(	O
as	O
he	O
term	O
'd	O
it	O
)	O
half	O
Speed	O
,	O
and	O
wanting	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
her	O
Companions	O
at	O
the	O
Gin	B-pers
Shop	I-pers
,	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
slip	O
behind	O
him	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
observing	O
,	O
turn	O
'd	O
about	O
with	O
the	O
Knife	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
to	O
prevent	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
in	O
Strugling	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
,	O
thrust	O
her	O
self	O
against	O
it	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
aware	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Aldersgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Philpot	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Common	O
Prayer	O
Book	O
and	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Abigal	B-pers
Leavy	I-pers
of	O
Aldgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
Ann	B-pers
Newcomb	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Gold	O
Ear-Rings	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
too	O
weak	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Rudgate	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
8	O
Bobbins	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Read	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hood	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Headcloaths	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Ghenning	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Pancras	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Wharton	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
11	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Avis	B-pers
,	I-pers
the	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
John	O
Freeman	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
3d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Purse	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
John	O
Wharton	O
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
Avis	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
from	O
Bellsize	O
House	O
at	O
Hamstead	O
,	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
betwixt	O
Fig	B-place
lane	I-place
and	O
the	O
Turn-pike	O
at	O
Totenham	B-place
court	I-place
,	O
a	O
Foot	O
pad	O
stopt	O
the	O
Coachman	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
he	O
spoke	O
,	O
fir	O
'd	O
into	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
demanded	O
their	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Wharton	O
about	O
10	O
or	O
11	O
s.	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Avis	O
Freeman	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
s.	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Freeman	O
a	O
purple	O
and	O
yellow	O
Silk	O
Purse	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
half	O
Crown	O
,	O
a	O
6	O
Pence	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
Groat	O
and	O
silver	O
3	O
Pence	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
(	O
which	O
Purse	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
same	O
pieces	O
of	O
Money	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
)	O
but	O
Company	O
coming	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
nothing	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Wharton	O
.	O
This	O
Evidence	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
Roberts	O
the	O
Coachman	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Woodson	O
,	O
--	O
Newgan	O
,	O
-	O
Hogan	O
,	O
and	O
-	O
Lilly	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
walking	O
together	O
from	O
Bellsize	O
,	O
and	O
suspecting	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Robbery	O
,	O
they	O
drew	O
their	O
Swords	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
towards	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
sliding	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
a	O
Dunghill	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hongan	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
him	O
down	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
then	O
threw	O
some	O
Money	O
in	O
the	O
Grass	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
thrust	O
his	O
Hand	O
into	O
the	O
Grass	O
;	O
where	O
,	O
upon	O
search	O
,	O
the	O
Purse	O
and	O
Money	O
were	O
sound	O
.	O
He	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
bellsize	O
Guards	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
over	O
hasty	O
in	O
coming	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Theobold	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
by	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
Pistol	O
discharged	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Mask	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Dunghill	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
One	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
then	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
the	O
Purse	O
,	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
hid	O
in	O
the	O
Grass	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Radford	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
being	O
delivered	O
to	O
his	O
Charged	O
by	O
Justice	O
Miller	O
,	O
be	O
found	O
13	O
s.	O
and	O
8	O
d.	O
2	O
Bullets	O
and	O
2	O
Flints	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
ran	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Hogan	O
.	O
because	O
he	O
feared	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
ill	O
design	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
charg	O
'd	O
with	O
a	O
Robbery	O
,	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
without	O
resistance	O
.	O
That	O
neither	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
not	O
Ladies	O
that	O
were	O
rob	O
'd	O
,	O
nor	O
the	O
Coachman	O
,	O
could	O
swear	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
put	O
the	O
Purse	O
in	O
the	O
Grass	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Banks	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Fulham	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
Richard	B-pers
Vincent	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
feloniously	O
steal	O
a	O
Cock	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
Drake	O
18	O
d.	O
4	O
Ducks	O
,	O
6	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
6	O
Hens	O
,	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Larkin	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Witnesses	O
that	O
charged	O
the	O
prisoner	O
being	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Arthur	B-pers
Casy	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Casy	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.Martin	B-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Lavy	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Junks	I-pers
,	O
did	O
assault	O
Michael	B-pers
Honeybourn	I-pers
,	O
and	O
take	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Michael	O
Honeybourn	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Mason	O
's	O
Skettle	O
Ground	O
,	O
at	O
Plimlico	B-place
,	O
he	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
Mason	O
's	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
helpt	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
mist	O
his	O
Watch	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Carrol	I-pers
deposed	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Hughs	O
being	O
committed	O
to	O
Tothill	O
Bridewell	O
for	O
cutting	O
off	O
a	O
Woman	O
's	O
Pocket	O
,	O
confest	O
to	O
him	O
that	O
Junks	O
sold	O
the	O
Watch	O
for	O
20	O
s.	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
kept	O
10	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
5	O
s.	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
to	O
Casy	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Kirk	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Casy	O
being	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
robbing	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
confest	O
this	O
Robbery	O
,	O
in	O
hopes	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
an	O
Evidence	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
said	O
little	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
no	O
body	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Hugh	B-pers
Towers	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Wetherly	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Towers	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Aldgate	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
Evans	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
Drink	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
brought	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
.	O
Soon	O
after	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
a	O
Tankard	O
behind	O
them	O
which	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
Pewter	O
.	O
Upon	O
inquiry	O
the	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
was	O
found	O
hid	O
under	O
a	O
Bed	O
at	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Spittlefields	O
,	O
which	O
Mary	O
Nichols	O
used	O
to	O
frequent	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Room	O
they	O
sat	O
in	O
was	O
a	O
thorow	O
fare	O
,	O
and	O
next	O
the	O
Street	O
;	O
and	O
therefore	O
though	O
they	O
left	O
it	O
there	O
,	O
yet	O
others	O
might	O
come	O
in	O
and	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
John	I-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Joseph	I-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
John	I-pers
Marshall	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Humphry	I-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
at	I-place
Newington	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Joshua	B-pers
Court	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
prisoners	O
lodg	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
coming	O
home	O
one	O
Night	O
,	O
found	O
their	O
Drawers	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
prisoners	O
gone	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
by	O
Allen	O
's	O
Information	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
Goldsmiths	O
in	O
Bishopsgate	O
street	O
The	O
prisoners	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
,	O
said	O
they	O
ow	O
'd	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
Creditors	O
hearing	O
where	O
they	O
lodg	O
'd	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
forc	O
'd	O
to	O
abscond	O
to	O
shun	O
being	O
affected	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Walker	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bennet	I-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Wharf	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Bugby	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
30	O
l	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Watches	O
being	O
lost	O
.	O
Warnings	O
were	O
delivered	O
out	O
to	O
Goldsmiths	O
and	O
Pawnbrokers	O
,	O
by	O
means	O
whereof	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Bugby	O
,	O
was	O
stopt	O
pawning	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Stone	O
in	O
Barbican	O
.	O
She	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
Boy	O
)	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Magnus	I-place
the	I-place
Martyr	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Gascoign	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
Philip	O
Gascoign	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
at	O
a	O
Funeral	O
,	O
he	O
mist	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Surbot	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Magnus	I-place
the	I-place
Martyr	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
2	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Gascoign	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
Fisher	O
,	O
they	O
seized	O
this	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
2	O
Handkerchiefs	O
tuck	O
'd	O
up	O
under	O
his	O
Armpits	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
of	O
Fisher	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Peck	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Magnus	I-place
the	I-place
Martyr	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Churcher	I-pers
,	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
Buck	B-pers
Skin	I-pers
Breeches	I-pers
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Doe	O
,	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
13	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheep	O
,	O
3	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
being	O
examined	O
,	O
confest	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
1	O
pair	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
,	O
another	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Daniel	O
,	O
both	O
Brandy	O
Shops	O
on	O
London	O
Bridge	O
;	O
and	O
13	O
pair	O
in	O
Pepper	O
Alley	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Downs	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Alhallows	B-place
the	I-place
Great	I-place
.	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
(	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Brain	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
of	O
the	O
East	B-pers
India	I-pers
Company	I-pers
,	O
one	O
Hundred	O
Weight	O
of	O
Tea	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Wade	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
East	B-place
India	I-place
Warehouse	I-place
,	O
and	O
Brian	O
,	O
often	O
brought	O
Tea	O
in	O
their	O
Pockets	O
and	O
Bags	O
to	O
the	O
Bell	O
and	O
Coopers	O
Arms	O
in	O
Bush	O
lane	O
,	O
where	O
Brian	O
sold	O
9	O
or	O
10	O
pound	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
,	O
for	O
7	O
s.	O
a	O
pound	O
;	O
for	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
that	O
about	O
a	O
Hundred	O
Weight	O
had	O
been	O
dispos	O
'd	O
of	O
that	O
way	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
being	O
taken	O
,	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
15	O
s.	O
for	O
Tea	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Jackson	O
who	O
kept	O
the	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
some	O
,	O
was	O
fled	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
several	O
creditable	O
Gentlemen	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Sir	O
Charles	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
Bart	O
.	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Gregory	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Cornelian	O
Seal	O
set	O
in	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
cheapened	O
a	O
Seal	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Ward	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
agree	O
upon	O
the	O
price	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Kirton	O
missing	O
a	O
Seal	O
,	O
and	O
observing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
shake	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
holding	O
one	O
corner	O
of	O
it	O
fast	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Seal	O
dropt	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
how	O
the	O
Seal	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
unless	O
she	O
put	O
it	O
there	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
his	O
Neighbours	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
civil	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
come	O
of	O
a	O
good	O
Family	O
in	O
Lincolnshire	O
,	O
but	O
lately	O
,	O
by	O
Misfortunes	O
,	O
reduc	O
'd	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Sladden	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
at	I-place
Hill	I-place
.	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
returning	O
from	O
Transportation	O
before	O
the	O
expiration	O
of	O
14	O
Years	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
prisoners	O
being	O
convicted	O
at	O
Maidstone	O
for	O
Burglary	O
,	O
was	O
shipt	O
off	O
for	O
Transportation	O
;	O
and	O
with	O
19	O
more	O
made	O
a	O
rising	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
off	O
in	O
the	O
Downs	O
.	O
In	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
he	O
deny	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
Man	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Hilton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
24	O
Leather	O
Soles	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
his	O
Leather	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
discovered	O
by	O
offering	O
it	O
to	O
sale	O
at	O
an	O
under	O
price	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Martha	B-pers
Inkhorn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Hat	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Pocket	O
Looking	O
Glass	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
5	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Hat	O
's	O
Goods	O
being	O
taken	O
upon	O
a	O
disputed	O
Execution	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
convey	O
'd	O
away	O
several	O
things	O
;	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Hat	O
,	O
whose	O
property	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
acknowledging	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
by	O
his	O
order	O
:	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bowl	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Badcock	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
3	O
Peruques	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
8	O
Razors	O
11	O
s.	O
24	O
oz	O
.	O
of	O
Human	O
Hair	O
20	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
Journy	O
Man	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Badcock	O
;	O
who	O
mist	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
enquiry	O
found	O
several	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
In	O
his	O
defence	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
wigs	O
in	O
his	O
masters	O
shop	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4s	O
.	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Bulpin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bay	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
5l	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
John	O
Johnson	O
,	O
in	O
July	O
1721.	O
lost	O
his	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
august	O
last	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
produced	O
the	O
Man	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
Grace	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
a	O
Girl	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Edmond	I-place
the	I-place
King	I-place
,	O
where	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Lason	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Damask	O
Table	O
Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
2	O
Handkerchiefs	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Head	O
Cloths	O
27	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
Baker	O
had	O
been	O
5	O
Months	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
that	O
several	O
things	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Grace	O
and	O
Mary	O
Davis	O
,	O
were	O
frequently	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Lasons	O
in	O
Sermon	O
time	O
;	O
the	O
Suit	O
of	O
Head	O
Cloths	O
being	O
lost	O
,	O
they	O
examined	O
Baker	O
strictly	O
,	O
who	O
after	O
a	O
stiff	O
denial	O
produc	O
'd	O
at	O
last	O
a	O
Gown	O
made	O
of	O
the	O
Diaper	O
Table	O
Cloth	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Handkerchiefs	O
:	O
and	O
the	O
Hangings	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
Davis	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
Grace	O
Davis	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Baker	O
told	O
her	O
her	O
Mrs.	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
the	O
Hangings	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
.	O
Baker	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
reaching	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Burden	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Wilshire	I-pers
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Stockings	O
,	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Charwoman	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
askt	O
about	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
wash	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
pretending	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
fetch'em	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
quite	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
taken	O
soon	O
after	O
,	O
confest	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Chun	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Twittenham	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Silas	B-pers
Ping	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Staff	O
,	O
a	O
mortal	O
wound	O
near	O
the	O
left	O
Ear	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
about	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
(	O
the	O
Moon	O
shining	O
)	O
as	O
himself	O
with	O
a	O
Flail	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
with	O
a	O
Hedge	O
Stake	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Screen	I-pers
,	O
since	O
absented	O
,	O
were	O
walking	O
160	O
Yards	O
from	O
Twittenham	B-place
Warren	I-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
a	O
Quarter	O
Staff	O
,	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceased	O
down	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Deceased	O
;	O
That	O
they	O
had	O
three	O
Dogs	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Perkins	O
,	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
One	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
the	O
prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
up	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
be	O
found	O
him	O
dead	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
opened	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Skull	O
broke	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
his	O
death	O
.	O
Not	O
far	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
Cony	O
newly	O
kill	O
'd	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
Witness	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
3	O
Men	O
advance	O
toward	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
askt	O
then	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
ran	O
back	O
to	O
call	O
assistance	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
she	O
got	O
in	O
,	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
cry	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Turner	O
,	O
come	O
help	O
me	O
.	O
She	O
heard	O
the	O
Dogs	O
bark	O
,	O
and	O
Sticks	O
rattle	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Turner	O
deposed	O
,	O
on	O
Mary	O
's	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
hastended	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
lying	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
They	O
asked	O
him	O
why	O
he	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
in	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
their	O
pardon	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Cunningham	O
confirmed	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Chun	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
following	O
his	O
Father	O
with	O
a	O
Gun	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Dogs	O
fall	O
on	O
his	O
Father	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Men	O
Strike	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
before	O
he	O
struck	O
at	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
askt	O
his	O
Father	O
if	O
he	O
should	O
shoot	O
the	O
Dogs	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
struck	O
at	O
his	O
Father	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Father	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
.	O
It	O
appearing	O
Se	O
defendendo	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
ordered	O
Brown	O
into	O
Custody	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Etheridge	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
bon	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
James	B-pers
Corbridge	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
(	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
and	O
place	O
)	O
Edward	B-pers
Sharp	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
5	O
s.	O
John	O
Corbridge	O
and	O
Edward	O
Sharp	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
with	O
2	O
Ladies	O
,	O
betwixt	O
Tyburn	B-place
and	O
Paddington	B-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
a	O
black	O
Gelding	O
,	O
stopt	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
some	O
Money	O
from	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
rode	O
off	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
both	O
positive	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Corbridge	O
afterwards	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
Mr	O
.	O
Beard	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
the	O
Bull	O
and	O
Bush	O
,	O
at	O
North	O
End	O
,	O
and	O
secured	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
found	O
Pistols	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
carried	O
as	O
Keeper	O
of	O
Moor	O
Park	O
.	O
The	O
latter	O
part	O
of	O
that	O
Evidence	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Beard	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
Richard	B-pers
Hat	I-pers
,	O
Ostler	O
at	O
the	O
Angel	O
Inn	O
in	O
Piccadilly	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Douglas	I-pers
,	O
Master	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
Christopher	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
said	O
Inn	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
,	O
11th	O
,	O
and	O
12th	O
of	O
June	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
upon	O
Cross-examination	O
,	O
to	O
contradict	O
one	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
Hat	O
and	O
While	O
were	O
ordered	O
into	O
Custody	O
.	O
The	O
King	O
's	O
Evidence	O
being	O
positive	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
.	O
Was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Adam	B-pers
Corbet	I-pers
,	O
2	O
Folio	O
Volumes	O
of	O
Pope	O
's	O
Homer	O
,	O
bound	O
in	O
one	O
,	O
Val	O
.	O
8s	O
.	O
2	O
Folio	O
Volumes	O
of	O
Dryden	O
's	O
Plays	O
,	O
16s	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
-	O
Noble	O
,	O
a	O
Bookseller	O
in	O
the	O
Long	O
Walk	O
,	O
by	O
Christ	O
's	O
Hospital	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
sold	O
him	O
the	O
Books	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Folio	O
Volume	O
of	O
Ben	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
's	O
Plays	O
for	O
8	O
s.	O
Mr.	O
Corbet	O
afterwards	O
enquiring	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
such	O
a	O
Book	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
Yes	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Corbet	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
15	O
s.	O
for	O
only	O
the	O
2	O
Books	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
at	O
2d	O
hand	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
of	O
White	B-place
Chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecution	O
appearing	O
malicious	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Lincoln	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
(	O
with	O
Daniel	B-pers
Carrel	I-pers
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
did	O
feloniously	O
Murder	O
Peter	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
Wilkinson	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
1	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
in	O
the	O
Back	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
Left	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
1	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
depth	O
of	O
9	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
;	O
and	O
Lincoln	O
by	O
being	O
present	O
,	O
aiding	O
and	O
abetting	O
the	O
said	O
Wilkinson	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Fleetwood	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
Fleetwood	O
Clark	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
passage	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
from	O
the	O
Bedford	B-place
Head	I-place
Tavern	I-place
in	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
to	O
Conduit	B-place
Street	I-place
,	O
the	O
Chair	O
was	O
stop	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
a	O
Man	O
stuck	O
his	O
Pistol	O
through	O
the	O
Glass	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
A	O
Woman	O
calling	O
out	O
of	O
Window	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
fired	O
a	O
Pistol	O
at	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
broke	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
but	O
mist	O
the	O
Woman	O
.	O
Williams	O
Lock	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
himself	O
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Carrol	I-pers
,	O
Valentine	B-pers
Carrick	I-pers
,	O
(	O
since	O
executed	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Carrick	I-pers
)	O
and	O
the	O
2	O
prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
met	O
the	O
Chair	O
in	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
was	O
rob	O
'd	O
.	O
This	O
Evidence	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
lower	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
Lincoln	O
at	O
the	O
upper	O
end	O
,	O
to	O
watch	O
and	O
give	O
notice	O
;	O
Wilkinson	O
stood	O
with	O
a	O
Pistol	O
over	O
one	O
Chairman	O
,	O
and	O
Carrol	O
over	O
the	O
other	O
:	O
Carrick	O
rob	O
'd	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
;	O
the	O
Woman	O
calling	O
out	O
at	O
Window	O
,	O
Wilkinson	O
fir	O
'd	O
at	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Chairman	O
confirmed	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
's	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
14	O
or	O
15	O
prisoners	O
were	O
placed	O
before	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
afterward	O
taken	O
aside	O
single	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
fixt	O
upon	O
the	O
same	O
Man	O
.	O
Lincoln	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
Cambridge	O
when	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
to	O
fetch	O
up	O
his	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
Wilkinson	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
Will	B-pers
Hyde	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Hyde	I-pers
,	O
Moses	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
Katherine	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Rich	B-pers
Beach	I-pers
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Hyde	O
was	O
arrested	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
for	O
Debt	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Wilkinson	O
,	O
was	O
from	O
7	O
till	O
12	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
helping	O
to	O
remove	O
Hyde	O
's	O
Goods	O
,	O
from	O
his	O
House	O
in	O
Southwark	O
.	O
Lack	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Pocket	O
was	O
pickt	O
in	O
Newgate	O
of	O
his	O
Information	O
,	O
whereby	O
the	O
prisoners	O
had	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
preparing	O
their	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
contradict	O
him	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Parry	O
the	O
Turnkey	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
2d	O
Indictment	O
,	O
Edw	B-pers
Parry	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
parted	O
with	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Camp	O
at	O
Hyde	B-place
Park	I-place
,	O
about	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
his	O
Fuzee	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Lock	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
with	O
the	O
same	O
Company	O
to	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Hyde	O
Park	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
met	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
;	O
that	O
Wilkinson	O
seiz	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
who	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
Lincoln	O
knocked	O
him	O
down	O
.	O
They	O
sent	O
this	O
Evidence	O
to	O
watch	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
came	O
out	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
led	O
between	O
Carrol	O
and	O
Wilkinson	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
latter	O
drawing	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
gave	O
him	O
several	O
pushes	O
in	O
the	O
Back	O
.	O
He	O
sunk	O
down	O
,	O
Lincoln	O
rifled	O
his	O
Pockets	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
there	O
but	O
a	O
Knife	O
and	O
a	O
Key	O
.	O
That	O
afterwards	O
they	O
attack	O
'd	O
Captain	O
Langley	B-pers
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
who	O
making	O
resistance	O
,	O
they	O
fir	O
'd	O
at	O
him	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
whereupon	O
two	O
Soldiers	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Wilkinson	O
,	O
struck	O
at	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
with	O
the	O
Butt	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Musket	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
it	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
afterwards	O
threw	O
the	O
broken	O
Gun	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Tyburn	O
Lane	O
.	O
Captain	O
Langley	B-pers
confirmed	O
most	O
of	O
Lock	O
's	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
added	O
,	O
the	O
Rogues	O
wounded	O
him	O
in	O
seven	O
places	O
with	O
their	O
Swords	O
.	O
Captain	O
Steward	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
next	O
day	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Deceased	O
dead	O
in	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
his	O
Pocket	O
turned	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Key	O
and	O
a	O
Knife-lying	O
by	O
.	O
The	O
broken	O
Stock	O
and	O
Barrel	O
of	O
the	O
Gun	O
were	O
found	O
by	O
Tyburn	O
lane	O
,	O
and	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
which	O
the	O
deceased	O
Pensioner	O
took	O
out	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Herbert	O
,	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
viewing	O
the	O
dead	O
body	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
several	O
mortal	O
Wounds	O
.	O
Wilkinson	O
insisted	O
on	O
the	O
Defence	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
to	O
the	O
former	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
Lincoln	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
no	O
body	O
could	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
ever	O
was	O
in	O
Lock	O
's	O
Company	O
.	O
-	O
Redgate	O
then	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
10	O
Weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
about	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
Lock	O
,	O
Carrick	O
,	O
and	O
Lincoln	O
,	O
were	O
all	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
together	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Red	O
Gate	O
in	O
Kingstreet	O
,	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Pancrass	B-place
,	O
was	O
a	O
3d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Ship	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
2	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
William	O
Ship	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
between	O
5	O
and	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
at	O
Fig	B-place
Lane	I-place
end	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
Shaw	O
and	O
Burridge	O
,	O
since	O
both	O
Executed	O
,	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Horses	O
Reins	O
,	O
clapt	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
rob	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Pancrass	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
4th	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
with	O
Richard	B-pers
Oakey	I-pers
,	O
for	O
assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Whip	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
7	O
s.	O
8	O
pence	O
half	O
penny	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
Wilkinson	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Graham	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Oakey	O
,	O
otherwise	O
than	O
by	O
Wilkinson	O
's	O
Information	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
a	O
5th	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Milksop	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Jennings	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Ghenning	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Trantum	I-pers
,	O
was	O
a	O
4th	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ping	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
assault	O
Ralph	B-pers
Keet	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
a	O
Bridle	O
,	O
Saddle	O
,	O
Whip	O
,	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
13	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
.	O
Ralph	O
Keet	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
rob	O
'd	O
by	O
3	O
Men	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
Hamstead	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
really	O
believed	O
Mithley	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
:	O
That	O
Wilkinson	O
had	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Information	O
before	O
Justice	O
Hewit	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Vincent	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hamstead	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Iron	O
Bar	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Banfield	I-pers
,	O
Esg	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Arthur	B-pers
Hughs	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Jane	B-pers
Young	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Pocket	O
,	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
9	O
s.	O
and	O
3	O
half	O
pence	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Young	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
along	O
Panton	B-place
street	I-place
,	O
about	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
4	O
Men	O
sitting	O
on	O
a	O
Bench	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
his	O
threw	O
her	O
down	O
,	O
cut	O
off	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
Comrade	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
punched	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Breast	O
with	O
a	O
short	O
Stick	O
which	O
he	O
carried	O
in	O
his	O
Sleeve	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
stopt	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Stick	O
in	O
his	O
Sleeve	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
playing	O
at	O
Trap	O
Ball	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
,	O
)	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Dames	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
Henry	B-pers
Thorp	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
privately	O
steal	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Bow	I-pers
,	O
2	O
Snuff	O
Boxes	O
,	O
value	O
45	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
about	O
noon	O
Luke	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
(	O
an	O
Evidence	O
aged	O
13	O
)	O
lean	O
'd	O
over	O
the	O
Show	O
Glass	O
which	O
was	O
unlock	O
'd	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
might	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
lifted	O
up	O
the	O
Glass	O
,	O
and	O
Thorp	O
who	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
afterwards	O
saw	O
them	O
run	O
cross	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
look	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
Show	O
.	O
Glass	O
mist	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
pursu	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
St.	O
Clements	O
Church	O
yard	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
took	O
Anderson	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
having	O
no	O
suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
2	O
others	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
at	O
his	O
Window	O
,	O
they	O
got	O
off	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bannister	I-pers
,	O
2	O
gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
28	O
s.	O
and	O
45	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Trunk	O
,	O
which	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bateman	I-pers
open	O
'd	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
stood	O
by	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
the	O
Comper	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
confest	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Rings	O
and	O
Money	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Pitway	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Mires	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dionis	I-place
Back	I-place
Church	I-place
(	O
both	O
little	O
Boys	O
,	O
)	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Manson	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
Pitway	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
11	O
pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
and	O
Mires	O
and	O
Manson	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
Stolen	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
missing	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
examined	O
the	O
prisoner	O
his	O
Boy	O
,	O
who	O
confest	O
that	O
the	O
Shoe	O
blacker	O
(	O
Mires	O
)	O
inticed	O
him	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
sold	O
him	O
11	O
pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Gloves	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Stockings	O
for	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
received	O
but	O
14	O
s.	O
2	O
odd	O
Silk	O
Stockings	O
and	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
Worked	O
,	O
he	O
sold	O
to	O
Ann	B-pers
Manson	I-pers
an	O
Apple	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
to	O
Joan	B-pers
Humphris	I-pers
a	O
Curd	O
and	O
Whey	O
Woman	O
,	O
both	O
in	O
Stocks	O
Market	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Manson	I-pers
in	O
her	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Pitway	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
produced	O
several	O
persons	O
of	O
Credit	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
Mires	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Pitway	O
told	O
him	O
his	O
Master	O
was	O
strainen	O
'd	O
for	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
the	O
Stockings	O
to	O
pawn	O
;	O
Pitway	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Mires	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
:	O
and	O
Manson	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Pitway	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Mires	O
:	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Thistleworth	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Bart	O
.	O
And	O
taking	O
thence	O
3	O
Coach	O
glasses	O
,	O
value	O
6l	O
.	O
and	O
4	O
sears	O
,	O
4l	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
July	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
whilst	O
Sir	O
John	O
was	O
at	O
London	O
,	O
his	O
Coach	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
gone	O
.	O
Simon	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
offer	O
'd	O
him	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
he	O
apprehended	O
him	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
and	O
advertised	O
the	O
Goods	O
:	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
Sir	O
John	O
found	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Scarlet	O
Riding	O
Hood	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Moreland	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
;	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
being	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
confest	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
them	O
home	O
again	O
.	O
In	O
her	O
defence	O
she	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
:	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
might	O
be	O
taken	O
by	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
,	O
for	O
her	O
Master	O
kept	O
a	O
very	O
disorderly	O
House	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
Crown	B-place
Tavern	I-place
in	I-place
Drury	I-place
Lane	I-place
;	O
)	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
worst	O
thing	O
she	O
ever	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
there	O
,	O
was	O
by	O
serving	O
her	O
Master	O
in	O
helping	O
Gentlemen	O
to	O
Whores	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Shambler	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bow	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
receiving	O
82	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
due	O
to	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
(	O
being	O
her	O
Christmas	O
Dividend	O
for	O
1650	O
l.	O
South	O
Sea	O
Stock	O
,	O
the	O
Produce	O
of	O
6000	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
3d	O
Subscription	O
)	O
by	O
vertue	O
of	O
a	O
forg	O
'd	O
and	O
Counterfeit	O
Note	O
,	O
he	O
knowing	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
be	O
forg	O
'd	O
and	O
Counterfeited	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Witness	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
a	O
Clerk	O
in	O
the	O
South	O
Sea	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
became	O
acquainted	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Shambler	I-pers
the	O
prisoners	O
Brother	O
;	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
Elizabeth	O
Turner	O
in	O
Mark	O
Lane	O
:	O
could	O
counterfeit	O
her	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
draw	O
a	O
Power	O
for	O
his	O
Brother	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
receive	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
that	O
a	O
Note	O
to	O
that	O
purpose	O
directed	O
to	O
Conrade	O
de	O
Gols	O
Esq	O
;	O
was	O
wrote	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Great	B-place
James	I-place
Tavern	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
Street	I-place
,	O
and	O
sign	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Elizabeth	O
Turner	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Shambler	I-pers
;	O
By	O
vertue	O
of	O
this	O
Power	O
this	O
Evidence	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Warrant	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
that	O
Authority	O
the	O
prisoner	O
received	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
sign	O
'd	O
the	O
Book	O
of	O
Entry	O
with	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
;	O
he	O
added	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
received	O
Four	O
Guineas	O
for	O
his	O
pains	O
.	O
His	O
receiving	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
signing	O
the	O
Name	O
Perry	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
by	O
others	O
.	O
His	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
was	O
read	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
employed	O
by	O
his	O
Brother	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
Power	O
,	O
by	O
vertue	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
received	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
sought	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
be	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
his	O
Brother	O
called	O
him	O
from	O
his	O
business	O
,	O
and	O
persuaded	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
Note	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
for	O
his	O
trouble	O
;	O
that	O
this	O
Evidence	O
himself	O
sign	O
'd	O
the	O
name	O
Turner	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
the	O
Projector	O
of	O
it	O
:	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
because	O
his	O
Friends	O
received	O
his	O
Salary	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
allow	O
him	O
Pocket	O
Money	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Stephen	I-place
Walbrook	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
going	O
away	O
sick	O
from	O
her	O
Mistresses	O
,	O
gave	O
the	O
prisoner	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
her	O
Trunk	O
,	O
to	O
give	O
to	O
her	O
Mistress	O
:	O
but	O
she	O
,	O
instead	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Cloths	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Trunk	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Rawlinson	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Hewthwait	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Coat	O
and	O
Wastcoat	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	O
Rawlinson	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Stockings	O
,	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Hewthwait	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
a	O
Holland	O
Stock	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
some	O
Child	O
bed	O
Linnen	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	O
Hewthwait	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
inticed	O
her	O
to	O
lay	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
might	O
get	O
in	O
;	O
The	O
prisoner	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
in	O
her	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
she	O
'd	O
kill	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
said	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
several	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dyer	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Faiths	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Reeve	I-pers
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Walter	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
John	O
Reeve	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
Wig	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Box	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
standing	O
to	O
hear	O
the	B-place
Ballad	I-place
singers	I-place
in	I-place
St.	I-place
Pauls	I-place
Church	I-place
Yard	I-place
,	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
at	O
night	O
on	O
Whitsun	O
Eve	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Lock	I-pers
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Carrick	O
and	O
himself	O
placed	O
themselves	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Wig	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Box	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
call	O
'd	O
John	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
being	O
oblig	O
'd	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
made	O
for	O
him	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
being	O
Whitsun	O
Eve	O
,	O
and	O
beginning	O
about	O
11	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
he	O
kept	O
to	O
his	O
Work	O
there	O
till	O
near	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
;	O
that	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
12	O
he	O
was	O
frequently	O
to	O
and	O
fro	O
at	O
the	O
prisoners	O
stall	O
,	O
in	O
Liquor	O
Pond	O
Street	O
to	O
see	O
after	O
his	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
found	O
him	O
hard	O
at	O
Work	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Halt	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Even	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
supt	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Stall	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
with	O
him	O
till	O
12	O
.	O
Lock	O
(	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
Trial	O
of	O
Wilkinson	O
)	O
said	O
,	O
his	O
Information	O
was	O
pickt	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
asleep	O
in	O
Newgate	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tinsly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Bishopsgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Shoe	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Thatcher	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
10	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
the	O
Glass	O
Case	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
Shoe	O
;	O
and	O
stept	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Katherine	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Priest	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
Ludgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Purser	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Purser	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Hackney	O
Coachman	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
driving	O
home	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
Coach	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
let	O
her	O
in	O
;	O
She	O
threw	O
her	O
Arms	O
round	O
his	O
Neck	O
,	O
and	O
hugg	O
'd	O
him	O
close	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
grew	O
familiar	O
with	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
She	O
was	O
not	O
gone	O
far	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
when	O
feeling	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
he	O
mist	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
:	O
he	O
followed	O
and	O
taxt	O
her	O
with	O
picking	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Watch	O
came	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
but	O
a	O
penny	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
strip	O
herself	O
before	O
them	O
all	O
that	O
they	O
might	O
search	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Watch	O
upon	O
examining	O
took	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Mouth	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
1	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Market	O
to	O
buy	O
black	O
Cherries	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
with	O
her	O
which	O
she	O
put	O
in	O
her	O
Mouth	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
meeting	O
with	O
rude	O
Fellows	O
who	O
might	O
pick	O
her	O
Pocket	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
but	O
a	O
half	O
penny	O
worth	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
a	O
short	O
Pipe	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
penny	O
for	O
her	O
Mornings	O
draught	O
;	O
as	O
she	O
past	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
feeding	O
his	O
Horses	O
on	O
Ludgate	O
Hill	O
,	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
Coach	O
:	O
she	O
was	O
frighted	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Wits	O
at	O
his	O
rudeness	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
follow	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Watch	O
and	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
what	O
she	O
was	O
as	O
innocent	O
of	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Child	O
unborn	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
(	O
a	O
Black	O
,	O
)	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
Mary	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Leak	I-pers
,	O
a	O
gold	O
Ring	O
and	O
2	O
Guineas	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Leak	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
seeing	O
the	O
prisoner	O
(	O
who	O
had	O
formerly	O
been	O
her	O
fellow	O
Servant	O
)	O
go	O
by	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
she	O
courted	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
in	O
and	O
drink	O
,	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
where	O
the	O
Ring	O
was	O
that	O
she	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
wear	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
heard	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
it	O
;	O
She	O
told	O
him	O
;	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
'd	O
shew	O
it	O
him	O
:	O
and	O
then	O
fetch	O
'd	O
down	O
a	O
Glove	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Ring	O
and	O
2	O
Guineas	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
see	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
;	O
He	O
threw	O
her	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Floor	O
and	O
struggled	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
till	O
a	O
Woman	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
gone	O
long	O
before	O
she	O
mist	O
the	O
Guineas	O
and	O
Ring	O
,	O
she	O
acquainted	O
her	O
Master	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
soon	O
in	O
an	O
uproar	O
:	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
an	O
hours	O
time	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
her	O
Master	O
aside	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
old	O
Glove	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
behind	O
the	O
Door	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
stood	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
occasion	O
to	O
use	O
any	O
force	O
to	O
throw	O
her	O
down	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
was	O
always	O
willing	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
pretended	O
she	O
was	O
rob	O
'd	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
very	O
familiar	O
together	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lain	O
with	O
her	O
20	O
and	O
20	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
kept	O
a	O
Sutlers	O
Booth	O
in	O
Hyde	O
Park	O
she	O
was	O
continually	O
running	O
after	O
him	O
:	O
but	O
having	O
lately	O
pickt	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
prosecuted	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
spight	O
.	O
Several	O
Persons	O
of	O
Credit	O
gave	O
the	O
prisoner	O
the	O
general	O
Character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Tysiere	I-pers
,	O
2	O
half	O
Guineas	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
John	O
Tysiere	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
,	O
In	O
Newport-street	O
near	O
de	O
7	O
Dials	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
de	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
say	O
to	O
her	O
how	O
you	O
do	O
Shild	O
O	O
Sir	O
,	O
say	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
be	O
vary	O
glad	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
,	O
what	O
will	O
you	O
treat	O
me	O
now	O
?	O
Ay	O
Shild	O
,	O
Says	O
he	O
,	O
but	O
you	O
no	O
go	O
vid	O
me	O
I	O
vil	O
go	O
first	O
to	O
de	O
tree	O
tun	O
Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
shall	O
come	O
dare	O
and	O
ask	O
a	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
well	O
,	O
she	O
tell	O
a	O
him	O
she	O
will	O
come	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
no	O
tink	O
dat	O
she	O
would	O
:	O
So	O
he	O
go	O
to	O
de	O
Tree	O
Inn	O
,	O
call	O
for	O
one	O
pint	O
of	O
Vine	O
and	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
and	O
vile	O
he	O
vas	O
a	O
Smoking	O
,	O
Mistres	O
Peggy	O
come	O
in	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
tree	O
Shilling	O
in	O
van	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
half	O
Guineas	O
in	O
de	O
oder	O
Pocket	O
;	O
She	O
was	O
very	O
free	O
vid	O
his	O
Breeshes	O
But	O
ven	O
be	O
go	O
to	O
pay	O
de	O
Reckoning	O
he	O
no	O
find	O
de	O
Money	O
de	O
Bish	O
had	O
pick	O
a	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
then	O
askt	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
her	O
the	O
Money	O
?	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
No	O
,	O
be	O
give	O
her	O
nothing	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
nothing	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
every	O
sing	O
of	O
his	O
Breeches	O
but	O
his	O
Vash	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
force	O
to	O
pawn	O
dat	O
for	O
de	O
Reckoning	O
;	O
den	O
he	O
called	O
de	O
Lan-Lord	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
try	O
make	O
de	O
van	O
an	O
strip	O
all	O
her	O
Cloths	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
search	O
her	O
every	O
where	O
but	O
could	O
no	O
find	O
de	O
Money	O
;	O
den	O
he	O
send	O
for	O
de	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
de	O
Constable	O
carry	O
dem	O
before	O
de	O
Shustice	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
send	O
a	O
her	O
to	O
preeson	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
her	O
Husband	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Hart	O
in	O
Leicester	O
Fields	O
,	O
she	O
met	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
askt	O
her	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
;	O
She	O
thought	O
at	O
first	O
she	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
found	O
her	O
self	O
mistaken	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Tavern	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
there	O
offer	O
'd	O
such	O
unseemly	O
and	O
shameful	O
things	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
strove	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
as	O
he	O
desired	O
her	O
he	O
'd	O
fit	O
her	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
charg	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
but	O
tho	O
he	O
made	O
her	O
strip	O
her	O
self	O
and	O
search	O
'd	O
her	O
all	O
over	O
,	O
yet	O
he	O
could	O
find	O
none	O
about	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Elvis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
Charles	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
two	O
Guineas	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecution	O
appearing	O
malicious	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
granted	O
her	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
her	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wheaton	I-pers
,	O
Junior	O
,	O
of	O
Islington	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wheaton	I-pers
,	O
Senior	O
,	O
his	O
Father	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Gun	O
,	O
value	O
35	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Wheaton	O
,	O
Senior	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
he	O
lockt	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
backwards	O
in	O
his	O
Ground	O
;	O
as	O
he	O
returned	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Gun	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
home	O
,	O
found	O
his	O
Door	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Waistcoat	O
and	O
Breeches	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bouch	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Bouch	O
lost	O
his	O
Cloths	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
afterwards	O
took	O
upon	O
William	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
who	O
prov	O
'd	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
In	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
made	O
at	O
Great	O
Yarmouth	O
,	O
but	O
brought	O
no	O
body	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Garton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
by	O
striking	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Breast	O
with	O
a	O
Gun	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
whereby	O
he	O
receiv	O
'd	O
one	O
mortal	O
Bruise	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languisht	O
till	O
the	O
16th	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2	O
d	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
Manslaughter	O
Robert	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Bail	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
being	O
a	O
young	O
Soldier	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
awkward	O
in	O
Exercising	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
his	O
Serjeant	O
,	O
struck	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
with	O
the	O
Muzzel	O
of	O
the	O
Musket	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Breast	O
with	O
the	O
Butt	O
end	O
,	O
so	O
violently	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
beat	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Rank	O
with	O
the	O
force	O
of	O
the	O
blow	O
.	O
Two	O
other	O
Soldiers	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
said	O
he	O
thought	O
his	O
Heart	O
was	O
beat	O
into	O
his	O
Throat	O
;	O
he	O
spit	O
Blood	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
often	O
said	O
he	O
believed	O
that	O
blow	O
would	O
be	O
his	O
death	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
'd	O
lay	O
his	O
death	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
-	O
Sparrier	O
,	O
and	O
-	O
rightly	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
exercising	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
saw	O
no	O
blow	O
given	O
:	O
That	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lifted	O
up	O
his	O
Piece	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
an	O
offer	O
to	O
strike	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Harris	O
,	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
dy	O
'd	O
of	O
a	O
Fever	O
,	O
attended	O
with	O
a	O
Vomiting	O
and	O
Looseness	O
,	O
which	O
proceeded	O
from	O
Cold	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
a	O
very	O
common	O
Distemper	O
in	O
the	O
Camp	O
.	O
That	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
sign	O
of	O
a	O
Bruise	O
outwardly	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
opened	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
no	O
extravasated	O
Blood	O
;	O
that	O
all	O
the	O
internal	O
Parts	O
were	O
clean	O
,	O
without	O
the	O
least	O
Symptoms	O
of	O
any	O
hurt	O
received	O
from	O
a	O
blow	O
.	O
Several	O
Officers	O
gave	O
the	O
prisoner	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
being	O
very	O
humane	O
,	O
hardly	O
ever	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
a	O
Passion	O
,	O
and	O
abuse	O
Men	O
;	O
but	O
was	O
remarkable	O
for	O
his	O
lenity	O
and	O
even	O
Temper	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Smocks	O
,	O
a	O
Box-Iron	O
,	O
Heater	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mollineux	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Pomeroy	I-pers
(	O
22	O
Boys	O
)	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Magnus	I-place
the	I-place
Martyr	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Harwood	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Elliot	I-pers
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
6	O
other	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
from	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
as	O
Elliot	O
was	O
looking	O
over	O
London	B-place
Bridge	I-place
,	O
Humphry	B-pers
Holloway	I-pers
saw	O
Sutton	O
pick	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
it	O
Pomroy	O
;	O
in	O
whose	O
Breeches	O
several	O
other	O
Handkerchiefs	O
were	O
found	O
.	O
Pomroy	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
Handkerchiefs	O
to	O
his	O
Cousin	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
Ship	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
his	O
Breeches	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
having	O
his	O
Pocket	O
pickt	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Sloane	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
4	O
Curtains	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
Bolster	O
,	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Pillow	O
,	O
2	O
s.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
21	O
Yards	O
of	O
Drugget	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Drugget	O
Suit	O
,	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Brass	O
Pot	O
,	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
19	O
Cotton	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
24	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
Wilson	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
carried	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
confess	O
'd	O
where	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
accordingly	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Garret	O
owed	O
her	O
39	O
s.	O
and	O
lent	O
her	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
could	O
pay	O
her	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Ambrose	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Martha	I-pers
Blacklock	I-pers
,	O
of	O
White	B-place
Chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d	O
a	O
Riding	O
Hood	O
,	O
3	O
d.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Paddington	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Woodstock	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Coat	O
with	O
Silver	O
Buttons	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Cane	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Wig	O
,	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
6	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
3d	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
of	O
Isington	B-place
,	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Comel	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
7	O
s.	O
a	O
Wig	O
,	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
1	O
s.	O
3	O
half-pence	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
all	O
which	O
Indictments	O
Wilson	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
;	O
and	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
Evidences	O
being	O
positive	O
to	O
Cole	O
,	O
their	O
knowledge	O
of	O
him	O
chiefly	O
depending	O
on	O
Wilson	O
's	O
Information	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Sparry	I-pers
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Raymund	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Pancrass	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ackersly	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hautboy	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Flagellet	O
,	O
21	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Ackersly	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
from	O
Kentish	B-place
Town	I-place
on	O
Saturday	O
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
about	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
Raymond	O
and	O
another	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
rob	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Stanly	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
7	O
at	O
Night	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
,	O
Raymond	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
(	O
Wright	O
's	O
)	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
the	O
Hautboy	O
to	O
sale	O
,	O
Sparry	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
.	O
Stanly	O
pretending	O
to	O
call	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
fetcht	O
Ackersly	O
and	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
who	O
apprehended	O
them	O
.	O
Sparry	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
his	O
Boy	O
found	O
the	O
Hautboy	O
in	O
the	O
Road	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fuller	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Sparry	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Taylor	O
,	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
from	O
8	O
to	O
9	O
that	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
:	O
and	O
that	O
then	O
Sparry	O
's	O
Wife	O
came	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
home	O
in	O
haste	O
to	O
seat	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
against	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
knew	O
the	O
prisoner	O
wrong	O
any	O
Man	O
in	O
his	O
life	O
.	O
Sparry	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Raymond	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susan	B-pers
Higner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
the	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Randal	I-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
her	O
with	O
her	O
Right	O
Fist	O
,	O
one	O
mortal	O
Bruise	O
on	O
the	O
Right	O
Temple	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
Languisht	O
till	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
as	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
were	O
scolding	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
,	O
My	O
Mother	O
never	O
was	O
a	O
Bawd	O
to	O
me	O
:	O
Whose	O
Mother	O
was	O
?	O
says	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
tell	O
you	O
mine	O
was	O
n't	O
says	O
the	O
Deceased	O
.	O
Why	O
Impudence	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
throw	O
the	O
Tea	O
in	O
your	O
Face	O
if	O
ye	O
call	O
my	O
Mother	O
Bawd	O
;	O
and	O
with	O
that	O
threw	O
Tea	O
,	O
Cup	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
at	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
which	O
missing	O
her	O
,	O
struck	O
Mary	B-pers
Fennel	I-pers
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
Maid	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
then	O
stept	O
up	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
Deceased	O
a	O
slap	O
on	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
fell	O
to	O
fighting	O
:	O
The	O
Deceased	O
cry	O
'd	O
Murder	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
up	O
Stairs	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
followed	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
a	O
Drinking	O
Glass	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
'd	O
have	O
her	O
Heart	O
's	O
Blood	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
shutting	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
the	O
Engagement	O
ended	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
was	O
taken	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
complained	O
of	O
a	O
swelling	O
in	O
her	O
Face	O
.	O
The	O
Surgeons	O
who	O
examin	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
violent	O
Feaver	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
St.	O
Anthony	O
's	O
Fire	O
in	O
her	O
Face	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
her	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Harlow	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
two	O
Guineas	O
,	O
2	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Things	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Trunk	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
from	O
home	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
afterwards	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
at	O
Hyde	O
Park	O
Camp	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Pope	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
)	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Wing	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
lost	O
,	O
he	O
confest	O
upon	O
Examination	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
sold	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bury	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	O
3	O
Wigs	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
Richard	O
Arnold	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
the	O
Wigs	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
Weeks	O
after	O
,	O
by	O
Robert	B-pers
Halfpenny	I-pers
's	O
Direction	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Farows	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Woman	O
they	O
were	O
sold	O
to	O
was	O
absconded	O
.	O
Halfpenny	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
himself	O
and	O
the	O
prisoners	O
coming	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
Williams	O
lookt	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
em	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Rum	O
Ken	O
,	O
i.e	O
.	O
a	O
Shop	O
easy	O
to	O
be	O
rob	O
'd	O
.	O
Williams	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
one	O
Wig	O
,	O
Bury	O
followed	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
this	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edmund	B-pers
Fitzgerald	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Fulham	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Saw	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Casebourn	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
Casebourn	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Rose	B-place
and	I-place
Crown	I-place
in	I-place
Clare	I-place
Court	I-place
in	I-place
Drury	I-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
and	O
laying	O
his	O
Saw	O
down	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
followed	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
because	O
he	O
saw	O
Whores	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Pancrass	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Iron	O
Coal-Rake	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Tow	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
of	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
James	B-pers
Hook	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Shirt	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
Hook	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
asleep	O
on	O
a	O
Bench	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
his	O
Bosom	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
knew	O
him	O
,	O
took'em	O
out	O
,	O
(	O
as	O
he	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
)	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Peters	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
with	O
John	B-pers
England	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Burden	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
feloniously	O
steal	O
300	O
Slates	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Burns	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wall	O
,	O
and	O
opening	O
the	O
Yard	O
Door	O
,	O
let	O
in	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
(	O
an	O
Evidence	O
)	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
Labourers	O
,	O
who	O
assisted	O
in	O
carrying	O
away	O
several	O
Baskets	O
full	O
of	O
Slates	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Matth.ew	B-pers
Dowling	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
dead	O
Carcase	O
of	O
a	O
Sheep	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Willes	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
September	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
loitering	O
about	O
Clare	B-place
Market	I-place
,	O
and	O
took	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
conveying	O
away	O
the	O
Sheep	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
inquiry	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
found	O
him	O
at	O
Hyde	O
Park	O
Camp	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
offered	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
Sheep	O
if	O
they	O
'd	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Emanuel	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Mark	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Wig	O
15	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	B-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
threw	O
him	O
on	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
snatch	O
'd	O
off	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
He	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
kept	O
his	O
Eye	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
the	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
pursuing	O
,	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
jostled	O
him	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
passing	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
Stand	O
by	O
for	O
a	O
Son	O
of	O
a	O
Bitch	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
shov	O
'd	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
forward	O
.	O
He	O
brought	O
proof	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
said	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
prisoner	O
only	O
shov	O
'd	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
fell	O
off	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
run	O
after	O
him	O
to	O
catch	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
knew	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
stop	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
for	O
12	O
s.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Hays	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Signiff	I-pers
,	O
4	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Mackenes	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Mackennis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Wilkins	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
Right	O
Pap	O
,	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
depth	O
of	O
5	O
Inches	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languish	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Swift	I-pers
and	O
Humphry	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Hearing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
quarrelled	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
gone	O
out	O
together	O
,	O
they	O
followed	O
them	O
to	O
Stepney	B-place
Fields	I-place
about	O
10	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
They	O
at	O
a	O
distance	O
saw	O
them	O
make	O
passes	O
at	O
one	O
another	O
with	O
their	O
Swords	O
drawn	O
;	O
and	O
before	O
they	O
could	O
come	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
leading	O
the	O
Deceased	O
by	O
the	O
Arm	O
:	O
They	O
both	O
readily	O
surrendered	O
themselves	O
prisoners	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
asking	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
how	O
he	O
receiv	O
'd	O
his	O
Wound	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
very	O
fairly	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
a	O
Corporal	O
on	O
the	O
Tower	O
Command	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
being	O
ordered	O
to	O
do	O
Corporals	O
Duty	O
,	O
met	O
the	O
Deceased	O
on	O
the	O
Parade	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
Brother	O
Corporal	O
?	O
What	O
's	O
that	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
?	O
Why	O
do	O
you	O
hide	O
your	O
Lace	O
?	O
says	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
Sirrah	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
your	O
officer	O
wont	O
trust	O
you	O
with	O
such	O
Lace	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
struck	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
challenged	O
him	O
out	O
to	O
fight	O
:	O
That	O
John	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
stept	O
in	O
to	O
part	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
ye	O
,	O
you	O
Son	O
of	O
a	O
Whore	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
fall	O
on	O
me	O
too	O
?	O
The	O
prisoner	O
then	O
askt	O
his	O
pardon	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
drink	O
and	O
be	O
friends	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Alehouse	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
then	O
askt	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
walk	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
swore	O
he	O
'd	O
have	O
satisfaction	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
fight	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
'd	O
run	O
his	O
Sword	O
through	O
his	O
jaws	O
.	O
Several	O
Witnesses	O
confirmed	O
the	O
prisoners	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Bullman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
White	B-place
Chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Shirts	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Waller	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
September	O
;	O
of	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Mires	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
returning	O
from	O
Transportation	O
before	O
the	O
expiration	O
of	O
Seven	O
Years	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Ash	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Chelsea	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Counterfeiting	O
,	O
Forging	O
,	O
and	O
Publishing	O
a	O
Promissory	O
Note	O
for	O
137	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Valentine	O
Arnold	O
,	O
payable	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Goodman	I-pers
,	O
or	O
Order	O
;	O
of	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Sail	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Macdonnel	I-pers
13	O
Guineas	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
September	O
.	O
Daniel	O
Macdonnel	O
on	O
his	O
Deposition	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
As	O
Isk	O
yer	O
Lairdship	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
just	O
tacken	O
my	O
Wadges	O
,	O
tharteen	O
Guineas	O
in	O
Good	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
ganging	O
along	O
King-street	O
in	O
Westminster	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
mat	O
this	O
fow	O
quean	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
speid	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
ganging	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
been	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
gen	O
I	O
wad	O
gang	O
wid	O
her	O
till	O
Joanny	O
Davis	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
she	O
wad	O
gi	O
me	O
a	O
Dram	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
tuck	O
hold	O
o	O
'	O
my	O
Hond	O
,	O
and	O
lad	O
me	O
to	O
gat	O
that	O
I	O
ken	O
na	O
'	O
right	O
need	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
she	O
caud	O
for	O
muckle	O
Beer	O
and	O
Brandy	O
and	O
gand	O
me	O
drunk	O
,	O
an	O
lik	O
yer	O
Honour	O
:	O
For	O
in	O
truth	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
she	O
kend	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
pore	O
agnorant	O
Fellow	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
had	O
stade	O
a	O
pratty	O
while	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
Hond	O
intul	O
me	O
Breiks	O
,	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Rackoning	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
na	O
feel	O
any	O
of	O
my	O
Gowd	O
at	O
aw	O
:	O
and	O
whan	O
I	O
speird	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
If	O
I	O
wad	O
na	O
gang	O
awaw	O
,	O
thay	O
woud	O
gar	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
geud	O
faith	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
they	O
beat	O
me	O
full	O
fair	O
,	O
and	O
turnd	O
me	O
intul	O
the	O
Street	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
carried	O
me	O
tull	O
the	O
Round	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
tod	O
'em	O
how	O
I	O
wos	O
rob	O
'd	O
and	O
naxt	O
day	O
I	O
spierd	O
out	O
Joanny	O
Davis	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
run	O
awaw	O
:	O
and	O
at	O
Night	O
I	O
mat	O
this	O
eampudent	O
Bitch	O
the	O
Prasoner	O
,	O
and	O
tuck	O
her	O
up	O
.	O
She	O
must	O
have	O
my	O
Gawd	O
,	O
for	O
na	O
body	O
alse	O
was	O
wi	O
'	O
me	O
but	O
Joanny	O
Davis	O
,	O
that	O
brought	O
what	O
we	O
caud	O
for	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
Camp	O
,	O
she	O
met	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
a	O
Coachman	O
,	O
who	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Davis	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
near	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
sat	O
up	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
nothing	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
No	O
body	O
appeared	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Faulkner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
23	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Katherine	O
,	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Redmane	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
September	O
.	O
Katherine	B-pers
Redmane	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
bought	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
Hundred	O
of	O
Eggs	O
of	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Market	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
her	O
tell	O
them	O
over	O
three	O
times	O
into	O
her	O
Apron	O
,	O
under	O
which	O
her	O
Pocket	O
hung	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
Neighbours	O
bid	O
her	O
see	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
nothing	O
;	O
she	O
look	O
'd	O
and	O
mist	O
her	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Osborn	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Holms	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Web	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Lovegrove	I-pers
Bridget	B-pers
Mortimer	I-pers
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgement	O
as	O
followeth	O
;	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
18.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Hulman	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Oxer	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Oxly	O
,	O
Matthias	B-pers
Brinsden	I-pers
,	O
Walker	O
Green	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Sladden	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Shambler	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Milksop	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Jennings	O
,	O
alias	O
Ghenning	O
,	O
alias	O
Jenkins	O
,	O
alias	O
Trantum	O
,	O
Arthur	B-pers
Hughs	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Casy	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Erberidge	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Lincoln	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Jones	O
,	O
alias	O
Williams	O
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Raymond	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Mires	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
6.	O
William	B-pers
Pitway	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Mackennis	I-pers
alias	O
Mackenes	O
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Osborn	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Holms	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Web	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Lovegrove	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Four	O
last	O
former	O
Convicts	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whip	O
'd	O
,	O
1.	O
Bridget	B-pers
Mortimer	I-pers
,	O
a	O
former	O
Convict	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
,	O
35.	O
Barbara	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sly	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Rudgate	I-pers
.	O
Sir	O
Charles	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
Bart	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hilton	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bowl	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Sourbes	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	O
Hill	O
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Peck	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Burden	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Mires	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Russel	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Vincent	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
Richard	O
rad	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tinsly	I-pers
,	O
Katherine	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Priest	O
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Pomeroy	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Sloan	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Harlow	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Pope	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bury	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Williams	O
Robinson	O
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Dowling	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bulliman	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Peters	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Ash	I-pers
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
at	O
Chelsea	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Ferry	O
,	O
Fin	O
'd	O
50	O
l.	O
and	O
to	O
suffer	O
12	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
pleaded	O
her	O
Belly	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
being	O
impanell	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
quick	O
with	O
Child	O
.	O
A	O
D	O
V	O
E	O
R	O
T	O
I	O
S	O
E	O
M	O
E	O
N	O
T	O
,	O
A	O
Water	O
that	O
perfectly	O
cures	O
the	O
Itch	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
Itching	O
Harbour	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
,	O
without	O
necessity	O
of	O
Purging	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
dangerous	O
Use	O
of	O
Mercury	O
Price	O
1s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
is	O
only	O
prepared	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
A	O
.	O
Downing	O
Chymist	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
and	O
Bull	O
,	O
in	O
Grange	O
Court	O
in	O
St.	O
Johns	O
Lane	O
by	O
Hick-Hall	O
,	O
near	O
West	O
Smithfield	O
.	O
Where	O
also	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
,	O
the	O
best	O
spirits	O
of	O
Scurvy	O
by	O
Wholesale	O
or	O
Resale	O
at	O
d.	O
a	O
Bottle	O
.	O
A	O
most	O
effectual	O
Remedy	O
for	O
the	O
vile	O
lene	O
pain	O
in	O
the	O
Teeth	O
,	O
Price	O
.	O
Also	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Remedy	O
for	O
preserving	O
the	O
Teeth	O
,	O
and	O
clearing	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
.	O
A	O
D	O
V	O
E	O
R	O
T	O
I	O
S	O
E	O
M	O
E	O
N	O
T	O
S.	O
Just	O
publish	O
'd	O
the	O
Second	O
Edition	O
of	O
THE	O
Life	O
and	O
Actions	O
of	O
LEWIS	B-pers
DOMINIQUE	I-pers
C	I-pers
A	O
R	O
T	O
O	O
U	O
C	O
H	O
E	O
,	O
the	O
famous	O
French	O
Robber	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
broken	O
alive	O
upon	O
the	O
Wheel	O
at	O
Paris	O
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
Giving	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
his	O
education	O
in	O
the	O
College	O
of	O
Jesuits	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Pranks	O
he	O
play	O
'd	O
there	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
several	O
robberies	O
he	O
committed	O
alone	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
his	O
turning	O
Thief	O
takes	O
;	O
how	O
after	O
several	O
and	O
various	O
escapes	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
himself	O
at	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
a	O
Gang	O
,	O
which	O
desy	O
'd	O
the	O
publick	O
Justice	O
of	O
France	O
above	O
Seven	O
Years	O
;	O
with	O
a	O
particular	O
relation	O
how	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
manner	O
of	O
his	O
Execution	O
.	O
Also	O
an	O
account	O
