TOKEN	NE
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
STEWART	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
.	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Powys	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Dormer	O
;	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
;	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justice	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
For	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
Edward	B-pers
Gregg	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Lister	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Shirley	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Stephen	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Moleson	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Chase	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Distan	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Harvy	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bush	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Chandler	I-pers
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Thomlinson	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Chad	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Gilmore	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pitman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
Crooked	I-place
lane	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
,	O
69	O
pound	O
of	O
Iron	O
Wire	O
,	O
value	O
48	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
pound	O
of	O
Brass	O
Wire	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
stopt	O
offering	O
Wire	O
to	O
sale	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
examin	O
'd	O
,	O
confest	O
that	O
he	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
to	O
buy	O
small	O
quantities	O
of	O
Wire	O
,	O
and	O
convey	O
'd	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
His	O
Confession	O
before	O
Sir	O
Francis	B-pers
Forbes	I-pers
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Yeomans	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
five	O
pound	O
of	O
Pork	O
,	O
a	O
Cabbage	O
Net	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	O
Lewis	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
last	O
;	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Prince	I-pers
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Greenwood	I-pers
for	O
feloniously	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
Yeomans	O
was	O
a	O
Chairwoman	O
to	O
Lewis	O
.	O
Who	O
missing	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
charge	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
stealing'em	O
.	O
Yeomans	O
then	O
sent	O
word	O
to	O
Prince	O
,	O
at	O
whose	O
House	O
she	O
lodg	O
'd	O
,	O
to	O
remove	O
her	O
Goods	O
.	O
Prince	O
call	O
'd	O
Greenwood	O
to	O
assist	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
going	O
to	O
Prince	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
met	O
Prince	O
and	O
Greenwood	O
on	O
the	O
Stairs	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
Prince	O
and	O
Greenwood	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
thought	O
somebody	O
was	O
coming	O
to	O
seize	O
Yeoman	O
's	O
Goods	O
for	O
Debt	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
secure'em	O
.	O
They	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
Yeomans	O
was	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
acquitted	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Billinsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Watch	O
and	O
Chain	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
1s	O
.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Matth.ew	B-pers
Rook	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
the	O
Watch	O
on	O
board	O
of	O
a	B-place
Ship	I-place
at	I-place
Fresh	I-place
Wharf	I-place
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
Captain	O
;	O
and	O
charging	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
be	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
His	O
Confession	O
before	O
Sir	O
Francis	B-pers
Forbes	I-pers
was	O
read	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Katharine	I-place
Creechurch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dunch	I-pers
,	O
4	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Leather	O
Clogs	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
7	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	O
Dunch	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
mist	O
the	O
Clogs	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
(	O
his	O
Servant	O
)	O
had	O
offer	O
'd	O
some	O
to	O
sale	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
found	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Ward	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
8	O
pair	O
of	O
Clogs	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
Confession	O
before	O
Sir	O
Gerrard	O
Conyers	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Clogs	O
produced	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
David	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
4	O
Sacks	O
,	O
and	O
16	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Malt	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
3	O
Carts	O
were	O
order	O
'd	O
to	O
carry	O
Malt	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Atkins	O
's	O
,	O
(	O
at	O
Paul	O
's	O
Wharf	O
)	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Templer	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Oldstreet	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
coming	O
through	O
Jewen	O
street	O
,	O
stood	O
still	O
,	O
with	O
four	O
Sacks	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Man	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
deliver	O
a	O
Sack	O
hard	O
by	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
upon	O
search	O
found	O
4	O
Sacks	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Maid	O
Servant	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Bird	O
askt	O
her	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
leave	O
a	O
Sack	O
there	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Hours	O
brought	O
in	O
3	O
more	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
then	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
drank	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Atkins	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
examining	O
the	O
3	O
Carmen	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
none	O
but	O
Jones	O
that	O
went	O
into	O
Jewin	O
Street	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
Old	O
street	O
.	O
This	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
confirm	O
'd	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Templer	O
's	O
Servant	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Malt	O
that	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
that	O
Day	O
,	O
came	O
2	O
Quarters	O
short	O
of	O
what	O
he	O
expected	O
.	O
Bird	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Malt	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Cart	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
by	O
Jones	O
's	O
Order	O
.	O
Jones	O
said	O
he	O
deliver	O
'd	O
all	O
the	O
Sacks	O
he	O
received	O
at	O
the	O
Wharf	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
order	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
going	O
through	O
Jewin	O
Street	O
,	O
Bird	O
askt	O
him	O
to	O
drink	O
.	O
He	O
brought	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Bird	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
,	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Rebeccah	B-pers
Tims	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Nicholas	I-place
Cole	I-place
Abby	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Watch	O
and	O
Chain	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
4	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Smith	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
(	O
the	O
Moon	O
shining	O
)	O
coming	O
along	O
Wood-street	B-place
in	O
his	O
Boots	O
,	O
being	O
just	O
come	O
from	O
drinking	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
walk	O
'd	O
by	O
his	O
side	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
left	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
askt	O
him	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
drink	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
to	O
her	O
Lodging	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
said	O
was	O
very	O
convenient	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
both	O
came	O
to	O
Old	O
Fishsteer	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
left	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
he	O
mist	O
his	O
Watch	O
.	O
About	O
10	O
Days	O
after	O
he	O
saw	O
her	O
come	O
by	O
a	O
Door	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
collecting	O
the	O
Tax	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
stop	O
her	O
,	O
not	O
being	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
Woman	O
;	O
but	O
seeing	O
her	O
again	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
he	O
secur	O
'd	O
her	O
.	O
Whilst	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
Custody	O
,	O
her	O
pretended	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Man	O
at	O
the	O
Black	O
Dog	O
in	O
Newgate	O
street	O
,	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
'd	O
give	O
a	O
Bond	O
not	O
to	O
prosecute	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
indemnified	O
for	O
not	O
prosecuting	O
her	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
Bonds	O
were	O
given	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
inform	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
prosecute	O
her	O
he	O
must	O
forfeit	O
his	O
Recognizances	O
,	O
he	O
thereupon	O
proceeded	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
till	O
he	O
apprehended	O
her	O
on	O
London	O
Bridge	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
sick	O
in	O
Bed	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
rob	O
'd	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Undershaft	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Timothy	B-pers
Sims	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Timothy	O
Sims	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
being	O
drinking	O
in	O
Sims	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
mist	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
examin	O
'd	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
who	O
confest	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
put	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
accordingly	O
.	O
The	O
Tankard	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
sworn	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
made	O
the	O
common	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Reynolds	B-pers
Winter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.Magnes	B-place
the	I-place
Martyr	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Siddal	I-pers
,	O
72	O
dozen	O
of	O
Bathmetal	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
21	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
dozen	O
of	O
Sword	O
Belt	O
Locks	O
,	O
value	O
48	O
s.	O
the	O
Good	O
's	O
of	O
John	O
Siddal	O
;	O
and	O
Susan	B-pers
Coats	I-pers
,	I-pers
Spinster	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Barret	I-pers
,	I-pers
Widow	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Winter	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
Reynolds	O
Winter	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
John	O
Siddal	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
off	O
his	O
Compter	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
Dinner	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
of'em	O
after	O
by	O
means	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Wass	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Anderson	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wass	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Coats	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
offer	O
'd	O
him	O
some	O
Rings	O
to	O
sale	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
stopt	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
own	O
'd	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Siddal	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
some	O
Belt	O
Locks	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Yeomans	O
,	O
which	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
Siddal	O
's	O
.	O
-	O
Yeomans	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
Winter	O
going	O
over	O
London	O
Bridge	O
,	O
Winter	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
off	O
Mr.	O
Siddal	O
's	O
Compter	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
and	O
-	O
Jackson	O
,	O
sold	O
the	O
Belt	O
Locks	O
to	O
Anderson	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Yeomans	O
left	O
the	O
Rings	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
Coats	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
sell'em	O
.	O
and	O
accordingly	O
they	O
went	O
together	O
to	O
Wass	O
's	O
,	O
Winter	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Yeomans	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
Coats	O
to	O
sell'em	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
,	O
and	O
Susan	B-pers
Coats	I-pers
acquitted	O
.	O
Reynolds	B-pers
Winter	I-pers
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Waterson	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Chints	O
Gown	O
value	O
42	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
Waterson	O
bring	O
a	O
Silk	O
Dyer	O
,	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
clean	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
stole	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shop	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
observ	O
'd	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
loitering	O
about	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Yeoman	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
stood	O
watching	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
whilst	O
Winter	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
off	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
afterwards	O
sold	O
in	O
Rag	O
Fair	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
40	O
pound	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Dawkins	I-pers
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
(	O
of	O
Alhallows	B-place
Barkin	I-place
)	O
for	O
stealing	O
28	O
pound	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
MICAJAH	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
seeing	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
loitering	O
about	O
Porter	B-place
's	I-place
Key	I-place
,	O
be	O
watch	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
November	O
the	O
30th	O
,	O
between	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
Langly	O
,	O
(	O
convicted	O
at	O
a	O
former	O
Sessions	O
)	O
in	O
Brewer	O
's	O
Key	O
Gate-way	O
,	O
taking	O
Tobacco	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Trowzers	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
Shirt	O
.	O
His	O
Confession	O
before	O
Sir	O
Francis	B-pers
Forbes	I-pers
was	O
read	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Isaac	B-pers
Ingram	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
his	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
her	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
depth	O
of	O
1	O
Inch	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Iron	O
Poker	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
;	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
languish	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
December	O
following	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
that	O
about	O
9	O
or	O
10	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
hearing	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
she	O
ran	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Chamber	O
Door	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
call	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
have	O
kill	O
'd	O
my	O
Wife	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
sitting	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
with	O
her	O
Hands	O
on	O
her	O
Head	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
freely	O
forgave	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
believe	O
he	O
threw	O
the	O
Poker	O
with	O
a	O
design	O
to	O
strike	O
her	O
;	O
advising	O
all	O
Women	O
to	O
forbear	O
provoking	O
Language	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
exprest	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
sorrow	O
for	O
the	O
unhappy	O
Accident	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Kite	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
about	O
3	O
Weeks	O
after	O
the	O
Accident	O
,	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
her	O
Husband	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
some	O
Words	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
:	O
that	O
he	O
depos	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
Breakfast	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
refus	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
several	O
entreaties	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
sure	O
to	O
be	O
killed	O
for	O
not	O
coming	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
come	O
,	O
using	O
other	O
provoking	O
Words	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
sat	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
behind	O
the	O
Curtain	O
;	O
that	O
having	O
the	O
Poker	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
it	O
towards	O
her	O
at	O
random	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
unfortunately	O
stuck	O
in	O
her	O
Head	O
.	O
Other	O
Witnesses	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
provok	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
freely	O
forgave	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
he	O
might	O
not	O
be	O
prosecuted	O
.	O
They	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
very	O
good	O
natur	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
liv	O
'd	O
very	O
lovingly	O
with	O
his	O
Wife	O
till	O
this	O
Accident	O
.	O
The	O
Poker	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
was	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
Yard	O
long	O
,	O
sharp	O
at	O
both	O
ends	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
very	O
thick	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Sadler	O
,	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
prob	O
'd	O
about	O
an	O
Inch	O
deep	O
,	O
the	O
Poker	O
having	O
penetrated	O
through	O
both	O
Tables	O
of	O
the	O
Skull	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Dura	O
Mater	O
,	O
or	O
first	O
Membrane	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
mild	O
Symptoms	O
for	O
about	O
3	O
Weeks	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
grew	O
worse	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
believ	O
'd	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
mortal	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
appear	O
'd	O
very	O
much	O
concern	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
Passion	O
,	O
and	O
highly	O
provok	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
unadvisedly	O
threw	O
the	O
Poker	O
at	O
random	O
towards	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
who	O
sat	O
behind	O
the	O
Curtain	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Malice	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
design	O
or	O
thought	O
of	O
hurting	O
her	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Merey	B-pers
Coop	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Pocket	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
3	O
Farthings	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Coop	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
Merey	O
Coop	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
going	O
along	O
by	O
the	O
dead	O
Wall	O
at	O
the	B-place
Meuse	I-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
run	O
by	O
her	O
,	O
who	O
threw	O
her	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
snatch	O
'd	O
her	O
Pocket	O
off	O
.	O
That	O
a	O
Chariot	O
coming	O
by	O
,	O
she	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
made	O
an	O
offer	O
to	O
strike	O
her	O
,	O
when	O
2	O
Men	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
More	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
hearing	O
a	O
Woman	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
offering	O
to	O
strike	O
her	O
with	O
one	O
Hand	O
,	O
whilst	O
he	O
held	O
the	O
Pocket	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
a	O
Link	O
found	O
the	O
Pocket	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
thrown	O
away	O
.	O
Other	O
Witnesses	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
disprov	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
York	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
and	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
Sarah	B-pers
Wilcox	I-pers
,	O
1	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
together	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
laid	O
her	O
Pockets	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
got	O
up	O
early	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
busy	O
about'em	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
suspecting	O
something	O
,	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
mist	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susan	B-pers
Ranse	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Finchley	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Noble	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
4	O
Guineas	O
,	O
2	O
half	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
15	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
Jan	O
.	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
William	O
Noble	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
latch	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
his	O
return	O
mist	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
afterwards	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
particularly	O
1	O
half	O
Guinea	O
very	O
much	O
worn	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
but	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ranse	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
(	O
as	O
she	O
believ	O
'd	O
by	O
her	O
Voice	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
alter	O
)	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
Bed	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
'd	O
cut	O
her	O
Throat	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
made	O
a	O
noise	O
.	O
She	O
then	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Chest	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
away	O
.	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
that	O
Morning	O
the	O
prisoner	O
told	O
her	O
her	O
brothers	O
House	O
was	O
rob	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
threatned	O
to	O
cut	O
the	O
old	O
Womans	O
Throat	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
before	O
the	O
prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
found	O
out	O
her	O
Mothers	O
Hoard	O
;	O
That	O
in	O
the	O
prisoners	O
house	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
board	O
of	O
the	O
Floor	O
crakt	O
and	O
under	O
it	O
a	O
Rag	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Rag	O
a	O
paper	O
with	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
told	O
them	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
own	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
lain	O
there	O
for	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Weeks	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
happen	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Paper	O
in	O
which	O
it	O
was	O
wrapt	O
up	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
Letter	O
which	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
,	O
this	O
Evidences	O
Wife	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
write	O
,	O
to	O
send	O
to	O
her	O
Mother	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susan	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Seamer	I-pers
a	O
Gold	O
ring	O
.	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Seamer	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
about	O
11	O
at	O
night	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
making	O
water	O
in	O
Fleet-street	B-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
askt	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Wine	O
which	O
he	O
refus	O
'd	O
.	O
With	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
fast	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
struggled	O
to	O
part	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
felt	O
her	O
pull	O
the	O
ring	O
of	O
his	O
Finger	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
watch	O
and	O
secured	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
drunk	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
making	O
water	O
it	O
being	O
moonlight	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
a	O
Woman	O
come	O
and	O
take	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Privities	O
;	O
he	O
likewise	O
taking	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
hand	O
.	O
As	O
she	O
(	O
the	O
prisoner	O
)	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
up	O
her	O
Coats	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
thrusting	O
his	O
hand	O
away	O
he	O
held	O
her	O
fast	O
;	O
and	O
swore	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
his	O
ring	O
.	O
and	O
he	O
'd	O
hang	O
her	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Appleton	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Appleby	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
John	I-pers
Doe	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wedhal	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
3	O
Peruques	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
Mark	B-pers
Pinkly	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
to	O
his	O
Masters	O
Chambers	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
shut	O
in	O
Grays	B-place
Inn	I-place
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Chamber	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
out	O
;	O
that	O
Nicholas	O
a	O
Porter	O
then	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Assistance	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Lodge	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
mist	O
3	O
Wigs	O
,	O
2	O
of	O
which	O
with	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
they	O
found	O
at	O
the	O
Stocks	O
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
standing	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
Richard	O
Jones	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
finding	O
Mr	O
Wedhall	O
's	O
Chamber	O
door	O
standing	O
a	O
Jar	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
brought	O
out	O
the	O
2	O
Wigs	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
hid	O
behind	O
the	O
Stocks	O
and	O
waited	O
there	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
prisoner	O
made	O
a	O
further	O
search	O
;	O
The	O
3	O
Wigs	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Barber	O
being	O
sworn	O
,	O
valued	O
them	O
at	O
but	O
4	O
s.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
James	B-pers
Appleton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Alice	B-pers
Merchant	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
time	O
;	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
2	O
suits	O
of	O
head	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
5	O
s.	O
6	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Alice	O
Merchant	O
.	O
Alice	O
Merchant	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
six	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
sitting	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
in	O
a	O
back	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
her	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
carry	O
'd	O
off	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
going	O
along	O
Castle	O
yard	O
in	O
Holbourn	B-place
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
door	O
standing	O
a	O
jar	O
;	O
Jones	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
entry	O
and	O
saw	O
only	O
one	O
Woman	O
within	O
.	O
Jones	O
then	O
broke	O
the	O
Shutter	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
down	O
a	O
whole	O
light	O
of	O
Glass	O
,	O
and	O
heaving	O
his	O
body	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
took	O
out	O
2	O
boxes	O
and	O
2	O
Books	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
Jones	O
who	O
hid	O
them	O
.	O
Jones	O
being	O
taken	O
at	O
the	O
Robbery	O
in	O
Grays	O
Inn	O
,	O
made	O
himself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
Tenters	O
,	O
9	O
Yards	O
of	O
Broad	O
Cloath	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
East	B-pers
India	I-pers
Company	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
;	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
9	O
yards	O
of	O
green	O
Cloth	O
was	O
cut	O
off	O
a	O
Piece	O
hanging	O
on	O
Mr.	O
Cardels	O
Tenter	O
,	O
November	O
27th	O
.	O
after	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Mayhew	O
a	O
Taylor	O
by	O
the	O
prisoners	O
order	O
,	O
and	O
dy	O
'd	O
a	O
dark	O
brown	O
;	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
the	O
Taylors	O
,	O
and	O
prov	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
with	O
the	O
remaining	O
piece	O
on	O
the	O
Tenter	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Mears	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
Foster	O
and	O
Cummins	O
,	O
who	O
abscond	O
,	O
had	O
stole	O
the	O
Cloth	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
lent	O
them	O
40	O
s.	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
lent	O
40	O
s.	O
to	O
Foster	O
and	O
Cummin	O
on	O
the	O
Cloth	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
they	O
had	O
stole	O
it	O
.	O
Archibald	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
and	O
Peter	B-pers
Nicholson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Nags	O
head	O
on	O
Snow	O
Hill	O
lend	O
Foster	O
and	O
Cummins	O
40	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
Cloth	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Note	O
to	O
repay	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
Month	O
or	O
forfeit	O
the	O
Cloth	O
;	O
which	O
Note	O
(	O
sign	O
'd	O
by	O
these	O
two	O
Evidences	O
)	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
Patrick	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
Town	O
November	O
24th	O
.	O
and	O
lay	O
every	O
night	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
till	O
December	O
the	O
5th	O
.	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
stay	O
out	O
late	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
November	O
26.	O
coming	O
to	O
settle	O
Accompts	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
staying	O
till	O
about	O
11	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
askt	O
him	O
to	O
lie	O
with	O
him	O
all	O
night	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
Turner	O
lying	O
likewise	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Duffus	I-pers
,	O
who	O
at	O
the	O
Sessions	O
in	O
December	O
last	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
and	O
committing	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
body	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Leader	I-pers
,	O
the	O
unnatural	O
sin	O
of	O
Sodomy	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
in	O
a	O
special	O
Verdict	O
:	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
high	O
Crime	O
and	O
Misdemeanour	O
in	O
Assaulting	O
,	O
and	O
Attempting	O
to	O
Commit	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Nicholas	O
Leader	O
,	O
the	O
unnatural	O
sin	O
of	O
Sodomy	O
.	O
Nicholas	O
Leader	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
(	O
being	O
in	O
Bed	O
with	O
him	O
)	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Throat	O
,	O
forcibly	O
turn	O
'd	O
him	O
on	O
his	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
commit	O
the	O
said	O
crime	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Lanman	I-pers
,	O
(	O
aged	O
11	O
)	O
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Armstrong	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Welshman	I-pers
,	O
(	O
aged	O
13	O
,	O
)	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Simon	B-pers
Hansel	I-pers
,	O
1	O
silver	O
snuff	O
Box	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Simon	B-pers
Hansel	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
Simon	O
Hansel	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
5	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
a	O
Porter	O
told	O
him	O
his	O
shew	O
Glass	O
was	O
rob	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
mist	O
snuff	O
Boxes	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
l.	O
William	B-pers
Dee	I-pers
the	O
Porter	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
by	O
a	O
shoe	O
cleaner	O
's	O
direction	O
he	O
took	O
Lanman	O
with	O
a	O
snuff	O
Box	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
next	O
day	O
Armstrong	O
,	O
Robin	B-pers
Drumman	I-pers
and	O
Katherine	B-pers
Rider	I-pers
,	O
coming	O
to	O
see	O
Lanman	O
in	O
the	O
Round	O
House	O
,	O
were	O
all	O
apprehended	O
.	O
Katherine	O
Rider	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
by	O
Charing	O
Cress	O
she	O
went	O
with	O
Robin	B-pers
Drumman	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
Simon	I-pers
,	O
Kitty	B-pers
Weaver	I-pers
and	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
Lanman	O
and	O
Armstrong	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hansell	O
's	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
stood	O
to	O
Watch	O
,	O
whilst	O
Armstrong	O
lifted	O
up	O
the	O
Glass	O
,	O
and	O
Lanman	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
snuff	O
Box	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Lanman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
with	O
Robert	B-pers
Drumman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stockdel	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Penn	I-pers
,	O
3	O
mother	O
of	O
Pearl	O
patch	O
Boxes	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
2	O
silver	O
snuff	O
Boxes	O
,	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stockdel	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	O
Penn	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Stockdel	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
shew	O
Glass	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Bushel	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
Robin	B-pers
Drumman	I-pers
and	O
his	O
Mother	O
in	O
Southwark	O
.	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
silver	O
Tobacco	O
Box	O
(	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Hansel	O
,	O
)	O
on	O
Drummans	O
Mother	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
sold	O
several	O
Goods	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
.	O
Katherine	B-pers
Rider	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Drumman	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
Lanman	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
good	O
many	O
Snuff	O
Boxes	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
show	O
Glass	O
in	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
Market	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
his	O
Mother	O
:	O
who	O
knew	O
where	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Guilty	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Drumman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
(	O
of	O
St.	O
Martins	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
)	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
with	O
Charles	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
Simon	I-pers
and	O
Kitty	B-pers
Weaver	I-pers
(	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
)	O
did	O
privately	O
steal	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Simon	B-pers
Hansel	I-pers
,	O
3	O
silver	O
snuff	O
Boxes	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Simon	O
Hansel	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
Katherine	B-pers
Rider	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
others	O
told	O
her	O
they	O
had	O
rob	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Hansel	O
's	O
shew	O
Glass	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
left	O
open	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Pascal	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
3	O
Ells	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
Guineas	O
and	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Sarah	O
Dawson	O
Widow	O
;	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
scandalous	O
Prosecution	O
concerted	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
Sarah	O
Dawson	O
,	O
a	O
married	O
Woman	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
open	O
Adultery	O
together	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Riding-hood	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
5	O
dozen	O
of	O
Knives	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
Spoon	O
and	O
Dram	O
Cup	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeard	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
Nurse	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Wife	O
in	O
her	O
lying	O
in	O
;	O
and	O
rising	O
earlier	O
than	O
ordinary	O
one	O
morning	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
afterward	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susan	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Evans	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Joel	B-pers
How	I-pers
,	O
a	O
silver	O
Tumbler	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Plate	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joel	B-pers
How	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
sent	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
to	O
draw	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
whilst	O
the	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
offering	O
them	O
to	O
sale	O
,	O
was	O
stopt	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Hatton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Coals	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hollyhock	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Coals	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
use	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
desire	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Daughter	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Darrent	I-pers
,	O
of	O
White	B-place
Chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Bradshaw	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Confession	O
before	O
Justice	O
Perry	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Shorter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Emanuel	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
a	O
suit	O
of	O
Drugget	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Granger	I-pers
;	O
13	O
Suits	O
of	O
Headcloaths	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
12	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
off	O
the	O
Goods	O
when	O
no	O
body	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Green	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
Bundle	O
of	O
Cloaths	O
.	O
Being	O
taken	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Bear	O
in	O
Puddle-dock	O
.	O
She	O
confest	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
offering	O
to	O
give	O
Evidence	O
against	O
William	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Pipemaker	O
at	O
Puddle-dock	O
,	O
with	O
whom	O
she	O
kept	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
who	O
partook	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
for	O
which	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
pawn	O
'd	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
.	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
.	O
20	O
Yards	O
of	O
Chequer	O
'd	O
Linnen	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	O
Welch	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
Jan	O
.	O
last	O
;	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shop	O
Window	O
.	O
Abina	B-pers
Lacheau	I-pers
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Lacheau	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ask'd'em	O
if	O
they	O
'd	O
buy	O
any	O
Cloth	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
his	O
Mother	O
,	O
who	O
shew'd'em	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
they	O
(	O
the	O
prisoners	O
)	O
both	O
telling'em	O
that	O
they	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
Indies	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Lacheau	I-pers
bought	O
some	O
Remnants	O
for	O
10	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
which	O
being	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Goods	O
at	O
Gosport	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Sailor	O
,	O
that	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
brought'em	O
from	O
the	O
Indies	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Mother	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Andrews	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Justus	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
;	O
rough	O
Looking	O
Glass	O
Plates	O
,	O
value	O
52	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Flower	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
Jan	O
.	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
John	B-pers
King	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
rented	O
a	O
Celler	O
in	O
Davis	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
About	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
the	O
Watch	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
rob	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Thieves	O
taken	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Grove	I-pers
,	O
Watchman	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
2	O
Glasses	O
on	O
his	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
Webster	O
with	O
one	O
,	O
near	O
Clerkenwel	O
.	O
Webster	O
then	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
is	O
since	O
dead	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
Webster	O
bind	O
him	O
to	O
carry'em	O
.	O
He	O
brought	O
several	O
Persons	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Burridge	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Berridge	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Field	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Bay	O
Gelding	O
,	O
val.8	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Will	B-pers
.	I-pers
Wragg	I-pers
,	O
on	O
23.	O
of	O
Jan	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Brecknock	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
receiv	O
'd	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Wragg	O
,	O
to	O
inform	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
Horse	O
Mr.	O
Brecknock	O
had	O
often	O
seen	O
.	O
)	O
Soon	O
after	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ride	O
by	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Bond-street	O
upon	O
that	O
very	O
Horse	O
.	O
They	O
dog	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Falcon	O
Inn	O
,	O
where	O
going	O
to	O
seize	O
him	O
he	O
pluck	O
'd	O
out	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
if	O
they	O
touch	O
'd	O
him	O
he	O
'd	O
shoot'em	O
through	O
the	O
Head	O
;	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
he	O
escap	O
'd	O
into	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
last	O
taken	O
.	O
In	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Horse	O
at	O
the	O
RoyalOak	O
in	O
Leicester	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Strickland	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Royal	O
Oak	O
at	O
Leicester	O
,	O
on	O
a	O
Monday	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Hill	O
making	O
a	O
Bargain	O
about	O
a	O
Horse	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
paid	O
12l	O
.	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hill	O
,	O
and	O
Hill	O
gave	O
a	O
Receipt	O
for	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Maid	O
sign	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ashworth	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Strickland	O
came	O
to	O
lodge	O
at	O
her	O
Mistress	O
,	O
the	O
Royal	O
Oak	O
at	O
Leicester	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Night	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
bought	O
the	O
Horse	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
that	O
Night	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pay	O
12	O
l.	O
in	O
Gold	O
to	O
Thomas	O
Hill	O
for	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
her	O
Self	O
Sign	O
'd	O
the	O
Receipt	O
.	O
The	O
Receipt	O
was	O
then	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
dated	O
January	O
the	O
6th	O
,	O
which	O
fell	O
out	O
on	O
a	O
Saturday	O
.	O
Besides	O
,	O
the	O
Horse	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
possession	O
till	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
Jan.	O
and	O
therefore	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
sold	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
.	O
Upon	O
these	O
apparent	O
Perjuries	O
Strickland	O
and	O
Ashworth	O
were	O
order	O
'd	O
into	O
Custody	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susan	B-pers
Stuart	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Murrel	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Hodges	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
mist	O
,	O
upon	O
examination	O
confest	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Table-Cloth	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
lent'em	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Meyric	O
.	O
Meyric	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Sheets	O
and	O
Table-Cloth	O
,	O
telling	O
her	O
she	O
had'em	O
from	O
her	O
Mother	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
.	O
None	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
Goods	O
were	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Starky	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
3	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
75	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lay	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
an	O
Inn	O
in	O
Canterbury	B-place
,	O
and	O
left	O
his	O
Pack	O
in	O
their	O
Bed-Chamber	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
mist	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
London	O
with	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
in	O
his	O
possession	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
swore	O
to	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Abbot	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
2	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
whilst	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
to	O
work	O
,	O
his	O
Room	O
was	O
rob	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
2	O
Women	O
were	O
apprehended	O
at	O
Kensington	O
on	O
suspicion	O
;	O
whither	O
he	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
one	O
of'em	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Breary	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Stephen	I-place
Coleman	I-place
Street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
Jan	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
put	O
up	O
some	O
Hanging	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Lucans	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
put	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
clean	O
Sheets	O
upon	O
Mr.	O
Lucan	O
's	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
What	O
would	O
you	O
give	O
to	O
lie	O
upon	O
such	O
a	O
Bed	O
with	O
a	O
good	O
Bedfellow	O
?	O
He	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
half	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
Pluckt	O
out	O
;	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
.	O
Let	O
me	O
see	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
not	O
being	O
but	O
a	O
Sixpence	O
,	O
and	O
snatching	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
ran	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
after	O
her	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
her	O
no	O
more	O
till	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
Days	O
after	O
,	O
her	O
Husband	O
having	O
before	O
arrested	O
him	O
an	O
100	O
l.	O
Action	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
Warrant	O
against	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
alone	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
offer	O
'd	O
her	O
Snuff	O
,	O
then	O
a	O
Snuff	O
Box	O
;	O
aftewards	O
to	O
present	O
her	O
with	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Damask	O
Pockets	O
,	O
all	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
refus	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
solicited	O
her	O
to	O
leave	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
5l	O
.	O
and	O
maintain	O
her	O
handsomely	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
inform	O
'd	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
who	O
arrested	O
him	O
in	O
an	O
Action	O
of	O
100l	O
.	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
brought	O
this	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Lucan	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
his	O
Servant	O
3	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
Year	O
,	O
that	O
hearing	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
affronted	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
dismist	O
him	O
his	O
Service	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
afterwards	O
arrested	O
by	O
Breary	O
for	O
assaulting	O
his	O
Wife	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
Granted	O
her	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
her	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Dallet	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
Stealing	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
,	O
15	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Armstead	I-pers
produc	O
'd	O
a	O
Purse	O
,	O
and	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
with	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
Richard	O
Marsh	O
,	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Beck	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
utter	O
,	O
expose	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
to	O
Sale	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
defraud	O
Thomas	B-pers
Merry	I-pers
,	O
5	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Silver	O
,	O
Tin	O
,	O
Lead	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Metals	O
,	O
Mixt	O
together	O
,	O
instead	O
of	O
good	O
Silver	O
,	O
knowing	O
the	O
same	O
be	O
conterfeit	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Merry	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
often	O
sold	O
him	O
Burnt	O
Silver	O
for	O
5	O
s.	O
4	O
d.	O
and	O
Ounce	O
.	O
That	O
his	O
Refiners	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
half	O
Silver	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
Stopt	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
discover	O
'd	O
the	O
Mixture	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
bought	O
the	O
Silver	O
of	O
an	O
Earthen-ware	O
Woman	O
,	O
not	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
bad	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Merry	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
)	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
if	O
she	O
could	O
raise	O
20	O
l.	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
now	O
had	O
her	O
Rings	O
in	O
his	O
possession	O
,	O
as	O
part	O
of	O
payment	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Latten	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Peter	I-place
Cornhil	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
of	O
small	O
value	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Farmer	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
Two	O
Witnesses	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
gave	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
appearing	O
malicious	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Whitechappel	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Curtis	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
on	O
8th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
drinking	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
Bar	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
.	O
The	O
Tankard	O
was	O
immediately	O
mist	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
at	O
the	O
Back-door	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pistol	O
(	O
but	O
not	O
charged	O
)	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
make	O
Water	O
,	O
not	O
knowing	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
out	O
backward	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Tankard	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
for	O
fear	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
Stole	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
carried	O
the	O
Pistol	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
Bailiffs	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
gave	O
him	O
no	O
extraordinary	O
Character	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Harman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Harly	I-pers
,	O
2	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Thimble	O
,	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Smelling	O
Bottle	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d	O
and	O
15	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeard	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Humphryson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Kildale	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
Richard	O
Kildale	O
depo	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
he	O
lay	O
together	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
got	O
up	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
confest	O
he	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
Watch	O
to	O
one	O
Nichols	O
,	O
in	O
Barbican	O
,	O
for	O
35	O
s.	O
which	O
the	O
Pawn-broker	O
confirm	O
'd	O
.	O
In	O
his	O
Defence	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Watch	O
voluntarily	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Plowman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
,	O
II	O
Yards	O
of	O
Sattin	O
,	O
value	O
9l	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
confest	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
when	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwel	I-place
,	O
was	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Quincy	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
Jan	O
.	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
Sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Stanborough	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Ickingham	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Viner	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Coat	O
and	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Rand	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
emply	O
'd	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Viner	O
's	O
as	O
a	O
Day	O
Labourer	O
For	O
about	O
5	O
Days	O
.	O
That	O
about	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
they	O
suddenly	O
mist	O
him	O
and	O
their	O
Cloths	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
after	O
they	O
took	O
him	O
at	O
Brentford	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
the	O
Breeches	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
In	O
his	O
Defence	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
he	O
deny	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
ever	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Viner	O
's	O
in	O
his	O
life	O
or	O
ever	O
saw	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Evidences	O
before	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lambert	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
Stolen	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Loding	O
.	O
She	O
found'em	O
expos	O
'd	O
to	O
sale	O
in	O
Middle-Row	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
trc	O
'd	O
out	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Stanford	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
to	O
Wife	O
Mary	B-pers
Langham	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
his	O
former	O
Wife	O
Ann	B-pers
Rasberry	I-pers
,	O
being	O
then	O
living	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Tipping	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
1714	O
he	O
married	O
Richard	O
Stanford	O
,	O
of	O
Cottingham	O
,	O
in	O
Northamptonshire	O
,	O
Carpenter	O
,	O
and	O
Ann	O
Rasberry	O
,	O
of	O
Lambeth	O
,	O
Spinster	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
entered	O
the	O
same	O
in	O
his	O
Book	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
but	O
Could	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Field	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
married	O
Ann	O
Rasberry	O
's	O
Sister	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
known	O
the	O
prisoners	O
and	O
his	O
first	O
Wife	O
for	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
Years	O
past	O
.	O
That	O
his	O
Name	O
was	O
Richard	B-pers
Stanford	I-pers
,	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
Northamptonshire	O
was	O
a	O
Carpenter	O
by	O
Trade	O
,	O
Liv	O
'd	O
with	O
Ann	O
Rasberry	O
as	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
one	O
Child	O
by	O
her	O
.	O
Last	O
August	O
Ann	O
Rasberry	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
very	O
ill	O
of	O
the	O
Foul	O
Disease	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
Friends	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
receiv	O
'd	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
her	O
last	O
Janaury	O
,	O
just	O
as	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
ask	O
him	O
how	O
his	O
Wife	O
did	O
-	O
Mary	B-pers
Langham	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
Church	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
Mary	O
Langham	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
cohabited	O
with	O
Ann	O
Rasberry	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
her	O
-	O
Afterwards	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
dead	O
before	O
he	O
married	O
Mary	O
Langham	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
proving	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Dun	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Rivington	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
wilful	O
and	O
corrupt	O
Perjury	O
,	O
in	O
giving	O
false	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Juston	I-pers
,	O
in	O
this	O
Court	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
when	O
an	O
Indictment	O
was	O
exhibited	O
against	O
the	O
said	O
Elizabeth	O
Juston	O
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
30	O
s.	O
But	O
the	O
Copy	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
indictment	O
not	O
being	O
produc	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Subornation	O
of	O
Perjury	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Pember	I-pers
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Pember	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
her	O
own	O
Door	O
,	O
(	O
the	B-place
Greyhound	I-place
in	I-place
West	I-place
Smithfield	I-place
)	O
about	O
8	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Arm	O
.	O
Go	O
along	O
Blockhead	O
(	O
says	O
she	O
)	O
its	O
very	O
bard	O
if	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
stand	O
at	O
my	O
own	O
Door	O
.	O
Who	O
do	O
you	O
call	O
Blockhead	O
,	O
ye	O
Bitch	O
you	O
?	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
lifting	O
up	O
his	O
Fist	O
,	O
he	O
struck	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
.	O
beat	O
out	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
Teeth	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
her	O
Thumb	O
out	O
of	O
joint	O
,	O
she	O
holding	O
up	O
her	O
Hand	O
to	O
ward	O
off	O
the	O
Blow	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
reel	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
blockheadly	O
Thief	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
being	O
very	O
much	O
affronted	O
at	O
,	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
slap	O
of	O
the	O
Face	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
at	O
first	O
fin	O
'd	O
10	O
l.	O
and	O
3	O
Years	O
Imprisonment	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
Mrs.	O
Pember	O
's	O
Entreaty	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
diminish	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
1	O
Years	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
a	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
2	O
Shirts	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
.	O
John	O
Holland	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
home	O
about	O
7	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
his	O
Window	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Goods	O
gone	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
own	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
just	O
before	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
who	O
committed	O
that	O
Robbery	O
.	O
This	O
prisoner	O
was	O
order	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
to	O
Gloucester	O
,	O
there	O
to	O
be	O
try	O
'd	O
for	O
several	O
Robberies	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
cast	O
for	O
their	O
Lives	O
this	O
Sessions	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
lusty	O
Fellow	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
was	O
inform	O
'd	O
that	O
this	O
was	O
a	O
Contrivance	O
to	O
prevent	O
his	O
going	O
to	O
Gloucester	O
;	O
that	O
so	O
by	O
being	O
condemn	O
'd	O
here	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
assist	O
them	O
in	O
their	O
Design	O
of	O
making	O
and	O
escape	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
the	O
Court	O
directed	O
the	O
Jury	O
to	O
find	O
him	O
not	O
guilty	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Keepers	O
to	O
secure	O
him	O
.	O
Matth.ew	B-pers
Cusworth	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Cutsworth	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
5	O
pair	O
of	O
Hinges	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
3	O
Quarts	O
of	O
Turpentine	O
Oil	O
.	O
2	O
Locks	O
2	O
s.	O
2	O
Iron	O
Bars	O
,	O
13	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
Bolts	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
7th	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecution	O
appear	O
'd	O
so	O
malicious	O
that	O
the	O
Court	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
prisoner	O
the	O
trouble	O
of	O
making	O
his	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
pray	O
'd	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
his	O
indictment	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
immediately	O
granted	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Gerrard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
,	I-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
2	O
Flanders	O
lac	O
'd	O
Pinners	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
13	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Katherine	B-pers
Greenaway	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
7th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
The	O
indictment	O
being	O
laid	O
before	O
the	O
last	O
Act	O
of	O
Grace	O
,	O
she	O
receiv	O
'd	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Pitman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
2	O
Gouges	O
,	O
value	O
20d	O
.	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Wood	O
,	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Cuff	I-pers
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Dehammel	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
gone	O
out	O
to	O
work	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
his	O
Name	O
for	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
let	O
him	O
take	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
might	O
have	O
his	O
Goods	O
again	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
sold'em	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Keeble	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Whitchurch	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Coats	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
Jan	O
last	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Briscoe	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
set	O
with	O
Diamonds	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
l.	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
8	O
s.	O
33	O
Guineas	O
,	O
1	O
Five-Guinea	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
35	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
9	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
.	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Clerkerwel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Eustace	B-pers
Miles	I-pers
,	O
2	O
Looking	O
Glasses	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
1	O
Sheet	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Eustace	O
Miles	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
to	O
sufficient	O
to	O
fix	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Barter	I-pers
,	O
3	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3rd	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
John	O
Barter	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
at	O
night	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
who	O
overpersuaded	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
Brandy	O
shop	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Andrews-street	I-place
:	O
Harrison	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
Geneva	O
and	O
grew	O
very	O
familiar	O
with	O
his	O
Breeches	O
:	O
that	O
he	O
felt	O
her	O
hand	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
which	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
his	O
own	O
hand	O
and	O
feeling	O
some	O
money	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
she	O
had	O
rob	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
missing	O
the	O
sum	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
out	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
committed	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
.	O
Harrison	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
so	O
much	O
Money	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
dropt	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
more	O
than	O
she	O
took	O
.	O
Harrison	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
quartern	O
of	O
Geneva	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
gave	O
a	O
Shilling	O
to	O
change	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
8	O
d.	O
he	O
had	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
beckon	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
lie	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
that	O
8	O
d.	O
but	O
she	O
refusing	O
,	O
he	O
swore	O
he	O
'd	O
be	O
reveng	O
'd	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
Being	O
askt	O
if	O
she	O
could	O
call	O
any	O
body	O
to	O
her	O
reputation	O
;	O
yes	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
here	O
's	O
this	O
Gentlewoman	O
(	O
pointing	O
to	O
her	O
fellow	O
prisoner	O
)	O
knows	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
honest	O
,	O
Harrison	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
reaching	O
Watkins	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
Queenhith	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Kilderkin	O
of	O
Ale	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Calcot	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
David	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stoln	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Roberts	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
Calcot	O
used	O
to	O
keep	O
Oxford	O
Ale	O
for	O
sale	O
in	O
a	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Bird	O
,	O
Robert	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
by	O
mistake	O
put	O
one	O
of	O
Calcot	O
's	O
Kilderkins	O
among	O
his	O
Masters	O
,	O
but	O
finding	O
his	O
mistake	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
presently	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
granted	O
them	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
their	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Tracy	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Pawn	O
broker	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
received	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
prisoners	O
name	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
let	O
the	O
Goods	O
lye	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Name	O
;	O
The	O
Prosecution	O
appear	O
'd	O
intirely	O
malicious	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Eaton	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
John	I-pers
the	I-pers
Grinder	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Picket	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Avery	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bartholomew	I-place
the	I-place
Great	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Knowles	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
;	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
silk	O
Pocket	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
Watch	O
and	O
Chain	O
5	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Snuff	O
Box	O
,	O
13	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Knowles	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
between	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
somebody	O
came	O
behind	O
her	O
in	O
Long	B-place
Lane	I-place
and	O
kick	O
'd	O
her	O
leg	O
,	O
and	O
snatch	O
'd	O
her	O
Pocket	O
off	O
;	O
that	O
applying	O
her	O
self	O
to	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
helpt	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Watch	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Eades	I-pers
alias	O
Eaves	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
3	O
prisoners	O
committed	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
Eades	O
strove	O
to	O
knock	O
her	O
down	O
,	O
Picket	O
snatch	O
'd	O
the	O
Pocket	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
James	O
.	O
Eades	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
Watch	O
for	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
shar	O
'd	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
search	O
of	O
John	O
the	O
Grinder	O
to	O
Crown	O
Court	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
:	O
that	O
Eaves	O
seeing	O
him	O
,	O
stood	O
against	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
but	O
Wild	O
threatning	O
to	O
fire	O
was	O
let	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Grinder	O
hid	O
under	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
secur	O
'd	O
him	O
and	O
Eaves	O
;	O
that	O
Eaves	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
snatch	O
'd	O
a	O
Pocket	O
with	O
a	O
Watch	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
in	O
Long	O
Lane	O
,	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
the	O
Grinder	O
,	O
Picket	O
and	O
Avery	O
:	O
upon	O
this	O
he	O
apprehended	O
Picket	O
and	O
Avery	O
whom	O
he	O
knew	O
to	O
be	O
old	O
snatch	O
Pockets	O
;	O
That	O
they	O
afterwards	O
confest	O
that	O
they	O
design	O
'd	O
to	O
become	O
Evidences	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
already	O
Impeach	O
'd	O
.	O
Some	O
Witnesses	O
appear	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
Grinder	O
who	O
knew	O
little	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
gave	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
of	O
his	O
Father	O
and	O
Mother	O
.	O
Several	O
spoke	O
for	O
Picket	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Hackney	O
Coachman	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
guilty	O
they	O
believed	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
lately	O
drawn	O
in	O
.	O
Many	O
gave	O
Avery	O
an	O
extraordinary	O
Character	O
:	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Bricklayer	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
always	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
careful	O
and	O
industrious	O
.	O
Avery	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
other	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Frances	B-pers
Lacey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
,	O
20	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Geneva	O
,	O
value	O
39	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	O
Austin	O
,	O
9	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Daughter	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Pew	I-pers
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
two	O
Years	O
ago	O
,	O
she	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
her	O
Father	O
's	O
Stairs	O
with	O
a	O
Pail	O
of	O
Geneva	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
:	O
who	O
threatned	O
to	O
kill	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
told	O
her	O
Father	O
:	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
her	O
Ten	O
or	O
a	O
Dozen	O
times	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
manner	O
:	O
another	O
time	O
she	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
9	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Father	O
's	O
Drawer	O
:	O
that	O
she	O
conceal	O
'd	O
it	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
acquainted	O
her	O
Father	O
with	O
it	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
before	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
that	O
Pew	O
had	O
quarrel	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
accus	O
'd	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
Spite	O
.	O
Several	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Good	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Margaret	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
Margaret	O
Kemp	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
along	O
Holbourn	B-place
about	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
her	O
Handkerchief	O
was	O
snatch	O
'd	O
off	O
her	O
Neck	O
:	O
she	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Thief	O
run	O
into	O
Stichbourn	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
thence	O
cross	O
the	O
way	O
into	O
Red	O
Lyon	O
Street	O
.	O
The	O
Handkerchief	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
Neck	O
;	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
another	O
swore	O
positively	O
to	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
standing	O
at	O
his	O
stall	O
in	O
Stichbourn	O
Court	O
:	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
Mob	O
running	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
after	O
them	O
into	O
Red	O
Lyon	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
back	O
found	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
he	O
shew	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
a	O
publick	O
company	O
in	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
that	O
same	O
Night	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
his	O
Stall	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Woman	O
cry	O
'd	O
stop	O
Thief	O
and	O
the	O
Mob	O
run	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ran	O
after	O
them	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
up	O
the	O
Hankerchief	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Bruce	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
Charity	B-pers
Withard	I-pers
and	O
Honour	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Damask	O
Chair	O
seat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
2	O
Chairmen	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
drinking	O
at	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
the	O
seat	O
was	O
stole	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
Chair	O
.	O
The	O
watchmen	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
some	O
Women	O
call	O
'd	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Privy	O
Garden	O
,	O
and	O
shew	O
'd	O
them	O
the	O
seat	O
of	O
the	O
Chair	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
found	O
between	O
the	O
two	O
Gates	O
.	O
Several	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
reputation	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hutchins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Saw	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
while	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
at	O
dinner	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Saw	O
off	O
the	O
Bench	O
,	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
stopt	O
by	O
one	O
that	O
watch	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bower	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
21	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
value	O
55	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Clogs	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hannel	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2nd	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
John	O
Hannel	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
the	O
Shoes	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
enquiry	O
found	O
them	O
at	O
Robert	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
Winifred	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
who	O
was	O
Hannels	O
Journyman	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
his	O
Master	O
had	O
turn	O
'd	O
them	O
upon	O
his	O
hands	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
apprehended	O
for	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Mac-cave	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Dun	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Galloway	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
in	O
Riotously	O
assaulting	O
several	O
Constables	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
execution	O
of	O
their	O
Office	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Burt	I-pers
Constable	O
,	O
produced	O
a	O
Warrant	O
for	O
Searching	O
Gaming	O
Houses	O
,	O
sign	O
'd	O
by	O
10	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
that	O
in	O
execution	O
of	O
that	O
Warrant	O
he	O
with	O
Jeffery	O
Nash	O
and	O
George	B-pers
Cartwright	I-pers
both	O
Constables	O
(	O
since	O
dead	O
)	O
and	O
several	O
others	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.Vandernans	O
House	O
in	O
Playhouse	B-place
passage	I-place
Drury-lane	I-place
,	O
where	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
enter	O
were	O
driven	O
back	O
with	O
drawn	O
Swords	O
;	O
that	O
those	O
within	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Window	O
shutter	O
and	O
threw	O
Brickbats	O
,	O
Ale-house	O
Pots	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Chamber	O
Pot	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Constables	O
.	O
The	O
Proclamation	O
was	O
read	O
,	O
and	O
those	O
within	O
cry	O
'd	O
A	O
T	O
-	O
d	O
of	O
your	O
Proclamation	O
.	O
The	O
Guards	O
were	O
then	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
Soldiers	O
came	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
round	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
let	O
in	O
the	O
rest	O
;	O
they	O
left	O
two	O
Soldiers	O
to	O
guard	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
but	O
Burden	O
and	O
Ringrose	O
pretending	O
to	O
be	O
Officers	O
,	O
and	O
commanding	O
the	O
Soldiers	O
away	O
,	O
the	O
Mob	O
then	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
the	O
Colonels	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Soldiers	O
are	O
going	O
;	O
-	O
Edward	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
being	O
charg	O
'd	O
to	O
assist	O
the	O
Constables	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
Vandernans	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
outer	O
Door	O
and	O
the	O
Hatch	O
within	O
open	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Cartwright	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
inward	O
Hatch	O
saw	O
above	O
20	O
Men	O
gaming	O
,	O
who	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
ye	O
we	O
're	O
all	O
taken	O
,	O
put	O
out	O
the	O
Candles	O
and	O
draw	O
your	O
Swords	O
;	O
which	O
they	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
forc	O
'd	O
him	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
retiring	O
his	O
Coat	O
fasten	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Hatch	O
;	O
over	O
which	O
they	O
made	O
Passes	O
at	O
him	O
with	O
their	O
Swords	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
tearing	O
his	O
Coat	O
he	O
crawld	O
on	O
his	O
hands	O
and	O
knees	O
to	O
the	O
outward	O
Door	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
saw	O
Galloway	O
coming	O
down	O
the	O
Passage	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
ye	O
there	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
Man	O
among	O
ye	O
!	O
and	O
bidding	O
him	O
go	O
about	O
his	O
business	O
,	O
he	O
replied	O
,	O
I	O
've	O
as	O
much	O
business	O
here	O
as	O
you	O
,	O
for	O
you	O
're	O
a	O
part	O
of	O
informing	O
Dogs	O
,	O
and	O
ought	O
to	O
have	O
your	O
Brains	O
beat	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
Proclamation	O
was	O
then	O
read	O
,	O
and	O
Galloway	O
said	O
.	O
D	O
-	O
-n	O
you	O
and	O
your	O
Proclamation	O
too	O
!	O
-	O
Come	O
but	O
over	O
the	O
Kennel	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
give	O
you	O
what	O
you	O
deserve	O
.	O
In	O
about	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
half	O
a	O
dozen	O
lusty	O
Fellows	O
would	O
beat	O
you	O
all	O
?	O
calling	O
them	O
informing	O
Dogs	O
,	O
Rogues	O
and	O
Raseals	O
.	O
About	O
10	O
days	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Riot	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
again	O
perfectly	O
well	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Galloway	O
confest	O
to	O
him	O
at	O
Justice	O
Vaughan	O
's	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Riot	O
.	O
-	O
Proclamation	O
was	O
made	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Cartwright	O
askt	O
those	O
within	O
if	O
they	O
'd	O
surrender	O
,	O
who	O
answer	O
'd	O
Ay	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
ye	O
if	O
you	O
'll	O
have	O
our	O
Swords	O
in	O
your	O
Guts	O
!	O
-	O
After	O
the	O
Constables	O
were	O
entered	O
they	O
shut	O
the	O
outer	O
Door	O
but	O
the	O
Mob	O
beat	O
so	O
violently	O
against	O
it	O
that	O
the	O
Nails	O
were	O
almost	O
forc	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Hinges	O
.	O
Ringrose	O
and	O
Burden	O
came	O
pretending	O
to	O
the	O
Officers	O
,	O
and	O
Ringrose	O
struck	O
this	O
Evidence	O
several	O
times	O
with	O
his	O
Cane	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
being	O
in	O
Playhouse	O
Passage	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Vaughan	O
take	O
Galloway	O
by	O
the	O
Arm	O
and	O
bring	O
him	O
out	O
;	O
that	O
Galloway	O
said	O
,	O
There	O
's	O
not	O
a	O
Man	O
among	O
ye	O
,	O
you	O
're	O
all	O
a	O
pack	O
of	O
informing	O
Rogues	O
?	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Vaughan	O
desir	O
'd	O
he	O
'd	O
go	O
about	O
his	O
business	O
;	O
you	O
Rascal	O
(	O
says	O
Galloway	O
)	O
you	O
dare	O
not	O
see	O
me	O
on	O
t'other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
!	O
-	O
The	O
Proclamation	O
was	O
read	O
,	O
and	O
Galloway	O
there	O
upon	O
lifting	O
up	O
his	O
left	O
hand	O
cry	O
'd	O
a	O
T	O
-	O
d	O
of	O
your	O
Proclamation	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
it	O
twice	O
already	O
but	O
do	O
n't	O
value	O
it	O
.	O
Further	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
great	O
disturbance	O
there	O
,	O
being	O
very	O
busy	O
and	O
abusive	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
likewise	O
saw	O
Dun	O
there	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
a	O
Mob	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
;	O
if	O
half	O
a	O
dozen	O
brisk	O
young	O
Fellows	O
would	O
but	O
go	O
down	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
'd	O
clear	O
the	O
Place	O
of	O
them	O
all	O
!	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
such	O
particular	O
notice	O
of	O
Galloway	O
and	O
Dun	O
,	O
(	O
Dun	O
especially	O
,	O
whom	O
she	O
saw	O
2	O
days	O
after	O
)	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
certain	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
the	O
Persons	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Rook	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Constables	O
came	O
,	O
the	O
Gamesters	O
were	O
playing	O
at	O
Dice	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
outer	O
door	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Hatch	O
was	O
shut	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Constables	O
could	O
get	O
in	O
,	O
Mac-cave	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
it	O
put	O
out	O
the	O
Candles	O
,	O
here	O
's	O
the	O
Informers	O
.	O
Stand	O
by	O
me	O
and	O
we	O
'll	O
keep	O
them	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
Candles	O
were	O
put	O
out	O
:	O
Maccave	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
passes	O
over	O
the	O
Hatch	O
;	O
says	O
Rook	O
,	O
the	O
Constables	O
seem	O
very	O
strenuous	O
,	O
let	O
them	O
come	O
in	O
,	O
perhaps	O
they	O
're	O
come	O
in	O
search	O
of	O
some	O
particular	O
Person	O
.	O
Maccave	O
reply	O
'd	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
ye	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
that	O
offers	O
to	O
come	O
in	O
or	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
mention	O
any	O
ones	O
Name	O
;	O
I	O
'll	O
run	O
my	O
Sword	O
thro	O
him	O
.	O
Brickbats	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
were	O
thrown	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
Mac-cave	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
having	O
often	O
Gam	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Depontu	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Constables	O
came	O
,	O
the	O
Candles	O
were	O
put	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
Mac-cave	O
draw	O
his	O
Sword	O
and	O
making	O
several	O
Passes	O
at	O
Vaughan	O
forced	O
him	O
back	O
.	O
The	O
Constables	O
askt	O
them	O
if	O
they	O
'd	O
surrender	O
,	O
and	O
Maccave	O
said	O
,	O
come	O
here	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
surrender	O
with	O
my	O
Sword	O
in	O
your	O
Body	O
-	O
A	O
Constables	O
staff	O
was	O
broke	O
and	O
the	O
Constables	O
forc	O
'd	O
to	O
retire	O
;	O
Brickbats	O
and	O
Alehouse	O
Pots	O
&	O
c.	O
were	O
thrown	O
at	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
gamed	O
with	O
Mac	O
cave	O
and	O
knew	O
him	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
Vandernans	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
common	O
Gaming	O
House	O
for	O
9	O
Years	O
past	O
;	O
being	O
cross	O
examin	O
'd	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
for	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Rioters	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
such	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
kept	O
in	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Randal	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Box-keeper	O
at	O
Vandernans	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Gamesters	O
were	O
playing	O
at	O
Hazard	O
,	O
the	O
outward	O
Door	O
open	O
:	O
but	O
the	O
Hatch	O
within	O
was	O
shut	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Constables	O
could	O
pass	O
it	O
:	O
the	O
Candles	O
were	O
put	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
Mac-cave	O
had	O
a	O
drawn	O
Sword	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
open	O
'd	O
to	O
let	O
out	O
one	O
Butler	O
a	O
reputed	O
Highwayman	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
Vandernans	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Gaming	O
house	O
8	O
or	O
9	O
Years	O
past	O
;	O
George	B-pers
Stewart	I-pers
deposed	O
the	O
Gamesters	O
were	O
at	O
Hazard	O
when	O
the	O
Constables	O
came	O
,	O
the	O
Candles	O
were	O
put	O
out	O
,	O
Mac-cave	O
made	O
Passes	O
over	O
the	O
Hatch	O
with	O
his	O
drawn	O
Sword	O
and	O
swore	O
none	O
should	O
go	O
out	O
or	O
come	O
in	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
askt	O
to	O
surrender	O
,	O
and	O
somebody	O
answer	O
'd	O
:	O
yes	O
,	O
we	O
'll	O
surrender	O
with	O
our	O
swords	O
in	O
your	O
guts	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
known	O
Vandernans	O
,	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
common	O
Gaming	O
house	O
3	O
Years	O
.	O
Several	O
Witnesses	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Riot	O
lasted	O
from	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
till	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
's	O
Council	O
,	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Leach	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
Ralph	B-pers
Ayres	I-pers
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Dun	O
and	O
Galloway	O
came	O
into	O
a	O
Brandyshop	O
opposite	O
to	O
Playhouse	O
Passage	O
,	O
soon	O
after	O
the	O
Riot	O
began	O
;	O
and	O
staid	O
there	O
till	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
;	O
except	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
for	O
10	O
Minutes	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Dun	O
was	O
no	O
Gamester	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
laborious	O
industrious	O
Man	O
.	O
commonly	O
working	O
till	O
late	O
at	O
Night	O
at	O
his	O
Business	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
Peruke	O
making	O
.	O
For	O
Mr.	O
Maccave	O
,	O
they	O
call	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Heybourn	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Heybourn	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
,	O
who	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
Vandernan	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Maccave	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
before	O
the	O
Gun	O
was	O
fir	O
'd	O
,	O
came	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Window	O
over	O
the	O
Houses	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
that	O
time	O
a	O
Man	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
her	O
Garret	O
Window	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
found	O
afterwards	O
to	O
be	O
Maccave	O
The	O
King	O
's	O
Council	O
,	O
by	O
way	O
of	O
Reply	O
,	O
read	O
Galloway	O
's	O
Confession	O
before	O
Justice	O
Wickham	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
he	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Freeman	O
in	O
the	O
Crowd	O
,	O
who	O
pull	O
'd	O
Dun	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
all	O
three	O
went	O
to	O
Leach	O
's	O
Brandyshop	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
all	O
went	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
betwixt	O
that	O
Shop	O
and	O
Vandernan	O
's	O
,	O
several	O
times	O
during	O
the	O
Riot	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
then	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Gun	O
was	O
not	O
fir	O
'd	O
till	O
2	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
just	O
at	O
the	O
close	O
of	O
the	O
Riot	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
all	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminister	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wallen	I-pers
,	O
9	O
Half-Peck	O
Loaves	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
Journeyman	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
(	O
a	O
Baker	O
)	O
and	O
sold	O
the	O
Loaves	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
for	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
piece	O
,	O
to	O
James	B-pers
Jordan	I-pers
in	O
Kingstreet	O
.	O
He	O
confest	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Chairs	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Chairs	I-pers
.	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Trunk	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Sheet	O
,	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
14	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Charwel	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
kept	O
by	O
the	O
Parish	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
Grandmother	O
to	O
the	O
prisoners	O
;	O
who	O
taking	O
an	O
opportunity	O
when	O
the	O
poor	O
Woman	O
was	O
a-bed	O
,	O
carried	O
away	O
her	O
Trunk	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Goods	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
afterwards	O
found	O
upon	O
'em	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Presman	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Pritman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Horse	O
Pannel	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Boswell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
the	O
Pannel	O
(	O
or	O
Pack-Saddle	O
)	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Stable	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
lock	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
preceding	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
His	O
Confession	O
before	O
Justice	O
Blany	O
was	O
read	O
:	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
22	O
Silver	O
Buttons	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Brangwin	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
Richard	O
Brangwin	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
22	O
Plate	O
Buttons	O
on	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
stolen	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Poultry	O
Compter	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Salgrove	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Baily	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
alone	O
,	O
cutting	O
the	O
Buttons	O
off	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Breeches	O
;	O
and	O
asking	O
him	O
why	O
he	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
he	O
bid	O
him	O
meddle	O
with	O
his	O
own	O
Business	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Dining	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sent	O
order	O
to	O
his	O
Wife	O
to	O
remove	O
all	O
his	O
Plate	O
,	O
(	O
all	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
own	O
'd	O
;	O
)	O
his	O
Wife	O
being	O
in	O
haste	O
,	O
defir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
help	O
her	O
cut	O
off	O
the	O
Buttons	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
.	O
this	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
.	O
Several	O
Gentlemen	O
appear	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
behalf	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecution	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
malicious	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
granted	O
him	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
his	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Wyatt	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Symson	I-pers
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Smock	O
,	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Scarf	O
,	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	O
Symson	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
gold	O
Locket	O
,	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
GERTRUDE	B-pers
Tuck	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
;	O
to	O
both	O
which	O
Indictments	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Clackston	I-pers
.	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Dryden	B-pers
Leach	I-pers
,	O
100	O
quire	O
of	O
printed	O
Paper	O
,	O
value	O
17	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Leach	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
moving	O
his	O
Goods	O
at	O
Michaelmas	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
his	O
Errand	O
boy	O
,	O
)	O
had	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
being	O
often	O
in	O
his	O
Warehouse	O
;	O
from	O
whence	O
(	O
as	O
he	O
confest	O
,	O
)	O
he	O
had	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
convey	O
'd	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Servants	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
bundle	O
of	O
printed	O
Paper	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
(	O
seeing	O
this	O
Evidence	O
,	O
)	O
then	O
left	O
behind	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Leonard	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confess	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
and	O
name	O
the	O
several	O
places	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
upon	O
enquiry	O
they	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
true	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Ely	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
quire	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
for	O
waste	O
Paper	O
,	O
at	O
2	O
d.	O
half	O
penny	O
a	O
quire	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
:	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
followeth	O
;	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
12.	O
George	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Claxton	I-pers
,	O
Reynolds	O
Winter	O
,	O
John	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Eaton	O
,	O
alias	O
John	O
the	O
Grinder	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Lanman	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Picket	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Appleby	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Appleton	O
,	O
alias	O
John	B-pers
Doe	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Armstrong	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Welsbman	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Lee	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Burridge	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Berridge	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Drumman	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Plowman	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
4.	O
Peter	B-pers
Jugular	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Alice	B-pers
Leaky	I-pers
,	O
(	O
both	O
these	O
Convicted	O
last	O
Sessions	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Stanford	I-pers
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Ingram	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
,	O
29.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pitman	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Yeomans	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
York	I-pers
,	O
Susan	B-pers
Ranse	I-pers
,	O
Susan	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Evans	O
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Darrent	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Shorter	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Auderson	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Justus	I-pers
,	O
Susan	B-pers
Stuart	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Starky	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Abbot	I-pers
,	O
MAry	O
Harman	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Humpbryson	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Stanborough	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lambert	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Pitman	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Chairs	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Chairs	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Presman	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Pritman	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hutchins	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
James	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
Fin	B-pers
'd	I-pers
5	O
l.	O
and	O
1	O
Years	O
Imprisonment	O
Alice	B-pers
Beck	I-pers
,	O
Fin	B-pers
'd	I-pers
40	O
s.	O
Charles	B-pers
Maccave	I-pers
,	O
Fin	O
'd	O
100l	O
.	O
5	O
Years	O
Imprisonment	O
and	O
to	O
find	O
Security	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
for	O
4	O
Years	O
afterward	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Dun	I-pers
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Galloway	I-pers
,	O
Fin	B-pers
'd	I-pers
50	O
l.	O
each	O
,	O
1	O
Years	O
Imprisonment	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
find	O
Security	O
for	O
their	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
for	O
2	O
Years	O
afterward	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Duffus	I-pers
,	O
Fin	B-pers
'd	I-pers
20	O
Marks	O
,	O
a	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
upon	O
the	O
Pillory	O
near	O
Old	O
Gravel	O
Lane	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
The	O
Compleat	O
Parish-Officer	O
;	O
Containing	O
1	O
.	O
The	O
Athority	O
and	O
Proccedings	O
of	O
High-Constables	O
,	O
Petty-Constables	O
,	O
Headboroughs	O
,	O
and	O
Tithingmen	O
,	O
to	O
every	O
Branch	O
of	O
their	O
Duties	O
,	O
pursuant	O
to	O
Acts	O
of	O
Parliament	O
;	O
with	O
the	O
High	O
Constables	O
Precepts	O
,	O
Presenments	O
,	O
Warrants	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
2	O
.	O
Of	O
Churchwardens	O
,	O
how	O
chosen	O
,	O
their	O
particular	O
Business	O
in	O
repairing	O
of	O
Churches	O
,	O
Bells	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
,	O
and	O
assigning	O
of	O
Seats	O
;	O
the	O
manner	O
of	O
passing	O
their	O
Accompts	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Laws	O
and	O
Statutes	O
concerning	O
the	O
Church	O
in	O
all	O
Cases	O
;	O
and	O
also	O
an	O
Abstract	O
of	O
the	O
Act	O
for	O
building	O
fifty	O
new	O
Churches	O
in	O
London	O
and	O
Westminster	O
&	O
c.	O
3	O
.	O
Of	O
Oversees	O
of	O
the	O
Poor	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
Office	O
;	O
their	O
Power	O
to	O
Relieving	O
,	O
Employing	O
,	O
and	O
Settling	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
of	O
poor	O
Persons	O
;	O
the	O
Laws	O
relating	O
to	O
the	O
Poor	O
,	O
and	O
Settlements	O
and	O
the	O
Statutes	O
concerning	O
Masters	O
and	O
Servants	O
.	O
4	O
.	O
Of	O
Surveyors	O
of	O
the	O
Highways	O
and	O
Scavengers	O
,	O
how	O
elected	O
,	O
their	O
Business	O
in	O
amending	O
the	O
Ways	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
the	O
Duty	O
of	O
others	O
;	O
with	O
the	O
Method	O
of	O
Taxation	O
,	O
Laws	O
of	O
the	O
Highways	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
To	O
which	O
are	O
added	O
,	O
The	O
Statutes	O
relating	O
to	O
Hackney-Coaches	O
and	O
Chairs	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Second	O
Edition	O
with	O
Additions	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
W.	O
Mears	O
at	O
the	O
Lamb	O
without	O
Temple-Bar	O
.	O
Just	O
publish	O
'd	O
.	O
Written	O
from	O
her	O
own	O
Memorandums	O
Printed	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
W.	O
Cherwood	O
at	O
the	O
Cato's-Head	O
in	O
Russel	O
Street	O
Covent-Garden	O
,	O
and	O
T.	O
Edlin	O
at	O
the	O
Prince	O
's	O
Arms	O
over-against	O
Exeter	O
Exchange	O
in	O
the	O
Stand	O
.	O
Price	O
5	O
s.	O
Just	O
publish	O
'd	O
The	O
Tryal	O
and	O
Conviction	O
of	O
Patrick	B-pers
Hurly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Moughna	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Clare	O
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
Kings	O
Bench	O
in	O
Ireland	O
,	O
on	O
Two	O
several	O
Indictments	O
.	O
The	O
one	O
for	O
Perjury	O
in	O
swearing	O
falsly	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
Twelve	O
Hundred	O
and	O
One	O
Pounds	O
,	O
Nine	O
Shillings	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
for	O
a	O
Conspiracy	O
in	O
Cheat	O
the	O
Popish	O
Inhabitants	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
of	O
