TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
:	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
4th	O
,	O
5th	O
,	O
and	O
6th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
1722.	O
in	O
the	O
Eighth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
STEWART	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Pouys	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Tracy	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
;	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
Shadrach	B-pers
Winsor	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hargrave	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Radly	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Croucher	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Symonds	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Tidmarsh	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Smithson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bembrick	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Skin	I-pers
,	O
Marmaduke	B-pers
Emerson	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
.	O
George	B-pers
Dagget	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Prior	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Dennis	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
Samnel	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Gouge	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nowel	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Duffel	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Blewit	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Higgs	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Church	I-place
,	O
mist	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
observ	O
'd	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
close	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
apprehended	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
return	O
'd	O
him	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
.	O
In	O
his	O
Defence	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
on	O
the	O
Church	O
Steps	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Harwood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
,	O
4	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Silver	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
offering	O
some	O
Silver	O
to	O
sale	O
to	O
Edward	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
,	O
was	O
stopt	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
discover	O
'd	O
,	O
who	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
In	O
her	O
Defence	O
she	O
only	O
called	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Scoon	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Spooner	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Crow	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Thatcher	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Thatcher	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Coats	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
Reeves	O
and	O
Scoon	O
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
16	O
Shirts	O
,	O
Smocks	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Linnen	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
3	O
Women	O
for	O
feloniously	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stoln	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Godfrey	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
she	O
left	O
the	O
Linnen	O
hanging	O
to	O
dry	O
on	O
the	O
Leads	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
4	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
Willis	O
the	O
Constable	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
apprehended	O
Scoon	O
,	O
who	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
Daniel	B-pers
Farmer	I-pers
's	O
,	O
a	O
Broker	O
in	O
Chick	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
other	O
places	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
found	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
Linnen	O
again	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Thornton	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
that	O
she	O
lay	O
in	O
Ann	O
Thatcher	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
Scoon	O
and	O
Reeves	O
brought	O
the	O
Bundle	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Thatcber	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Coats	O
,	O
who	O
brought	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
Ann	B-pers
Thatcher	I-pers
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
'd	O
give	O
for'em	O
?	O
she	O
answer	O
'd	O
8	O
s.	O
-	O
Phoo	O
,	O
says	O
Mary	O
Thatcher	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
very	O
well	O
afford	O
to	O
give	O
12	O
.	O
The	O
Mens	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
wherein	O
they	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found'em	O
all	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Hedgly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
New	I-place
Fish-street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Smalwood	I-pers
,	O
5	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
17	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
John	O
Smalwood	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Shop	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
stopt	O
him	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
meer	O
necessity	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Mekins	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
George	B-pers
Criton	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Cambric	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
George	O
Criton	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
--	O
Thorp	O
,	O
were	O
walking	O
near	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Church	I-place
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
passing	O
close	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
felt	O
something	O
go	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
run	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
he	O
mist	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
found	O
it	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Corn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Saucepan	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Guyon	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
walking	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
asleep	O
in	O
a	O
Ditch	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Saucepan	O
,	O
a	O
Pot	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
lying	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
inform	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Saucepan	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
drunk	O
,	O
fell	O
asleep	O
in	O
the	O
Ditch	O
:	O
but	O
bringing	O
no	O
proof	O
of	O
what	O
be	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Barbara	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Trafford	I-pers
,	O
3	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
Trafford	O
gave	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
her	O
Charwoman	O
)	O
to	O
carry	O
home	O
,	O
who	O
carried'em	O
to	O
the	O
Pawn-brokers	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Bowls	O
in	O
Drury	O
lane	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
her	O
Husband	O
made	O
her	O
pawn'em	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Winden	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Teaspoons	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
Tortoiseshel	O
Snuff	O
box	O
,	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Foster	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Landress	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
his	O
Chambers	O
in	O
the	O
Temple	O
.	O
At	O
11	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
treble	O
lockt	O
his	O
Door	O
but	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
2	O
Tea-spoons	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
days	O
before	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Snuff-box	O
and	O
Money	O
in	O
a	O
private	O
Drawer	O
in	O
his	O
Scrutore	O
.	O
At	O
his	O
return	O
,	O
about	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Door	O
as	O
he	O
left	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Window	O
Curtains	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
different	O
order	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
he	O
knew	O
his	O
Landress	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
.	O
Next	O
Morning	O
he	O
mist	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
Chamber	O
about	O
6	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
a	O
Woman	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Spoons	O
were	O
then	O
missing	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Colgrave	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Gowns	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Ralph	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Mary	O
Wood	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
having	O
been	O
11	O
Weeks	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
at	O
her	O
return	O
the	O
found	O
her	O
Trunk	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Goods	O
gone	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confest	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
some	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Pigeons	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
at	O
one	O
Hartly	O
's	O
in	O
Chick	O
lane	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
.	O
Most	O
of	O
this	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
val	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Humphry	B-pers
Hunion	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
:	I-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Brass	O
Cocks	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
hundred	O
Weight	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
when	O
he	O
workt	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
which	O
upon	O
Examination	O
he	O
confest	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hains	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Gregory	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
a	O
Pot	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
17	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Saucepan	O
5	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Glover	O
's	O
Shop	O
to	O
drink	O
Geneva	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
Frances	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
saw	O
Smith	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
deliver	O
them	O
to	O
Hains	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Behn	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Macopny	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Blundel	I-pers
,	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
39	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
April	O
.	O
Edward	O
Blundel	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
along	O
with	O
a	O
Bag	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
50	O
s.	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
jostled	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Pint	O
;	O
that	O
missing	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
return	O
'd	O
his	O
Bag	O
,	O
with	O
11	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Watchman	O
putting	O
his	O
Finger	O
in	O
her	O
Mouth	O
,	O
she	O
bit	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
it	O
off	O
;	O
but	O
squeezing	O
her	O
hard	O
by	O
the	O
Throat	O
,	O
forced	O
5	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Mouth	O
.	O
In	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
askt	O
her	O
if	O
her	O
Name	O
was	O
an	O
Irish	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
charg	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
his	O
Money	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
askt	O
all	O
the	O
Women	O
he	O
met	O
for	O
his	O
Money	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Market	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
some	O
Money	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
put	O
into	O
her	O
Mouth	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
-respited	O
for	O
pregnancy	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
George	B-pers
Curry	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
Wig	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
5	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Curry	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
1	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
Everet	O
's	O
(	O
a	O
Distillers	O
)	O
Shop	O
,	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
a	O
Watchman	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
told	O
him	O
they	O
'd	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
Shilling	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
refus	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
they	O
presently	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Shirt	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
off	O
of	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Purse	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
44	O
l.	O
but	O
he	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
they	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
Joseph	O
and	O
Francis	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
two	O
Drovers	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
they	O
beard	O
Curry	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
stamping	O
on	O
his	O
Breast	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Everest	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
after	O
Curry	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
left	O
a	O
Ridinghood	O
in	O
pawn	O
for	O
their	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
and	O
followed	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
look	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
saw'em	O
knock	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
down	O
near	O
Cloth	O
Fair	O
.	O
Soon	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
this	O
Evidence	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
set	O
upon	O
and	O
abus	O
'd	O
.	O
He	O
kept	O
him	O
in	O
Discourse	O
till	O
the	O
Watch	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
secur	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
in	O
drunk	O
and	O
dirty	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
his	O
Comrade	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Arm	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
staid	O
behind	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Geneva	O
,	O
then	O
followed	O
'em	O
,	O
saw	O
'	O
em	O
both	O
fall	O
down	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
help	O
'	O
em	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
parted	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Alice	B-pers
Phenix	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
49s	O
.	O
and	O
10d	O
.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Smalpit	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
John	O
Smalpit	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Duke	B-place
of	I-place
Gloucester	I-place
's	I-place
Head	I-place
in	I-place
Chelsea	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
Ale	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
sat	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
Drink	O
,	O
he	O
mist	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
He	O
charg	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
Anderson	O
said	O
,	O
Do	O
n't	O
make	O
a	O
noise	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
see	O
you	O
shall	O
have	O
your	O
Money	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
then	O
ran	O
into	O
another	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
Anderson	O
fetch	O
'd	O
William	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
who	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
beat	O
him	O
almost	O
blind	O
,	O
and	O
stript	O
him	O
naked	O
,	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
searching	O
for	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
A	O
Constable	O
then	O
took	O
the	O
Soldier	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
when	O
Anderson	O
call	O
'd	O
after	O
him	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Here	O
's	O
your	O
Money	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
dropt	O
it	O
into	O
my	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Spinage	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
call	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Anderson	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
crying	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
beat	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
crying	O
for	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
Landlady	O
had	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Soldier	O
to	O
beat	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
beating	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Soldier	O
was	O
swearing	O
,	O
the	O
Landlady	O
scolding	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
House	O
in	O
confusion	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Whitfield	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
:	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
were	O
withdrawn	O
to	O
a	O
private	O
Room	O
,	O
a	O
Hot	O
pot	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Breeches	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
his	O
Nastiness	O
out	O
;	O
at	O
which	O
sight	O
she	O
was	O
so	O
asham	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
ran	O
out	O
again	O
.	O
Deborah	B-pers
Hancock	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
by	O
Anderson	O
's	O
,	O
she	O
heard	O
a	O
Woman	O
was	O
murdered	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
in	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
Prosecutor	O
both	O
stark-naked	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
askt	O
her	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
drank	O
like	O
a	O
Maid	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
well	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
another	O
Room	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
Ale	O
and	O
Geneva	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
her	O
a	O
Shilling	O
to	O
have	O
carnal	O
Copulation	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
refusing	O
,	O
he	O
thrust	O
it	O
down	O
her	O
Bosom	O
,	O
and	O
beat	O
her	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
comply	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
before	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Company	O
,	O
she	O
stript	O
her	O
self	O
quite	O
naked	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
search	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Money	O
could	O
be	O
found	O
about	O
her	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
and	O
William	O
Pain	O
are	O
next	O
Sessions	O
to	O
be	O
indicted	O
as	O
Accessaries	O
,	O
and	O
John	O
Smalpit	O
is	O
bound	O
over	O
to	O
prosecute'em	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Hannah	B-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Ann	I-pers
Fitz-gerald	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Mince	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
Scarf	O
,	O
40	O
s.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
whilst	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
proof	O
being	O
brought	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Fen	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	O
Cowden	O
,	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
two	O
Table	O
Clocks	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
Sheet	O
,	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Cowden	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
charg	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
confest	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mumford	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Dames	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cambric	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Frederick	B-pers
Ashfield	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Frederick	O
Ashfield	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
by	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Peters	O
street	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
folding	O
up	O
a	O
white	O
Handkerchief	O
;	O
he	O
stopt	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
another	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
struck	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
came	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
,	O
rather	O
than	O
he	O
'd	O
come	O
into	O
trouble	O
,	O
he	O
'd	O
make	O
him	O
satisfaction	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Tims	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Gregory	I-place
by	I-place
St.	I-place
Pauls	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Bonwick	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
Cornelian	O
Seal	O
,	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
steel	O
Seal	O
,	O
1	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
10	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
making	O
water	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Pauls	I-place
Church-Yard	I-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
jostled	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
felt	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pull	O
out	O
his	O
Watch	O
;	O
he	O
kept	O
his	O
Eye	O
on	O
him	O
,	O
follow	O
'd	O
and	O
stopt	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Watch	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
Mr	O
Cousins	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
hearing	O
a	O
noise	O
he	O
stept	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Persons	O
about	O
Mr.	O
Bonwick	O
,	O
who	O
held	O
the	O
prisoner	O
by	O
the	O
Coat	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
charged	O
Mr.	O
Bonwick	O
with	O
Sodomy	O
:	O
which	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Cullen	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
came	O
along	O
drunk	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
another	O
quarrelling	O
:	O
he	O
past	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
came	O
running	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
almost	O
knocked	O
him	O
down	O
;	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
then	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Hooper	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
his	O
Grace	O
the	O
Duke	B-pers
of	I-pers
Somerset	I-pers
a	O
silver	O
Plate	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hartly	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Poky	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Francis	B-pers
Hackabout	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Roger	B-pers
Worthington	I-pers
,	O
in	O
an	O
open	O
place	O
near	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
Wig	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Coat	O
and	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
Neckcloth	O
,	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Buckles	O
,	O
4	O
d.	O
and	O
2	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Roger	B-pers
Worthington	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
over	O
the	O
Fields	O
at	O
Anniseed	B-place
clear	I-place
about	O
9	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
Reeves	O
bid	O
him	O
stand	O
;	O
and	O
Hartly	O
struck	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
with	O
a	O
Pistol	O
;	O
that	O
4	O
more	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
collar	O
'd	O
him	O
and	O
knockt	O
him	O
down	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
bound	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
him	O
naked	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
positive	O
that	O
Hackabout	O
was	O
one	O
,	O
but	O
Reeves	O
and	O
Hartly	O
he	O
swore	O
to	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Groves	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
having	O
bought	O
a	O
Frock	O
of	O
Reeves	O
,	O
and	O
wearing	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
in	O
Anniseed	O
Clear	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Rogues	O
that	O
rob	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
had	O
that	O
very	O
Coat	O
on	O
;	O
whereupon	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Crown	O
in	O
Fore	O
street	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
pointed	O
out	O
Reeves	O
,	O
before	O
this	O
Evidence	O
told	O
him	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Frock	O
from	O
.	O
Reeves	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Grove	O
was	O
a	O
scandalous	O
Fidler	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
fellow	O
of	O
no	O
Credit	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
ow	O
'd	O
them	O
a	O
spite	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
made	O
his	O
brags	O
that	O
he	O
'd	O
hang	O
6	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
get	O
the	O
money	O
allow	O
'd	O
for	O
taking	O
them	O
;	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
appear	O
'd	O
for	O
Hartly	O
's	O
Reputation	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
positive	O
against	O
him	O
and	O
Reeves	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
And	O
Hackabout	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Cope	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Hannah	I-pers
Banks	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Hannah	I-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Wattis	I-pers
in	O
the	O
night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
a	O
silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Peter	O
Wattis	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
hir	O
'd	O
as	O
his	O
Servant	O
on	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
doors	O
open	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
apprehended	O
in	O
the	O
Mint	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Cup	O
and	O
a	O
Mug	O
upon	O
her	O
:	O
which	O
Edward	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
confirm	O
'd	O
.	O
Her	O
Confession	O
was	O
then	O
read	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
she	O
said	O
;	O
that	O
about	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
she	O
let	O
in	O
William	B-pers
Banks	I-pers
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
believ	O
'd	O
he	O
then	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
for	O
that	O
afterwards	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Plate	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Cope	I-pers
,	O
was	O
2	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
her	O
Mary	B-pers
Hipsly	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Ranson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Thistleworth	B-place
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Bourn	I-pers
in	O
the	O
night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
2	O
silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
Sarah	O
Bourne	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Poke	O
came	O
as	O
Servant	O
to	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Hannah	O
Hill	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
;	O
she	O
Confest	O
before	O
Justice	O
Perry	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
)	O
that	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
5	O
at	O
night	O
Hipsly	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
Poke	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
reaching	O
Hipsly	O
,	O
She	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Pancras	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
John	O
Lewis	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
riding	O
in	O
Hampstead	B-place
road	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
He	O
was	O
positive	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
,	O
having	O
known	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
keeps	O
the	O
Cock	O
at	O
South	O
Halsted	O
,	O
about	O
40	O
miles	O
from	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
(	O
being	O
in	O
debt	O
,	O
)	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
about	O
10	O
days	O
before	O
Christmas	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
employ	O
'd	O
him	O
there	O
as	O
his	O
Ostler	O
till	O
10	O
days	O
after	O
Christmas	O
;	O
in	O
all	O
which	O
time	O
the	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
lye	O
out	O
one	O
night	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Duvall	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Bright	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Katherines	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
our	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Wade	I-pers
Widow	O
,	O
12	O
Gold	O
rings	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
of	O
value	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Molony	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
March	O
her	O
Trunk	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Goods	O
gone	O
.	O
Katherine	B-pers
Newby	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Duval	O
brought	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
Harp	O
at	O
Iron	O
Gate	O
)	O
about	O
7	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
The	O
Headborough	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
Gold	O
Chain	O
and	O
2	O
rings	O
in	O
Brights	O
hair	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
Spoon	O
put	O
down	O
her	O
back	O
.	O
Duval	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Molony	I-pers
(	O
whose	O
name	O
was	O
then	O
Wade	O
)	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
married	O
her	O
Grandaughter	O
;	O
but	O
one	O
Molony	O
,	O
an	O
Irishman	O
,	O
falling	O
in	O
love	O
with	O
the	O
old	O
Woman	O
,	O
she	O
married	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
his	O
Instigation	O
,	O
prosecuted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
give	O
up	O
some	O
Land	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
right	O
to	O
in	O
Surry	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Mary	B-pers
Bright	I-pers
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
.	O
Duvals	O
Mother	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
Dorothy	O
give	O
the	O
Key	O
to	O
her	O
Son	O
,	O
and	O
says	O
,	O
Heres	O
the	O
Key	O
,	O
take	O
what	O
you	O
want	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
is	O
your	O
own	O
,	O
adding	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
old	O
Woman	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
should	O
dye	O
first	O
,	O
somebody	O
may	O
Cheat	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Molony	O
(	O
the	O
Husband	O
)	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
Gary	O
by	O
chance	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
place	O
they	O
went	O
together	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
they	O
accidentally	O
met	O
Katherine	B-pers
Newby	I-pers
.	O
Gary	O
offer	O
'd	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
Parchment	O
to	O
sign	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
(	O
Molony	O
)	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
only	O
Gary	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
of	O
service	O
to	O
him	O
(	O
Molony	O
)	O
and	O
all	O
his	O
Family	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Rouse	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Perry	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
deed	O
being	O
shewn	O
the	O
prisoner	O
he	O
snatch	O
'd	O
it	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
want	O
to	O
put	O
a	O
trick	O
upon	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
shall	O
never	O
have	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Molony	O
was	O
a	O
prisoner	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
on	O
suspicion	O
of	O
putting	O
off	O
Counterfeit	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
Simon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Simon	B-pers
Hansel	I-pers
,	O
3	O
silver	O
Snuff	O
Boxes	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
Simon	O
Hansel	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
out	O
between	O
3	O
and	O
5	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
his	O
Shew	O
glass	O
rob	O
'd	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
Katherine	B-pers
Rider	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Robin	B-pers
Drumman	I-pers
,	O
Kitty	B-pers
Weaver	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
brought	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Drumman	O
,	O
telling	O
her	O
where	O
they	O
stole	O
them	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Drumman	O
gave	O
them	O
Money	O
for	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
shar	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
Drumman	O
give	O
his	O
Mother	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tobacco	O
Box	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Hannah	B-pers
Blackmoor	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Blackamore	I-pers
,	I-pers
Spinster	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Barnard	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
Francis	O
Barnard	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Marrying	O
James	B-pers
Doyne	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
7th	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
her	O
former	O
Husband	O
Francis	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
being	O
then	O
alive	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
marriage	O
,	O
being	O
within	O
the	O
limits	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
Act	O
of	O
Grace	O
,	O
she	O
receiv	O
'd	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
Crow	I-pers
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Robert	O
Crow	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
Playhouse	O
door	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brusht	O
by	O
him	O
and	O
clapt	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
his	O
Bosom	O
;	O
that	O
missing	O
his	O
Wig	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
there	O
again	O
the	O
next	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
standing	O
with	O
the	O
Wig	O
upon	O
his	O
Head	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
in	O
Drury	O
Lane	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
Spinster	O
,	O
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Kendrick	B-pers
Edisbury	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
3	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
Evans	O
the	O
Daughter	O
being	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
Evans	O
the	O
Mother	O
persuaded	O
her	O
Daughter	O
,	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
have	O
some	O
of	O
her	O
Masters	O
Goods	O
to	O
pawn	O
:	O
the	O
Girl	O
consented	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Mother	O
afterwards	O
brought	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
again	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
the	O
Mother	O
took	O
the	O
Fact	O
intirely	O
upon	O
her	O
self	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Daughter	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Dicks	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Meeson	I-pers
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
commit	O
the	O
unnatural	O
Sin	O
of	O
Sodomy	O
.	O
John	O
Meeson	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
day	O
on	O
which	O
the	O
first	O
Stone	O
was	O
laid	O
in	O
St.	O
Martins	O
Church	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
standing	O
in	O
the	O
Church	O
Yard	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
Honest	O
Dyer	O
!	O
how	O
fares	O
it	O
?	O
and	O
askt	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Ale	O
house	O
which	O
he	O
refus	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
the	O
prisoner	O
overpersuading	O
him	O
he	O
went	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
made	O
him	O
almost	O
fuddled	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
this	O
Evidences	O
Breeches	O
:	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Evidences	O
hand	O
and	O
put	O
into	O
his	O
own	O
Breeches	O
;	O
from	O
this	O
Ale-house	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
Cellar	O
in	O
the	O
Second	O
,	O
where	O
not	O
being	O
private	O
enough	O
they	O
drank	O
but	O
one	O
pint	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
another	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
Chancery	O
Lane	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
drank	O
Ale	O
and	O
Geneva	O
:	O
from	O
thence	O
he	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Golden	B-place
Ball	I-place
in	I-place
Bonds	I-place
Stables	I-place
near	I-place
Fetter	I-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
private	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
more	O
Ale	O
and	O
Geneva	O
,	O
till	O
this	O
Evidence	O
was	O
so	O
drunk	O
and	O
sick	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
vomited	O
and	O
laid	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Bench	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
sleep	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
then	O
unbutton	O
'd	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
turn	O
'd	O
him	O
on	O
his	O
face	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
sensible	O
enough	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
Meeson	O
come	O
in	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
only	O
a	O
thin	O
Partition	O
betwixt	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
Meeson	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
which	O
this	O
Evidence	O
was	O
:	O
he	O
could	O
plainly	O
hear	O
the	O
prisoner	O
kiss	O
him	O
,	O
call	O
him	O
his	O
Dear	O
,	O
and	O
use	O
several	O
other	O
fond	O
and	O
foolish	O
Expressions	O
,	O
common	O
betwixt	O
persons	O
of	O
different	O
Sexes	O
;	O
hearing	O
this	O
,	O
he	O
bid	O
the	O
Ale-house	O
Boy	O
go	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
about	O
.	O
The	O
Ale	O
house	O
Boy	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
Meeson	O
(	O
the	O
other	O
Boy	O
)	O
was	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
Bench	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
askt	O
this	O
Evidence	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
bid	O
him	O
set	O
down	O
,	O
kist	O
him	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
told	O
Rogers	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
that	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
Rogers	O
then	O
farther	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
spying	O
a	O
hole	O
in	O
the	O
Partition	O
,	O
he	O
looked	O
through	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Boy	O
lying	O
upon	O
the	O
Bench	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
very	O
Act	O
of	O
Sodomy	O
,	O
the	O
Boy	O
's	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
Breeches	O
being	O
down	O
.	O
Soon	O
after	O
the	O
Boy	O
still	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Posture	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
repeated	O
his	O
unnatural	O
Enormities	O
upon	O
the	O
Boy	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
beastly	O
manner	O
,	O
making	O
several	O
motions	O
with	O
his	O
Body	O
.	O
This	O
Evidence	O
then	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
who	O
peeping	O
a	O
pretty	O
while	O
at	O
last	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
I	O
can	O
look	O
no	O
longer	O
!	O
I	O
'm	O
ready	O
to	O
Swoon	O
?	O
He	O
'll	O
ruin	O
the	O
Boy	O
;	O
they	O
then	O
both	O
rusht	O
in	O
,	O
seiz	O
'd	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
he	O
(	O
notwithstanding	O
the	O
Posture	O
they	O
surpris	O
'd	O
him	O
in	O
,	O
)	O
made	O
many	O
protestations	O
of	O
his	O
Innocence	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
said	O
;	O
Well	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
swear	O
against	O
me	O
and	O
take	O
away	O
my	O
life	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
help	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
this	O
to	O
comfort	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
fit	O
to	O
dye	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
often	O
turn	O
'd	O
up	O
his	O
Eyes	O
very	O
devoutly	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
ever	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
to	O
Meeson	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
more	O
than	O
he	O
knew	O
off	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Flood	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
an	O
Assault	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Caruthers	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
wilful	O
and	O
Corrupt	O
Perjury	O
,	O
in	O
making	O
a	O
false	O
Affidavit	O
in	O
the	O
Prerogative	O
Court	O
of	O
Canterbury	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
sixth	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
Her	O
Affidavit	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
contradicted	O
by	O
the	O
Testimony	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Vincent	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
Bridget	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Rea	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Wimberly	I-pers
.	O
In	O
her	O
defence	O
,	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
one	O
Murray	O
,	O
who	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
forsworn	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
was	O
order	O
'd	O
into	O
Custody	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
not	O
being	O
positive	O
to	O
the	O
Time	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pavit	I-pers
,	O
by	O
striking	O
,	O
kicking	O
and	O
bruising	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
Back	O
,	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
parts	O
of	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
21st	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Month	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Dy	O
'd	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
being	O
at	O
the	B-place
Rose	I-place
and	I-place
Crown	I-place
in	I-place
Shoo	I-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
strok	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceased	O
over	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
provok	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
fight	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
fought	O
together	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
People	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
part	O
them	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
would	O
fight	O
on	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
enough	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
struck	O
him	O
several	O
times	O
afterwards	O
on	O
the	O
Breast	O
and	O
Head	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
on	O
his	O
Death	O
Bed	O
declar	O
'd	O
,	O
Carter	O
had	O
kill	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Surgeons	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Hurts	O
were	O
not	O
mortal	O
,	O
unless	O
by	O
throwing	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
Fever	O
,	O
which	O
night	O
be	O
caus	O
'd	O
by	O
hard	O
Drinking	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
called	O
Thomas	B-pers
Greenaway	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Dyer	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Mounsey	I-pers
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Lodging	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
the	O
Fight	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
drank	O
plentifully	O
,	O
made	O
no	O
complaint	O
,	O
only	O
took	O
a	O
Bill	O
of	O
Carter	O
for	O
the	O
loss	O
of	O
his	O
time	O
.	O
Several	O
gave	O
the	O
prisoner	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
civil	O
,	O
quiet	O
Man	O
,	O
not	O
given	O
to	O
quarrel	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Renton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Large	I-pers
,	O
7	O
Suits	O
of	O
Headcloaths	O
,	O
value	O
17	O
l.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
John	O
Large	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
four	O
more	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
drink	O
.	O
That	O
seeing	O
a	O
Neckcloth	O
lie	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
near	O
a	O
Box	O
of	O
Linnen	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
all	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ran	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
alone	O
staid	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
pay	O
his	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
along	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
Man	O
sing	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
pleased	O
with	O
the	O
Song	O
,	O
he	O
invited	O
him	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Dram	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
,	O
when	O
presently	O
came	O
in	O
3	O
Men	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
stranger	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
no	O
way	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bow	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Grey	O
Gelding	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Greenaway	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
Samuel	O
Greenaway	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
Horse	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Field	O
at	O
Marybone	B-place
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
again	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Strutton	O
's	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
.	O
-	O
Strutton	O
depos	O
'd	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Horse	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
(	O
Aug	O
.	O
5	O
.	O
)	O
at	O
the	O
Bell	O
Inn	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
sitting	O
at	O
the	O
Swan	O
and	O
Horseshoe	O
Door	O
in	O
Tyburn	O
Road	O
,	O
a	O
Man	O
offer	O
'd	O
the	O
Horse	O
to	O
sale	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Broom	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sorrel	O
Mare	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	O
Smith	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
Mare	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
of	O
his	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
upon	O
her	O
about	O
two	O
Miles	O
off	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
pursued	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
Mare	O
together	O
in	O
a	O
Stable	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Hart	O
and	O
Three	O
Tobacco	O
Pipes	O
in	O
White	O
Chappel	O
.	O
He	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
Justice	O
Perry	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
)	O
In	O
his	O
Defence	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Son	O
gave	O
him	O
leave	O
to	O
take	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
contradicted	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Parrot	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Fustian	O
Frock	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Fortune	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
at	O
work	O
at	O
Lime	B-place
house	I-place
,	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
his	O
Frock	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
it	O
was	O
stoln	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
Rag	O
Fair	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
apprehended	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mark	B-pers
Horton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Gregory	I-place
by	I-place
St.	I-place
Paul	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hankey	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Cambrick	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Church	I-place
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
he	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
of	O
The	O
.	O
Mossy	O
,	O
125	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Camels	O
Hair	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Mossy	O
's	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
Robert	B-pers
Rossiter	I-pers
,	O
who	O
paid	O
him	O
part	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
in	O
Hats	O
.	O
In	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Mossy	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
sweepings	O
of	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
;	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
and	O
he	O
committed	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
be	O
try	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
as	O
Principal	O
,	O
and	O
Cross	O
as	O
Accessary	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
and	I-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
his	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
in	O
forging	O
a	O
Note	O
for	O
25	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Ann	O
Lockyer	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
defraud	O
Richard	B-pers
Hemmings	I-pers
of	O
the	O
said	O
Sum	O
.	O
Richard	O
Hemmings	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
telling	O
him	O
he	O
wanted	O
25	O
l.	O
Hemmings	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
'd	O
advance	O
the	O
Money	O
on	O
good	O
security	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
'd	O
get	O
a	O
Note	O
of	O
Madam	O
Lockyer	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
brought	O
a	O
Note	O
for	O
25	O
l.	O
sign	O
'd	O
Ann	O
Lockyer	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
paid	O
him	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
going	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Lockyer	O
,	O
she	O
denied	O
the	O
Bill	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
being	O
examin	O
'd	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
who	O
confest	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
wrote	O
the	O
Note	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
herself	O
sign	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
John	O
Francis	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Mrs	O
Lockyer	O
having	O
often	O
lent	O
'em	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
wrote	O
the	O
Note	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
his	O
Wife	O
to	O
get	O
Mrs.	O
Lockyer	O
to	O
sign	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
thought	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
.	O
His	O
Wife	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
sign	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
it	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Lockyer	O
's	O
Order	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
John	O
Francis	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Francis	O
:	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
John	O
Francis	O
:	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Par	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Halsted	I-pers
,	O
17	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Worsted	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Abel	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
12	O
Bushel	O
of	O
Oats	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Hughs	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
carried	O
,	O
a	O
Sack	O
of	O
Oats	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Hugh	O
's	O
Stable	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Higdens	O
,	O
in	O
Vine	O
Street	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
Order	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
for	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Saddle	O
Horses	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Higden	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
In	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
out	O
of	O
place	O
,	O
he	O
design	O
'd	O
to	O
keep	O
Horses	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
the	O
Corn	O
;	O
but	O
hearing	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Hughs	O
's	O
Service	O
,	O
he	O
changed	O
his	O
Mind	O
,	O
and	O
mixt	O
his	O
own	O
Corn	O
among	O
his	O
Masters	O
,	O
and	O
only	O
took	O
the	O
same	O
quantity	O
he	O
put	O
in	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Colthorp	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Cambric	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
the	O
prisoner	O
stood	O
by	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Choir	O
of	O
Westminster	B-place
Abbey	I-place
,	O
he	O
felt	O
his	O
Hand	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
almost	O
drawn	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
being	O
not	O
quite	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
directed	O
the	O
Jury	O
to	O
acquit	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
he	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
Stevens	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
rob	O
him	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
D'arbieau	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Polwell	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Mug	O
,	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Salver	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
In	O
the	O
7th	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Polwel	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
she	O
made	O
all	O
the	O
Doors	O
and	O
Windows	O
fast	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
7	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
the	O
Window	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
gone	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Leonard	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
Trantum	O
,	O
about	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
turned	O
the	O
Pin	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
till	O
the	O
Key	O
dropt	O
out	O
;	O
he	O
and	O
Trantum	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
handed	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
afterwards	O
carried	O
to	O
Trantum	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Days	O
after	O
sold'em	O
to	O
Tho	B-pers
Glanister	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
for	O
29	O
l.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
Trantum	O
,	O
as	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Trantum	O
and	O
Leonard	O
brought	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
's	O
Father	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Polwel	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
prisoner	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
refused	O
.	O
That	O
when	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
Leonard	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
made	O
himself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
he	O
askt	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
no	O
fear	O
?	O
she	O
answered	O
No	O
.	O
Most	O
of	O
this	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Polwel	O
himself	O
.	O
She	O
brought	O
some	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Truth	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
intirely	O
depending	O
on	O
Leonard	O
's	O
Evidence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Kingston	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
d.	O
4	O
Towels	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
other	O
Child-bed	O
Linen	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hat	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
given	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
's	O
Sister	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
by	O
driving	O
a	O
loaded	O
Cart	O
,	O
with	O
3	O
Horses	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
means	O
of	O
which	O
driving	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Andrew	O
was	O
thrown	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Off-Wheel	O
of	O
the	O
Cart	O
run	O
over	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
his	O
Skull	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
Fracture	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
driven	O
very	O
easily	O
and	O
moderately	O
along	O
Ratcliff	B-place
Highway	I-place
.	O
The	O
Cart	O
was	O
loaded	O
with	O
Coals	O
,	O
and	O
drawn	O
by	O
three	O
Horses	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
walking	O
at	O
the	O
Head	O
of	O
the	O
Horse	O
next	O
the	O
Cart	O
;	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
saw	O
the	O
Child	O
before	O
it	O
was	O
kill	O
'd	O
nor	O
was	O
any	O
notice	O
given	O
of	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
being	O
there	O
.	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Off-wheel	O
ran	O
over	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
then	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Cart	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
possibly	O
see	O
the	O
Child	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Sedgwick	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stoke	B-place
Newington	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Marmaduke	B-pers
Sole	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Major	O
Sole	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Coat	O
lying	O
upon	O
his	O
Coach-box	O
,	O
just	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
Dinner	O
;	O
not	O
long	O
after	O
he	O
heard	O
somebody	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
Major	O
Sole	O
's	O
Coat	O
is	O
stol'n	O
and	O
stepping	O
out	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
going	O
across	O
the	O
Field	O
with	O
the	O
Coat	O
in	O
his	O
Arms	O
.	O
A	O
Servant	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Coat	O
upon	O
a	O
Hedge	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
finding	O
no	O
body	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
thought	O
he	O
might	O
take	O
it	O
for	O
his	O
own	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Conner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Basket	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
three	O
Half-peck	O
Loaves	O
,	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
Quartern	O
Loaves	O
,	O
9	O
d.	O
and	O
other	O
Bread	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Dascomb	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Little	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
leaving	O
the	O
Basket	O
near	O
the	O
Two	B-place
Blue	I-place
Posts	I-place
Tavern	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Searle	I-place
Street	I-place
,	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
the	O
Basket	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Cary	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
meeting	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Basket	O
,	O
in	O
Boswel	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
knowing	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
no	O
Baker	O
,	O
he	O
inform	O
'd	O
Little	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
who	O
afterwards	O
apprehended	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
a	O
Baker	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Beer	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
Basket	O
for	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Rebeccah	B-pers
Stanton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
a	O
Coat	O
and	O
Wastcoat	O
.	O
value	O
32	O
s.	O
3	O
Hats	O
,	O
17	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Stanton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Stanton	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
employ	O
'd	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Simson	I-pers
,	O
to	O
assist	O
him	O
in	O
removing	O
his	O
Goods	O
from	O
Saffron	O
Hill	O
to	O
Turnmil	O
street	O
.	O
At	O
Night	O
they	O
left	O
all	O
the	O
Doors	O
and	O
Windows	O
safe	O
,	O
at	O
their	O
House	O
in	O
Turnmil	B-place
street	I-place
,	O
and	O
lay	O
at	O
Saffron	O
Hill	O
;	O
next	O
Morning	O
they	O
found	O
their	O
House	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
Goods	O
gone	O
The	O
three	O
Hats	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
at	O
Simpson	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
since	O
fled	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a-bed	O
when	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Simpson	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
leave	O
the	O
Hats	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Tottenham	B-place
High	I-place
Cross	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
a	O
Smock	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
18	O
d.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
.	O
Margaret	O
Hill	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
Nine	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
all	O
the	O
Doors	O
and	O
Windows	O
fast	O
;	O
and	O
returning	O
about	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
found	O
a	O
pane	O
of	O
Glass	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
the	O
wooden	O
Bar	O
broke	O
,	O
the	O
Shutter	O
taken	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Door	O
open	O
.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Elliot	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
Noon	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
loitering	O
about	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hathorn	I-pers
bought	O
the	O
Smock	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
at	O
her	O
own	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
sworn	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
In	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Stranger	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Rachel	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Edmunds	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
-Buckstone	B-pers
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
Case	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
in	O
drink	O
,	O
fell	O
down	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
prisoners	O
helping	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
carry	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
Buckstone	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
where	O
pulling	O
out	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
Edmunds	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
see	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
giving	O
it	O
to	O
Porter	O
.	O
She	O
return	O
'd	O
it	O
without	O
the	O
Case	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
missing	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
apprehended	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
,	O
deny	O
'd	O
that	O
they	O
ever	O
saw	O
the	O
Watch	O
or	O
Case	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
felonious	O
taking	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquited	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Plummer	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Edward	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Peruque	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
having	O
the	O
Wig	O
in	O
a	O
Box	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
before	O
,	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
Shook	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
where	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
?	O
I	O
'll	O
knock	O
you	O
down	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
gone	O
twenty	O
Yards	O
before	O
he	O
mist	O
the	O
Wig	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
saw	O
in	O
the	O
Box	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Lee	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
've	O
been	O
rob	O
'd	O
of	O
a	O
Wig	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
who	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
:	O
Yes	O
,	O
says	O
Lee	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
him	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
They	O
then	O
went	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Fen	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Coleston	O
Court	O
,	O
in	O
Drury	O
lane	O
where	O
they	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
sitting	O
.	O
Lee	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
told	O
the	O
Constable	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Thief	O
in	O
that	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
another	O
.	O
One	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Lee	O
said	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
Wig	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Shop	O
.	O
and	O
another	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
lost	O
it	O
in	O
Princes	O
Street	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Johnson	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Lee	O
,	O
(	O
her	O
Husband	O
's	O
Apprentice	O
)	O
borrowed	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
of	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Cunning	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
he	O
charg	O
'd	O
the	O
Robbery	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
insufficient	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
appearing	O
malicious	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Hicks	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
his	O
Mother	O
Alice	B-pers
Hicks	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
her	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
with	O
both	O
his	O
Hands	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Month	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Dy	O
'd	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hicks	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
March	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
he	O
found	O
his	O
Wife	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
and	O
her	O
Hands	O
shaking	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
spoke	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
speechless	O
,	O
and	O
dy	O
'd	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
8	O
on	O
Friday	O
night	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
home	O
drunk	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
shut	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
barred	O
him	O
out	O
into	O
a	O
Gallery	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
then	O
broke	O
the	O
Window	O
Shutter	O
and	O
Windows	O
,	O
this	O
Evidence	O
perswaded	O
the	O
Deceased	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
in	O
,	O
which	O
at	O
last	O
she	O
did	O
:	O
he	O
advised	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
who	O
answer	O
'd	O
he	O
would	O
buss	O
his	O
Mother	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
his	O
Hands	O
about	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Neck	O
,	O
she	O
shrieck	O
'd	O
and	O
said	O
My	O
Rogue	O
has	O
Murdered	O
me	O
!	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
given	O
her	O
a	O
sly	O
knock	O
;	O
let	O
the	O
Old	O
Bitch	O
Dye	O
and	O
be	O
damn	O
'd	O
.	O
Susan	B-pers
Clare	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
violent	O
passion	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
and	O
scolded	O
as	O
heartily	O
after	O
her	O
Son	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
kiss	O
her	O
as	O
before	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
sat	O
up	O
with	O
her	O
about	O
11	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
sensible	O
and	O
made	O
no	O
Complaint	O
of	O
any	O
hurt	O
.	O
Several	O
Witnesses	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
Quarrelsome	O
and	O
Malicious	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
frequently	O
cry	O
out	O
Murder	O
,	O
when	O
no	O
body	O
touch	O
'd	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
very	O
often	O
Lunatick	O
.	O
2	O
Surgeons	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
opening	O
the	O
Head	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
no	O
Contusion	O
nor	O
any	O
sign	O
of	O
hurt	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
believed	O
she	O
died	O
of	O
Convulsions	O
,	O
which	O
her	O
violent	O
Passion	O
might	O
have	O
thrown	O
her	O
into	O
.	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	O
.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Field	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Thorndel	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
get	O
over	O
Ditton	O
's	O
Wall	O
,	O
jump	O
back	O
again	O
and	O
cram	O
something	O
white	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
she	O
raised	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
him	O
near	O
a	O
Brewhouse	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
Stable	O
belonging	O
to	O
that	O
Brew	O
house	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Shirt	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
a	O
large	O
Wallet	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Tinder	O
Box	O
,	O
Flint	O
,	O
Steel	O
,	O
Matches	O
,	O
a	O
Gimblet	O
,	O
Knife	O
and	O
Pick-lock-key	O
:	O
all	O
which	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
carried	O
the	O
Wallet	O
to	O
put	O
Carrots	O
in	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
sent	O
to	O
buy	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
pursued	O
by	O
the	O
Bailiffs	O
,	O
he	O
jumpt	O
over	O
the	O
Wall	O
to	O
hide	O
himself	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Deroff	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Bradly	I-pers
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
when	O
Robert	B-pers
Bradly	I-pers
was	O
gone	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
a	O
bed	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lifted	O
up	O
the	O
latch	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Goods	O
:	O
sold	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
charged	O
with	O
the	O
Fact	O
confest	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Casey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Francis	B-pers
Godelard	I-pers
,	O
in	O
an	O
open	O
place	O
near	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
one	O
Shilling	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Godelard	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
dusk	O
of	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
sitting	O
on	O
the	O
Bench	O
at	O
that	O
end	O
of	O
the	B-place
Mall	I-place
next	I-place
Buckingham	I-place
House	I-place
in	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Park	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
,	O
sat	O
by	O
him	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Clock	O
?	O
About	O
six	O
,	O
said	O
the	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
(	O
says	O
the	O
prisoner	O
)	O
,	O
can	O
you	O
be	O
positive	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
just	O
6	O
?	O
Let	O
me	O
see	O
your	O
Watch	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
thinking	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
good	O
design	O
by	O
being	O
so	O
inquisitive	O
,	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
walking	O
down	O
the	O
Mall	O
the	O
prisoner	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
and	O
askt	O
him	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
.	O
But	O
says	O
he	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
have	O
.	O
With	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Collar	O
,	O
drag	O
'd	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Mall	O
towards	O
the	O
Canal	O
,	O
threw	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
search	O
'd	O
his	O
Pockets	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
Shilling	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
where	O
the	O
rest	O
was	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
knew	O
he	O
had	O
more	O
.	O
He	O
answer	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
than	O
askt	O
him	O
for	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
none	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
then	O
broke	O
the	O
Wastband	O
of	O
his	O
Breeches	O
to	O
search	O
him	O
:	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
cry	O
'd	O
Murder	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
Sodomite	O
.	O
They	O
ask't	O
the	O
prisoner	O
why	O
he	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
Sodomy	O
.	O
Why	O
(	O
says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
see	O
my	O
Hand	O
in	O
his	O
breeches	O
?	O
They	O
were	O
then	O
carried	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
both	O
committed	O
to	O
the	O
Gate-house	O
,	O
on	O
suspicion	O
of	O
Sodomy	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
a	O
Soldier	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
upon	O
Duty	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
disturbance	O
in	O
the	O
Grass	O
:	O
he	O
went	O
towards	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
expecting	O
to	O
have	O
found	O
a	O
Man	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
engag	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
approaching	O
near	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Centry	O
come	O
hither	O
,	O
here	O
's	O
a	O
Sodomite	O
!	O
When	O
he	O
came	O
close	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
have	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
privities	O
,	O
and	O
asking	O
him	O
the	O
reason	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
answer	O
'd	O
:	O
He	O
wants	O
to	O
B	O
-	O
r	O
me	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
charge	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
Robbery	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Edwards	B-pers
Moyers	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Mires	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hughs	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
and	O
Breeches	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
27	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
a	O
Lodging	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Hughs	O
,	O
and	O
instead	O
of	O
going	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
ransack	O
'd	O
the	O
Garrets	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
followeth	O
;	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
9.	O
James	B-pers
Tims	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Hooper	I-pers
,	O
Tho	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Hartly	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Poky	O
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Broome	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Bean	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Macopny	O
,	O
Alice	B-pers
Phenix	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
2.	O
John	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Harwood	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
,	O
32.	O
William	B-pers
Blewit	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Scoon	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Spooner	O
,	O
alias	O
Crow	O
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Thatcher	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Thatcher	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Coats	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Hedgly	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Mekins	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Corn	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Colgrave	I-pers
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Cope	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Hannah	B-pers
Banks	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Hannah	O
Hill	O
,	O
Humphry	O
Hunion	O
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hains	I-pers
,	O
Mark	B-pers
Horton	I-pers
,	O
Abel	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
Mary	O
D'arbieau	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Fen	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Parrot	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mumford	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Renton	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Deross	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Sedgwick	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Connor	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Moyers	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Mires	O
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
Simon	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Janes	O
Evans	O
,	O
sen	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Par	I-pers
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Caruthers	I-pers
Fin	O
'd	O
20	O
Marks	O
,	O
12	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
once	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
near	O
Doctors	O
Commons	O
.	O
John	O
Francis	O
Fin	O
'd	O
25	O
l.	O
And	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
imprison	O
'd	O
for	O
6	O
Months	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Colthurp	I-pers
,	O
Fin	O
'd	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
12	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dicks	I-pers
Fin	O
'd	O
20	O
Marks	O
,	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
without	O
Temple-Bar	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Years	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Flood	I-pers
Fin	O
'd	O
10	O
Marks	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Bean	I-pers
pleaded	O
her	O
Belly	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
being	O
impanell	O
'd	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
quick	O
with	O
Child	O
.	O
A	O
D	O
V	O
E	O
R	O
T	O
I	O
S	O
E	O
M	O
E	O
N	O
T	O
S.	O
Original	O
Gown	O
Ware-house	O
,	O
at	O
Baker	O
's	O
Coffee-house	O
is	O
Exchange	O
Ally	O
,	O
Cornhill	O
.	O
Gowns	O
for	O
Men	O
,	O
Women	O
,	O
Boys	O
,	O
Girls	O
,	O
and	O
Children	O
in	O
Arms	O
,	O
are	O
continued	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
both	O
by	O
Wholesale	O
and	O
Retail	O
made	O
up	O
of	O
rich	O
Brocaded	O
Silks	O
,	O
Italian	O
Silks	O
,	O
Garden	O
Sattins	O
,	O
stained	O
Silks	O
,	O
Damasks	O
,	O
Thread	O
Sattins	O
,	O
Scotch	O
Plods	O
,	O
richly	O
lin	O
'd	O
,	O
Stuffs	O
,	O
Callamancas	O
,	O
and	O
Callicoes	O
:	O
All	O
made	O
very	O
large	O
,	O
and	O
suitable	O
Linings	O
the	O
like	O
was	O
never	O
expos	O
'd	O
to	O
Sale	O
by	O
any	O
Man	O
before	O
;	O
where	O
Caps	O
and	O
Sashes	O
are	O
sold	O
,	O
they	O
being	O
a	O
fresh	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Goods	O
,	O
bought	O
of	O
the	O
Executors	O
of	O
a	O
great	O
Mrecer	O
lately	O
deceas	O
'd	O
;	O
The	O
Price	O
set	O
on	O
each	O
Gown	O
.	O
BOOKS	O
Printed	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
Sold	O
by	O
Arthur	B-pers
Bettesworth	I-pers
at	O
the	O
Red	O
Lyons	O
in	O
Paternoster-Row	O
.	O
Schism	O
try	O
'd	O
and	O
Condemn	O
'd	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Sentiments	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
eminent	O
Writers	O
among	O
the	O
Dissenters	O
,	O
written	O
for	O
the	O
Conviction	O
of	O
Gain-sayers	O
and	O
those	O
who	O
complain	O
of	O
Persecution	O
upon	O
Occasion	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
Act	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Prevention	O
of	O
the	O
Growth	O
of	O
Schism	O
the	O
8th	O
Edition	O
.	O
The	O
2nd	O
part	O
,	O
Containing	O
the	O
sentiments	O
of	O
the	O
Foreign	O
reform	O
'd	O
Churches	O
,	O
Proving	O
that	O
all	O
the	O
Pleas	O
against	O
Conformity	O
to	O
the	O
Church	O
of	O
England	O
are	O
vain	O
and	O
frivolous	O
and	O
Separation	O
from	O
is	O
Sinful	O
,	O
pr	O
6	O
d	O
,	O
each	O
.	O
The	O
Laymen	O
's	O
Antidote	O
against	O
the	O
Heretical	O
Notions	O
of	O
his	O
Mr.	O
Whiston	O
,	O
Dr.	O
Clarke	O
and	O
other	O
Modern	O
Enthusiasts	O
,	O
who	O
are	O
for	O
destroying	O
the	O
Church	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
Reformation	O
,	O
pr	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
An	O
Examination	O
of	O
Dr.	O
Clark	O
's	O
Scripture-Doctrine	O
of	O
the	O
Trinity	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Confutation	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
inserted	O
in	O
an	O
Exposition	O
of	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
difficult	O
places	O
of	O
the	O
New	O
Testament	O
,	O
wherein	O
the	O
9th	O
chapter	O
of	O
Romans	O
is	O
set	O
in	O
a	O
Clear	O
Light	O
,	O
by	O
valentine	O
Haywood	B-pers
M.A	I-pers
.	O
pr	O
.	O
2s	O
.	O
Bidding	O
of	O
Prayers	O
before	O
Sermon	O
,	O
no	O
mark	O
of	O
Disaffection	O
in	O
the	O
present	O
Government	O
being	O
being	O
an	O
Historical	O
Vindication	O
of	O
the	O
55th	O
Canon	O
,	O
by	O
Charles	B-pers
Wheatly	I-pers
M	I-pers
A	O
Author	O
of	O
the	O
Rational	O
Illustration	O
of	O
the	O
Common-Prayer	O
,	O
pr	O
.	O
1s	O
.	O
The	O
Clergyman	O
's	O
Advocate	O
,	O
or	O
an	O
Historical	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Ill	O
Treatment	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
and	O
Clergy	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
the	O
Reformation	O
to	O
this	O
Time	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
Lay	O
Hand	O
,	O
pr	O
.	O
1s	O
..	O
Just	O
Publish	O
'd	O
Episcopal	O
the	O
only	O
Apostolical	O
Ordination	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
Case	O
of	O
the	O
Ordination	O
truly	O
Consider	O
'd	O
to	O
which	O
is	O
prefix	O
'd	O
Letter	O
from	O
the	O
Rev	O
.	O
Dr.	O
Hicks	O
.	O
The	O
Invalidity	O
of	O
Dissenting	O
Ministry	O
,	O
or	O
Presbyterian	O
Ordination	O
an	O
irregular	O
and	O
unjustifiable	O
Practice	O
in	O
two	O
Parts	O
.	O
The	O
Original	O
Draught	O
of	O
the	O
Primitive	O
Church	O
,	O
that	O
flourish	O
'd	O
within	O
the	O
first	O
three	O
Hundred	O
years	O
after	O
Christ	O
.	O
Episopacy	O
vindicated	O
by	O
W.	O
Richardson	O
lately	O
a	O
Dissenting	O
Teacher	O
but	O
now	O
a	O
Presby	O
er	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
of	O
England	O
.	O
Rights	O
Notions	O
of	O
God	O
and	O
Religion	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
Discourses	O
for	O
correcting	O
Prevailing	O
Errors	O
.	O
Salvation	O
the	O
peculiar	O
Privilege	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
,	O
those	O
two	O
by	O
J.	O
Cockburne	O
D.D	O
.	O
All	O
Printed	O
for	O
G.	O
Strahan	O
at	O
the	O
Golden	O
Ball	O
against	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
.	O
Just	O
publish	O
'd	O
Great	O
Britains	O
Vade	O
Mecum	O
Containing	O
1	O
.	O
A	O
concise	O
Geographical	O
Description	O
of	O
the	O
world	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
enquiry	O
into	O
the	O
Nature	O
.	O
Quality	O
,	O
and	O
principal	O
Commodities	O
of	O
each	O
Country	O
.	O
2.	O
the	O
several	O
Counties	O
of	O
England	O
and	O
Wales	O
,	O
particularly	O
describ	O
'd	O
;	O
An	O
account	O
of	O
their	O
valuable	O
Products	O
,	O
Market-Towns	O
,	O
Market-Days	O
,	O
chief	O
Fairs	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
3	O
.	O
A	O
short	O
view	O
of	O
Trade	O
in	O
General	O
and	O
an	O
Enumeration	O
of	O
the	O
chief	O
Commo	O
dities	O
and	O
Manufactures	O
of	O
Great	O
Britain	O
;	O
o	O
'	O
Weights	O
and	O
Measures	O
,	O
Coin	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
4	O
.	O
A	O
Description	O
of	O
the	O
Cities	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
Westminster	O
,	O
more	O
exact	O
and	O
regular	O
than	O
any	O
extant	O
,	O
with	O
Tables	O
of	O
Fees	O
of	O
the	O
several	O
Courts	O
in	O
London	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
5	O
.	O
Of	O
the	O
Courts	O
of	O
the	O
Judicature	O
held	O
at	O
Westminster	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
Chancery	O
,	O
Kings	O
Bench	O
,	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
also	O
an	O
exact	O
Table	O
of	O
their	O
Respective	O
Fees	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
A	O
Compleat	O
useful	O
Table	O
,	O
shewing	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
any	O
Quantities	O
of	O
Goods	O
or	O
Merchandize	O
ready	O
cast	O
up	O
,	O
from	O
One	O
Penny	O
he	O
Pound	O
,	O
Ell	O
Yard	O
,	O
Ounce	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
to	O
Twenty	O
Shillings	O
.	O
7	O
.	O
The	O
best	O
instructions	O
for	O
Gauging	O
and	O
Measuring	O
Work	O
in	O
Town	O
and	O
Country	O
.	O
8	O
.	O
Directions	O
for	O
taking	O
and	O
entering	O
Goods	O
at	O
the	O
Custom	O
House	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
business	O
of	O
the	O
Water-side	O
;	O
the	O
Statutes	O
relating	O
to	O
the	O
Customs	O
.	O
Table	O
of	O
Fess	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
9	O
.	O
Rates	O
of	O
Post	O
Letters	O
,	O
as	O
establish	O
'd	O
by	O
Act	O
of	O
Parliament	O
,	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Penny	O
post	O
,	O
the	O
Stiles	O
and	O
Titles	O
due	O
to	O
Persons	O
of	O
rank	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Office	O
.	O
10	O
The	O
Rates	O
and	O
Orders	O
of	O
Coachmen	O
,	O
Chairmen	O
,	O
Carmen	O
,	O
Watermen	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
11	O
An	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
Roads	O
to	O
London	O
from	O
the	O
Principal	O
Cities	O
and	O
Market	O
Towns	O
in	O
England	O
and	O
Wales	O
:	O
of	O
Stage	O
Coaches	O
,	O
Waggoners	O
,	O
Carriers	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
that	O
come	O
to	O
all	O
Parts	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
their	O
Inns	O
,	O
Days	O
of	O
coming	O
in	O
and	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Rates	O
and	O
Prices	O
.	O
The	O
whole	O
of	O
univer'al	O
use	O
to	O
all	O
Persons	O
of	O
all	O
Ranks	O
,	O
in	O
Town	O
any	O
Country	O
,	O
particularly	O
to	O
Country	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
Travellers	O
,	O
Lawyers	O
,	O
Merchants	O
,	O
Tradesmen	O
,	O
Builders	O
Gaugers	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Printed	O
for	O
W.	O
Mears	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Lamb	O
without	O
Temple	O
Bar	O
.	O
Just	O
publish	O
'd	O
the	O
Sixth	O
Edition	O
,	O
(	O
with	O
Additions	O
and	O
Amendments	O
of	O
A	O
Rational	O
and	O
Useful	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Veneral	O
Disease	O
With	O
Observations	O
on	O
the	O
Nature	O
,	O
Symptoms	O
and	O
Cure	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bad	O
Consequences	O
that	O
attend	O
by	O
ill	O
Management	O
,	O
with	O
proper	O
Admonitions	O
,	O
recommended	O
as	O
a	O
Friendly	O
instructions	O
to	O
all	O
Persons	O
who	O
do	O
,	O
or	O
may	O
,	O
labour	O
under	O
this	O
Misfortune	O
.	O
Also	O
a	O
short	O
Enquiry	O
into	O
old	O
Gleets	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Weaknesses	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Reason	O
why	O
they	O
are	O
so	O
seldom	O
cur	O
'd	O
:	O
With	O
the	O
Author	O
's	O
Method	O
of	O
Cure	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
are	O
added	O
,	O
Some	O
Hints	O
on	O
the	O
PRACTICAL	O
SCHEME	O
,	O
The	O
Method	O
and	O
Medicines	O
therein	O
expos	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
gross	O
Impositions	O
justly	O
detected	O
.	O
With	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
Specificks	O
,	O
the	O
Use	O
and	O
Abuse	O
of	O
the	O
Name	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
it	O
covers	O
Ignorance	O
and	O
a	O
Cheat	O
.	O
By	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
Cam	I-pers
M	I-pers
.D	O
.	O
Evasti	O
?	O
credo	O
metues	O
doctusque	O
cavebis	O
:	O
Quares	O
quando	O
iterum	O
pavea	O
,	O
iterumque	O
perira	O
Possit	O
,	O
o	O
totius	O
servus	O
!	O
Horat	O
.	O
Principiss	O
obsta	O
Ovid	O
,	O
Printed	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
G.	O
Strahan	O
against	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
without	O
Temple-Bar	O
,	O
C.	O
King	O
in	O
Westminster-Hall	O
,	O
T.	O
Norris	O
on	O
London	O
Bridge	O
J	O
Baker	O
against	O
Hatton-Garden	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Author	O
at	O
the	O
Golden	O
Ball	O
and	O
Lamp	O
in	O
Bow	O
Church	O
yard	O
,	O
Cheapside	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
An	O
Essay	O
upon	O
the	O
Soul	O
of	O
Man	O
,	O
Moral	O
,	O
Natural	O
,	O
and	O
Divine	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
following	O
Heads	O
.	O
I	O
.	O
The	O
Preference	O
due	O
to	O
the	O
Soul	O
above	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Reason	O
of	O
its	O
Spiritual	O
and	O
Immortal	O
Nature	O
.	O
II	O
.	O
Of	O
our	O
Duties	O
of	O
Religion	O
and	O
Morality	O
,	O
whether	O
towards	O
God	O
,	O
whether	O
towards	O
our	O
Selves	O
,	O
whether	O
towards	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
our	O
Duty	O
of	O
all	O
Gospel	O
Self	O
denial	O
;	O
which	O
result	O
from	O
the	O
manner	O
how	O
one	O
Souls	O
are	O
and	O
Operate	O
in	O
our	O
Bodies	O
under	O
the	O
visible	O
Empire	O
of	O
God	O
.	O
III	O
.	O
Concerning	O
our	O
Duties	O
of	O
Time	O
and	O
Eternity	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
present	O
World	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
World	O
to	O
come	O
;	O
which	O
result	O
from	O
the	O
manner	O
how	O
our	O
Souls	O
ought	O
to	O
be	O
out	O
of	O
our	O
Bodies	O
,	O
first	O
of	O
all	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
in	O
our	O
Spritualiz	O
'd	O
Bodies	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
Universal	O
Resurrection	O
.	O
London	O
:	O
Printed	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
James	B-pers
Lacy	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Ship	O
near	O
Temple-Bar	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
under	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
;	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Combes	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
and	O
Dove	O
in	O
Paternoster	O
Row	O
.	O
1722	O
.	O
Just	O
publish	O
'd	O
The	O
Tryal	O
and	O
Conviciton	O
of	O
Patrick	B-pers
Hutly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Moughna	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Clare	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
Kings	O
Bench	O
in	O
Ireland	O
,	O
on	O
Two	O
several	O
Indictments	O
.	O
The	O
one	O
for	O
Perjury	O
in	O
swearing	O
falsly	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
Twelve	O
Hundred	O
and	O
One	O
Pounds	O
,	O
Nine	O
Shillings	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
for	O
a	O
Conspiracy	O
to	O
Cheat	O
the	O
Popish	O
Inhabitants	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
at	O
Clare	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Sum	O
,	O
by	O
Colour	O
of	O
an	O
Act	O
of	O
Parliament	O
,	O
Entitled	O
,	O
an	O
Act	O
for	O
the	O
better	O
suppressing	O
Tories	O
,	O
Robbers	O
,	O
Rapparies	O
;	O
&	O
c.	O
Printed	O
for	O
J	O
Roberts	O
in	O
Warwick	O
Lane	O
(	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
)	O
Where	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
,	O
I	O
.	O
Of	O
The	O
Laws	O
of	O
CHANCE	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
Method	O
of	O
Calculation	O
of	O
the	O
Hazards	O
of	O
GAME	O
,	O
Plainly	O
demonstrated	O
and	O
applied	O
to	O
Games	O
at	O
present	O
most	O
in	O
use	O
.	O
Which	O
may	O
be	O
easily	O
extended	O
to	O
the	O
most	O
intricate	O
case	O
Chance	O
imaginable	O
.	O
The	O
Third	O
Edition	O
,	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
II	O
.	O
Uzziah	O
and	O
Jotham	O
:	O
Occasin	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
late	O
Revolution	O
in	O
1688.	O
and	O
containing	O
impartial	O
and	O
instructive	O
Characters	O
of	O
the	O
several	O
persons	O
of	O
distinction	O
of	O
both	O
Parties	O
who	O
were	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
that	O
memorable	O
Event	O
.	O
The	O
Third	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
6	O
d.	O
A	O
Water	O
that	O
perfectly	O
cures	O
the	O
Itch	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
Itching	O
Humour	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
,	O
without	O
necessity	O
of	O
Purging	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
dangerous	O
Use	O
of	O
Mercury	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
6d	O
.	O
is	O
only	O
prepared	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
A.Downing	O
Chymist	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
and	O
Ball	O
,	O
in	O
George	O
Court	O
in	O
St.	O
Johns	O
Lane	O
by	O
Hick	O
's	O
Hall	O
,	O
near	O
West-Smithfield	O
.	O
Where	O
also	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
,	O
the	O
best	O
Spirits	O
of	O
Scurvy	O
Grass	O
,	O
by	O
Wholesale	O
or	O
Retale	O
at	O
8d	O
.	O
a	O
Bottle	O
.	O
A	O
most	O
effectual	O
Remedy	O
for	O
the	O
Violent	O
Pain	O
in	O
the	O
Teeth	O
,	O
Price	O
1s	O
.	O
Also	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Remedy	O
for	O
preserving	O
the	O
Teeth	O
,	O
and	O
clearing	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
Scurvey	O
.	O
Just	O
publish	O
'd	O
.	O
Written	O
from	O
her	O
own	O
Memorandums	O
.	O
Printed	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
W.	O
Chetwood	O
at	O
the	O
Cato's-Head	O
in	O
Russel	O
Street	O
Covent-Garden	O
,	O
and	O
T	O
Edlin	O
at	O
the	O
Prince	O
's	O
Arms	O
over-against	O
Exeter	O
Exchange	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
Price	O
5s	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
BENJ	O
.	O
MOTTE	O
in	O
Aldersgate-Street	O
.	O
Sold	O
by	O
J.	O
ROBERTS	O
in	O
Warwick	O
Lane	O
,	O
Price	O
3	O
d	O
.	O
