TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice	O
Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
24th	O
,	O
26th	O
,	O
and	O
27th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Ninth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
GERARD	B-pers
CONYERS	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
Prat	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Tracy	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Price	I-pers
;	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
JURORS	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
The	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Walden	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Peacock	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hillar	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Bellis	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Kightly	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Hammerton	I-pers
,	O
Ford	B-pers
Bechum	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Haddon	I-pers
,	O
Marmaduke	B-pers
Emmerson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Richmond	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Linney	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Whitton	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Ashman	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Gouge	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Arnott	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bush	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
.	O
Humphry	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Stephen	I-place
Coleman-street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Curtains	O
,	O
Vallance	O
,	O
Linnen	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lamb	I-pers
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
;	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
Joseph	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
convicted	O
for	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
like	O
Facts	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Lodgings	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Lodgings	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
miss	O
'd	O
immediately	O
upon	O
their	O
going	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
his	O
having	O
taken	O
the	O
Lodging	O
,	O
but	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Fast	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s	O
10d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Glassbrook	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
159	O
l.	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
;	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hyam	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
April	O
.	O
His	O
Confession	O
before	O
Sir	O
Francis	B-pers
Forbes	I-pers
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
wherein	O
he	O
had	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
stealing	O
40	O
l.	O
of	O
Sugar	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Brick	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
Buttolph	I-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cask	O
,	O
containing	O
32	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Oil	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Law	I-pers
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
apprehended	O
rolling	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
Keys	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
he	O
was	O
hired	O
by	O
a	O
Man	O
that	O
was	O
rolling	O
it	O
,	O
to	O
roll	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Corner	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hobson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
Ludgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
half	O
an	O
Ounce	O
of	O
Human	O
Hair	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
and	O
half	O
an	O
Ounce	O
of	O
Horse	O
Hair	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Launder	I-pers
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Journey-Man	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Hair	O
and	O
Sold	O
it	O
.	O
His	O
Confession	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fryer	I-pers
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
wherein	O
he	O
had	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Buckingham	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Loyd	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Simpkin	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Hassel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Istleworth	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Anne	O
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bristol	I-pers
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecution	O
was	O
carried	O
on	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Attorney	O
General	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
was	O
as	O
followeth	O
,	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
being	O
Nurse	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Ruffin	O
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
Hardin	O
Ruffin	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Red	O
Lion	O
on	O
Smallberry	B-place
Green	I-place
,	O
did	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
see	O
four	O
Men	O
drinking	O
with	O
Anne	B-pers
Bristol	I-pers
.	O
That	O
she	O
did	O
believe	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
George	O
Smith	O
,	O
Joseph	O
Buckingham	O
,	O
James	O
Simpkin	O
,	O
and	O
Samuel	O
Loyd	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
positive	O
as	O
to	O
George	O
Smith	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
about	O
seven	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
and	O
drank	O
there	O
till	O
about	O
eleven	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
away	O
together	O
.	O
The	O
Examination	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ruffin	I-pers
(	O
since	O
deceased	O
)	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
to	O
this	O
Effect	O
.	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
Smith	O
,	O
Buckingham	O
,	O
Simpkin	O
and	O
Loyd	O
,	O
did	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
drink	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Anne	O
Bristol	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
very	O
familiar	O
,	O
Buckingham	O
Kissing	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
her	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Dear	O
,	O
and	O
asking	O
her	O
sometimes	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
;	O
that	O
Simkin	O
also	O
kissed	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
that	O
at	O
paying	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
Anne	O
Bristol	O
paid	O
three	O
Pence	O
,	O
the	O
rest	O
their	O
Shots	O
,	O
except	O
Simpkin	O
,	O
who	O
paid	O
nothing	O
.	O
After	O
which	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
together	O
.	O
Susan	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
living	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Ruffin	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Red	O
Lion	O
on	O
Smallberry	O
Green	O
,	O
did	O
,	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
she	O
can	O
think	O
,	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2nd	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
hear	O
a	O
Woman	O
's	O
Voice	O
upon	O
the	O
Green	O
,	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
calling	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
;	O
the	O
Woman	O
answered	O
,	O
The	O
Men	O
were	O
very	O
rude	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
And	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
heard	O
a	O
Man	O
's	O
Voice	O
,	O
saying	O
to	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
That	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
yield	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
throw	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
Pond	O
.	O
And	O
likewise	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
consented	O
to	O
be	O
-	O
it	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
all	O
over	O
by	O
that	O
Time	O
.	O
That	O
hereupon	O
she	O
called	O
to	O
them	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
and	O
asked	O
.	O
What	O
they	O
were	O
doing	O
?	O
And	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Men	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
They	O
were	O
-	O
a	O
Woman	O
to	O
Death	O
against	O
her	O
Will	O
.	O
And	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
heard	O
the	O
Woman	O
cry	O
out	O
Murder	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
Anne	O
Bristol	O
upon	O
the	O
Green	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
Condition	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
with	O
her	O
?	O
And	O
she	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
O	O
,	O
the	O
Watermen	O
,	O
the	O
Waterman	O
!	O
George	B-pers
Ockram	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
Woman	O
's	O
Voice	O
cry	O
out	O
Murder	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
heard	O
Men	O
hollow	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
heard	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
melancholy	O
Tone	O
say	O
,	O
O	O
dear	O
.	O
He	O
likewise	O
heard	O
her	O
call	O
to	O
a	O
Waggoner	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Waggon	O
stopp	O
'd	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
desired	O
to	O
Waggoner	O
to	O
help	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
thinks	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
That	O
about	O
seven	O
a	O
Clock	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
he	O
saw	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Green	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
bid	O
her	O
go	O
to	O
some	O
House	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
.	O
That	O
Hardin	O
Ruffin	O
and	O
Hassel	O
lifted	O
her	O
into	O
a	O
Wheel-Barrow	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
wheel	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Bridge	O
and	O
there	O
left	O
her	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
Cap	O
on	O
her	O
Head	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
dirty	O
Condition	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Clothes	O
tore	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Ockram	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
about	O
two	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
she	O
heard	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
being	O
waked	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Sleep	O
by	O
it	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
a	O
Man	O
swear	O
to	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
He	O
would	O
throw	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
Pond	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
quiet	O
.	O
And	O
about	O
seven	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
she	O
saw	O
Anne	O
Bristol	O
sitting	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
nine	O
the	O
Beadle	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
carried	O
her	O
into	O
her	O
Barn	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
dirty	O
Condition	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
dy	O
'd	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
carried	O
in	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
some	O
Bruises	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
biggest	O
was	O
on	O
her	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
scratches	O
upon	O
her	O
Hands	O
and	O
Knees	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Welman	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
Anne	O
Bristol	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
at	O
Hardin	O
Ruffin	O
's	O
at	O
the	O
Red	O
Lyon	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
four	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
suppos	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
knew	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
but	O
George	O
Smith	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
call	O
Anne	O
Bristol	O
home	O
to	O
her	O
Quarters	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
his	O
putting	O
in	O
his	O
Stick	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
drinking	O
,	O
George	O
Smith	O
jump	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Chair	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
,	O
He	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
any	O
Body	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Company	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Welman	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
That	O
the	O
Baker	O
coming	O
to	O
bring	O
her	O
Bread	O
,	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Country	O
Woman	O
lay	O
upon	O
the	O
Green	O
either	O
dead	O
or	O
a	O
dying	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
near	O
the	O
Bridge	O
,	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
with	O
her	O
Head	O
upon	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
begg	O
'd	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Lord	O
's	O
sake	O
,	O
to	O
have	O
her	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
her	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
telling	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Woman	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
had	O
turn	O
'd	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
to	O
her	O
Destruction	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
went	O
and	O
talk	O
'd	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Ruffin	O
about	O
turning	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
fetch	O
'd	O
the	O
Beadle	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
help	O
'd	O
into	O
a	O
Wheel-Barrow	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
into	O
a	O
Barn	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
That	O
three	O
of	O
the	O
Men	O
had	O
held	O
her	O
while	O
the	O
fourth	O
would	O
have	O
lain	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
If	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
desir	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
cut	O
her	O
Lace	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
died	O
presently	O
after	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Leerwood	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
She	O
being	O
in	O
Bed	O
was	O
waked	O
by	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
but	O
knows	O
not	O
at	O
what	O
Time	O
of	O
the	O
Night	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
heard	O
a	O
Woman	O
shriek	O
out	O
twice	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Voice	O
was	O
towards	O
the	O
Ponds	O
on	O
the	O
Green	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
heard	O
a	O
Waggon	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Man	O
cry	O
Woo	O
to	O
his	O
Horses	O
three	O
Times	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
heard	O
a	O
Woman	O
cry	O
Murder	O
when	O
the	O
Waggon	O
stopp	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
Woman	O
groan	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
should	O
die	O
.	O
That	O
seeing	O
Anne	O
Bristol	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
she	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
Why	O
she	O
made	O
such	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
disturbed	O
her	O
rest	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
sorry	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
Waggon	O
had	O
run	O
over	O
her	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
the	O
Waggon	O
,	O
the	O
Waggon	O
,	O
the	O
cursed	O
Waggon	O
,	O
has	O
killed	O
me	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Ware	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
a	O
Woman	O
cry	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
Waggoner	O
,	O
Waggoner	O
,	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
help	O
,	O
saying	O
she	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Brentford	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
her	O
lie	O
there	O
and	O
he	O
damned	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
then	O
about	O
fifteen	O
Yards	O
from	O
the	O
Road	O
where	O
the	O
Waggon	O
pass	O
'd	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Loton	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
going	O
by	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
Ware	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
,	O
a	O
Woman	O
sat	O
about	O
fourteen	O
or	O
fifteen	O
Yards	O
from	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
Waggoner	O
,	O
Waggoner	O
,	O
have	O
me	O
to	O
Brentford	O
.	O
James	O
Bothune	O
,	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
upon	O
viewing	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Anne	O
Bristol	O
,	O
her	O
left	O
Eye	O
was	O
black	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
receiv	O
'd	O
a	O
Blow	O
with	O
the	O
Fist	O
.	O
And	O
also	O
,	O
her	O
Elbow	O
was	O
broken	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Wrists	O
,	O
one	O
Knee	O
,	O
and	O
both	O
her	O
Ancles	O
,	O
were	O
hurt	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
a	O
Scratch	O
upon	O
her	O
Thigh	O
,	O
two	O
Inches	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
long	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Contusion	O
,	O
like	O
a	O
Blow	O
,	O
on	O
her	O
Breast	O
.	O
Upon	O
opening	O
her	O
he	O
found	O
her	O
first	O
five	O
Ribs	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
bent	O
out	O
wards	O
towards	O
the	O
Thorax	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Coagulated	O
Blood	O
in	O
the	O
Thorax	O
.	O
Her	O
fourth	O
Rib	O
was	O
broke	O
in	O
the	O
vertebra	O
of	O
the	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
End	O
had	O
pressed	O
the	O
Pleura	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Lungs	O
.	O
And	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
How	O
he	O
thought	O
this	O
might	O
be	O
done	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
done	O
by	O
stamping	O
upon	O
,	O
or	O
some	O
such	O
Violence	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
believe	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
by	O
the	O
Wheel	O
of	O
a	O
Waggon	O
,	O
because	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
had	O
run	O
over	O
her	O
Stomach	O
it	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
broken	O
so	O
many	O
of	O
her	O
Ribs	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
the	O
Impression	O
of	O
the	O
Wheel	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
a	O
loaded	O
Waggon	O
,	O
it	O
must	O
have	O
broke	O
her	O
to	O
Pieces	O
almost	O
,	O
whereas	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
outward	O
manifest	O
Signs	O
of	O
any	O
such	O
Accident	O
.	O
And	O
if	O
a	O
Waggon	O
had	O
run	O
over	O
her	O
Breast	O
length	O
ways	O
,	O
it	O
must	O
also	O
have	O
broken	O
the	O
Collar	O
Bone	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
whole	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
no	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Body	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
the	O
Scarf	O
Skin	O
broke	O
.	O
That	O
if	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
done	O
by	O
the	O
Stamping	O
of	O
an	O
Horse	O
on	O
her	O
Breast	O
,	O
where	O
her	O
Clothes	O
were	O
not	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
of	O
Opinion	O
,	O
there	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
some	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Nails	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
her	O
Pudenda	O
were	O
of	O
a	O
livid	O
unnatural	O
Colour	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
the	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
deposed	O
much	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Purpose	O
with	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
,	O
adding	O
,	O
That	O
both	O
her	O
Ancles	O
and	O
Wrists	O
were	O
black	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
grasp	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
Opinion	O
likewise	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
receive	O
the	O
Wounds	O
,	O
and	O
breaking	O
her	O
Ribs	O
,	O
by	O
being	O
run	O
over	O
by	O
a	O
Waggon	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hedom	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
Church-Warden	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
of	O
a	O
Woman	O
hurt	O
upon	O
Smallberry	O
Green	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
the	O
Beadle	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
he	O
went	O
himself	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
her	O
dead	O
.	O
That	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Bruise	O
on	O
her	O
right	O
Eye	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Arms	O
had	O
Bruises	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Backs	O
of	O
her	O
Hands	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
trod	O
or	O
kneeled	O
upon	O
,	O
her	O
Thighs	O
full	O
of	O
Bruises	O
as	O
if	O
from	O
Kicks	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Overseer	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
much	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Purpose	O
.	O
These	O
Persons	O
having	O
given	O
their	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
following	O
Evidences	O
were	O
called	O
as	O
to	O
their	O
absconding	O
.	O
Hester	B-pers
Tims	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	O
Burkingham	O
's	O
Mistress	O
was	O
examined	O
,	O
Whether	O
he	O
lay	O
at	O
home	O
that	O
Night	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
done	O
?	O
who	O
declared	O
,	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
And	O
also	O
,	O
that	O
George	O
Smith	O
and	O
James	O
Simpkin	O
lodged	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
neither	O
of	O
them	O
lay	O
at	O
home	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
That	O
about	O
seven	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
they	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
about	O
ten	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
saw	O
them	O
no	O
more	O
till	O
after	O
their	O
being	O
apprehended	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	O
Loyd	O
's	O
Mistress	O
,	O
being	O
examined	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
lie	O
at	O
home	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
came	O
home	O
about	O
seven	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
with	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
Lighters	O
,	O
according	O
as	O
her	O
Husband	O
had	O
left	O
Orders	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
afterwards	O
saw	O
him	O
no	O
more	O
till	O
after	O
his	O
being	O
apprehended	O
.	O
Brian	B-pers
Cade	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
carried	O
George	O
Smith	O
and	O
Joseph	O
Buckingham	O
cross	O
the	O
Water	O
that	O
Morning	O
,	O
from	O
Thistleworth	O
to	O
Sheene	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Peck	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
took	O
George	O
Smith	O
and	O
Joseph	O
Buckingham	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
latter	O
confess	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
stood	O
by	O
while	O
Smith	O
lay	O
with	O
Anne	O
Bristol	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
two	O
others	O
kicked	O
her	O
on	O
her	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
afterwards	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
him	O
lain	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
shov	O
'd	O
him	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
They	O
had	O
kill	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
broke	O
some	O
of	O
her	O
Ribs	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
carried	O
her	O
afterwards	O
to	O
the	O
Sign	O
Post	O
at	O
the	O
Landlord	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
And	O
,	O
that	O
George	O
Smith	O
also	O
owned	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lain	O
with	O
Anne	O
Bristol	O
.	O
Simpkin	O
's	O
Examination	O
before	O
the	O
Mayor	O
of	O
Gravesand	O
,	O
was	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
wherein	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
three	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
were	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
Anne	O
Bristol	O
on	O
Smallberry	O
Green	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
Smith	O
lay	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
others	O
attempted	O
to	O
lie	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
whether	O
they	O
did	O
or	O
no	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
Loyd	O
kick	O
her	O
as	O
she	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
Joseph	O
Buckingham	O
's	O
Examination	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
and	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
wherein	O
he	O
confessed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
Anne	O
Bristol	O
at	O
the	O
Red	O
Lion	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
that	O
Smith	O
lay	O
with	O
her	O
upon	O
the	O
Green	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
that	O
Loyd	O
kick	O
'd	O
her	O
because	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
lie	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
This	O
being	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
made	O
the	O
following	O
Defence	O
.	O
Smith	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
near	O
Smallberry	O
Green	O
,	O
Anne	O
Bristol	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
where	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
?	O
That	O
they	O
met	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
help	O
'd	O
her	O
our	O
of	O
a	O
Ditch	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
dropp	O
'd	O
half	O
a	O
Pound	O
of	O
Butter	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
fell	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
Hardin	O
Ruffin	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Red	O
Lion	O
;	O
that	O
Anne	O
Bristol	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
in	O
their	O
Company	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
smoaking	O
a	O
Pipe	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
his	O
Pipe	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
mouth	O
,	O
and	O
smoak	O
'd	O
it	O
:	O
That	O
they	O
went	O
in	O
about	O
six	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
stay	O
'd	O
till	O
about	O
eleven	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
paid	O
her	O
three	O
Peace	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
follow	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
a	O
Waggon	O
coming	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Waggon	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
saw	O
her	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
following	O
Evidences	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Duffil	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
over	O
Smallberry	O
Green	O
,	O
about	O
7	O
a-Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
a	O
Woman	O
was	O
sitting	O
upon	O
her	O
Breech	O
,	O
about	O
40	O
or	O
50	O
Yards	O
from	O
the	O
Red	O
Lion	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
she	O
fell	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Waggon	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Waggon	O
run	O
over	O
her	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
Story	O
was	O
not	O
right	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
talk	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
very	O
heartily	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
offered	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Beer	O
to	O
lead	O
her	O
to	O
her	O
quarters	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
said	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Green	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
Saunders	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
confirm	O
'd	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
her	O
saying	O
a	O
Waggon	O
had	O
run	O
over	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
help	O
her	O
self	O
.	O
That	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
Time	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
came	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
drunk	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
beshit	O
herself	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Men	O
wheel	O
'd	O
her	O
out	O
in	O
a	O
Wheel-Barrow	O
.	O
He	O
added	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
knew	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
ill	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Man	O
might	O
do	O
what	O
he	O
would	O
with	O
her	O
for	O
two	O
Pence	O
or	O
three	O
Pence	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Nevil	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Oakingham	O
Market	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
baited	O
at	O
Belfount	O
and	O
going	O
over	O
Smallberry	O
Green	O
,	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
a-Clock	O
,	O
a	O
Woman	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Fore-Horse	O
,	O
and	O
led	O
him	O
over	O
most	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Green	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
bid	O
her	O
let	O
go	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
swore	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
four	O
Men	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Team	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
take	O
her	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
swore	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
:	O
That	O
the	O
Men	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
several	O
Times	O
,	O
You	O
Bitch	O
,	O
let	O
go	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
her	O
Part	O
,	O
for	O
those	O
four	O
Men	O
wanted	O
to	O
lie	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
let	O
go	O
the	O
Horse	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
her	O
Part	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
still	O
swore	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
go	O
.	O
That	O
going	O
down	O
a	O
Hill	O
the	O
Fill-Horse	O
could	O
not	O
stop	O
,	O
and	O
drove	O
all	O
the	O
rest	O
forwards	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
came	O
of	O
her	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Waggon	O
run	O
over	O
her	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
bear	O
her	O
cry	O
out	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Waggon	O
on	O
Smallberry	O
Green	O
,	O
near	O
Strip	O
Hall	O
,	O
did	O
bear	O
great	O
cursing	O
and	O
swearing	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
Woman	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Waggoner	O
,	O
asking	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
her	O
Part	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
Men	O
who	O
would	O
lie	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Fore-Horse	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
go	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
heard	O
Men	O
's	O
Voices	O
say	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
You	O
drunken	O
Bitch	O
,	O
let	O
go	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
trod	O
under	O
the	O
Horses	O
Heels	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
swore	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Waggon	O
going	O
down	O
an	O
Hill	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
heavy	O
loaded	O
,	O
the	O
Fill	O
Horse	O
could	O
not	O
stop	O
the	O
Load	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
felt	O
the	O
Wheel	O
go	O
over	O
something	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
afraid	O
the	O
Waggon	O
went	O
over	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
her	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
not	O
saw	O
her	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
let	O
go	O
the	O
Horse	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Leerwood	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
about	O
Seven	O
a-Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
he	O
saw	O
Anne	O
Bristol	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
Green	O
,	O
not	O
far	O
from	O
Ruffin	O
's	O
House	O
:	O
That	O
she	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
help	O
'd	O
to	O
her	O
Lodgings	O
.	O
That	O
William	O
Hassel	O
fetch	O
'd	O
a	O
Wheel-Barrow	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
,	O
Ruffin	O
,	O
and	O
Ockham	O
,	O
put	O
her	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
wheel	O
'd	O
her	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
the	O
Bridge	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
could	O
go	O
no	O
further	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
down	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
so	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
a	O
Waggon	O
had	O
hurt	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hix	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
he	O
saw	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
her	O
say	O
the	O
Waggon	O
had	O
run	O
over	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
like	O
was	O
depos	O
'd	O
by	O
Robert	B-pers
Noble	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Sharp	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
.	O
Micheal	B-pers
Purse	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
about	O
eight	O
a-Clock	O
he	O
saw	O
her	O
,	O
heard	O
her	O
groan	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Ockham	O
's	O
Maid	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
you	O
have	O
been	O
with	O
some	O
fellows	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
have	O
abus	O
'd	O
you	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Woodman	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Evening	O
before	O
she	O
saw	O
her	O
lying	O
in	O
a	O
Ditch	O
,	O
and	O
help	O
'd	O
her	O
out	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
fell	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
dropp	O
'd	O
half	O
a	O
Pound	O
of	O
Butter	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
,	O
this	O
Evidence	O
,	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
overtook	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
Anne	O
Bristol	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
three	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
about	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
she	O
dy	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
Anne	O
Bristol	O
lye	O
in	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
she	O
help	O
'd	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
thank	O
'd	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Course	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Evidence	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
upon	O
a	O
full	O
Hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
acquitted	O
them	O
all	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Porto	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Copper	O
Stew-Pan	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Pan	O
stood	O
over	O
against	O
his	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
carrying	O
it	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
said	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
shew	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
Liberty	O
so	O
to	O
do	O
.	O
Several	O
appeared	O
that	O
gave	O
him	O
an	O
honest	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
crazy	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Katherine	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Katherine	I-pers
Blood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Muslin	O
Neckcloth	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Benson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
to	O
buy	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Neckcloth	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Key	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shift	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Sadler	I-pers
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Shift	O
being	O
laid	O
upon	O
some	O
Sacks	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Body	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
and	O
take	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
discover	O
'd	O
dropp	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
pretended	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Penny	O
Brick	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
a	O
Baker	O
's	O
Shop	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Wilbourn	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Esther	B-pers
Nicholson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
9	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Plate	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
three	O
Forks	O
and	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
honourable	O
Robert	B-pers
Walpole	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
Esther	O
Nicholson	O
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Fork	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
Wilbourn	O
had	O
us	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Walpole	O
's	O
House	O
for	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Years	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
Cook	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Things	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
had	O
been	O
lost	O
at	O
different	O
Times	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
inspected	O
upon	O
Examination	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Plate	O
and	O
one	O
Fork	O
had	O
been	O
pawn	O
'd	O
by	O
Esther	O
Nicholson	O
,	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Sadler	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
pawn	O
'd	O
according	O
to	O
Nicholson	O
's	O
direction	O
.	O
Both	O
their	O
confessions	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
were	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
Wilbourn	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
stole	O
one	O
Fork	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Plate	O
.	O
Nicholson	O
pleaded	O
,	O
she	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
for	O
Wilbourn	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
not	O
they	O
were	O
stolen	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
Sarah	B-pers
Wilbourn	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
And	O
Acquitted	O
Esther	O
Nicholson	O
.	O
Luke	B-pers
Nunny	I-pers
and	O
Martin	B-pers
Nunny	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
Luke	O
Nunny	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bramston	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
of	O
the	O
Length	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
five	O
Inches	O
,	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
Martin	O
Nunny	O
,	O
for	O
being	O
aiding	O
and	O
abetting	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Howel	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
a-Clock	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Whitechapel	B-place
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
assaulting	O
and	O
beating	O
James	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
giving	O
him	O
many	O
Blows	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
little	O
Time	O
after	O
the	O
Deceased	O
came	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
Stop	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
looking	O
on	O
.	O
That	O
Luke	O
Nunny	O
gave	O
the	O
Deceased	O
a	O
Blow	O
with	O
his	O
Fist	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
no	O
Provocation	O
.	O
That	O
upon	O
his	O
having	O
received	O
the	O
Blow	O
from	O
Luke	O
,	O
he	O
mov	O
'd	O
his	O
right	O
Foot	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
an	O
Offer	O
to	O
strike	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
recovered	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
as	O
he	O
did	O
before	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
Luke	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
the	O
second	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
Sort	O
of	O
a	O
Push	O
at	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
this	O
Push	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
stabb	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
dead	O
Man	O
,	O
dropp	O
'd	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
against	O
his	O
Legs	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
about	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
a	O
Yard	O
from	O
the	O
Deceased	O
.	O
That	O
a	O
Light	O
coming	O
by	O
,	O
he	O
look	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Blood	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
to	O
their	O
own	O
Being	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
pursued	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
.	O
That	O
as	O
Luke	O
Nunny	O
was	O
making	O
of	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
stabb	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
James	O
Young	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Whitechapel	O
about	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
a-Clock	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
talking	O
with	O
a	O
Man	O
near	O
the	O
Kennel	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Man	O
with	O
his	O
Stick-struck	O
Martin	O
Nunny	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
asked	O
him	O
why	O
he	O
struck	O
him	O
?	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
they	O
fell	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
James	O
Young	O
,	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
defended	O
himself	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
beat	O
him	O
very	O
much	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
gotten	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
Man	O
say	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
them	O
run	O
away	O
into	O
an	O
Alley	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
followed	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
an	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
were	O
immediately	O
pursued	O
and	O
taken	O
.	O
He	O
added	O
,	O
That	O
Martin	O
,	O
indeed	O
was	O
very	O
drunk	O
,	O
but	O
Lukes	O
seemed	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
drink	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Tuckwell	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
upon	O
the	O
Watch	O
he	O
heard	O
Murder	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
immediately	O
ran	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
done	O
in	O
four	O
Minutes	O
Time	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
deceased	O
he	O
was	O
quite	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
near	O
his	O
Head	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
which	O
Knife	O
afterwards	O
did	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Knife	O
of	O
Martin	O
Nunny	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
had	O
no	O
Hats	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
into	O
Custody	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
Hats	O
taken	O
up	O
not	O
far	O
from	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
which	O
Hats	O
they	O
afterwards	O
owned	O
were	O
theirs	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
afterwards	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Mother	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
found	O
there	O
a	O
third	O
Brother	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
enquiring	O
concerning	O
his	O
Brother	O
's	O
Knife	O
,	O
he	O
exactly	O
described	O
the	O
Knife	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
showing	O
to	O
him	O
he	O
swore	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
Brother	O
's	O
Knife	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
(	O
Martin	O
Nunny	O
)	O
owned	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
Knife	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
at	O
Yarmouth	O
.	O
He	O
added	O
,	O
That	O
after	O
their	O
Commitment	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
Damn	O
it	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
hanged	O
they	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
either	O
the	O
first	O
or	O
the	O
last	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hamblaton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Watchman	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
coming	O
to	O
Moses	O
and	O
Aaron	O
Alley	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
told	O
there	O
was	O
Murder	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
apprehend	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
Martin	O
's	O
Face	O
was	O
bloody	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
below	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
Luke	O
was	O
run	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
found	O
him	O
leaning	O
upon	O
his	O
Elbow	O
on	O
the	O
Stair-head	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
assaulted	O
him	O
with	O
great	O
Violence	O
.	O
That	O
Martin	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
but	O
Luke	O
not	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
,	O
jun	O
.	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
upon	O
opening	O
the	O
Body	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Wound	O
to	O
have	O
penetrated	O
between	O
the	O
fifth	O
and	O
sixth	O
Ribs	O
,	O
and	O
into	O
the	O
Heart	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Luke	O
Nunny	O
,	O
pleaded	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
one	O
Edward	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
began	O
to	O
quarrel	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
his	O
Brother	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
two	O
Seamen	O
came	O
by	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
What	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
no	O
drunker	O
yet	O
?	O
And	O
follow	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Constable	O
and	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
Time	O
the	O
Accident	O
happened	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
how	O
,	O
And	O
Martin	O
Nunny	O
pleading	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
Luke	O
Nunny	O
guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
but	O
acquitted	O
Martin	O
Nunny	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
the	O
thirteenth	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
being	O
taken	O
upon	O
her	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Michelson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Carn	I-pers
,	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
deficient	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Arthur	B-pers
Dun	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
six	O
Pair	O
of	O
Thread	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
du	I-pers
Meny	I-pers
,	O
the	O
sixth	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
Stockings	O
.	O
A	O
Constable	O
hearing	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
Geneva	O
Shop	O
,	O
were	O
offering	O
the	O
Stockings	O
to	O
Sale	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Stockings	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Frances	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
four	O
Yards	O
of	O
Muslin	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Wrather	I-pers
,	O
the	O
seventeenth	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
view	O
'd	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Muslin	O
,	O
and	O
each	O
bought	O
a	O
Quarter	O
and	O
a	O
Half	O
,	O
he	O
missed	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Muslin	O
of	O
four	O
Yards	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
being	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
he	O
called	O
them	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
taxing	O
them	O
with	O
the	O
Muslin	O
,	O
it	O
dropp	O
'd	O
from	O
under	O
Jane	O
Bird	O
's	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
upon	O
her	O
Shoes	O
.	O
After	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
Jane	O
Bird	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
And	O
acquitted	O
Frances	O
Edwards	O
.	O
Isaak	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Hackney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sir	O
Daniel	B-pers
Dowlin	I-pers
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Usk	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Ulk	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Gay	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Bodice	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Soursby	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Kelly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Carpenters	O
Tools	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Elwinton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
deficient	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Web	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Scarlet	O
Cloak	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
from	O
Katharine	B-pers
Sherwin	I-pers
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
deficient	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Burgess	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Purchase	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Spurs	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
deficient	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Grant	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Elin	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Thimble	O
and	O
30	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cupid	I-pers
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Chandler	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Fitzgerald	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
's	O
Show	O
Glass	O
,	O
with	O
Gold	O
,	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Snuff	O
Boxes	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
40	O
l.	O
from	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Ker	I-pers
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
Mary	B-pers
Chandler	I-pers
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Hitch	I-pers
came	O
to	O
sell	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
Silver	O
Lace	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
after	O
a	O
Man	O
came	O
in	O
(	O
supposed	O
to	O
be	O
Fitzgerald	O
)	O
to	O
ask	O
for	O
Silver	O
Buttons	O
;	O
that	O
while	O
the	O
was	O
talking	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
sending	O
her	O
Son	O
up	O
for	O
the	O
Key	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
abruptly	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Show-Glass	O
was	O
stolen	O
from	O
the	O
Shop	O
Window	O
.	O
Ann	O
Hitch	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
her	O
self	O
did	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
carried	O
off	O
the	O
Glass	O
to	O
an	O
Ale-House	O
,	O
broke	O
the	O
Glass	O
and	O
Frame	O
,	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
the	O
Frame	O
down	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
;	O
sold	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Snuff	O
Boxes	O
for	O
8	O
Ponds	O
,	O
and	O
shar	O
'd	O
the	O
Money	O
amongst	O
them	O
.	O
Mary	O
Chandler	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Proof	O
against	O
Joseph	O
Chandler	O
but	O
that	O
of	O
Ann	O
Hitch	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
and	O
Mary	O
Chandler	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Patrick	B-pers
Clifford	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Harrold	I-pers
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Silver	O
Mugs	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Shutter	O
of	O
a	O
back	O
Parlor	O
was	O
bored	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Bar	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
stolen	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
borrowed	O
a	O
Gimblet	O
about	O
a	O
Week	O
before	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
which	O
he	O
found	O
near	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
where	O
,	O
whoever	O
did	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
came	O
over	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
done	O
it	O
was	O
wet	O
Weather	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
Footsteps	O
in	O
the	O
Dirt	O
.	O
That	O
a	O
Stick	O
was	O
found	O
that	O
Morning	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
affirm	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
several	O
Times	O
seen	O
in	O
Patrick	O
Clifford	O
's	O
Hands	O
.	O
Mrs.Harrold	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
came	O
in	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
drinking	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
maintained	O
him	O
several	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
she	O
left	O
him	O
but	O
one	O
Week	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
to	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
.	O
Joseph	O
Watson	O
was	O
his	O
Companion	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
his	O
reputed	O
Wife	O
goes	O
out	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
does	O
nothing	O
but	O
drink	O
all	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
keeps	O
a	O
disorderly	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
Watson	O
asked	O
him	O
for	O
something	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
spent	O
eight	O
Pence	O
Half	O
Penny	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
Watson	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
What	O
,	O
must	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Booty	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
?	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
carrying	O
them	O
to	O
Prison	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
Clifford	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
wish	O
we	O
had	O
committed	O
the	O
Robbery	O
Yesterday	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
far	O
enough	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
might	O
catch	O
me	O
if	O
they	O
could	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
commited	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
Clifford	O
and	O
another	O
come	O
from	O
the	O
back	O
Yard	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Way	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
when	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Robinson	O
the	O
Beadle	O
gave	O
Clifford	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
keeping	O
the	O
worst	O
House	O
in	O
ten	O
Parishes	O
,	O
in	O
harbouring	O
all	O
manner	O
of	O
ill	O
People	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
out	O
many	O
Children	O
that	O
he	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
no	O
entertain	O
and	O
encourage	O
in	O
ill	O
Practices	O
.	O
Clifford	O
call	O
'd	O
some	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
discharged	O
for	O
being	O
an	O
Irish	O
Man	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
could	O
say	O
nothing	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
way	O
at	O
living	O
since	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Lewis	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
Shadwel	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
eight	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Wheat	O
,	O
value	O
28	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
Sacks	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Earfard	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
.	O
Wright	O
confes	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
Hudson	O
several	O
other	O
Felonies	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
Confessions	O
were	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
However	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
they	O
did	O
when	O
they	O
sign	O
'd	O
their	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
Hudson	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Wright	O
guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Swinburn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Hamstead	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
three	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
27	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Shipway	I-pers
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Spoons	O
were	O
stolen	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
stopped	O
at	O
London	O
when	O
offered	O
to	O
Sale	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Frances	B-pers
Waterhouse	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
printed	O
Linnen	O
,	O
value	O
22	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Risum	I-pers
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
buy	O
Linnen	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Piece	O
being	O
missing	O
,	O
they	O
charged	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
taking	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
creditable	O
People	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Becket	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Burkit	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Guineas	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Tilbury	I-pers
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
His	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
wherein	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Trunk	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
However	O
,	O
he	O
deny	O
'd	O
all	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elisabeth	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Randal	I-pers
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
,	O
not	O
only	O
by	O
the	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
her	O
Landlady	O
,	O
that	O
though	O
she	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
unknown	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
yet	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
leave	O
her	O
Lodging	O
when	O
so	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
abscond	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
design	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
receiving	O
some	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
to	O
have	O
redeemed	O
them	O
again	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Archer	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Enfield	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
9	O
Iron	O
Bars	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s	O
.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
malicious	O
prosecution	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
granted	O
him	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Humphry	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holburn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Curtains	O
,	O
Vallance	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Haydon	I-pers
,	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
Lodgings	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
lain	O
there	O
one	O
Night	O
,	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
for	O
the	O
like	O
Fact	O
,	O
in	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rutkins	I-pers
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
so	O
full	O
to	O
this	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
former	O
Indictment	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dunham	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Pancrass	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Pewter	O
Places	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
.	O
And	O
the	O
second	O
Time	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Cronacre	I-pers
.	O
And	O
the	O
third	O
Time	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Pewter	O
Plate	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Tarrant	I-pers
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
The	O
Facts	O
being	O
all	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Places	O
taken	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
all	O
three	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Duke	B-pers
Burgess	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
100	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Emerson	I-pers
and	I-pers
Company	I-pers
and	O
Company	O
,	O
the	O
6th	O
April	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dale	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
an	O
Assault	O
,	O
committed	O
on	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Infant	O
of	O
eight	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
ravish	O
her	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
Grand	O
Mother	O
had	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Park	B-place
at	I-place
Cranbury	I-place
House	I-place
,	O
where	O
he	O
attempted	O
to	O
force	O
her	O
,	O
had	O
very	O
much	O
injured	O
her	O
,	O
as	O
was	O
deposed	O
by	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Offence	O
,	O
fined	O
him	O
ten	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
sentenced	O
him	O
also	O
to	O
six	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Barry	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Marrying	O
Susannah	B-pers
Holt	I-pers
,	O
while	O
his	O
first	O
Wife	O
Catharine	O
was	O
living	O
.	O
Which	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
Burned	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
48	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Malt	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Body	O
appearing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Hockabout	I-pers
,	O
Gresham	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wats	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Cornelius	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
a	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
having	O
been	O
at	O
Highgate	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
and	O
weary	O
,	O
he	O
sat	O
down	O
on	O
a	O
Bench	O
in	O
Smithfield	B-place
and	O
fell	O
a-sleep	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
waked	O
had	O
lost	O
the	O
Things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
how	O
much	O
.	O
A	O
Drover	O
's	O
Lad	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
seeing	O
Thomas	O
Wats	O
by	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
went	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
knowing	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
loose	O
Person	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
Notice	O
to	O
the	O
Watch	O
.	O
The	O
Watchman	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
hearing	O
by	O
the	O
Drover	O
afterwards	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
by	O
the	O
Drover	O
carried	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
of	O
Resort	O
of	O
ill	O
Persons	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
they	O
found	O
Pipety	O
Popety	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
Name	O
he	O
knew	O
Watson	O
by	O
)	O
hid	O
in	O
a	O
Closet	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Hat	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
Hockabout	O
hid	O
in	O
a	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shoes	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
Mason	O
a	O
Bed	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
Hockabout	O
and	O
Watson	O
each	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
And	O
acquitted	O
Mason	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Taverner	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Marrying	O
a	O
second	O
Wife	O
,	O
his	O
former	O
being	O
alive	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
Burned	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Michael	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Allhallow	B-place
's	I-place
Barkin	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
30	O
Bed	O
Ticks	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Roger	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Confession	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Bail	O
in	O
a	O
Lighter	O
,	O
by	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Hobbs	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Keysell	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
three	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Button	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
to	O
sell	O
some	O
Linnen	O
Aprons	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Handkerchiefs	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Handkerchiefs	O
about	O
their	O
Necks	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
pretended	O
they	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
Woman	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
Plea	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
them	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Sheet	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Testament	O
,	O
value	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Banner	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
an	O
Assault	O
,	O
committed	O
upon	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Burgess	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Lad	O
of	O
15	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
commit	O
the	O
Act	O
of	O
Sodomy	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
fell	O
into	O
Discourse	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
about	O
his	O
Father	O
's	O
Business	O
,	O
and	O
kiss	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Woodstreet	B-place
run	I-place
him	I-place
up	I-place
against	I-place
the	I-place
Gate	I-place
of	I-place
the	I-place
Cross	I-place
Keys	I-place
,	O
and	O
unbuttoned	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
acted	O
several	O
indecent	O
Things	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
him	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
some	O
Ale-House	O
or	O
Tavern	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
consent	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
meet	O
him	O
again	O
another	O
Night	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Night	O
he	O
having	O
informed	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Father	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
Post	O
Office	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
in	O
carrying	O
his	O
Father	O
's	O
Letters	O
every	O
Post	O
Night	O
,	O
at	O
about	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Post-House	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
clapp	O
'd	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
carry	O
his	O
Father	O
's	O
Letters	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
waited	O
for	O
his	O
coming	O
out	O
,	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Poultrey	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Woodstreet	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
former	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
began	O
to	O
renew	O
his	O
former	O
Indecencies	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
But	O
he	O
having	O
before	O
acquainted	O
his	O
Friends	O
,	O
his	O
Father	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
,	O
dogg	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
seiz	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Father	O
of	O
the	O
Lad	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
latter	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
having	O
had	O
Information	O
of	O
the	O
preceeding	O
Attempt	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
Appointment	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
with	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
more	O
,	O
dog	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Son	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
Place	O
mentioned	O
came	O
upon	O
him	O
on	O
a	O
sudden	O
,	O
and	O
apprehended	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
probably	O
a	O
little	O
too	O
soon	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
ever	O
having	O
seen	O
Nicholas	O
Burgess	O
before	O
that	O
Night	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
;	O
and	O
also	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
Indecencies	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
were	O
of	O
Opinion	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
strong	O
enough	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Assault	O
and	O
Intention	O
of	O
committing	O
Sodomy	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
yet	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Obscenities	O
he	O
had	O
sworn	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
the	O
other	O
Evidences	O
had	O
deposed	O
of	O
the	O
Lad	O
's	O
having	O
given	O
Information	O
of	O
the	O
appointed	O
Meeting	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
having	O
apprehended	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Place	O
according	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
seemed	O
,	O
to	O
that	O
Appointment	O
,	O
were	O
strong	O
Circumstances	O
of	O
the	O
Truth	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
required	O
to	O
call	O
Persons	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
called	O
one	O
Person	O
(	O
out	O
of	O
many	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
ready	O
)	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
And	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
what	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
?	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
School	O
Master	O
in	O
Swedeland	O
Court	O
,	O
near	O
East	O
Smithfield	O
.	O
And	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
if	O
any	O
Body	O
did	O
trust	O
their	O
Children	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
He	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
himself	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
others	O
,	O
who	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
,	O
sober	O
Person	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
coming	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Indictment	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Irish	I-pers
,	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Breadth	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
six	O
Inches	O
,	O
the	O
17th	O
Day	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church	O
Yard	O
he	O
overtook	O
Mr.	O
Irish	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
other	O
Gentlemen	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
as	O
they	O
went	O
along	O
Mr.	O
Irish	O
was	O
very	O
rude	O
,	O
shoving	O
and	O
thumping	O
People	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
going	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
(	O
as	O
he	O
suppos	O
'd	O
)	O
Husband	O
,	O
he	O
struck	O
her	O
cross	O
the	O
Buttocks	O
with	O
his	O
Cane	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
heard	O
several	O
people	O
complain	O
of	O
his	O
Rudeness	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
followed	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
over	O
against	O
Mr.	O
Innys	O
's	O
the	O
Bookseller	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Irish	O
threaten	O
to	O
strike	O
the	O
deceased	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
deceased	O
went	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Irish	O
followed	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
returned	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
deceased	O
go	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
Mr.	O
Irish	O
struck	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
several	O
Blows	O
pass	O
'd	O
between	O
them	O
.	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Irish	O
pursued	O
the	O
deceased	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
deceased	O
said	O
,	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Irish	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
before	O
any	O
Blow	O
was	O
given	O
,	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
Matter	O
with	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
?	O
Bear	O
witness	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
meddle	O
with	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
means	O
that	O
he	O
does	O
not	O
go	O
along	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Word	O
,	O
The	O
Man	O
was	O
killed	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
he	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
seize	O
Mr.	O
Irish	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
threaten	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
meddle	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
swear	O
a	O
Robbery	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
naked	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
People	O
apprehended	O
Mr.	O
Irish	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Hubbert	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
Ludgate	B-place
Hill	I-place
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
several	O
People	O
standing	O
in	O
the	O
Path-Way	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
asked	O
,	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
?	O
That	O
after	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
they	O
parted	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
on	O
about	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
Steps	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
upon	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
.	O
That	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
a	O
Coach	O
coming	O
between	O
him	O
and	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
first	O
Blow	O
,	O
but	O
saw	O
several	O
Blows	O
pass	O
afterward	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
Word	O
,	O
The	O
Man	O
is	O
dead	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church	O
Yard	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
some	O
Gentlemen	O
at	O
Blows	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
one	O
drive	O
the	O
other	O
from	O
the	O
Toy	O
Shop	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
deceased	O
retreated	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
People	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
fool	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
make	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
after	O
a	O
Coach	O
had	O
pass	O
'd	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
made	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
several	O
Blows	O
passed	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
drove	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
near	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms	O
Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Irish	O
dropped	O
,	O
he	O
thought	O
,	O
upon	O
his	O
Knees	O
.	O
That	O
when	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
he	O
drove	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
People	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
foul	O
play	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
deceased	O
fell	O
,	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
opened	O
his	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
perceived	O
the	O
Wound	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
to	O
secure	O
Mr.	O
Irish	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Irish	O
asking	O
this	O
Evidence	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
twice	O
?	O
He	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
down	O
but	O
once	O
,	O
but	O
whether	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
,	O
or	O
fallen	O
down	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
follow	O
the	O
deceased	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Inny	O
's	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
several	O
Blows	O
were	O
struck	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
down	O
,	O
he	O
thinks	O
on	O
one	O
or	O
both	O
Knees	O
.	O
That	O
when	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
he	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
deceased	O
's	O
Cane	O
,	O
gave	O
a	O
push	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
dropped	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jeff	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
much	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Dally	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
seeing	O
a	O
Crowd	O
of	O
People	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
deceased	O
say	O
,	O
The	O
Man	O
has	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
quarrel	O
.	O
That	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
got	O
ten	O
or	O
fifteen	O
Yards	O
off	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
by	O
him	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
and	O
run	O
after	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
People	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
fair	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
then	O
the	O
deceased	O
having	O
turned	O
again	O
several	O
Strokes	O
passed	O
with	O
their	O
Canes	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Sword	O
glitter	O
;	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Man	O
that	O
wore	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Wound	O
given	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Forster	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
Innys	O
's	O
Door	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
strike	O
the	O
deceased	O
several	O
Blows	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
People	O
cried	O
to	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
At	O
him	O
again	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
so	O
;	O
and	O
several	O
Blows	O
pass	O
'd	O
between	O
them	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
deceased	O
's	O
Cane	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
People	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
It	O
was	O
foul	O
Play	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
immediately	O
the	O
deceased	O
dropp	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
upon	O
this	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
seize	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
pick	O
his	O
Pocket	O
?	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
charge	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
Bishop	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
passing	O
by	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Deceased	O
,	O
striking	O
with	O
their	O
Canes	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
first	O
Blow	O
he	O
saw	O
given	O
,	O
was	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Irish	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
went	O
over	O
the	O
Canal	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
several	O
more	O
Blows	O
were	O
struck	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
strike	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
say	O
,	O
stand	O
off	O
,	O
I	O
wear	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
know	O
how	O
to	O
use	O
it	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Cane	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
drop	O
'd	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Badger	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
Accidentally	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
a	O
Man	O
was	O
wounded	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Coffee-House	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
the	O
Man	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
searching	O
the	O
Wound	O
,	O
found	O
it	O
had	O
penetrated	O
a	O
Ventricle	O
of	O
the	O
Heart	O
,	O
went	O
obliquely	O
upwards	O
into	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
his	O
Heart	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Irish	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
with	O
a	O
Couple	O
of	O
Friends	O
,	O
at	O
Greenwich	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
along	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church	O
Yard	O
,	O
towards	O
Fleetstreet	O
:	O
passing	O
by	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
jostled	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
holding	O
up	O
his	O
Cane	O
,	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
it	O
down	O
his	O
Throat	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
should	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
well	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
having	O
passed	O
a	O
little	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
Satisfaction	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
assaulted	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
turn	O
to	O
assault	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
knocked	O
down	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
the	O
Booksellers	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
driven	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Mob	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
knock	O
out	O
his	O
Brains	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
Murther	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
take	O
Care	O
,	O
I	O
wear	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
how	O
to	O
use	O
it	O
.	O
Zachariah	B-pers
Burrio	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Allen	O
,	O
being	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church	O
Yard	O
,	O
near	O
Mr.	O
Wilday	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
jostled	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
abusive	O
,	O
holding	O
up	O
his	O
Cane	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
strike	O
Mr.	O
Irish	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
thereupon	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Irish	O
by	O
the	O
Arm	O
,	O
to	O
prevent	O
Mischief	O
.	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Irish	O
was	O
coming	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
assaulted	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
now	O
his	O
Time	O
to	O
assault	O
;	O
that	O
thereupon	O
Mr.	O
Irish	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
meant	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
Satisfaction	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
Mr.	O
Irish	O
over	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
driven	O
over	O
to	O
Innys	O
's	O
:	O
That	O
a	O
Coach	O
coming	O
by	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
parted	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Crowd	O
were	O
driven	O
towards	O
the	O
Kings	O
Arms	O
Tavern	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
Mr.	O
Irish	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
does	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
struck	O
by	O
more	O
Caves	O
than	O
one	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Mob	O
were	O
very	O
averse	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Irish	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
he	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
Retreat	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
retir	O
'd	O
towards	O
Doctors-Commons	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
retreated	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
the	O
Fellow	O
stand	O
off	O
,	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
went	O
toward	O
Mr.	O
Truby	O
's	O
,	O
so	O
get	O
some	O
People	O
to	O
part	O
them	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
given	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Allen	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Irish	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Burrio	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
near	O
the	O
Toy	O
Shop	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church	O
Yard	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
jostled	O
,	O
and	O
damned	O
Mr.	O
Irish	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Burrio	O
defined	O
Mr.	O
Irish	O
not	O
to	O
mind	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
Satisfaction	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
his	O
Cane	O
gave	O
Mr.	O
Irish	O
a	O
Blow	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Blows	O
having	O
been	O
interchanged	O
,	O
a	O
Coach	O
came	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
parted	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
the	O
Fight	O
was	O
renew	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Irish	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
drew	O
his	O
Swords	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Stand	O
off	O
,	O
take	O
Care	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
my	O
Sword	O
Drawn	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
,	O
or	O
falling	O
down	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
beat	O
him	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Deceased	O
fell	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Irish	O
just	O
getting	O
up	O
as	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
falling	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Stokes	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
come	O
up	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Irish	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Irish	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
twice	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Crowd	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
more	O
Sticks	O
used	O
against	O
Mr.	O
Irish	O
than	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
:	O
that	O
near	O
the	O
Kings	O
Arms	O
Tavern	O
the	O
Deceased	O
knock	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Irish	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
struck	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
thought	O
,	O
to	O
keep	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Deceased	O
fell	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Irish	O
was	O
upon	O
one	O
or	O
both	O
Knees	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
them	O
fight	O
with	O
Sticks	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
short	O
Man	O
followed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
struck	O
by	O
two	O
Persons	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
getting	O
up	O
his	O
Wig	O
fell	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
short	O
Man	O
knocked	O
him	O
down	O
again	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Barns	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Innys	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
fighting	O
with	O
Canes	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
towards	O
Truby	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
short	O
Man	O
run	O
to	O
the	O
Tall	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
knocked	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
rising	O
,	O
some	O
Body	O
struck	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
down	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Pick-pocket	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
Mob	O
was	O
all	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
Thieves	O
and	O
Murder	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Sword	O
drawn	O
.	O
That	O
several	O
Blows	O
were	O
struck	O
afterwards	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
defended	O
himself	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
on	O
his	O
Legs	O
.	O
One	O
Surgeon	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
being	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Irish	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
he	O
had	O
several	O
Contusions	O
on	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
Wrist	O
,	O
and	O
Hand	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
opened	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Wound	O
in	O
the	O
Skin	O
was	O
four	O
Inches	O
below	O
the	O
Wound	O
that	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
left	O
Ventricle	O
of	O
the	O
Heart	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
given	O
by	O
some	O
Person	O
below	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
Point	O
go	O
upwards	O
,	O
the	O
Hilt	O
must	O
be	O
downwards	O
.	O
Another	O
Surgeon	O
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Purpose	O
.	O
After	O
a	O
full	O
Hearing	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
Burned	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Day	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Gold	O
and	O
Silver	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
55	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gravestock	I-pers
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
,	O
for	O
defrauding	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
Gravestock	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
handsome	O
Mourning	O
Chariot	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Footman	O
behind	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
a	O
Sort	O
of	O
Lace	O
called	O
Spanish	O
Point	O
,	O
for	O
trimming	O
for	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Clothes	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
being	O
a	O
Sort	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
usually	O
keep	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
made	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
However	O
,	O
he	O
fixed	O
upon	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Goods	O
for	O
present	O
Use	O
,	O
those	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
carried	O
home	O
to	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
in	O
Queen	O
's	O
Square	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Marmaduke	O
Davenport	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
That	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
wanted	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
more	O
,	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
would	O
trim	O
five	O
Liveries	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
then	O
tell	O
the	O
Quantity	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
his	O
Tailor	O
.	O
Whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
again	O
to	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
talking	O
very	O
familiarly	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Hinchley	O
the	O
Mercer	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
on	O
to	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
whither	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
soon	O
after	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
among	O
other	O
Discourse	O
,	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
gold	O
Equipages	O
,	O
and	O
show	O
'd	O
him	O
one	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Present	O
of	O
to	O
a	O
Lady	O
,	O
and	O
opening	O
a	O
Drawer	O
,	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
a	O
Paper	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
Silver	O
Lace	O
,	O
and	O
Silver	O
Shoulder	O
Knots	O
;	O
the	O
Quantities	O
were	O
so	O
large	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Liveries	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
as	O
rich	O
as	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Newcastle	O
's	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
furnish	O
him	O
with	O
these	O
Things	O
and	O
then	O
to	O
bring	O
in	O
his	O
Bill	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
off	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Markham	O
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
fixed	O
upon	O
a	O
handsome	O
gold	O
Equipage	O
for	O
a	O
Lady	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
l.	O
which	O
he	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
.	O
That	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
there	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
drink	O
Tea	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
drinking	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
wanted	O
several	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
gold	O
Watch	O
Chain	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
there	O
a	O
Squirrel	O
with	O
a	O
Silver	O
Chain	O
and	O
Lock	O
,	O
he	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
Gold	O
one	O
;	O
which	O
Things	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
furnished	O
him	O
with	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
paid	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
observing	O
the	O
Collar	O
,	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
one	O
he	O
had	O
about	O
six	O
Months	O
before	O
sold	O
to	O
a	O
Lady	O
.	O
He	O
admiring	O
at	O
that	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
desirous	O
to	O
know	O
something	O
of	O
his	O
Character	O
before	O
he	O
trusted	O
him	O
farther	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Lady	O
,	O
and	O
enquir	O
'd	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
Marmaduke	O
Davenport	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
But	O
the	O
Lady	O
could	O
not	O
recollect	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
any	O
such	O
Person	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
strange	O
,	O
since	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
in	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
the	O
Collar	O
for	O
a	O
Squirrel	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
her	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
describing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Person	O
,	O
she	O
knew	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
his	O
Name	O
was	O
Alexander	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
greatest	O
Bites	O
and	O
Sharpers	O
of	O
the	O
Town	O
.	O
Whereupon	O
he	O
presently	O
got	O
Officers	O
and	O
arrested	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
his	O
gold	O
Equipage	O
again	O
.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Greathead	I-pers
deposed	O
;	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Man	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
good	O
Horses	O
;	O
he	O
show	O
'd	O
him	O
a	O
pair	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
,	O
who	O
liked	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
Price	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
having	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
reasonable	O
enough	O
.	O
Then	O
desir	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
furnish	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
good	O
Coachman	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
left	O
his	O
at	O
his	O
Country-seat	O
;	O
would	O
have	O
a	O
lusty	O
Man	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Coachman	O
's	O
Livery	O
might	O
fit	O
him	O
:	O
He	O
procur	O
'd	O
him	O
a	O
lusty	O
Coachman	O
,	O
on	O
whom	O
his	O
Livery	O
being	O
try	O
'd	O
,	O
was	O
something	O
too	O
little	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Esquire	O
pausing	O
a	O
little	O
said	O
,	O
Well	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
send	O
for	O
my	O
own	O
Coachman	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
country	O
;	O
but	O
his	O
Man	O
Lewis	O
saying	O
they	O
might	O
be	O
let	O
out	O
for	O
a	O
small	O
Matter	O
,	O
he	O
approv	O
'd	O
the	O
Motion	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
procur	O
'd	O
the	O
Chariot	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Coachman	O
and	O
Horses	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
first	O
Day	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
thinking	O
he	O
should	O
guess	O
something	O
of	O
him	O
that	O
Way	O
,	O
enquir	O
'd	O
of	O
the	O
Coachman	O
at	O
Night	O
what	O
Visits	O
he	O
made	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
first	O
to	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Montague	O
's	O
,	O
then	O
to	O
Hannover-Square	O
,	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Law	O
's	O
,	O
then	O
to	O
a	O
Coffee-house	O
in	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Upon	O
which	O
he	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
pretty	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
satisfied	O
.	O
But	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
the	O
Horses	O
about	O
nine	O
Days	O
,	O
he	O
bid	O
the	O
Coachman	O
drive	O
to	O
a	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Red	O
Lion	O
Square	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Tavern	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Mountain	O
,	O
drank	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
told	O
the	O
People	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
Gentlemen	O
appointed	O
to	O
sup	O
there	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
there	O
again	O
presently	O
;	O
and	O
going	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
other	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
leaving	O
his	O
Wine	O
unpaid	O
for	O
,	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Chariot	O
and	O
Horses	O
,	O
which	O
having	O
waited	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Esquire	O
coming	O
,	O
the	O
Coachman	O
brought	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
heard	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
his	O
being	O
apprehended	O
.	O
That	O
soon	O
after	O
the	O
Owner	O
of	O
the	O
Chariot	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
third	O
Time	O
,	O
for	O
defrauding	O
Samuel	B-pers
Scrimpshaw	I-pers
,	O
of	O
72	O
Ells	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
and	O
fine	O
Cambrick	O
,	O
value	O
48	O
l.	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
shop	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Chariot	O
,	O
and	O
Attendants	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
before-mention	O
'd	O
,	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
more	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
paid	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
next	O
Night	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
fourth	O
Time	O
for	O
defrauding	O
George	B-pers
Kendrick	I-pers
of	O
25	O
Pounds	O
of	O
Congo	O
Tea	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Tea	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
26	O
l	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Man	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
Samples	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
brought	O
Orders	O
for	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
Quantity	O
sent	O
of	O
another	O
Sort	O
of	O
Tea	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
Orders	O
that	O
his	O
Steward	O
should	O
pay	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
'Squire	O
having	O
remov	O
'd	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
before	O
he	O
sent	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Tea	O
he	O
spoke	O
for	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
never	O
find	O
the	O
Steward	O
to	O
pay	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
first	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
fifth	O
Time	O
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
three	O
Yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
rich	O
Brocade	O
,	O
value	O
26	O
l.	O
and	O
15	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cherry	O
powder	O
'd	O
Podesay	O
,	O
and	O
15	O
Yards	O
of	O
White	O
Podesay	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
September	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
the	O
sixth	O
Time	O
,	O
for	O
defrauding	O
Mr	O
Hinchliff	O
,	O
and	O
Partner	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
before-mentioned	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
his	O
Chariot	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hinchliffs	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
at	O
Home	O
,	O
he	O
left	O
Word	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Hinchliff	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Marmaduke	O
Davenport	O
,	O
in	O
Queen	O
's	O
Square	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Chariot	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
enquiring	O
of	O
his	O
Landlady	O
,	O
was	O
told	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Yorkshire	O
Gentleman	O
.	O
That	O
being	O
introduced	O
to	O
the	O
Esquire	O
by	O
his	O
Man	O
,	O
after	O
some	O
Discourse	O
of	O
Packs	O
of	O
Dogs	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
insignificant	O
Affairs	O
,	O
the	O
Esquire	O
fell	O
seriously	O
upon	O
the	O
grand	O
Affair	O
,	O
and	O
desire	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
send	O
him	O
such	O
and	O
such	O
rich	O
Silks	O
to	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
see	O
them	O
.	O
But	O
Mr.	O
Hinchliff	O
telling	O
him	O
he	O
might	O
see	O
more	O
Choice	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
he	O
consented	O
to	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
Mr.	O
Hinchliff	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
Chariot	O
;	O
talking	O
by	O
the	O
Way	O
of	O
Sir	O
Marmaduke	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Persons	O
of	O
Consideration	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
be	O
marry	O
'd	O
to	O
a	O
Daughter	O
of	O
Counsellor	O
Ward	O
's	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
furnish	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
should	O
want	O
considerable	O
Quantities	O
of	O
Goods	O
he	O
deals	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
fix	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
home	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
Chariot	O
,	O
having	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
rich	O
Damasks	O
for	O
Bedding	O
,	O
Hangings	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
near	O
1000	O
l.	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Hinchliff	O
telling	O
the	O
Esquire	O
,	O
That	O
Ladies	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
thought	O
the	O
most	O
capable	O
of	O
chusing	O
such	O
Things	O
,	O
be	O
enquir	O
'd	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Lady	O
of	O
his	O
Acquaintance	O
to	O
assist	O
him	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
Yes	O
,	O
the	O
Lady	O
Davenport	O
his	O
Kinswoman	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
the	O
Silks	O
might	O
be	O
sent	O
to	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
get	O
her	O
there	O
to	O
view	O
them	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
he	O
(	O
Mr.	O
Hinchliff	O
)	O
being	O
desirous	O
to	O
have	O
some	O
Satisfaction	O
concerning	O
the	O
Esquire	O
,	O
sent	O
an	O
Excuse	O
for	O
the	O
Delay	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
sent	O
to	O
enquire	O
at	O
Counsellor	O
Ward	O
's	O
;	O
but	O
was	O
inform	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Counsellor	O
had	O
no	O
Daughter	O
going	O
to	O
be	O
married	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
one	O
Daughter	O
had	O
indeed	O
already	O
been	O
married	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Davenport	O
(	O
into	O
whose	O
Acquaintance	O
he	O
afterwards	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
insinuated	O
himself	O
,	O
accidentally	O
meeting	O
him	O
at	O
a	O
Coffee	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
prevailed	O
upon	O
to	O
call	O
him	O
Cousin	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
their	O
Coats	O
of	O
Arms	O
were	O
both	O
the	O
same	O
)	O
.	O
This	O
Account	O
prevented	O
him	O
from	O
sending	O
the	O
other	O
great	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
him	O
about	O
the	O
former	O
Parcel	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
elop	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
could	O
hear	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
at	O
Clapham	O
,	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
robbing	O
the	O
Bristol	O
Mail	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
pleaded	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
steal	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
bought	O
them	O
fairly	O
for	O
his	O
present	O
Occasions	O
,	O
designing	O
honestly	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
done	O
,	O
had	O
they	O
not	O
disappointed	O
him	O
;	O
alledging	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
an	O
Estate	O
of	O
200	O
l.	O
per	O
Annum	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Durham	O
,	O
mortgag	O
'd	O
for	O
1200	O
l.	O
but	O
not	O
proving	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
nor	O
giving	O
any	O
Account	O
of	O
himself	O
,	O
nor	O
willing	O
one	O
Witness	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
believing	O
the	O
Honesty	O
of	O
his	O
Intention	O
in	O
all	O
these	O
Affairs	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
they	O
acquitted	O
him	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
felonious	O
stealing	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
several	O
Indictments	O
,	O
yet	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Misdemeanours	O
,	O
in	O
defrauding	O
all	O
the	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
sentenc	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
pay	O
a	O
Fine	O
of	O
200	O
l.	O
i.e	O
.	O
50	O
l.	O
upon	O
each	O
Indictment	O
,	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
twice	O
,	O
once	O
in	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
,	O
and	O
once	O
on	O
Ludgate	O
Hill	O
;	O
to	O
be	O
imprisoned	O
for	O
two	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
find	O
Security	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
for	O
two	O
Years	O
more	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Trantham	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Trantum	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Folwell	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
54	O
l.	O
of	O
Bologna	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
70	O
l.	O
one	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
Silver	O
Silver	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
one	O
Silver	O
Mug	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Plate	O
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
1721	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
making	O
but	O
a	O
trifling	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Isabel	B-pers
Carr	I-pers
Sarah	B-pers
Salisbury	I-pers
(	O
whose	O
Trial	O
was	O
publish	O
'd	O
at	O
large	O
on	O
Monday	O
last	O
)	O
fin	O
'd	O
a	O
100	O
l.	O
to	O
suffer	O
a	O
Years	O
Imprisonment	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
find	O
Sureties	O
for	O
her	O
Behaviour	O
two	O
Years	O
more	O
.	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
over	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
Three	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Chandler	I-pers
,	O
Richard	O
Trantham	O
,	O
alias	O
Trantum	O
,	O
Luke	B-pers
Nunny	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
Seven	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Irish	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Taverner	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Barry	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Moor	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Swan	I-pers
,	O
Anthony	B-pers
Dunbar	I-pers
.	O
The	O
last	O
four	O
convicted	O
the	O
former	O
Sessions	O
.	O
For	O
Transportation	O
,	O
Twenty	O
Four	O
.	O
Humphry	O
Jones	O
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Glassbrook	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Brick	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hobson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Michael	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Hockabout	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Hobbs	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Keysell	I-pers
,	O
Katherine	O
White	O
,	O
alias	O
Blood	O
,	O
Williams	O
Key	O
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Wilbourn	I-pers
,	O
David	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Arthar	O
Dnn	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Swinburn	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Becket	I-pers
,	O
Isaak	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Usk	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Ulk	O
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Gay	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Grant	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dunham	I-pers
,	O
Duke	O
Burgess	O
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
,	O
Three	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Burgess	I-pers
,	O
Philip	B-pers
Large	I-pers
,	O
Isabel	B-pers
Carr	I-pers
,	O
convicted	O
the	O
former	O
Sessions	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Day	I-pers
,	O
fin	O
'd	O
200	O
l.	O
to	O
stand	O
Twice	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
,	O
to	O
suffer	O
Imprisonment	O
two	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
find	O
Sureties	O
for	O
his	O
Behaviour	O
two	O
Years	O
more	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Salisbury	I-pers
(	O
whose	O
Trial	O
was	O
publish	O
'd	O
at	O
large	O
on	O
Monday	O
last	O
)	O
fin	O
'd	O
a	O
100	O
l.	O
to	O
suffer	O
a	O
Years	O
Imprisonment	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
find	O
Sureties	O
for	O
her	O
Behaviour	O
two	O
Years	O
more	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dale	I-pers
fined	O
ten	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
suffer	O
six	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Chandler	I-pers
pleaded	O
her	O
Belly	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
being	O
impannelled	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
not	O
quick	O
with	O
Child	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
Just	O
published	O
(	O
neatly	O
printed	O
in	O
a	O
Packet	O
Volume	O
)	O
the	O
8th	O
Edition	O
(	O
above	O
12,000	O
of	O
the	O
former	O
Editions	O
having	O
been	O
sold	O
)	O
of	O
ONANIA	O
;	O
or	O
,	O
The	O
heinous	O
Sin	O
of	O
Self-pollution	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
its	O
frightful	O
Consequences	O
,	O
in	O
both	O
Sexes	O
,	O
considered	O
,	O
with	O
Spiritual	O
and	O
Physical	O
Advice	O
to	O
those	O
,	O
who	O
have	O
already	O
injur	O
'd	O
themselves	O
by	O
this	O
abominable	O
Practice	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
are	O
added	O
,	O
divers	O
remarkable	O
Letters	O
from	O
such	O
offenders	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Author	O
,	O
lamenting	O
their	O
Impotencies	O
and	O
Diseases	O
thereby	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
Letters	O
from	O
eminent	O
Divines	O
,	O
in	O
answer	O
to	O
a	O
Case	O
of	O
Conscience	O
relating	O
theseto	O
;	O
as	O
like	O
wise	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
a	O
Lady	O
(	O
very	O
curious	O
)	O
and	O
another	O
from	O
a	O
married	O
Man	O
,	O
concerning	O
the	O
Use	O
and	O
Abuse	O
of	O
the	O
Marriage	O
Bed	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Author	O
's	O
Answers	O
,	O
manifesting	O
(	O
from	O
Scripture	O
)	O
that	O
a	O
married	O
Couple	O
may	O
commit	O
Whoredom	O
between	O
themselves	O
;	O
as	O
also	O
his	O
Answers	O
,	O
as	O
promised	O
in	O
the	O
6th	O
Edition	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Letters	O
of	O
C.	O
T.	O
and	O
Philalethes	O
,	O
urging	O
the	O
Necessity	O
of	O
Self-pollution	O
;	O
and	O
another	O
surprizing	O
Letter	O
from	O
a	O
young	O
married	O
Lady	O
,	O
who	O
by	O
this	O
detectable	O
Practice	O
,	O
become	O
barren	O
and	O
diseased	O
;	O
and	O
two	O
astonishing	O
Cases	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
a	O
Clergyman	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
young	O
Man	O
and	O
a	O
young	O
Woman	O
,	O
who	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
Knowledge	O
,	O
had	O
so	O
abused	O
themselves	O
thereby	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
died	O
;	O
and	O
three	O
curious	O
Casuistical	O
Letters	O
on	O
that	O
Subject	O
,	O
since	O
,	O
one	O
signed	O
Will	O
.	O
Smith	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
N.	O
Pedigogus	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
Answers	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Answer	O
to	O
a	O
Letter	O
,	O
subscribed	O
Dives	O
,	O
concerning	O
his	O
Son	O
's	O
Fornication	O
,	O
and	O
Adultery	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
Impotency	O
,	O
by	O
Self-pollution	O
in	O
Men	O
,	O
and	O
Barreness	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
the	O
strange	O
Effects	O
of	O
that	O
Practice	O
in	O
Women	O
,	O
hardly	O
ever	O
till	O
now	O
taken	O
Notice	O
of	O
;	O
with	O
seasonable	O
Admonitions	O
to	O
the	O
Youth	O
of	O
the	O
Nation	O
(	O
of	O
both	O
Sexes	O
)	O
and	O
those	O
whose	O
Tuition	O
they	O
are	O
under	O
,	O
whether	O
Parents	O
,	O
Guardians	O
,	O
Masters	O
,	O
or	O
Mistresses	O
.	O
A	O
very	O
grave	O
and	O
learned	O
Divine	O
and	O
Physician	O
,	O
having	O
perused	O
this	O
Edition	O
before	O
it	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Press	O
,	O
return	O
'd	O
it	O
with	O
his	O
Opinion	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
these	O
Words	O
,	O
This	O
little	O
Book	O
ought	O
to	O
be	O
read	O
by	O
all	O
Sorts	O
of	O
People	O
,	O
of	O
both	O
Sexes	O
,	O
of	O
what	O
Age	O
,	O
Degree	O
,	O
Profession	O
,	O
or	O
Condition	O
soever	O
,	O
Guilty	O
or	O
not	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Sin	O
declaimed	O
against	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Sold	O
by	O
Thomas	B-pers
Crouch	I-pers
,	O
Bookseller	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bell	O
in	O
Pater	O
Noster-Row	O
,	O
near	O
Cheapside	O
.	O
Price	O
stitch	O
'd	O
Two	O
Shillings	O
.	O
Just	O
published	O
,	O
the	O
Sixth	O
Edition	O
(	O
with	O
many	O
Additions	O
and	O
Amendments	O
)	O
of	O
A	O
Rational	O
and	O
Useful	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Venercal	O
Disease	O
With	O
Observations	O
on	O
the	O
Nature	O
,	O
Symptoms	O
and	O
Cure	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bad	O
Consequences	O
that	O
attend	O
by	O
ill	O
Management	O
;	O
with	O
proper	O
Admonitions	O
;	O
recommended	O
as	O
a	O
Friendly	O
Instruction	O
to	O
all	O
Persons	O
who	O
do	O
,	O
or	O
may	O
,	O
labour	O
under	O
this	O
Misfortune	O
.	O
Also	O
,	O
A	O
short	O
Inquiry	O
into	O
Old	O
Gleens	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Weakness	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Reason	O
why	O
they	O
are	O
so	O
seldom	O
cured	O
:	O
With	O
the	O
Author	O
's	O
Method	O
of	O
Cure	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
are	O
added	O
,	O
Some	O
Hints	O
on	O
the	O
Practical	O
Scheme	O
,	O
the	O
Methods	O
and	O
Medicines	O
therein	O
exposed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
gross	O
Impositions	O
justly	O
detected	O
:	O
With	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
Specifics	O
,	O
the	O
Use	O
and	O
Abuse	O
of	O
the	O
Name	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
it	O
covers	O
Ignorance	O
and	O
a	O
Cheat	O
.	O
By	O
Joseph	B-pers
Cam	I-pers
,	O
M.D	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
G.	O
Strahan	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
W.	O
Mears	O
without	O
Temple-Bar	O
,	O
C.	O
King	O
in	O
Westminister-Hall	O
,	O
T.	O
Norris	O
on	O
