TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice	O
Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
,	O
On	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
30th	O
,	O
and	O
31st	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
and	O
1st	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Ninth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
GERARD	B-pers
CONYERS	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
King	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Ayres	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Page	I-pers
;	O
John	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Deputy-Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
JURORS	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
The	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Portress	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Prat	I-pers
,	O
Brian	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Tudor	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Emmerton	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Bedbury	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Skirret	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Best	I-pers
,	O
Michael	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hickman	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Dunbar	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Combs	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Sloman	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Sheffield	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Craddock	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Shelton	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Stanford	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Washford	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
28	O
Yards	O
of	O
Strip	O
'd	O
Silk	O
Cotton	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
no	O
Body	O
being	O
therein	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Humphrys	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
60	O
Peach	O
,	O
Nectarine	O
;	O
and	O
Plum	O
Trees	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Carpenter	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gun	O
,	O
a	O
watering	O
pot	O
,	O
and	O
Orange	O
Trees	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Wise	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
first	O
Indictment	O
,	O
the	O
Proof	O
being	O
not	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
second	O
Indictment	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
a	O
Watering-pot	O
out	O
of	O
Brumpton	B-place
Park	I-place
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
Burchet	O
,	O
or	O
Burchel	O
,	O
in	O
Rosemary	O
Lane	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
always	O
kept	O
Things	O
a	O
Year	O
before	O
he	O
sold	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Ju-Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Winifred	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Jarvis	B-pers
Wiseman	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Linnen	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lock	O
'd	O
the	O
Street-Door	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
about	O
five	O
a-Clock	O
,	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
found	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
stolen	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
upon	O
her	O
being	O
apprehended	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shift	O
,	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
Second	O
Time	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Olifant	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Pot	O
,	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
going	O
out	O
about	O
nine	O
a-Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
left	O
lock	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
about	O
ten	O
was	O
found	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
gone	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
bought	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
to	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
.	O
But	O
those	O
Persons	O
to	O
whom	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
sold	O
having	O
absconded	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
this	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Gay	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
a	O
Dimity	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
divers	O
Persons	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Blower	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
by	O
her	O
,	O
as	O
an	O
Assistant	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
taking	O
in	O
Linnen	O
to	O
wash	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
out	O
and	O
leaving	O
her	O
there	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
home	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
missing	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
sometime	O
after	O
apprehended	O
,	O
she	O
owned	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
:	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bone	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
black	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Windsor	I-pers
,	O
the	O
First	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Horse	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
Ground	O
the	O
last	O
Day	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
missing	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
that	O
having	O
had	O
Information	O
,	O
that	O
such	O
a	O
Horse	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
,	O
was	O
rapp	O
'd	O
for	O
in	O
Tyburn	O
Road	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
George	O
Inn	O
,	O
in	O
Tyburn	O
Road	O
,	O
and	O
asking	O
the	O
Inn-keeper	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
there	O
was	O
such	O
a	O
Horse	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
being	O
show	O
'd	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
Inn	O
Yard	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
did	O
own	O
he	O
had	O
brought	O
the	O
Horse	O
thither	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
coming	O
that	O
Morning	O
from	O
St.	O
Albans	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
with	O
two	O
Men	O
,	O
and	O
swapp	O
'd	O
away	O
a	O
white	O
Horse	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
three	O
Guineas	O
in	O
exchange	O
.	O
The	O
Inn-keeper	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
white	O
Horse	O
,	O
which	O
stood	O
two	O
Nights	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
about	O
ten	O
Days	O
before	O
,	O
which	O
Horse	O
he	O
judged	O
to	O
be	O
worth	O
about	O
50	O
s.	O
but	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
set	O
a	O
Horse	O
there	O
before	O
two	O
Nights	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
also	O
brought	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Horse	O
to	O
his	O
Inn	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
those	O
two	O
several	O
Times	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Buck	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Wellam	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Barlington	I-pers
,	O
the	O
fifth	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
Friend	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Custody	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
an	O
Officer	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
that	O
she	O
might	O
lie	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
there	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
granted	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
Chamber	O
,	O
where	O
her	O
Acquaintance	O
was	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
Chamber	O
was	O
a	O
Closet	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Hat	O
was	O
;	O
that	O
before	O
Night	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
under	O
a	O
Pretence	O
to	O
fetch	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
the	O
Hat	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
which	O
upon	O
her	O
Apprehension	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
;	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
for	O
two	O
Shillings	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
according	O
to	O
her	O
Evidence	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipp	O
'd	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Pancras	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bedstead	O
,	O
4	O
Bottles	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
4	O
Bottles	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
of	O
Geneva	O
,	O
the	O
tenth	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
he	O
keeping	O
a	O
publick	O
House	O
at	O
Tottenham	B-place
Court	I-place
,	O
and	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
Lodging	O
for	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
inform	O
'd	O
his	O
Liquors	O
were	O
carried	O
there	O
,	O
went	O
and	O
search	O
'd	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
his	O
Bottles	O
with	O
some	O
Liquors	O
in	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
some	O
Persons	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
intrusted	O
with	O
the	O
Liquors	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
could	O
at	O
most	O
be	O
but	O
a	O
Breach	O
of	O
Trust	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Lyon	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Laurence	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Turnover	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
Shilling	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Sparrow	I-pers
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
Meat	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
himself	O
cut	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Justice	O
Martin	O
's	O
about	O
Business	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
had	O
Word	O
brought	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
away	O
privately	O
,	O
and	O
without	O
paying	O
his	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
also	O
Linnen	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Garden	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
siezed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Linnen	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Hester	B-pers
Sparrow	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
She	O
had	O
wash	O
'd	O
the	O
Linnen	O
,	O
and	O
hung	O
it	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
Garden	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
gone	O
away	O
privately	O
,	O
without	O
paying	O
his	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Cole	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Garden	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Things	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
She	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Linnen	O
which	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Cole	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
she	O
washed	O
and	O
hung	O
in	O
the	O
Garden	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
his	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
go	O
away	O
without	O
paying	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
because	O
a	O
Friend	O
going	O
by	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
him	O
drink	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
drinking	O
in	O
another	O
House	O
,	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
the	O
Linnen	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
him	O
pawn	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
the	O
Person	O
from	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
seeing	O
Mr.	O
Cole	O
,	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
put	O
the	O
Things	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Cole	O
siezed	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Barns	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Richard	I-pers
Bourn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Cokes	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Peruke	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Rayner	I-pers
,	O
and	O
also	O
another	O
Peruke	O
,	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Towers	I-pers
,	O
and	O
14	O
Ounces	O
of	O
human	O
Hair	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Rainer	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Nathaniel	O
Rainer	O
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
entertain	O
'd	O
for	O
three	O
Days	O
as	O
a	O
Journey	O
Man	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
having	O
work	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
a	O
Day	O
and	O
a	O
Piece	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
to	O
shave	O
a	O
Customer	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
selling	O
of	O
the	O
Wigs	O
and	O
Hair	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
dispos	O
'd	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
where	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
and	O
the	O
Hair	O
were	O
found	O
accordingly	O
,	O
but	O
pretended	O
,	O
that	O
drinking	O
at	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
he	O
was	O
drinking	O
with	O
,	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Moakes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
13	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
28	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Birch	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Cap	I-pers
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Cap	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
miss	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
.	O
That	O
suspecting	O
him	O
they	O
apprehended	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
Goods	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Danger	O
of	O
being	O
arrested	O
,	O
and	O
only	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
raise	O
present	O
Money	O
,	O
designing	O
to	O
return	O
them	O
in	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Days	O
;	O
but	O
was	O
apprehended	O
before	O
he	O
had	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
of	O
doing	O
so	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Wayley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Savoy	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Alman	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Pen-knife	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Collar-bone	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Length	O
of	O
1	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
6	O
Inches	O
,	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
of	O
which	O
Wound	O
he	O
languish	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
a	O
Second	O
Time	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
.	O
Humphry	B-pers
Hood	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
keeping	O
a	O
Victualling-house	O
in	O
Lukenors	B-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
a-Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
Peter	O
Alman	O
,	O
was	O
brought	O
into	O
his	O
House	O
by	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
thinks	O
because	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
carry	O
him	O
with	O
them	O
their	O
Rounds	O
:	O
And	O
that	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Wayley	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
,	O
something	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Drink	O
.	O
That	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
few	O
Words	O
of	O
Anger	O
pass	O
'd	O
between	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Blockhead	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
to	O
draw	O
some	O
Drink	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
Pistol	O
go	O
off	O
,	O
which	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
had	O
been	O
discharged	O
against	O
the	O
Back	O
of	O
the	O
Chimney	O
.	O
That	O
upon	O
the	O
doing	O
of	O
this	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
did	O
tax	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
being	O
a	O
Highwayman	O
,	O
or	O
Robber	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
desire	O
the	O
Deceased	O
to	O
be	O
easy	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
offence	O
,	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
carried	O
it	O
,	O
being	O
in	O
Danger	O
of	O
being	O
robb	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
discharg	O
'd	O
it	O
that	O
it	O
might	O
do	O
no	O
Mischief	O
;	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Cyder	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
drank	O
together	O
some	O
Time	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
thought	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
good	O
Friends	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
tell	O
the	O
Deceased	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
send	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
a	O
good	O
Account	O
of	O
himself	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
five	O
a-Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
went	O
to	O
parrying	O
with	O
their	O
Canes	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
thrown	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Hat	O
was	O
thrown	O
into	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Cane	O
was	O
fallen	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
began	O
the	O
parrying	O
with	O
their	O
Sticks	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
suppose	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
Order	O
to	O
have	O
siezed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
as	O
a	O
Highwayman	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
following	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
as	O
he	O
retreated	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
stuck	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
led	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Dram	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
about	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
Days	O
after	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
of	O
Mr	O
.	O
Hood	O
was	O
confirmed	O
by	O
Thomas	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
,	O
and	O
that	O
after	O
the	O
firing	O
off	O
the	O
Pistol	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
and	O
Prisoner	O
drank	O
together	O
for	O
about	O
an	O
Hour	O
.	O
That	O
afterwards	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
parry	O
'd	O
with	O
their	O
Sticks	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
was	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
having	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
drew	O
his	O
Penknife	O
,	O
and	O
stabbed	O
the	O
Deceased	O
in	O
the	O
Breast	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
he	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
sieze	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
another	O
laying	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
wherein	O
the	O
Knife	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
apprehended	O
him	O
,	O
being	O
before	O
afraid	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
danger	O
of	O
being	O
kill	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
himself	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
he	O
had	O
several	O
other	O
Penknives	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
He	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
did	O
strike	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
several	O
Times	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
down	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
drawn	O
his	O
Penknife	O
,	O
he	O
bid	O
the	O
Deceased	O
stand	O
off	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
given	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
standing	O
still	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
then	O
advance	O
towards	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
added	O
also	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
hear	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Mr	O
.	O
Hood	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
offer	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
the	O
Deceased	O
would	O
send	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
himself	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Strowd	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
see	O
the	O
Deceased	O
beating	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
great	O
End	O
of	O
his	O
Stick	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
fell	O
against	O
a	O
Cellar	O
Door	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
strike	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
down	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
making	O
at	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
little	O
Push	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
retired	O
.	O
The	O
Surgeon	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
having	O
paid	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Men	O
,	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
,	O
went	O
pretty	O
late	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
Pound	O
of	O
Stakes	O
dress	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
going	O
home	O
late	O
found	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Family	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
being	O
willing	O
to	O
disturb	O
them	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
several	O
Places	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
meeting	O
with	O
a	O
Lodging	O
,	O
did	O
go	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Hood	O
's	O
,	O
as	O
had	O
been	O
before	O
deposed	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Fact	O
it	O
was	O
committed	O
as	O
had	O
been	O
before	O
deposed	O
,	O
with	O
only	O
the	O
Alteration	O
of	O
some	O
Circumstances	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
threatned	O
to	O
knock	O
his	O
Brains	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
knock	O
him	O
down	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Times	O
with	O
the	O
But	O
End	O
of	O
his	O
Stick	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
appear	O
by	O
Evidences	O
he	O
should	O
call	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Pistol	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
one	O
that	O
he	O
put	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
small	O
Time	O
before	O
been	O
sent	O
by	O
his	O
Master	O
with	O
some	O
Goods	O
of	O
Value	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
Place	O
call	O
'd	O
Lee	O
,	O
and	O
feeling	O
something	O
heavy	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
Pistol	O
,	O
he	O
discharg	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
left	O
it	O
should	O
happen	O
to	O
do	O
any	O
Injury	O
.	O
That	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Penknives	O
he	O
had	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
always	O
carry	O
'd	O
two	O
to	O
mend	O
Pens	O
for	O
Writing	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
also	O
another	O
which	O
was	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Sons	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
,	O
which	O
having	O
been	O
broken	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
and	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
new	O
Blade	O
put	O
in	O
.	O
And	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
following	O
Evidences	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Mackintosh	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
engaged	O
with	O
Sticks	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
much	O
beaten	O
by	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
great	O
End	O
of	O
his	O
Stick	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
from	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
press	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Doors	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
knock	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Brains	O
out	O
,	O
or	O
kill	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
a	O
Penknife	O
in	O
a	O
Sheaf	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
let	O
him	O
alone	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
still	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
fell	O
against	O
a	O
Cellar	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
after	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
wounded	O
,	O
he	O
follow	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
Yards	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
beat	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
great	O
End	O
of	O
his	O
Stick	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
cry	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
knock	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Pash	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
struck	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
very	O
violently	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
reel	O
'd	O
from	O
one	O
side	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
retreated	O
from	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drew	O
his	O
Penknife	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
drawn	O
his	O
Penknife	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
keep	O
off	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
'll	O
stick	O
you	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
design	O
to	O
knock	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
several	O
Yards	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
bid	O
him	O
stand	O
off	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
would	O
kill	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
produc	O
'd	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
many	O
Years	O
,	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
a	O
very	O
quiet	O
and	O
peaceable	O
Person	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
of	O
his	O
Masters	O
,	O
with	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
and	O
did	O
at	O
present	O
live	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
an	O
extraordinary	O
Character	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bullen	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Hill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Baskets	O
and	O
27	O
Pair	O
of	O
Soles	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
Pair	O
of	O
Soles	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Ingry	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
asleep	O
in	O
his	O
Boat	O
,	O
near	O
Billinsgate	B-place
,	O
about	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Baskets	O
of	O
Fish	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
another	O
Boy	O
that	O
took	O
the	O
Fish	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
11	O
Pair	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Kneller	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ask	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
as	O
a	O
hired	O
Servant	O
10	O
Days	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
about	O
six	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
without	O
the	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
her	O
Master	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Family	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
missing	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
intelligence	O
of	O
her	O
going	O
to	O
Newbury	O
,	O
he	O
follow	O
'd	O
the	O
Waggon	O
,	O
overtook	O
it	O
about	O
Hounslow	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
secur	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Waggon	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
accordingly	O
;	O
her	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
wherein	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
however	O
,	O
her	O
Defence	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
Child	O
by	O
her	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
these	O
Things	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Newbury	O
to	O
lye	O
in	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Master	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Story	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
learn	O
'd	O
in	O
Newgate	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Aslin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolph	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Mosse	I-pers
,	O
of	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Clifton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
entering	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Trippet	I-pers
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
up	O
three	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
11	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Pike	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Cripplegate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Linnen	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bagley	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
as	O
a	O
Nurse	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
pawn	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
with	O
a	O
felonious	O
intent	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Ferguson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Savoy	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
half	O
Peck	O
Loaves	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Bradley	I-pers
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Bread	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Basket	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Man	O
had	O
set	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
carried	O
Bread	O
into	O
a	O
Tavern	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
Hunger	O
in	O
excuse	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
.	O
Rebecka	B-pers
Brockwell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Bedding	O
,	O
Linnen	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
13	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Humphreys	I-pers
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Lodger	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
she	O
did	O
design	O
to	O
redeem	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
return	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Frizwell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
12	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hayward	I-pers
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
having	O
been	O
inform	O
'd	O
by	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
this	O
Fact	O
,	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
into	O
the	O
Money	O
Box	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
before	O
miss	O
'd	O
Money	O
,	O
was	O
resolved	O
to	O
try	O
an	O
Experiment	O
,	O
therefore	O
he	O
put	O
40	O
s.	O
into	O
the	O
Draw	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
having	O
mark	O
'd	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
to	O
watch	O
him	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
another	O
Person	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
next	O
Night	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Shop	O
was	O
shut	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Quart	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
to	O
be	O
fetch	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
Boy	O
was	O
gone	O
down	O
to	O
draw	O
the	O
Brandy	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Box	O
.	O
Charnock	O
Hayward	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
upon	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
did	O
,	O
through	O
the	O
Banisters	O
of	O
the	O
Stair-Case	O
,	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
Boy	O
was	O
gone	O
down	O
to	O
draw	O
the	O
Brandy	O
,	O
open	O
the	O
Money	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
out	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
on	O
the	O
Stairs	O
did	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
go	O
behind	O
the	O
Counter	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Till	O
,	O
that	O
thereupon	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
immediately	O
and	O
siez	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
12	O
Shillings	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
upon	O
examining	O
the	O
Draw	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
just	O
28	O
Shillings	O
left	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
wanting	O
just	O
the	O
12	O
Shillings	O
that	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
these	O
Shillings	O
so	O
taken	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
were	O
those	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
mark	O
'd	O
on	O
purpose	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
Experiment	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
however	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
too	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Colechurch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Silk	O
Gowns	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
a	O
Pettycoat	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
2	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shift	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edmund	B-pers
Camden	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Edmund	O
Camden	O
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
Mrs.Camden	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
her	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Martha	O
Watson	O
were	O
brought	O
and	O
left	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Body	O
came	O
there	O
from	O
the	O
Time	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
,	O
till	O
they	O
were	O
miss	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
from	O
between	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
till	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
Prison	O
,	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
's	O
Shift	O
on	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
She	O
knew	O
nothing	O
what	O
became	O
of	O
the	O
Silk	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
but	O
as	O
to	O
her	O
Mistress	O
's	O
Shift	O
,	O
she	O
only	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
while	O
she	O
washt	O
her	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
remember	O
to	O
tell	O
her	O
Mistress	O
of	O
it	O
before	O
,	O
by	O
Reason	O
of	O
the	O
Surprise	O
of	O
her	O
being	O
apprehended	O
for	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
She	O
call	O
'd	O
many	O
reputable	O
Persons	O
to	O
her	O
Character	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
an	O
extraordinary	O
good	O
one	O
.	O
Upon	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Minskip	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Convent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Parcels	O
of	O
Linnen	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Brotherton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Box	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
to	O
carry	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Black	B-place
Swan	I-place
Inn	I-place
at	I-place
Holbourn-Bridge	I-place
,	O
to	O
the	O
Golden	O
Ball	O
in	O
York	O
Street	O
,	O
Convent	O
Garden	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
carried	O
them	O
thither	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
a	O
Cook	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
making	O
but	O
a	O
trifling	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Cannon	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
George	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
3	O
s.	O
5	O
d.	O
Halfpenny	O
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Knights-Bridge	B-place
,	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Day	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Cannon	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
Money	O
?	O
That	O
he	O
replied	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
asking	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
again	O
if	O
he	O
thought	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
his	O
Shrimps	O
for	O
nothing	O
?	O
(	O
For	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
selling	O
Shrimps	O
)	O
.	O
That	O
thereupon	O
Cannon	O
struck	O
up	O
his	O
Heels	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Throat	O
,	O
and	O
Williams	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
that	O
thereupon	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
Thieves	O
and	O
Murder	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
coming	O
to	O
his	O
Assistance	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
5	O
d.	O
Halfpenny	O
of	O
his	O
Money	O
was	O
afterwards	O
found	O
near	O
the	O
Brick-Wall	O
Jane	B-pers
Pool	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
heard	O
the	O
Outcry	O
of	O
Thieves	O
and	O
Murder	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Preslove	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
Scuffling	O
in	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
and	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
a	O
Man	O
that	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
strip	O
'd	O
;	O
that	O
coming	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
asking	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
had	O
knocked	O
him	O
down	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
thereupon	O
he	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
and	O
siez	O
'd	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
more	O
Assistance	O
coming	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
afterwards	O
found	O
5	O
d.	O
Halfpeny	O
by	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Silver	O
.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Dennis	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
hearing	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
towards	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
he	O
heard	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
saw	O
Cannon	O
stripp	O
'd	O
,	O
as	O
tho	O
'	O
it	O
were	O
to	O
fight	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
being	O
a	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
Fox	O
at	O
Knight-Bridge	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
there	O
to	O
sell	O
Shrimps	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
he	O
join	O
'd	O
his	O
3	O
Halfpence	O
and	O
drank	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
coming	O
together	O
towards	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
pretty	O
much	O
fuddled	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Discourse	O
among	O
them	O
of	O
listing	O
into	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Service	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Words	O
arising	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
began	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
quarrelsome	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
Cannon	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
thereupon	O
he	O
was	O
pulling	O
off	O
his	O
Cloaths	O
to	O
fight	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
Money	O
they	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
nor	O
had	O
any	O
Intention	O
to	O
rob-him	O
.	O
They	O
both	O
called	O
Persons	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Thornton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
,	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cutter	I-pers
,	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pick	O
'd	O
him	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Wine	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
her	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
she	O
know	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
no	O
matter	O
for	O
that	O
,	O
they	O
could	O
soon	O
be	O
better	O
acquainted	O
;	O
that	O
thereupon	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
such	O
a	O
Churl	O
as	O
to	O
refuse	O
to	O
give	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Wine	O
to	O
a	O
Woman	O
:	O
That	O
there	O
upon	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Crown-Tavern	B-place
near	O
St.	O
Clement	O
s	O
Church	O
and	O
having	O
drank	O
together	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
Upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
something	O
for	O
staying	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
threw	O
down	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
Guinea	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
put	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
that	O
afterwards	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
sitting	O
together	O
,	O
he	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Hand	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
take	O
hold	O
of	O
,	O
she	O
clapped	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
Mouth	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
suppos	O
'd	O
,	O
swallow	O
'd	O
the	O
half	O
Guinea	O
,	O
for	O
searching	O
his	O
Pocket	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denyed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
her	O
have	O
the	O
half	O
Guinea	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Hurst	I-pers
,	O
Bookbinder	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
on	O
5	O
Indictments	O
,	O
for	O
so	O
many	O
Misdemeanours	O
,	O
for	O
defrauding	O
so	O
many	O
Persons	O
of	O
several	O
Quantities	O
of	O
Books	O
,	O
by	O
false	O
Notes	O
,	O
sent	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Names	O
of	O
other	O
Booksellers	O
,	O
as	O
follows	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
For	O
defrauding	O
Mr	B-pers
Goslin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
divers	O
Books	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
false	O
Note	O
sent	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Burt	I-pers
.	O
2	O
.	O
For	O
defrauding	O
Mr.	O
Burt	O
of	O
divers	O
Books	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
false	O
Note	O
sent	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Goslin	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
For	O
defrauding	O
Mr.	B-pers
Mears	I-pers
of	O
divers	O
Books	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
false	O
Note	O
sent	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Innis	I-pers
.	O
4	O
.	O
For	O
defrauding	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wootton	I-pers
of	O
divers	O
Books	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
false	O
Note	O
sent	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Wyat	I-pers
.	O
5	O
.	O
For	O
defrauding	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Hazard	I-pers
of	O
divers	O
Books	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
false	O
Note	O
sent	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Banister	I-pers
.	O
These	O
Notes	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
upon	O
Oath	O
deny	O
'd	O
they	O
ever	O
wrote	O
,	O
or	O
sent	O
such	O
Notes	O
.	O
The	O
Porter	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
employ	O
'd	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
received	O
these	O
Notes	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
deliver	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
Books	O
sent	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
,	O
pursuant	O
to	O
those	O
Notes	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
Facts	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
on	O
all	O
the	O
5	O
Indictments	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Court	O
impos	O
'd	O
a	O
Fine	O
of	O
5	O
l.	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
every	O
Misdemeanour	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Book	O
,	O
called	O
the	O
Compleat	O
Measurer	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
used	O
to	O
work	O
as	O
a	O
Journeyman	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Book	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Work-Shop	O
.	O
The	O
Book	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Custody	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
to	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
;	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Garraway	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
,	I-place
Lothbury	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Robert-Hoe	B-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Salver	O
,	O
Value	O
4	O
l.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
Value	O
6	O
l.	O
2	O
Silver	O
Salts	O
,	O
Value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Plate	O
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Hoe	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
between	O
2	O
and	O
3	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
Watchman	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
his	O
Cellar	O
door	O
was	O
open	O
;	O
that	O
going	O
down	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Plate	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
That	O
thereupon	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wild	O
,	O
and	O
acquainted	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
long	O
after	O
a	O
Message	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
him	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Wild	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
one	O
of	O
those	O
that	O
committed	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
acquaint	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Robbery	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
inquiring	O
of	O
him	O
the	O
manner	O
of	O
the	O
committing	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
the	O
Secret	O
lay	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Family	O
:	O
That	O
however	O
he	O
promising	O
to	O
serve	O
him	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
,	O
his	O
Daughter	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
show	O
him	O
some	O
other	O
Plate	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Arms	O
or	O
Graving	O
that	O
was	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
there	O
a	O
Messenger	O
came	O
from	O
Stephen	B-pers
Gardener	I-pers
,	O
to	O
ask	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
that	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
tell	O
him	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Person	O
would	O
come	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
inform	O
him	O
concerning	O
it	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
his	O
Word	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
safe	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
Voluntary	O
Evidence	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
having	O
given	O
his	O
Word	O
for	O
his	O
Safety	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
an	O
Information	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Persons	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
Nan	O
Gill	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
in	O
Woodstreet	O
Compter	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
had	O
the	O
Place	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
kept	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
cheated	O
him	O
and	O
his	O
Comrades	O
.	O
That	O
upon	O
this	O
be	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
Ann	B-pers
Gill	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
not	O
then	O
a	O
Prisoner	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
only	O
gone	O
thither	O
to	O
see	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
Acquaintance	O
;	O
that	O
knowing	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Dealer	O
in	O
bad	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
her	O
have	O
something	O
that	O
he	O
thought	O
was	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
Money	O
she	O
had	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
if	O
that	O
was	O
all	O
she	O
was	O
safe	O
enough	O
,	O
for	O
hers	O
was	O
good	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
show	O
'd	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
6	O
l.	O
That	O
then	O
he	O
secur	O
'd	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
That	O
Gardiner	O
informing	O
him	O
that	O
Garraway	O
was	O
at	O
Nan	O
Gill	O
's	O
Lodging	O
,	O
having	O
hurt	O
himself	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
lame	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
thither	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
by	O
his	O
Information	O
took	O
Sly	O
in	O
Grubstreet	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fryer	I-pers
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Gardiner	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Jeremiah	O
Garraway	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
rich	O
Unkle	O
that	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
Lothbury	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
interrogated	O
,	O
answer	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
his	O
Wife	O
's	O
Sister	O
's	O
Son	O
)	O
and	O
that	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
taking	O
a	O
Walk	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
they	O
met	O
Nan	O
Gill	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
treat	O
them	O
with	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Drink	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
but	O
Sly	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
two	O
Pots	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Geneva	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
they	O
discoursed	O
of	O
the	O
intended	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
Nan	O
Gill	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Plate	O
there	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
Garraway	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
To	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
about	O
30	O
l.	O
That	O
he	O
this	O
Evidence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
they	O
did	O
get	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
Nan	O
Gill	O
took	O
that	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
That	O
Garraway	O
,	O
Sly	O
,	O
and	O
himself	O
,	O
went	O
together	O
about	O
9	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
Garraway	O
bid	O
them	O
go	O
in	O
and	O
cheapen	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Gold	O
Scales	O
,	O
telling	O
them	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Key	O
that	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
Pin	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Place	O
of	O
a	O
Cellar-door	O
,	O
bidding	O
them	O
take	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
pull	O
it	O
out	O
:	O
That	O
they	O
did	O
go	O
in	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
pull	O
it	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
coming	O
out	O
and	O
telling	O
him	O
so	O
,	O
he	O
swore	O
they	O
were	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
Fools	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
Garraway	O
went	O
in	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
supp	O
'd	O
with	O
his	O
Cousins	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
told	O
them	O
he	O
had	O
pull	O
'd	O
the	O
Key	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Pin	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
all	O
things	O
ready	O
to	O
get	O
in	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
Moorfields	O
,	O
and	O
walk	O
'd	O
about	O
till	O
after	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
again	O
at	O
almost	O
12	O
,	O
but	O
Sly	O
espying	O
a	O
Light	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
they	O
walk	O
'd	O
about	O
till	O
almost	O
one	O
a	O
Clock	O
;	O
and	O
supposing	O
all	O
then	O
to	O
be	O
fast	O
asleep	O
,	O
Sly	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
the	O
Pin	O
,	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Bar	O
and	O
Garraway	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
brought	O
out	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
Tankard	O
and	O
Salver	O
to	O
Sly	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Plate	O
being	O
dispos	O
'd	O
to	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
some	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
gone	O
out	O
at	O
Cripplegate	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
dare	O
to	O
adventure	O
,	O
because	O
of	O
the	O
Watch	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
going	O
to	O
Moorgate	O
,	O
where	O
there	O
was	O
but	O
one	O
Watchman	O
,	O
there	O
Sly	O
went	O
through	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
Garraway	O
and	O
he	O
this	O
Evidence	O
went	O
through	O
into	O
Moorfields	O
,	O
and	O
thence	O
to	O
Nan	O
Gill	O
's	O
where	O
being	O
let	O
in	O
,	O
they	O
set	O
the	O
Plate	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
and	O
Nan	O
Gill	O
poising	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
but	O
light	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
would	O
not	O
fetch	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
she	O
judg	O
'd	O
about	O
7	O
l.	O
s	O
but	O
telling	O
them	O
she	O
would	O
sell	O
it	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
wrong	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
half	O
Peny	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
go	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
saw	O
her	O
no	O
more	O
till	O
she	O
was	O
secured	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
some	O
to	O
their	O
Reportation	O
.	O
Some	O
depos	O
'd	O
they	O
knew	O
Garraway	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
kept	O
a	O
Turner	O
's	O
Shop	O
in	O
Fenchurch-street	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
left	O
off	O
about	O
New-Years-Day	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
thus	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
in	O
stealing	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Alhallows	B-place
Lombardstreet	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
ravishing	O
,	O
and	O
carnally	O
knowing	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Hix	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Mary	O
Hix	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
Journeyman	O
to	O
her	O
Master	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Allen	O
,	O
Confectioner	O
,	O
in	O
Gracechurchstreet	B-place
,	O
came	O
thither	O
the	O
Night	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
a-Clock	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
fell	O
asleep	O
:	O
That	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
the	O
Family	O
were	O
for	O
going	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Journeyman	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
lie	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
refus	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
still	O
sat	O
as	O
tho	O
'	O
asleep	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
Man	O
and	O
Boy	O
were	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
young	O
Woman	O
also	O
that	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
to	O
Bed	O
likewise	O
;	O
but	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
upon	O
her	O
Desire	O
,	O
to	O
bear	O
her	O
Company	O
,	O
she	O
not	O
being	O
willing	O
to	O
be	O
left	O
alone	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
That	O
some	O
Time	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
Garret	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Bed	O
with	O
the	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
did	O
suppose	O
:	O
Upon	O
which	O
they	O
also	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
,	O
the	O
Keys	O
of	O
both	O
their	O
Chamber	O
Doors	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
much	O
surpris	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
not	O
having	O
other	O
Fastening	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
afraid	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
for	O
Fear	O
of	O
some	O
Design	O
.	O
And	O
thinking	O
the	O
Keys	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
away	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
Garret	O
,	O
to	O
ask	O
him	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
who	O
after	O
some	O
Time	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
their	O
Rooms	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
shew	O
them	O
where	O
the	O
Keys	O
were	O
.	O
That	O
being	O
all	O
three	O
enter	O
'd	O
into	O
the	O
young	O
Woman	O
's	O
the	O
Lodger	O
's	O
Room	O
,	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
the	O
Key	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
lock	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
Key	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
siezing	O
on	O
her	O
,	O
threw	O
her	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
violent	O
Manner	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
he	O
threw	O
up	O
her	O
Coats	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
strove	O
,	O
and	O
sav	O
'd	O
herself	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
she	O
could	O
,	O
for	O
Half	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
'till	O
being	O
quite	O
spent	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
resist	O
no	O
longer	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
violent	O
,	O
that	O
notwithstanding	O
all	O
she	O
could	O
do	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
young	O
Woman	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
who	O
also	O
assisted	O
her	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
she	O
could	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
overpower	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
nor	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
call	O
out	O
very	O
loud	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Window-Shutters	O
being	O
nail	O
'd	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
at	O
length	O
force	O
her	O
Body	O
,	O
put	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
into	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
-	O
(	O
which	O
though	O
the	O
Exactness	O
of	O
our	O
Law	O
makes	O
necessary	O
to	O
be	O
express	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
I	O
depend	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Modesty	O
of	O
Female	O
Readers	O
will	O
excuse	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
omit	O
,	O
and	O
leave	O
it	O
to	O
them	O
to	O
supply	O
the	O
Omission	O
)	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
bad	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
scarce	O
turn	O
herself	O
in	O
her	O
Bed	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
young	O
Woman	O
who	O
was	O
there	O
present	O
;	O
who	O
added	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
to	O
her	O
for	O
Help	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
endeavour	O
what	O
she	O
could	O
to	O
prevent	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
do	O
her	O
no	O
Good	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
broken	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Allen	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
Home	O
,	O
perceiving	O
his	O
Maid	O
,	O
or	O
House-keeper	O
,	O
in	O
some	O
Disorder	O
,	O
and	O
crying	O
,	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
gave	O
him	O
an	O
Account	O
how	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
abus	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
she	O
show	O
'd	O
no	O
such	O
Resentment	O
of	O
any	O
such	O
Usage	O
as	O
she	O
show	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
drank	O
Coffee	O
with	O
her	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
said	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
drank	O
Coffee	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
with	O
others	O
of	O
the	O
Family	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
breakfasting	O
some	O
Time	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
an	O
Hour	O
before	O
she	O
would	O
permit	O
him	O
to	O
have	O
any	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
heard	O
this	O
Prosecution	O
was	O
carrying	O
on	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
whether	O
she	O
meant	O
to	O
hang	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
rather	O
marry	O
him	O
than	O
hang	O
him	O
.	O
Upon	O
a	O
full	O
Hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Minshal	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Wilful	O
Perjury	O
,	O
committed	O
in	O
making	O
a	O
false	O
Affidavit	O
.	O
But	O
Proof	O
thereof	O
not	O
being	O
produc	O
'd	O
,	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Linstead	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Hern	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
7	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
for	O
assaulting	O
and	O
robbing	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutors	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
having	O
been	O
at	O
Kensington	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
coming	O
back	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
they	O
were	O
attack	O
'd	O
by	O
two	O
Men	O
with	O
Pistols	O
,	O
on	O
Horseback	O
,	O
between	O
Hide	B-place
Park	I-place
Corner	I-place
,	O
and	O
Pimlico	B-place
,	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
That	O
though	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
swear	O
positively	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
the	O
Men	O
,	O
they	O
then	O
having	O
black	O
Crape	O
over	O
their	O
Faces	O
,	O
yet	O
by	O
their	O
size	O
and	O
Voices	O
they	O
did	O
verily	O
believe	O
they	O
were	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
calling	O
some	O
Evidences	O
to	O
prove	O
their	O
being	O
elsewhere	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
John	O
Turner	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
in	O
cutting	O
the	O
Yard	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Dowdeswell	I-pers
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
Keeping	O
a	O
Coachyard	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
stood	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Coaches	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
at	O
two	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
he	O
pretended	O
he	O
shelter	O
'd	O
himself	O
there	O
for	O
Fear	O
of	O
being	O
arrested	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
appearing	O
but	O
a	O
frivolous	O
Excuse	O
,	O
considering	O
the	O
Time	O
,	O
he	O
pretended	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
it	O
was	O
from	O
an	O
Apprehension	O
of	O
being	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
a	O
Deserter	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
one	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
sentenc	O
'd	O
to	O
suffer	O
Six	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Pancrass	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Chesnut	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stoke	B-place
Newington	I-place
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Black	O
Brown	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Hargrave	I-pers
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
a	O
third	O
Time	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Black	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Ruskin	I-pers
,	O
the	O
same	O
17th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Facts	O
being	O
all	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
all	O
Three	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Tyrrel	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Tarrant	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Tyrrel	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Tarrant	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Hornsey	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Grey	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
Second	O
Time	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bay	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Webster	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Brown	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Horse	O
from	O
Sourby	B-place
,	I-place
beyond	I-place
the	I-place
City	I-place
of	I-place
York	I-place
.	O
That	O
upon	O
this	O
he	O
got	O
Advertisements	O
printed	O
,	O
by	O
Means	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
heard	O
of	O
his	O
Horse	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
towards	O
London	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
an	O
Advertisement	O
at	O
Highgate	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
Means	O
he	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
Highgate	O
,	O
John	O
Tyrrel	O
the	O
Father	O
,	O
riding	O
upon	O
one	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
leading	O
three	O
others	O
ty	O
'd	O
Head	O
to	O
Tail	O
;	O
and	O
also	O
William	O
Tyrrel	O
the	O
Son	O
,	O
riding	O
on	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
leading	O
three	O
others	O
ty	O
'd	O
likewise	O
Head	O
to	O
Tail	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
informing	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
owned	O
the	O
Horse	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Webster	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
having	O
lost	O
his	O
Horse	O
from	O
Carlton	B-pers
Hustwit	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Yorkshire	O
receiv	O
'd	O
information	O
concerning	O
him	O
from	O
Thomas	O
Brown	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Highgate	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
his	O
Horse	O
accordingly	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Tyrrel	I-pers
,	O
pleaded	O
,	O
He	O
had	O
bought	O
these	O
Horses	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
the	O
six	O
others	O
,	O
at	O
Northampton	O
Fair	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
bring	O
any	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
desired	O
his	O
Son	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Tyrrel	I-pers
,	O
might	O
be	O
acquitted	O
of	O
committing	O
the	O
Facts	O
,	O
asserting	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
how	O
the	O
Horses	O
were	O
come	O
by	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
William	B-pers
Tyrrel	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Son	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Father	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
the	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Else	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
14	O
Glass	O
Bottles	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
and	I-pers
Company	I-pers
and	O
Company	O
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
the	O
Bottles	O
were	O
given	O
him	O
by	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
who	O
owned	O
in	O
Court	O
he	O
did	O
allow	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
six	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
what	O
he	O
took	O
more	O
he	O
went	O
beyond	O
his	O
Commission	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Davenport	I-pers
,	O
Bacon	B-pers
Dinn	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Frederick	B-pers
Vicount	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
Heath	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
And	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
other	O
Two	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
the	O
1	O
st	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Watkins	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
being	O
asleep	O
upon	O
a	O
Bench	O
without	O
Doors	O
,	O
her	O
Ring	O
was	O
taken	O
off	O
from	O
her	O
Finger	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Boy	O
had	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
other	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
but	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Plant	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Linnen	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
lodging	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
,	O
took	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
lay	O
sick	O
of	O
Fever	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Whetcomb	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
Convent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
;	O
26	O
Yards	O
of	O
Canvas	O
value	O
44s	O
.	O
and	O
6	O
Yards	O
of	O
Thickset	O
,	O
value	O
8s	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Emanuel	B-pers
Hainey	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4s	O
.	O
10d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Round	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Guineas	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Venge	I-pers
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Christian	B-pers
Beams	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Hasdom	I-pers
:	O
But	O
no	O
Body	O
appearing	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Calamanca	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
20s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Westleak	I-pers
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
There	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
without	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Carmoul	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Pawnbroker	O
's	O
Man	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Recognizance	O
ordered	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bowman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
10	O
Yards	O
of	O
China	O
Stuff	O
,	O
value	O
13s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Hinkley	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4s	O
.	O
10d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Darius	B-pers
Humphreys	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Whitechapel	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Frith	I-pers
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Body	O
appearing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Recognizance	O
,	O
for	O
his	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
was	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
James	B-pers
Hix	I-pers
Ralph	B-pers
Barrow	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Farlow	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hyam	I-pers
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Girdle	O
,	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
13	O
s.	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
Evidence	O
to	O
convict	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hawksworth	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ransum	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Musket	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
right	O
Ear	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
died	O
on	O
the	O
said	O
29th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Holt	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Ransum	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
from	O
Westminster	O
,	O
being	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Strand	B-place
:	O
That	O
coming	O
near	O
the	O
Admiralty	O
Office	O
,	O
a	O
Company	O
of	O
Soldiers	O
were	O
coming	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
Soldier	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
His	O
Rank	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
hold	O
by	O
the	O
Mouth	O
;	O
whereupon	O
she	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
You	O
Fool	O
,	O
what	O
is	O
that	O
for	O
?	O
And	O
heard	O
Mr.	O
Ransum	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
say	O
,	O
You	O
Puppy	O
,	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
meddle	O
with	O
the	O
Girl	O
for	O
?	O
That	O
she	O
made	O
Haste	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
Admiralty	O
Corner	O
;	O
and	O
looking	O
back	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Ransum	O
,	O
The	O
saw	O
him	O
lie	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
weltering	O
in	O
his	O
Blood	O
.	O
But	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
which	O
of	O
the	O
Soldiers	O
,	O
or	O
who	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
wounded	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Cottam	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
living	O
over	O
against	O
the	O
Adminalty	O
Office	O
,	O
saw	O
out	O
at	O
her	O
Window	O
,	O
the	O
Soldiers	O
coming	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Rank	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
a	O
Girl	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
came	O
next	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
push	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
to	O
push	O
him	O
off	O
from	O
the	O
Girl	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
small	O
Blow	O
or	O
two	O
past	O
between	O
the	O
Deceased	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
but	O
who	O
gave	O
the	O
first	O
Blow	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
but	O
thinks	O
they	O
both	O
struck	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
immediately	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Soldier	O
take	O
his	O
Gun	O
off	O
his	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
a	O
Turn	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
did	O
believe	O
with	O
the	O
Firelock	O
End	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
immediately	O
fell	O
:	O
That	O
afterwards	O
the	O
Soldiers	O
all	O
march	O
'd	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
pass	O
'd	O
over	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
flight	O
Kick	O
with	O
the	O
Foot	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
some	O
Body	O
set	O
the	O
Deceased	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
to	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
But	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
that	O
did	O
knock	O
the	O
Deceased	O
down	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
that	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
the	O
Deceased	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Ranks	O
about	O
seven	O
Paces	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
:	O
That	O
taking	O
his	O
Musket	O
off	O
his	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
a	O
Turn	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
the	O
Deceased	O
with	O
the	O
Butt-End	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Rear	O
Ranks	O
marched	O
over	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
hearing	O
his	O
Neighbour	O
Ransum	O
's	O
Wound	O
would	O
prove	O
mortal	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Savoy	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Name	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
asking	O
how	O
he	O
could	O
be	O
so	O
barbarous	O
as	O
to	O
strike	O
the	O
Man	O
with	O
the	O
Butt	O
End	O
of	O
his	O
Musket	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
answered	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
strike	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Butt-End	O
,	O
but	O
with	O
the	O
Barrel	O
.	O
And	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
talking	O
with	O
him	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Provocation	O
given	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
press	O
'd	O
hard	O
upon	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
Rank	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Wipe	O
over	O
his	O
Cheek	O
with	O
his	O
Fingers	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
with	O
the	O
Deceased	O
about	O
twelve	O
a-Clock	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
speechless	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
large	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
Side	O
of	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
three	O
Inches	O
long	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Skull	O
broken	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
Crucial	O
Incision	O
to	O
discharge	O
the	O
Blood	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
got	O
Instruments	O
proper	O
to	O
trepan	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
about	O
two	O
Hours	O
after	O
and	O
the	O
Piece	O
of	O
the	O
Skull	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
was	O
broken	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
found	O
about	O
an	O
Ounce	O
and	O
2	O
Quarter	O
of	O
Blood	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Blood	O
Vessels	O
of	O
the	O
Meninges	O
of	O
the	O
Brain	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
broken	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Pulsation	O
of	O
the	O
Brain	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Man	O
died	O
about	O
Nine	O
a	O
Clock	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
Several	O
Neighbours	O
spoke	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Character	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
humour	O
'd	O
,	O
peaceable	O
,	O
and	O
quiet	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
whose	O
Death	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
lamented	O
by	O
his	O
Neighbours	O
.	O
This	O
being	O
the	O
Substance	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
this	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
jostled	O
him	O
against	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
a	O
Stir	O
is	O
here	O
with	O
King	O
George	O
's	O
Soldiers	O
?	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
stir	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Rank	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
strike	O
the	O
Deceased	O
with	O
the	O
Butt	O
End	O
but	O
the	O
Barrel	O
of	O
his	O
Musket	O
:	O
And	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
following	O
Evidences	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
marching	O
from	O
the	O
Prince	O
's	O
Guard	O
,	O
the	O
Soldier	O
shoving	O
against	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
back	O
Wipe	O
with	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Soldier	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
not	O
with	O
the	O
Butt-End	O
,	O
but	O
with	O
the	O
Barrel	O
of	O
his	O
Gon	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
fell	O
between	O
his	O
Feet	O
;	O
and	O
gave	O
this	O
Reason	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
Muzzle	O
End	O
of	O
his	O
Piece	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
Ram-Rod	O
was	O
broken	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dunning	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
much	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Purpose	O
.	O
The	O
like	O
did	O
also	O
John	O
Andrews	O
;	O
and	O
also	O
High	O
Stevenson	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
some	O
Body	O
jostled	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Back-Wipe	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
knock	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceased	O
down	O
with	O
the	O
Muzzle	O
End	O
of	O
his	O
Musket	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Colonel	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
peaceable	O
,	O
quiet	O
temper	O
'd	O
Fellow	O
,	O
having	O
known	O
him	O
four	O
Years	O
,	O
two	O
Years	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
his	O
Servant	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
upon	O
a	O
full	O
Hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
in	O
taking	O
four	O
Guineas	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
,	O
not	O
to	O
prosecute	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
for	O
a	O
Felony	O
he	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
,	O
in	O
stealing	O
from	O
him	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d	O
.	O
John	O
Mitchel	O
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tutchin	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
former	O
being	O
Father-in-Law	O
to	O
Smith	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
simple	O
Lad	O
,	O
little	O
better	O
than	O
an	O
Idiot	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
committed	O
by	O
Sir	O
Francis	B-pers
Forbes	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
John	O
Smith	O
having	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
robbing	O
him	O
of	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
get	O
his	O
Consent	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
bail	O
'd	O
out	O
.	O
That	O
Thomas	O
Tutchin	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Red	O
Lion	O
,	O
near	O
Cock-Hill	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Spurrel	I-pers
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
leave	O
the	O
Matter	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
treating	O
with	O
Spurrel	O
he	O
insisted	O
upon	O
five	O
Guineas	O
,	O
but	O
after	O
farther	O
Discourse	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
That	O
Smith	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
any	O
Thing	O
in	O
the	O
Matter	O
under	O
four	O
Guineas	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
,	O
John	O
Mitchel	O
,	O
rather	O
than	O
the	O
Boy	O
should	O
lie	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
convicted	O
of	O
a	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
transported	O
,	O
did	O
with	O
much	O
Difficulty	O
get	O
three	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
given	O
his	O
Note	O
for	O
the	O
fourth	O
Guinea	O
:	O
But	O
this	O
not	O
being	O
accepted	O
,	O
his	O
Friend	O
lent	O
him	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
offer	O
'd	O
the	O
four	O
Guineas	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
,	O
but	O
Spurrel	O
said	O
he	O
must	O
not	O
take	O
them	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
offer	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
Spurrel	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
refus	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
They	O
should	O
lay	O
the	O
Money	O
down	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
Spurrel	O
call	O
'd	O
Smith	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
suppos	O
'd	O
,	O
for	O
Smith	O
said	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
Now	O
I	O
am	O
ready	O
;	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
I	O
'll	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
you	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
Boy	O
out	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
him	O
give	O
a	O
Note	O
not	O
to	O
prosecute	O
Thomas	O
Smith	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Occasion	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
now	O
satisfied	O
:	O
And	O
Spurrel	O
said	O
any	O
Bail	O
would	O
do	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
plain	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
by	O
this	O
and	O
other	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
actually	O
take	O
the	O
four	O
Guineas	O
to	O
stifle	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
of	O
Thomas	O
Smith	O
.	O
And	O
two	O
Women	O
,	O
Grace	B-pers
Thornton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
meeting	O
with	O
them	O
at	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
in	O
some	O
Discourse	O
concerning	O
this	O
Affair	O
,	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
like	O
to	O
go	O
hard	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
unless	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
some	O
Persons	O
to	O
swear	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
And	O
told	O
them	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
a	O
Yellow	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
in	O
Consideration	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
represented	O
a	O
poor	O
Man	O
,	O
sentenc	O
'd	O
him	O
only	O
to	O
pay	O
a	O
Fine	O
of	O
25	O
l.	O
and	O
three	O
Month	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
Hannah	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hobson	I-pers
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
over	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
Four	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hawksworth	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Tyrrel	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
Five	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Wayley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Moakes	I-pers
;	O
also	O
William	B-pers
Broughton	I-pers
,	O
David	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Marmaduke	B-pers
Burgess	I-pers
;	O
the	O
three	O
last	O
convicted	O
the	O
preceding	O
Sessions	O
.	O
For	O
Transportation	O
,	O
Twenty	O
One	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Washford	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Humphreys	I-pers
,	O
Winifred	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
Anne	B-pers
Gay	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Lyon	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Barns	I-pers
,	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Garraway	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sly	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bullen	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Kneller	I-pers
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Aslin	I-pers
,	O
Philip	B-pers
Hurst	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Frizwell	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Minskip	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Whetcomb	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Plant	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Hix	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Ralph	B-pers
Barrow	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bowman	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
,	O
Five	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Ferguson	I-pers
,	O
Rebeckah	B-pers
Brockwell	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
Hannah	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hobson	I-pers
;	O
the	O
three	O
last	O
convicted	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
.	O
Fined	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Hurst	I-pers
fined	O
25	O
l.	O
and	O
to	O
be	O
transported	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Clifton	I-pers
fined	O
5	O
l.	O
John	O
Smith	O
fined	O
25	O
l.	O
and	O
to	O
suffer	O
three	O
months	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
And	O
John	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
to	O
suffer	O
six	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
Just	O
publish	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Sixth	O
Edition	O
(	O
with	O
many	O
Additions	O
and	O
Amendments	O
)	O
of	O
A	O
Rational	O
and	O
Useful	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Venereal	O
Disease	O
.	O
With	O
Observations	O
on	O
the	O
Nature	O
,	O
Symptoms	O
and	O
Care	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bad	O
Consequences	O
that	O
attend	O
by	O
ill	O
Management	O
;	O
with	O
proper	O
Admonitions	O
;	O
recommended	O
as	O
a	O
Friendly	O
Instruction	O
to	O
all	O
Persons	O
who	O
do	O
,	O
or	O
may	O
,	O
labour	O
under	O
this	O
Misfortune	O
.	O
Also	O
,	O
A	O
short	O
Inquiry	O
into	O
Old	O
Gleets	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Weaknesses	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Reason	O
why	O
they	O
are	O
so	O
seldom	O
cured	O
:	O
With	O
the	O
Author	O
's	O
Method	O
of	O
Cure	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
are	O
added	O
,	O
Some	O
Hints	O
on	O
the	O
Practical	O
Scheme	O
,	O
the	O
Methods	O
and	O
Medicines	O
therein	O
exposed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
gross	O
Impositions	O
justly	O
detected	O
:	O
With	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
Specificks	O
the	O
Use	O
a	O
nd	O
Abuse	O
of	O
the	O
Name	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
it	O
covers	O
Ignorance	O
and	O
a	O
Cheat	O
.	O
By	O
Joseph	B-pers
Cam	I-pers
,	O
M.D	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
G.	O
Strahan	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
W.	O
Means	O
without	O
Temple-Bar	O
,	O
C.	O
King	O
in	O
Westminster-Hall	O
,	O
T.	O
Norris	O
on	O
London	O
Bridge	O
,	O
J.	O
Baker	O
against	O
Hatton-Garden	O
in	O
Holborn	O
;	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Author	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Golden	O
Ball	O
and	O
Lamp	O
in	O
Bow	O
Church	O
Yard	O
,	O
Cheapside	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
A	O
Water	O
that	O
perfectly	O
cures	O
the	O
Itch	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
Itching	O
,	O
Humour	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
,	O
without	O
Necessary	O
of	O
Purging	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
dangerous	O
Use	O
of	O
Mercury	O
,	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
only	O
is	O
prepared	O
and	O
sold	O
,	O
by	O
A	O
.	O
Downing	O
,	O
Chymist	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
and	O
Ball	O
,	O
in	O
George	O
Court	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
John's-Lane	O
,	O
by	O
Hicks's-Hall	O
,	O
near	O
West-Smithfield	O
.	O
Where	O
also	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
,	O
the	O
best	O
Spirits	O
of	O
Scurvy-Grass	O
,	O
by	O
Wholesale	O
or	O
Retale	O
,	O
at	O
8	O
d.	O
a	O
Bottle	O
.	O
A	O
most	O
effectual	O
Remedy	O
for	O
the	O
violent	O
Pain	O
in	O
the	O
Teeth	O
,	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
Also	O
a	O
those	O
excellent	O
Remedy	O
for	O
the	O
Teeth	O
,	O
and	O
clearing	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
.	O
As	O
Full	O
and	O
Compleat	O
History	O
of	O
the	O
Lives	O
,	O
Robberies	O
,	O
and	O
Murders	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
most	O
notorious	O
High	O
way	O
men	O
that	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
England	O
,	O
Scotland	O
,	O
France	O
and	O
Ireland	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Reign	O
of	O
William	O
the	O
Conqueror	O
,	O
to	O
this	O
present	O
Year	O
1722	O
,	O
beginning	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dun	I-pers
,	O
Robin	B-pers
Hood	I-pers
and	O
Little	O
John	O
,	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Falstaff	I-pers
,	O
Capt	O
.	O
Hind	O
,	O
the	O
Golden	O
Farmer	O
,	O
Nevison	O
,	O
Whitney	O
,	O
and	O
above	O
a	O
Hundred	O
more	O
also	O
giving	O
a	O
more	O
full	O
Account	O
than	O
any	O
yet	O
published	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Robberies	O
committed	O
by	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Child	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
George	B-pers
Sympson	I-pers
,	O
who	O
were	O
all	O
Three	O
executed	O
for	O
Robbing	O
the	O
Bristol	O
Mail	O
;	O
concluding	O
with	O
the	O
Life	O
and	O
Robberies	O
of	O
the	O
famous	O
Cartouche	O
in	O
France	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Robberies	O
and	O
remarkable	O
Actions	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Malkoni	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Carrick	I-pers
,	O
lately	O
executed	O
for	O
robbing	O
William	O
Young	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
in	O
his	O
Chair	O
.	O
The	O
whole	O
being	O
faithfully	O
collected	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
best	O
Histories	O
,	O
Records	O
,	O
Trails	O
,	O
Ordinaries	O
Accounts	O
,	O
and	O
Manuscripts	O
,	O
and	O
written	O
regularly	O
as	O
the	O
Facts	O
were	O
committed	O
.	O
By	O
J.W	O
.	O
The	O
Second	O
Edition	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
bound	O
in	O
Ship	O
,	O
and	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Calf	O
.	O
Where	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
also	O
,	O
The	O
Life	O
and	O
most	O
Surprizing	O
Adventures	O
of	O
Robinson	B-pers
Crusoe	I-pers
,	O
of	O
York	O
,	O
Mariner	O
.	O
The	O
whole	O
Three	O
Volumes	O
done	O
into	O
One	O
,	O
with	O
Cuts	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Both	O
printed	O
for	O
M.	O
Hotham	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Black	O
Boy	O
on	O
London	O
Bridge	O
.	O
