TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice	O
Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
,	O
On	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
21st	O
,	O
and	O
22nd	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Tenth	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
PETER	B-pers
DELME	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Dormier	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Sergeant	O
at	O
Law	O
;	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
JURORS	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
The	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Bartlet	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Stanley	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Gower	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Norris	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Halsey	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Betts	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cotton	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Leg	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Vernon	I-pers
,	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Kiffe	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Dunbar	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Curtis	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Sloman	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Goldwin	I-pers
,	O
Mathew	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Neal	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Brinne	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Craddock	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Hook	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Farmer	I-pers
,	O
Archibald	B-pers
Vaunce	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Britton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pancras	I-place
Soaper	I-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
under	O
a	O
Pretence	O
to	O
buy	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
pretended	O
to	O
want	O
divers	O
Sorts	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
show	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
coming	O
in	O
under	O
Pretence	O
to	O
offer	O
Thread-stockings	O
to	O
Sale	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
suppos	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Contrivance	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
favourable	O
Opportunity	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
the	O
Shop-keeper	O
was	O
busi	O
'd	O
in	O
talking	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
privately	O
convey	O
'd	O
2	O
Pair	O
,	O
one	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
into	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
bidding	O
a	O
very	O
low	O
Rate	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Stockings	O
being	O
miss	O
'd	O
,	O
was	O
followed	O
,	O
and	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Defence	O
pleaded	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
think	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
paid	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
But	O
this	O
Presence	O
not	O
availing	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
a	O
Lodging	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
one	O
Morning	O
to	O
get	O
into	O
the	O
Landlady	O
's	O
Room	O
,	O
open	O
a	O
Drawer	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
out	O
two	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
afterwards	O
went	O
away	O
from	O
his	O
Lodging	O
,	O
nor	O
return	O
'd	O
any	O
more	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
at	O
last	O
apprehended	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
Circumstances	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
which	O
render	O
'd	O
the	O
Matter	O
to	O
plain	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bonner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Helen	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Alexander	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Katherine	B-pers
Gascoign	I-pers
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
Abraham	O
Alexander	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Gascoign	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
hung	O
his	O
Coat	O
up	O
in	O
his	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Gown	O
over	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
Night	O
coming	O
home	O
he	O
found	O
his	O
Coat	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
enquiring	O
for	O
it	O
of	O
his	O
Landlady	O
,	O
the	O
suspecting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
went	O
and	O
search	O
'd	O
his	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
there	O
found	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Gascoign	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
missing	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
admir	O
'd	O
what	O
should	O
become	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
before	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
she	O
for	O
some	O
Reasons	O
Suspected	O
him	O
to	O
have	O
taken	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
one	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
Lodging	O
,	O
found	O
it	O
lying	O
on	O
his	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Wastcoat	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
Person	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
finding	O
the	O
Coat	O
,	O
as	O
has	O
been	O
before	O
related	O
;	O
and	O
both	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
own	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
put	O
up	O
the	O
Sash-Window	O
,	O
got	O
in	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Room	O
unperceiv	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
away	O
the	O
Coat	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
nothing	O
material	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Luke	B-pers
Tench	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Lines	I-pers
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Apprentice	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
by	O
Trade	O
a	O
Brazier	O
,	O
and	O
though	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Time	O
by	O
some	O
Years	O
,	O
had	O
married	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
lodge	O
with	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
but	O
came	O
there	O
to	O
work	O
a	O
Days	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
take	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
of	O
taking	O
,	O
from	O
Time	O
to	O
Time	O
,	O
divers	O
small	O
Parcels	O
of	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
working	O
Tools	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Curtis	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Friend	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
James	I-pers
Grundy	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Johanna	B-pers
Grundy	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mildred	I-place
's	I-place
Poultry	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
first	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Fluellin	B-pers
Aspley	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tea-Pot	O
,	O
Value	O
9	O
l.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Plate	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
Value	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
Wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Latter	O
for	O
receiving	O
it	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
Friday	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Servants	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
House	O
had	O
been	O
broken	O
open	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
coming	O
down	O
,	O
found	O
that	O
the	O
House	O
had	O
been	O
entred	O
at	O
a	O
Window	O
which	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Necessary	O
House	O
that	O
look	O
'd	O
into	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
's	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
being	O
an	O
Iron	O
Bar	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
measured	O
the	O
Distance	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
believe	O
it	O
must	O
have	O
been	O
entred	O
by	O
a	O
Boy	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
but	O
8	O
Inches	O
Distance	O
between	O
the	O
Bar	O
and	O
the	O
Frame	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
his	O
Servant	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Family	O
in	O
general	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
that	O
Night	O
between	O
a	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
made	O
all	O
fast	O
before	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Plate	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
was	O
then	O
standing	O
on	O
the	O
Side-board	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
she	O
rising	O
the	O
First	O
,	O
was	O
inform	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
that	O
had	O
rung	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
suspected	O
the	O
House	O
had	O
been	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
by	O
Reason	O
of	O
what	O
there	O
was	O
perceived	O
by	O
the	O
Window	O
before	O
mentioned	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Shellow	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Peter	O
Curtis	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
lend	O
him	O
three	O
Guineas	O
on	O
some	O
Clothes	O
that	O
he	O
brought	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
silver	O
Ladle	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
an	O
unhappy	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
wanted	O
to	O
take	O
out	O
some	O
Goods	O
that	O
had	O
before	O
been	O
pawned	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
were	O
his	O
Mistresses	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
that	O
thereupon	O
he	O
did	O
lend	O
him	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
redeem	O
the	O
Womans	O
Clothes	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
soon	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
have	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
on	O
the	O
Clothes	O
again	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
that	O
that	O
Money	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
before	O
did	O
not	O
answer	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Occasions	O
.	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
April	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
again	O
with	O
some	O
other	O
Plate	O
,	O
to	O
borrow	O
2	O
Guineas	O
more	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
having	O
seen	O
an	O
Advertisement	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
given	O
out	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
must	O
give	O
him	O
Satisfaction	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
and	O
who	O
his	O
Master	O
was	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
must	O
secure	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
so	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
begg	O
'd	O
very	O
heartily	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
his	O
Liberty	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
him	O
ample	O
Satisfaction	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
could	O
by	O
no	O
means	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
followed	O
after	O
could	O
best	O
be	O
declared	O
by	O
the	O
next	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Winnet	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Pawn-broker	O
had	O
stopp	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
;	O
and	O
went	O
and	O
search	O
'd	O
the	O
Lodging	O
of	O
Peter	O
Curtis	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Johanna	O
Grundy	O
's	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
find	O
nothing	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
again	O
,	O
when	O
Curtis	O
was	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
better	O
for	O
her	O
to	O
discover	O
what	O
she	O
knew	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Plate	O
,	O
whereas	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
perhaps	O
she	O
and	O
her	O
Son	O
might	O
come	O
to	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
still	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
own	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
That	O
soon	O
after	O
she	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
said	O
had	O
a	O
Dream	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
had	O
put	O
her	O
into	O
a	O
great	O
Hurry	O
and	O
Confusion	O
;	O
she	O
having	O
dreamt	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
muddling	O
among	O
Dirt	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Plate	O
,	O
among	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
Coffee-Pot	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Things	O
,	O
such	O
as	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
lost	O
;	O
pretending	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
glad	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
likely	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Providence	O
of	O
God	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
Instrumental	O
in	O
helping	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
his	O
Goods	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
search	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
not	O
giving	O
much	O
heed	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
till	O
she	O
pretended	O
the	O
Dream	O
was	O
repeated	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
urgent	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
did	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
her	O
Cellar	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
Corner	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Plate	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Coffee-Pot	O
uppermost	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Basket	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Johanna	O
Grundy	O
's	O
.	O
And	O
it	O
did	O
appear	O
that	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
hidden	O
in	O
the	O
Ground	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Ground	O
had	O
been	O
digged	O
up	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
he	O
afterwards	O
went	O
to	O
Curtis	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lifted	O
the	O
Boy	O
,	O
Thomas	O
James	O
Grundy	O
's	O
over	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
put	O
him	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Street	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
himself	O
and	O
Joanna	O
Grundy	O
's	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
carried	O
off	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
desired	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Grundy	O
's	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
last	O
own	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
:	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
not	O
sufficient	O
Proof	O
against	O
Johanna	O
Grundy	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
privy	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Boy	O
Thomas	O
James	O
Grundy	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
Curtis	O
had	O
said	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
not	O
Evidence	O
in	O
Law	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
likewise	O
,	O
but	O
Curtis	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
,	O
Value	O
35	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Douling	I-pers
,	O
April	O
the	O
7th	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Lydia	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
of	O
Allhallow	B-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Wall	I-place
,	O
were	O
,	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cotton	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
Dicks	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Lightfoot	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
in	O
to	O
wash	O
and	O
starch	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Lightfoot	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Lydia	O
Edwards	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
.	O
Two	O
Evidences	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Edward	O
Edwards	O
declared	O
that	O
his	O
Mother	O
,	O
Lydia	O
Edwards	O
,	O
had	O
put	O
him	O
Edward	O
Edwards	O
,	O
her	O
Son	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
flung	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
let	O
him	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Edward	O
Edwards	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
declared	O
this	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
If	O
he	O
did	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
Gallows	O
,	O
his	O
Mother	O
had	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
Edward	O
Edwards	O
gave	O
an	O
Account	O
by	O
whom	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
pawn	O
'd	O
.	O
But	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
clear	O
his	O
Mother	O
,	O
as	O
knowing	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
:	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
20	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Parkinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Goodman	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
divers	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
before	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Window	O
had	O
been	O
opened	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
10	O
or	O
11	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
20	O
Guineas	O
.	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	O
Goodman	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
,	O
Value	O
25	O
s.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
after	O
his	O
Apprehension	O
,	O
did	O
confess	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
over	O
two	O
Walls	O
,	O
and	O
making	O
Use	O
of	O
a	O
Ladder	O
that	O
belonged	O
to	O
a	O
neighbouring	O
Bricklayer	O
;	O
he	O
and	O
another	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
cutting	O
the	O
Glass	O
with	O
a	O
Diamond	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
what	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
having	O
apprehended	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Coat	O
on	O
his	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Papers	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
so	O
Guineas	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
ill	O
used	O
that	O
they	O
gave	O
him	O
but	O
a	O
Guinea	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
stood	O
by	O
,	O
while	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
in	O
himself	O
:	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
Robbery	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
himself	O
,	O
but	O
two	O
others	O
did	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Clothes	O
that	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
privy	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
's	I-place
Queen-Hith	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
50	O
Pound	O
of	O
Wool	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hussey	I-pers
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Cresse	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
a	O
Person	O
coming	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
telling	O
him	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
Siezers	O
upon	O
Bull	B-place
Wharf	I-place
:	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pulling	O
Wool	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Sacks	O
of	O
Wool	O
that	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hussey	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
stuffing	O
it	O
into	O
two	O
torn	O
Sacks	O
,	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
Ho	O
!	O
Who	O
is	O
there	O
?	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
brustling	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
Pontius	O
Pilate	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
push	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
but	O
another	O
Person	O
coming	O
up	O
to	O
his	O
Assistance	O
,	O
he	O
apprehended	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Cooper	O
's	O
Adze	O
behind	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Netherwood	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
perceived	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
putting	O
Wool	O
into	O
a	O
Sack	O
,	O
upon	O
Bull	O
Wharf	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
and	O
acquainted	O
Mr.	O
Cresse	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
apprehended	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
or	O
his	O
having	O
meddled	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Hussey	O
's	O
Wool	O
,	O
though	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
Wharf	O
,	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
no	O
Body	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Luke	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lomas	I-pers
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Coat	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Waggon	O
on	O
the	O
over	O
Night	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Castle	B-place
and	I-place
Faulcon	I-place
in	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
Street	I-place
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Signer	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sell	O
it	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Waggoner	O
at	O
the	O
Ball	O
Head	O
Inn	O
,	O
at	O
Snow	O
Hill	O
,	O
for	O
8	O
s.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Swan	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
acknowledged	O
to	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
stolen	O
the	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Constable	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
upon	O
his	O
being	O
apprehended	O
he	O
did	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
also	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
lye	O
in	O
the	O
Waggon	O
all	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
on	O
the	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
went	O
away	O
and	O
forgot	O
to	O
pull	O
it	O
off	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
,	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Charles	I-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Moulton	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Infant	O
of	O
five	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
by	O
pushing	O
her	O
under	O
the	O
Wheel	O
of	O
a	O
Dray	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquest	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
had	O
been	O
Fighting	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
parted	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
sitting	O
on	O
a	O
Bench	O
at	O
her	O
own	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
stood	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
at	O
this	O
Evidence	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
disputing	O
about	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
their	O
Quarrel	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
being	O
standing	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Dray	O
coming	O
by	O
,	O
she	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Child	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
of	O
the	O
Dray	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
gave	O
the	O
Child	O
a	O
Push	O
with	O
both	O
her	O
Hands	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Dray-Horse	O
,	O
was	O
pass	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Child	O
fell	O
within	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
Yard	O
before	O
the	O
Wheel	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
ran	O
over	O
the	O
Head	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Dray-Man	O
could	O
stop	O
the	O
Dray	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Cartwright	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Alcock	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
very	O
same	O
Purpose	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
could	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
say	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
any	O
Malice	O
against	O
the	O
Child	O
or	O
its	O
Mother	O
,	O
she	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
Supposed	O
,	O
not	O
knowing	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
her	O
self	O
own	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
.	O
There	O
not	O
appearing	O
Malice	O
prepense	O
in	O
the	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
5	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
The	O
Property	O
of	O
Clement	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
brought	O
the	O
Brandy	O
from	O
the	O
Northward	O
on	O
Board	O
the	O
Ship	O
called	O
the	O
Royal	O
Launch	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Father	O
was	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
informed	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Ship	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Brandy	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
asking	O
why	O
he	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
two	O
Bottles	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
hold	O
his	O
Tongue	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
and	O
to	O
confront	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
James	O
Johnson	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
-	O
Thompson	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
14	O
s.	O
to	O
swear	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Brandy	O
;	O
and	O
also	O
James	B-pers
Douglas	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
James	O
Johnson	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
Clement	O
Roberts	O
was	O
a	O
Rogue	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
14	O
s.	O
to	O
buy	O
Brandy	O
the	O
next	O
Voyage	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
swear	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Brandy	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
great	O
Number	O
of	O
reputable	O
People	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
an	O
extraordinary	O
Character	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
seeming	O
to	O
be	O
malicious	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
black	O
Horse	O
,	O
Value	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Jenkinson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
set	O
his	O
Horse	O
up	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Stables	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Horton	I-pers
:	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Redding	O
Fair	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
the	O
Horse	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Search	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Horse	O
in	O
the	O
Custody	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Woolley	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
offer	O
'd	O
him	O
the	O
Horse	O
in	O
Sale	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Horse	O
publickly	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
of	O
one	O
Price	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
now	O
find	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Monk	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
-	O
Price	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
his	O
Master	O
would	O
buy	O
such	O
a	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
Partner	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
Thames-Street	O
,	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Redding	O
,	O
left	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
that	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
follow	O
him	O
to	O
Redding	O
,	O
to	O
buy	O
Horses	O
,	O
he	O
himself	O
finding	O
Skill	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
Money	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
acquainted	O
his	O
Master	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Villars	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Farrier	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Horse	O
having	O
been	O
offered	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
buy	O
him	O
without	O
his	O
Advice	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
bought	O
him	O
he	O
must	O
expect	O
to	O
buy	O
nothing	O
but	O
a	O
blind	O
Horse	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
as	O
'	O
k	O
12	O
l.	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
bid	O
him	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
afterwards	O
6	O
l.	O
and	O
-	O
Price	O
saying	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
make	O
it	O
Guineas	O
,	O
he	O
thinking	O
that	O
that	O
might	O
probably	O
be	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
the	O
Horse	O
between	O
Man	O
and	O
Man	O
,	O
advised	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
it	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
Reputation	O
,	O
a	O
Keeper	O
of	O
Hackney	O
Coaches	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
bought	O
the	O
Horse	O
publickly	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
granted	O
him	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
his	O
Indictment	O
.	O
William	B-pers
alias	I-pers
Richard	I-pers
Hudson	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Thickhead	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
together	O
with	O
Henry	B-pers
Salter	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Yeoman	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night	O
Time	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
before	O
last	O
Christmas	O
was	O
Twelve-month	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
20	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
Shop	O
was	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Shoes	O
stolen	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
who	O
stole	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
next	O
Evidence	O
sent	O
to	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
an	O
Information	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Quin	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
Henry	O
Salter	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
steal	O
45	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
he	O
either	O
knew	O
where	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
was	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
ever	O
seen	O
Edward	O
Quin	O
before	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
now	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
one	O
Person	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
Mother	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
she	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
brought	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
always	O
been	O
an	O
honest	O
industrious	O
Lad	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
about	O
two	O
Years	O
since	O
led	O
away	O
by	O
ill	O
Company	O
,	O
who	O
would	O
call	O
him	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
let	O
him	O
be	O
at	O
rest	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
desire	O
his	O
Liberty	O
,	O
but	O
begg	O
'd	O
the	O
Court	O
to	O
consider	O
his	O
Youth	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
spare	O
his	O
Life	O
;	O
but	O
to	O
grant	O
him	O
Transportation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Katherine	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Ashley	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
the	O
Savoy	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Headclothes	O
,	O
of	O
Leonora	B-pers
Bodin	I-pers
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
other	O
Persons	O
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Things	O
were	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Trunk	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
Evidence	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Marrying	O
a	O
second	O
Wife	O
,	O
while	O
his	O
first	O
was	O
alive	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
White	B-place
Chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Iron	O
Bolts	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Iron	O
Crow	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Baxendine	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Waggoner	O
's	O
Man	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
received	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
Watford	O
,	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
a	O
Stable	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Prisoner	O
were	O
both	O
gone	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Brian	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
at	O
the	O
Cock	O
in	O
Old-street	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
something	O
to	O
eat	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
eat	O
,	O
he	O
left	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
eat	O
something	O
and	O
come	O
again	O
,	O
leaving	O
the	O
Goods	O
there	O
;	O
but	O
never	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
about	O
6	O
Weeks	O
after	O
,	O
the	O
Carrier	O
and	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
Produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
two	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Zachariah	B-pers
Polock	I-pers
.	O
But	O
no	O
Body	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Court	O
ordered	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Recognizance	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Starling	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Peter	I-place
le	I-place
Poor	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ambrose	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
as	O
a	O
Washer-woman	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Spoon	O
was	O
missing	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
apprehended	O
offering	O
,	O
the	O
Spoon	O
to	O
Sale	O
,	O
being	O
suspected	O
not	O
to	O
have	O
come	O
honestly	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
The	O
Spoon	O
was	O
given	O
to	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Maid	O
,	O
with	O
broken	O
Victuals	O
.	O
But	O
this	O
thing	O
contradicted	O
by	O
the	O
Maid	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Sharloe	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
drinking	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
drink	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
consenting	O
to	O
,	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
a	O
publick	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
having	O
drank	O
he	O
fell	O
a-sleep	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
awak	O
'd	O
found	O
his	O
Pocket	O
had	O
been	O
pick	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
ow	O
'd	O
her	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
promised	O
her	O
another	O
for	O
a	O
particular	O
Service	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
him	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Burgess	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
5	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
and	O
14	O
Silver	O
Forks	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Gustavus	I-pers
Spar	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Charles	O
Gustavus	O
Spar	O
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
Butler	O
to	O
Baron	O
Spar	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
entertain	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Baron	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
Tutor	O
,	O
to	O
teach	O
the	O
Baron	O
's	O
Valet	O
de	O
Chambre	O
the	O
French	O
Tongue	O
;	O
that	O
after	O
Dinner	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
the	O
Plate	O
was	O
carried	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
to	O
be	O
clean	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
only	O
Person	O
,	O
except	O
the	O
Servant	O
Maids	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Kichen	O
till	O
the	O
Plate	O
was	O
missing	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
again	O
on	O
the	O
Morrow	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
came	O
again	O
any	O
more	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Lamp	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
borrowed	O
Money	O
on	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Spoons	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
lost	O
Money	O
at	O
Play	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
afterwards	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
borrow	O
more	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
that	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
before	O
did	O
not	O
answer	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Occasions	O
;	O
that	O
a	O
considerable	O
Time	O
afterwards	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
borrowed	O
more	O
Money	O
on	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Forks	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
having	O
seen	O
an	O
Advertisement	O
concerning	O
the	O
Baron	O
's	O
Forks	O
and	O
Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
perceiving	O
the	O
Marks	O
,	O
which	O
as	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
was	O
the	O
Baron	O
's	O
Coat	O
of	O
Arms	O
,	O
very	O
artificially	O
filed	O
out	O
;	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
stopp	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
thereupon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
entreated	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
undone	O
if	O
he	O
stopp	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
his	O
Liberty	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
the	O
Plate	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
telling	O
him	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
do	O
that	O
,	O
sent	O
for	O
an	O
Officer	O
,	O
secur	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
Word	O
to	O
the	O
Baron	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Confession	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
he	O
deny	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Winter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Wooden	O
Box	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
Penny	O
,	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Upstall	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
using	O
to	O
frequent	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
stolen	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Daughter	O
's	O
Chamber	O
,	O
they	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
informed	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
seen	O
to	O
be	O
fuller	O
of	O
Money	O
than	O
usual	O
,	O
that	O
having	O
apprehended	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Box	O
and	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
a	O
Place	O
near	O
to	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sat	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Rumsey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
an	O
Handkerchief	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Doidge	I-pers
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Dunbar	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Rainer	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3d	O
.	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
Pawning	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
pleaded	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
with	O
a	O
felonious	O
Intent	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
design	O
to	O
redeem	O
them	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
return	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
but	O
considering	O
her	O
Poverty	O
,	O
desired	O
the	O
Court	O
to	O
favour	O
her	O
so	O
far	O
as	O
to	O
change	O
her	O
Transportation	O
into	O
Whipping	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
granted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Katherine	B-pers
Marriot	I-pers
,	O
the	O
:	O
16th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Fire	O
in	O
Wild	B-place
Street	I-place
,	O
and	O
the	O
Spoons	O
being	O
lost	O
in	O
the	O
Confusion	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
apprehended	O
offering	O
them	O
to	O
sale	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
assisted	O
at	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
found	O
them	O
taking	O
up	O
a	O
Floor	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
for	O
his	O
Pains	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
not	O
thinking	O
it	O
meet	O
,	O
if	O
what	O
he	O
alledg	O
'd	O
was	O
true	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
thus	O
be	O
his	O
own	O
Pay	O
Master	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Susanna	B-pers
Walley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White-chapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Ludlam	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
.	O
There	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stole	O
the	O
Shoes	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Todd	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
silver	O
Lace	O
,	O
and	O
silver	O
Thread	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Tailor	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Lace	O
Weaver	O
,	O
and	O
work	O
'd	O
as	O
a	O
Journey-Man	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
the	O
Lace	O
off	O
from	O
his	O
Piece	O
in	O
the	O
Loom	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mobbs	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Precinct	B-place
of	I-place
Norton	I-place
Falgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Sarah	B-pers
Mears	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
High-Way	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
and	O
another	O
young	O
Woman	O
having	O
been	O
in	O
Aldermanbury	O
,	O
about	O
Business	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Time	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
were	O
returning	O
Home	O
,	O
pretty	O
late	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
percerving	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
to	O
follow	O
them	O
,	O
who	O
appeared	O
to	O
the	O
Shabby	O
Fellows	O
,	O
were	O
under	O
some	O
Apprehension	O
of	O
being	O
injured	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
going	O
thro	O
'	O
Spittle-Square	B-place
,	O
perceiving	O
a	O
Watchman	O
not	O
far	O
off	O
,	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
Companion	O
,	O
that	O
now	O
they	O
were	O
out	O
of	O
Danger	O
;	O
but	O
had	O
no	O
sooner	O
spoken	O
the	O
Words	O
,	O
but	O
immediately	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
pull	O
'd	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
off	O
from	O
her	O
Neck	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
crying	O
out	O
the	O
Watchman	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
.	O
Her	O
Evidence	O
was	O
confirmed	O
by	O
the	O
other	O
young	O
Woman	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
her	O
Companion	O
:	O
The	O
apprehending	O
of	O
him	O
upon	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Outcry	O
,	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Constable	O
and	O
Watchman	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
on	O
the	O
High-Way	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Valentine	B-pers
Clinton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Linnen	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
divers	O
Persons	O
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Linnen	O
was	O
laid	O
out	O
in	O
a	O
Garden	O
,	O
to	O
Whiten	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
Pales	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
follow	O
'd	O
was	O
apprehended	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wyman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
two	O
Guineas	O
out	O
of	O
about	O
seven	O
Guineas	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Chest	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Chamber	O
:	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
Evidence	O
sufficient	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Day	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
:	O
divers	O
Wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Shippey	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Hagget	I-pers
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Prosecutor	O
were	O
both	O
Lodgers	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Chamber	O
,	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Hagget	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
going	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
to	O
his	O
Business	O
,	O
left	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
Home	O
his	O
Clothes	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
though	O
he	O
had	O
before	O
signified	O
to	O
his	O
Landlady	O
Mrs.	O
Hagget	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
intended	O
to	O
lodge	O
all	O
the	O
Winter	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
did	O
on	O
that	O
very	O
Day	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
previous	O
Notice	O
,	O
tell	O
her	O
on	O
a	O
sudden	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
must	O
go	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
paid	O
her	O
for	O
his	O
Lodging	O
did	O
go	O
;	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stole	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Clothes	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Susanna	B-pers
Hutchins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
taking	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Edsar	I-pers
,	O
four	O
Guineas	O
,	O
a	O
Moidore	O
,	O
and	O
8	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Newgate	O
Street	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
formerly	O
been	O
his	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
having	O
dwelt	O
the	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
him	O
about	O
3	O
Years	O
,	O
that	O
asking	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
liv	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
Service	O
,	O
and	O
wrought	O
hard	O
for	O
her	O
Living	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
drink	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
consented	O
so	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
in	O
the	O
publick	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
drank	O
till	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
came	O
to	O
14	O
Pence	O
,	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
his	O
Bag	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
his	O
Money	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
sitting	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
felt	O
for	O
his	O
Money	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
immediately	O
charg	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
having	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
required	O
a	O
Constable	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
for	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
persisted	O
still	O
in	O
denying	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
resolutely	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
search	O
'd	O
before	O
she	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
carried	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
there	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Bag	O
and	O
Money	O
were	O
found	O
about	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
charg	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
having	O
picked	O
his	O
Pocket	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
search	O
'd	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
committed	O
her	O
to	O
two	O
Watchmen	O
,	O
bidding	O
them	O
not	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
have	O
her	O
Hands	O
at	O
Liberty	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
observe	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
throw	O
or	O
convey	O
away	O
any	O
Thing	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
went	O
along	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
before	O
Justice	O
Hewet	O
,	O
she	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
search	O
'd	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Justice	O
bidding	O
him	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
by	O
Violence	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
permit	O
him	O
by	O
fair	O
Means	O
;	O
he	O
attempting	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
a	O
clasp	O
'd	O
Knife	O
,	O
threatning	O
to	O
stick	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
attempt	O
it	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
the	O
Justice	O
ordered	O
them	O
to	O
get	O
some	O
Women	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Bag	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
he	O
had	O
before	O
described	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
it	O
about	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Women	O
that	O
search	O
'd	O
her	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Money	O
thrust	O
between	O
her	O
Shift	O
and	O
outward	O
Clothes	O
,	O
upon	O
loosening	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
nothing	O
was	O
freer	O
than	O
Gift	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
before	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
meeting	O
her	O
in	O
Newgate	O
Street	O
,	O
fell	O
into	O
Discourse	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Wine	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
consented	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Dean	B-place
's	I-place
Head	I-place
in	I-place
St.	I-place
Martins	I-place
le	I-place
Grand	I-place
,	O
and	O
being	O
there	O
drinking	O
together	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Penny	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
Penny	O
worth	O
of	O
Rods	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Chandler	O
's	O
Shop	O
hard	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
Rods	O
,	O
and	O
whipt	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
till	O
she	O
had	O
worn	O
them	O
quite	O
to	O
the	O
Stumps	O
,	O
that	O
having	O
so	O
done	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Bag	O
and	O
Money	O
for	O
so	O
obliging	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
so	O
well	O
pleas	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
had	O
it	O
been	O
twice	O
as	O
much	O
more	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
given	O
her	O
it	O
all	O
;	O
and	O
also	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
her	O
serch	O
another	O
Penny	O
worth	O
of	O
Rods	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Purpose	O
,	O
but	O
because	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
his	O
Money	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
having	O
given	O
it	O
her	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
often	O
repeated	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
Nothing	O
was	O
freer	O
than	O
Gift	O
,	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
thereupon	O
he	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
charge	O
her	O
with	O
robbing	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
hang	O
her	O
.	O
This	O
her	O
darling	O
Maxim	O
,	O
Nothing	O
was	O
freer	O
than	O
Gift	O
,	O
she	O
often	O
repeated	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
more	O
Confidence	O
and	O
Levity	O
,	O
than	O
became	O
one	O
under	O
her	O
dangerous	O
Circumstances	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Service	O
by	O
which	O
she	O
pretended	O
to	O
merit	O
the	O
Prosetor	O
's	O
Money	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
to	O
bring	O
Proof	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
either	O
by	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
or	O
of	O
whom	O
she	O
bought	O
the	O
Rods	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
producing	O
any	O
Evidences	O
,	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
but	O
an	O
extravagant	O
Sally	O
,	O
designed	O
to	O
render	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
ridiculous	O
.	O
Whereupon	O
after	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bennet	I-place
's	I-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Wharf	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Saw	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Bowles	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Perkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Christchurch	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Sewel	I-pers
,	I-pers
and	I-pers
Company	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Company	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
apprehended	O
offering	O
them	O
to	O
Sale	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Draper	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Townley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Townley	I-pers
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Ebenezer	B-pers
Pendril	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
been	O
Journeyman	O
to	O
a	O
Barber	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
himself	O
was	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
(	O
whose	O
House	O
adjoined	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
)	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
enticed	O
him	O
to	O
assist	O
him	O
in	O
robbing	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
let	O
him	O
into	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Cellar	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
pull	O
'd	O
down	O
Part	O
of	O
a	O
Brick-Wall	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Counting-house	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
what	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Burglary	O
not	O
being	O
so	O
plain	O
,	O
they	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
that	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
An	O
Appeal	O
was	O
lodg	O
'd	O
against	O
Lewis	B-pers
Hussare	I-pers
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
by	O
Solomon	B-pers
Rondeau	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Brother	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgement	O
as	O
followeth	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
Four	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Curtis	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Parkinson	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Burgess	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Susannah	B-pers
Hutchins	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
,	O
Twenty	O
Two	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Britton	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bonner	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Luke	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	O
Johnson	O
,	O
William	O
alias	O
Richard	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Starling	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Sharloe	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Winter	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Rumsey	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Todd	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mobbs	I-pers
,	O
Valentine	B-pers
Clinton	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Perkins	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Draper	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
Luke	B-pers
Tench	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
Three	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Walkup	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Barber	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Two	O
last	O
former	O
Convicts	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
,	O
One	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Dunbar	I-pers
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Hutchins	I-pers
pleaded	O
her	O
Belly	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
being	O
impannell	O
'd	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
not	O
with	O
Quick	O
Child	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
Just	O
publish	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Seventh	O
Edition	O
(	O
with	O
many	O
Additions	O
and	O
Amendments	O
)	O
of	O
A	O
Rational	O
and	O
Useful	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Venereal	O
Disease	O
.	O
With	O
Observations	O
on	O
the	O
Nature	O
,	O
Symptoms	O
,	O
and	O
Cure	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
ill	O
Consequences	O
that	O
attend	O
it	O
by	O
ill	O
Management	O
;	O
with	O
proper	O
Admonitions	O
;	O
recommended	O
as	O
a	O
Friendly	O
Instruction	O
to	O
all	O
Persons	O
who	O
do	O
,	O
or	O
may	O
,	O
labour	O
under	O
this	O
Misfortune	O
.	O
Also	O
,	O
A	O
short	O
Inquiry	O
into	O
Old	O
Gleets	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Weaknesses	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Reason	O
why	O
they	O
are	O
so	O
seldom	O
cured	O
:	O
With	O
the	O
Author	O
's	O
Method	O
of	O
Cure	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
are	O
added	O
,	O
Some	O
Hints	O
on	O
the	O
Practical	O
Scheme	O
.	O
The	O
Methods	O
and	O
Medicines	O
there	O
in	O
exposed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
gross	O
Impositions	O
justly	O
detected	O
:	O
With	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
Specificks	O
,	O
the	O
Use	O
and	O
Abuse	O
of	O
the	O
Name	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
it	O
covers	O
Ignorance	O
and	O
a	O
Cheat	O
.	O
By	O
Joseph	B-pers
Cam	I-pers
,	O
M.D	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
G.	O
Strahan	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
W.	O
Mears	O
,	O
without	O
Temple-Bar	O
,	O
C.	O
King	O
,	O
in	O
Westminster-Hall	O
,	O
T.	O
Norris	O
on	O
London-Bridge	O
,	O
J.	O
Baker	O
against	O
Hatton-Garden	O
in	O
Holborn	O
;	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Author	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Golden	O
Ball	O
and	O
Lamp	O
in	O
Bow-Church-Yard	O
,	O
Cheapside	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
A	O
compleat	O
List	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Minters	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
cleared	O
at	O
Guilford	O
,	O
Kingston	O
,	O
Croydon	O
and	O
Ryegate	O
,	O
Amounting	O
to	O
above	O
6000	O
from	O
all	O
Parts	O
of	O
Great	O
Britain	O
and	O
Ireland	O
,	O
with	O
their	O
Names	O
,	O
Trades	O
,	O
Towns	O
and	O
Countries	O
,	O
of	O
their	O
last	O
Abode	O
,	O
Alphabetically	O
done	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
more	O
easy	O
finding	O
out	O
any	O
particular	O
Person	O
.	O
Publish	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
general	O
Information	O
to	O
all	O
Mankind	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
Where	O
may	O
he	O
had	O
also	O
,	O
An	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Lives	O
,	O
Intreagues	O
,	O
and	O
Comical	O
Advertisement	O
's	O
of	O
Rob	O
Roy	O
,	O
alias	O
Robert	B-pers
Mac	I-pers
Gregor	I-pers
,	O
Capt	O
.	O
Stanley	O
,	O
Sally	B-pers
Salisbury	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Sarah	B-pers
Pridden	I-pers
,	O
and	O
wear	O
a	O
hunred	O
more	O
,	O
who	O
have	O
either	O
dy	O
'd	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
or	O
been	O
executed	O
for	O
several	O
Villanies	O
and	O
Murders	O
committed	O
by	O
them	O
:	O
Wherein	O
is	O
contained	O
a	O
more	O
full	O
and	O
true	O
Account	O
,	O
than	O
has	O
been	O
publish	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Ordinary	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
other	O
.	O
The	O
Whole	O
being	O
not	O
only	O
very	O
Diverting	O
to	O
read	O
,	O
but	O
very	O
Useful	O
to	O
preserve	O
others	O
from	O
being	O
impos	O
'd	O
upon	O
by	O
Sharpens	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
Both	O
printed	O
for	O
M.	O
Hotham	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Black-Boy	O
on	O
London-Bridge	O
.	O
A	O
Water	O
that	O
perfectly	O
cures	O
the	O
Itch	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
Itching	O
Humour	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
,	O
without	O
Necessity	O
of	O
Purging	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
dangerous	O
Use	O
of	O
Mercury	O
,	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
only	O
is	O
prepared	O
and	O
sold	O
,	O
by	O
A	O
.	O
Downing	O
,	O
Chymist	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
and	O
Ball	O
,	O
in	O
George	O
Court	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
John's-Lane	O
,	O
by	O
Hicks's-Hall	O
,	O
near	O
West-Smithfield	O
.	O
Where	O
also	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
the	O
best	O
Spirits	O
of	O
Scurvy-Grass	O
,	O
by	O
Wholesale	O
or	O
Retale	O
,	O
at	O
8	O
d.	O
a	O
Bottle	O
.	O
A	O
most	O
effectual	O
Remedy	O
for	O
the	O
violent	O
Pain	O
in	O
the	O
Teeth	O
,	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
Also	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Remedy	O
for	O
the	O
Teeth	O
,	O
and	O
clearing	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
.	O
Youth	O
's	O
Introduction	O
to	O
Trade	O
and	O
Business	O
:	O
Containing	B-pers
,	I-pers
I	I-pers
.	I-pers
Tables	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
usual	O
Clerk-like	O
Contractions	O
of	O
Words	O
:	O
A	O
Collection	O
of	O
English	O
Words	O
,	O
alike	O
in	O
Sound	O
,	O
but	O
different	O
in	O
Signification	O
;	O
with	O
proper	O
,	O
Directions	O
how	O
to	O
address	O
to	O
Persons	O
of	O
elevated	O
Rank	O
,	O
and	O
those	O
in	O
Office	O
.	O
II	O
.	O
Acquittances	O
and	O
Promissory	O
Notes	O
diversisy	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
adapted	O
to	O
such	O
Circumstances	O
as	O
occur	O
in	O
real	O
Business	O
.	O
III	O
.	O
Variety	O
of	O
Bills	O
of	O
Parcels	O
,	O
and	O
Bills	O
on	O
Book	O
Debts	O
,	O
to	O
enter	O
the	O
Learner	O
in	O
the	O
Manner	O
and	O
Methods	O
of	O
Commerce	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
ready	O
at	O
Computation	O
.	O
IV	O
.	O
Bills	O
of	O
Exchange	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
necessary	O
for	O
the	O
right	O
Understanding	O
and	O
Management	O
of	O
Remittances	O
;	O
several	O
Orders	O
for	O
Goods	O
,	O
Letters	O
of	O
Credit	O
,	O
Invoyces	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Merchant-like	O
Examples	O
.	O
V.	O
Authentick	O
Forms	O
of	O
such	O
Law-Precedents	O
as	O
are	O
most	O
frequently	O
to	O
be	O
met	O
with	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Course	O
of	O
Trassick	O
.	O
VI	O
.	O
A	O
Collection	O
of	O
Questions	O
to	O
exemplify	O
the	O
common	O
Rules	O
of	O
Arithmetick	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
reduce	O
them	O
to	O
Practice	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Use	O
of	O
Schools	O
.	O
Done	O
upon	O
the	O
Plan	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
Col.	O
Ayre	B-pers
's	O
Essay	O
.	O
By	O
M.	O
Clare	O
,	O
School-Master	O
in	O
Soho-Square	O
,	O
London	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
Edward	O
Symon	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Pope	O
's	O
Head	O
Alley	O
,	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
.	O
BOOKS	O
Printed	O
for	O
EDWARD	O
SYMON	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Popes-Head-Alley	O
,	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
.	O
THE	O
History	O
of	O
the	O
Revolutions	O
that	O
happened	O
in	O
the	O
Government	O
of	O
the	O
Roman	B-pers
Republick	I-pers
.	O
Written	O
in	O
French	O
by	O
the	O
Abbot	O
de	O
Vertot	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Royal	O
Academy	O
of	O
Inscriptions	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
English	O
'd	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Ozell	O
from	O
the	O
Original	O
,	O
newly	O
reprinted	O
at	O
Paris	O
,	O
with	O
Amendments	O
and	O
Additions	O
by	O
the	O
Author	O
himself	O
,	O
in	O
almost	O
every	O
Page	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
prefix	O
'd	O
,	O
a	O
Translation	O
of	O
a	O
Memorial	O
sent	O
from	O
London	O
by	O
the	O
late	O
Earl	B-pers
Scanhope	I-pers
,	O
to	O
the	O
Abbot	O
de	O
Vertot	O
at	O
Paris	O
;	O
containing	O
divers	O
Questions	O
relating	O
to	O
the	O
Constitution	O
of	O
the	O
Roman	B-pers
Senate	I-pers
.	O
With	O
the	O
Abbot	O
's	O
Answer	O
.	O
The	O
Third	O
Edition	O
.	O
In	O
2	O
Vol	O
.	O
An	O
universal	O
Etymological	O
English	O
Dictionary	O
;	O
Comprehending	O
the	O
Derivations	O
of	O
the	O
Generality	O
of	O
Words	O
in	O
the	O
English	O
Tongue	O
,	O
either	O
Ancient	O
or	O
Modern	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Ancient	O
British	O
,	O
Saxon	O
,	O
Danish	O
,	O
Norman	O
,	O
and	O
Modern	O
French	O
,	O
Tuetonic	O
,	O
Dutch	O
,	O
Spanish	O
,	O
Italian	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
from	O
the	O
Latin	O
,	O
Greek	O
,	O
and	O
Hebrew	O
Languages	O
,	O
each	O
in	O
their	O
proper	O
Characters	O
.	O
And	O
also	O
a	O
brief	O
and	O
clear	O
Explication	O
of	O
all	O
difficult	O
Words	O
derived	O
from	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Languages	O
;	O
and	O
Terms	O
of	O
Art	O
,	O
relating	O
to	O
Anatomy	O
,	O
Botany	O
,	O
Physick	O
,	O
Pharmacy	O
,	O
Surgery	O
,	O
Chymistry	O
,	O
Philosophy	O
,	O
Divinity	O
,	O
Mathematicks	O
,	O
Grammer	O
,	O
Logick	O
,	O
Rhetorick	O
,	O
Musick	O
Heraldry	O
,	O
Maritime	O
Affairs	O
,	O
Military	O
Discipline	O
,	O
Horsemanship	O
,	O
Hunting	O
,	O
Hawking	O
,	O
Fowling	O
,	O
Fishing	O
,	O
Gardening	O
,	O
Husbandry	O
,	O
Handicrafts	O
,	O
Confectionary	O
,	O
Carving	O
,	O
Cookery	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Together	O
with	O
a	O
large	O
Collection	O
and	O
Explication	O
of	O
Words	O
and	O
Phrases	O
us	O
'd	O
in	O
our	O
Ancient	O
Statutes	O
,	O
Charters	O
,	O
Writs	O
,	O
old	O
Records	O
,	O
and	O
Processes	O
at	O
Law	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Etymology	O
and	O
Interpretation	O
of	O
the	O
proper	O
Names	O
of	O
Men	O
,	O
Women	O
,	O
and	O
remarkable	O
Places	O
in	O
Great	O
Britain	O
:	O
Also	O
the	O
Dialects	O
of	O
our	O
different	O
Counties	O
.	O
Containing	O
many	O
Thousand	O
Words	O
more	O
than	O
either	O
Harris	O
,	O
Philips	O
,	O
Kersey	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
English	O
Dictionary	O
before	O
Extant	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
a	O
Collection	O
of	O
our	O
most	O
common	O
Proverbs	O
,	O
with	O
their	O
Explication	O
and	O
Illustration	O
.	O
The	O
whole	O
Work	O
compiled	O
and	O
Methodically	O
digested	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
for	O
the	O
Entertainment	O
of	O
the	O
Curious	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Information	O
of	O
the	O
Ignorant	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
the	O
Benefit	O
of	O
young	O
Students	O
,	O
Artificers	O
,	O
Tradesmen	O
and	O
Foreigners	O
,	O
who	O
are	O
desirous	O
thorowly	O
to	O
understand	O
what	O
they	O
Speak	O
,	O
Read	O
or	O
Write	O
.	O
The	O
Second	O
Edition	O
,	O
with	O
large	O
Additions	O
.	O
By	O
N.	O
Bailey	O
,	O
Philologos	O
.	O
M.	O
Misson	O
's	O
Memoirs	O
and	O
Observations	O
in	O
his	O
Travels	O
over	O
England	O
:	O
With	O
some	O
Account	O
of	O
Scotland	O
and	O
Ireland	O
.	O
Dispos	O
'd	O
in	O
Alphabetical	O
Order	O
.	O
Written	O
originally	O
in	O
French	O
,	O
and	O
translated	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Ozell	O
.	O
The	O
Miscellaneous	O
Works	O
of	O
that	O
eminent	O
States-man	O
Francis	B-pers
Osborn	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
in	O
two	O
Vol	O
.	O
The	O
Eleventh	O
Edition	O
.	O
Lately	O
Publish	O
'd	B-pers
,	I-pers
A	I-pers
Gray	B-pers
Cap	I-pers
for	O
a	O
Green	O
Head	O
.	O
Written	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Puckle	O
.	O
A	O
compleat	O
History	O
of	O
the	O
Lives	O
and	O
Robberies	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
Notorious	O
Highway-men	O
,	O
Foot-pads	O
,	O
Shop-lifts	O
,	O
and	O
Cheats	O
,	O
of	O
both	O
Sexes	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
about	O
London	O
,	O
Westminster	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
Parts	O
of	O
Great	O
Britain	O
,	O
for	O
above	O
an	O
hundred	O
years	O
,	O
past	O
,	O
continued	O
to	O
the	O
present	O
Time	O
.	O
By	O
Capt	O
.	O
Alex	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
In	O
two	O
Vol	O
.	O
Miscellaneous	O
Essays	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
Of	O
Company	O
and	O
Conversation	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
Of	O
Solitariness	O
and	O
Retirement	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
Of	O
Nobility	O
.	O
4	O
.	O
Of	O
Contentment	O
.	O
5	O
.	O
Of	O
Women	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
Of	O
the	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
God	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
Atheism	O
.	O
7	O
.	O
Of	O
Religion	O
.	O
8	O
.	O
Of	O
Kings	O
,	O
Princes	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Education	O
of	O
a	O
Prince	O
.	O
9	O
.	O
Of	O
Greatness	O
of	O
Mind	O
.	O
10	O
.	O
Of	O
the	O
Education	O
of	O
Children	O
.	O
11	O
.	O
Of	O
Law	O
.	O
12	O
.	O
Of	O
Man	O
.	O
13	O
.	O
Of	O
Old	O
Age	O
.	O
With	O
the	O
Life	O
and	O
Conversion	O
of	O
St.	O
Mary	O
Magdalen	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Reflections	O
upon	O
the	O
Conversion	O
of	O
the	O
good	O
Thief	O
;	O
also	O
,	O
the	O
Life	O
and	O
Conversion	O
of	O
St.	O
Paul	O
.	O
By	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Bulstrode	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Envoy	O
at	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
Brussels	O
,	O
from	O
King	O
Charles	B-pers
II	I-pers
.	O
and	O
King	O
James	B-pers
II	I-pers
.	O
Published	O
with	O
a	O
Preface	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
Son	O
Whitlock	O
Bulstrode	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
The	O
Second	O
Edition	O
.	O
An	O
Essay	O
on	O
Perspective	O
.	O
Written	O
in	O
French	O
by	O
William	B-pers
James	I-pers
's	O
Gravesande	O
,	O
Doctor	O
of	O
Laws	O
and	O
Philosophy	O
,	O
Professor	O
of	O
Mathematicks	O
and	O
Astronomy	O
at	O
Leyden	O
,	O
and	O
Fellow	O
of	O
the	O
Royal	O
Society	O
at	O
London	O
.	O
And	O
now	O
translated	O
into	O
English	O
.	O
