TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice	O
Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
,	O
Monday	O
,	O
and	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
14th	O
,	O
15th	O
,	O
16th	O
,	O
17th	O
,	O
19th	O
,	O
and	O
21st	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Eleventh	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
PETER	B-pers
DELME	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Tracy	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Serjeant	O
at	O
Law	O
;	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
The	O
JURORS	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
The	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Appleby	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Morsden	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Leppige	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Fewtril	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Humston	I-pers
,	O
Stephen	B-pers
Skinner	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Whiting	I-pers
;	O
John	B-pers
Darwin	I-pers
,	O
Stephen	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tailor	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Gardener	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Winterbottom	I-pers
,	O
The	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ingram	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Tame	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Richmond	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Timbrel	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Frith	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fann	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Gilmore	I-pers
,	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Wimberly	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Young	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Doleman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Turncock	O
Key	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
Governor	B-pers
and	I-pers
Company	I-pers
of	I-pers
the	I-pers
New	I-pers
River	I-pers
Water	I-pers
,	O
brought	O
from	O
Amwel	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Turncock	O
Key	O
was	O
lost	O
from	O
without	O
Bishopsgate	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
that	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
Notice	O
voluntarily	O
of	O
his	O
having	O
the	O
Key	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
Evidences	O
to	O
prove	O
his	O
buying	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
divers	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
Vintry	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
Linnen	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Soloman	B-pers
Baudwin	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
Day	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Priscilla	B-pers
Hilliard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolph	I-place
's	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Carrington	I-pers
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
under	O
Pretence	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
suspected	O
,	O
was	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Stockings	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Lawrence	I-place
Old	I-place
Jury	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Breeches	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
The	O
Property	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Charden	I-pers
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
And	O
also	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Grey	I-pers
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
confest	O
the	O
Facts	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
but	O
deny	O
'd	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
being	O
positively	O
sworn	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Armitage	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Christopher	I-place
's	I-place
Broadstreet	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Paper	O
Book	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Moses	B-pers
Ouseman	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Souseman	I-pers
,	O
a	O
German	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolph	I-place
's	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
109	O
Guineas	O
,	O
16	O
Moidores	O
,	O
one	O
4	O
Pistole	O
Piece	O
,	O
20	O
Broad	O
Pieces	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Farmer	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Clements	I-pers
,	O
in	O
their	O
Dwelling-house	O
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
abroad	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
Closet	O
in	O
the	O
Back-Shop	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Lodging	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Relation	O
to	O
a	O
Jew	O
Family	O
that	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
liv	O
'd	O
there	O
before	O
for	O
about	O
seven	O
Months	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
lodge	O
there	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
when	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
dined	O
there	O
the	O
Day	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
therefore	O
suspecting	O
him	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
first	O
he	O
deny	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
inform	O
'd	O
by	O
another	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
got	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
it	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
hid	O
it	O
between	O
the	O
Tiles	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
wanted	O
three	O
Pound	O
of	O
the	O
Sum	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
pretended	O
that	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
an	O
Englishman	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
What	O
he	O
did	O
there	O
?	O
whereupon	O
he	O
threw	O
the	O
Bag	O
of	O
Money	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
Home	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
much	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Purpose	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
;	O
the	O
Reason	O
he	O
gave	O
for	O
not	O
stopping	O
the	O
Person	O
he	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Thing	O
of	O
very	O
dangerous	O
Consequence	O
in	O
his	O
Country	O
,	O
to	O
call	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
like	O
,	O
after	O
a	O
Person	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
hid	O
it	O
between	O
the	O
Tiles	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
keep	O
it	O
safe	O
,	O
in	O
Order	O
to	O
return	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
no	O
Lock	O
,	O
or	O
Security	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Lodging	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
about	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
at	O
first	O
deny	O
his	O
knowing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
in	O
Hopes	O
they	O
would	O
offer	O
him	O
some	O
Reward	O
.	O
He	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Jews	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Barnet	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bartholomew	I-place
the	I-place
Less	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Selby	I-pers
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
:	O
Which	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bucknel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Money	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Bucknel	I-pers
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Grove	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Magdalen	I-place
Old	I-place
Fishstreet	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Tomlin	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Day-time	O
,	O
no	O
Person	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
25	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
left	O
in	O
Charge	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
Master	O
came	O
back	O
in	O
about	O
Half	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
the	O
Door	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
gone	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
after	O
to	O
Ipswich	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
eight	O
Weeks	O
after	O
,	O
had	O
spent	O
all	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
gotten	O
38	O
s.	O
in	O
Debt	O
,	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Edmunds	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
Stockings	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Web	I-pers
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Willoughby	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bartholomew	I-place
the	I-place
Less	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Perriwigs	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wenham	I-pers
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Yoe	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Eastcheap	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
2	O
Guineas	O
,	O
3	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
18	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Ruth	B-pers
Tailor	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Prosecutor	O
were	O
Fellow	O
Servant	O
s	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Heath	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Newport	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Dascomb	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
October	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
several	O
Times	O
lost	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Breeches	O
Pocket	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
in	O
some	O
remarkable	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Hooper	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Duboi	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Cookmaid	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Things	O
being	O
lost	O
,	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Trunk	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
lodg	O
'd	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
Place	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
that	O
she	O
stole	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Stable	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Pitfield	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Fernello	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Pancras	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
Years	O
and	O
three	O
Quarters	O
old	O
,	O
by	O
beating	O
down	O
the	O
Child	O
with	O
the	O
Coach	O
Pole	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
his	O
Sister	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
him	O
in	O
her	O
Arms	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
driving	O
the	O
Wheel	O
over	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
which	O
kill	O
'd	O
him	O
out	O
right	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
driving	O
his	O
Coach	O
into	O
Tottenham	B-place
Fair	I-place
,	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
Turn	O
committed	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
to	O
,	O
to	O
stop	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Others	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
saw	O
him	O
pulling	O
the	O
Reins	O
with	O
all	O
his	O
Might	O
,	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
stop	O
the	O
Houses	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
,	O
peaceable	O
,	O
good	O
temper	O
'd	O
and	O
careful	O
Fellow	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
brought	O
in	O
their	O
Verdict	O
,	O
Chance	O
Medley	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Darby	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Risdell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Leonard	O
Shoreditch	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
together	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
former	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Orchard	I-pers
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
Pritchard	O
and	O
Risdel	O
for	O
being	O
aiding	O
and	O
abetting	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
:	O
And	O
a	O
third	O
Time	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Samuel	O
Orchard	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Weapon	O
drawn	O
.	O
The	O
Witnesses	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
were	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dillo	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Batten	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
,	O
and	O
-	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
who	O
all	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Purpose	O
following	O
.	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
Time	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
Henry	O
Griffin	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
being	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Samuel	O
Orchard	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
'till	O
after	O
eleven	O
a-Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
having	O
at	O
Haggerstone	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Dillo	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Batten	O
,	O
and	O
Samuel	O
Orchard	O
,	O
agreed	O
to	O
bear	O
them	O
Company	O
over	O
the	O
Fields	O
to	O
Haggerstone	B-place
.	O
That	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
they	O
met	O
with	O
William	O
Pritchard	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Pritchard	O
,	O
and	O
William	O
Risdel	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
them	O
some	O
affronting	O
Language	O
,	O
calling	O
them	O
Taylors	O
,	O
and	O
King	O
John	O
's	O
Men	O
,	O
and	O
Risdel	O
very	O
rudely	O
and	O
violently	O
would	O
kiss	O
Mrs.	O
Griffin	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
permitted	O
for	O
Peace	O
Sake	O
,	O
and	O
parted	O
:	O
And	O
afterwards	O
they	O
heard	O
them	O
say	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
a	O
little	O
Way	O
from	O
them	O
,	O
What	O
had	O
they	O
three	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
the	O
Woman	O
?	O
they	O
would	O
take	O
her	O
from	O
them	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
them	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
Mrs.	O
Griffin	O
from	O
them	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
then	O
holding	O
by	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
violently	O
pull	O
her	O
away	O
,	O
though	O
they	O
told	O
them	O
she	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Griffin	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
not	O
being	O
willing	O
to	O
be	O
carried	O
away	O
,	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
;	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Griffin	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
Risdel	O
that	O
knock	O
'd	O
her	O
down	O
,	O
giving	O
her	O
several	O
Blows	O
on	O
the	O
Face	O
and	O
Head	O
with	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
which	O
hurt	O
her	O
so	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
bear	O
to	O
touch	O
her	O
Head	O
with	O
a	O
Comb	O
for	O
a	O
considerable	O
Time	O
:	O
But	O
her	O
Husband	O
getting	O
her	O
away	O
,	O
while	O
Thomas	O
Batten	O
was	O
fighting	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Pritchard	O
and	O
Risdel	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
give	O
no	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
killing	O
of	O
Orchard	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Dillo	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
upon	O
this	O
Violence	O
offered	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Griffin	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
fell	O
upon	O
them	O
:	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
a	O
Stick	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
pull	O
'd	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
assisted	O
Orchard	O
,	O
to	O
pull	O
the	O
Stick	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
Pritchard	O
stopp	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
go	O
,	O
unless	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
shilling	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
running	O
to	O
the	O
Town	O
to	O
get	O
Assistance	O
,	O
for	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Pritchards	O
and	O
Risdel	O
were	O
fighting	O
with	O
Thomas	O
Batten	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
they	O
return	O
'd	O
into	O
the	O
Fray	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
near	O
John	O
Darby	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
who	O
,	O
upon	O
an	O
Outcry	O
(	O
as	O
he	O
supposes	O
)	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
made	O
of	O
Murder	O
,	O
was	O
come	O
out	O
in	O
his	O
Shirt	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
looking	O
over	O
his	O
Gate	O
with	O
a	O
Stick	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Fray	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
by	O
,	O
while	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Pritchards	O
and	O
Risdel	O
had	O
Thomas	O
Batten	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
Darby	O
,	O
not	O
to	O
make	O
any	O
Party	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
make	O
Peace	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
might	O
go	O
Home	O
about	O
their	O
Business	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
standing	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
giving	O
no	O
Provocation	O
,	O
not	O
fighting	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
John	O
Darby	O
with	O
his	O
Stick	O
knock	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceased	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
died	O
in	O
about	O
Half	O
an	O
Hour	O
:	O
That	O
having	O
apprehended	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
hoped	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
kill	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
him	O
dead	O
,	O
he	O
kneel	O
'd	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
Kill	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
Carry	O
me	O
where	O
you	O
please	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
willing	O
to	O
die	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Batten	O
depos	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Circumstances	O
before	O
the	O
Beginning	O
of	O
the	O
Fray	O
,	O
and	O
Occasion	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
killing	O
of	O
Orchard	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
Risdel	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Pritchards	O
fighting	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
give	O
no	O
Account	O
of	O
that	O
.	O
Henry	O
Griffin	O
depos	O
'd	O
much	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
,	O
saving	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
to	O
get	O
his	O
Wife	O
away	O
to	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
return	O
'd	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
in	O
Sight	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
John	O
Darby	O
give	O
the	O
Deceased	O
the	O
Fatal	O
Blow	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
standing	O
still	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
fighting	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
Risdel	O
and	O
Pritchard	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
pleaded	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Beginning	O
of	O
the	O
Fray	O
,	O
That	O
meeting	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
and	O
Deceased	O
,	O
about	O
twelve	O
a-Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
with	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
suspected	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
ill	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
been	O
drinking	O
,	O
there	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
some	O
Words	O
pass	O
,	O
which	O
proceeded	O
to	O
Blows	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
being	O
the	O
Aggressors	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
for	O
Mrs.	O
Griffin	O
's	O
being	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
,	O
Risdel	O
deny	O
'd	O
his	O
striking	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
she	O
might	O
possibly	O
be	O
push	O
'd	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
Fray	O
.	O
John	O
Darby	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
had	O
no	O
Malice	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
They	O
all	O
called	O
Persons	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
them	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
honest	O
,	O
laborious	O
Person	O
in	O
their	O
Calling	O
of	O
Brickmaking	O
.	O
Upon	O
a	O
full	O
Hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
John	O
Darby	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
And	O
acquitted	O
Pritchard	O
and	O
Risdel	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
2	O
Cheeses	O
,	O
2	O
Bottles	O
of	O
Strong	O
Waters	O
,	O
and	O
11	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
His	O
Shop	O
was	O
broken	O
open	O
before	O
three	O
a-Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
call	O
'd	O
up	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
:	O
Thus	O
the	O
Things	O
before	O
mentioned	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
more	O
Goods	O
were	O
Put	O
into	O
a	O
Baker	O
's	O
Sack	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
be	O
carried	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
disturbed	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Shoebridge	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
himself	O
did	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Pin	O
and	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
Berry	O
took	O
down	O
the	O
Shutter	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
opened	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
in	O
Berry	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
carried	O
away	O
the	O
Things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
having	O
Time	O
could	O
not	O
carry	O
away	O
any	O
more	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
Break	O
of	O
Day	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
Persons	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Frances	B-pers
Jakes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stripping	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Child	O
of	O
six	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Frock	O
,	O
Stays	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
own	O
Confession	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
call	O
the	O
Child	O
from	O
School	O
,	O
stripp	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
Church-Porch	O
,	O
near	O
Ormond-street	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainty	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Whitechapel	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Milton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Saw	O
and	O
Planes	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
,	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Moreby	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Spur	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Oswald	B-pers
Dyke	I-pers
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
in	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Her	O
Master	O
and	O
Mistress	O
begging	O
the	O
Favour	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Scarlet	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Scarlet	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
Andrew	B-pers
Scarlet	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
.	O
That	O
whereas	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wakelin	I-pers
had	O
robbed	O
her	O
Master	O
Ebenezer	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
divers	O
Goods	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
convicted	O
at	O
a	O
former	O
Sessions	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
received	O
divers	O
Goods	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
Servant	O
gave	O
an	O
Account	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
lately	O
he	O
had	O
Notice	O
given	O
him	O
of	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Goods	O
dropt	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
directed	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
his	O
Goods	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Proof	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
,	I-pers
the	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
William	I-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jenkin	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cordwell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sauce	O
Pan	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Burnham	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coverlet	O
and	O
Sheet	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Holms	I-pers
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
the	O
Trinity	B-place
Minories	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Silver	O
Watches	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Astbury	I-pers
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
Being	O
drinking	O
in	O
Southwark	B-place
,	O
he	O
fell	O
asleep	O
upon	O
a	O
Table	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
awaked	O
his	O
Watches	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
a	O
Week	O
after	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Hands	O
of	O
a	O
Constable	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Graves	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Constable	O
in	O
the	O
Trinity	O
Minories	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Soldiers	O
brought	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
show	O
'd	O
him	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
asking	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
she	O
had	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
she	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
them	O
by	O
Dibbling	O
in	O
Southwark	O
Fair	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
Lamb	O
Alley	O
,	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
going	O
by	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
round	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
kiss	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
drink	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
refus	O
'd	O
,	O
as	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
use	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
a	O
Stranger	O
;	O
'till	O
she	O
thinking	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
some	O
Acquaintance	O
of	O
her	O
Husband	O
's	O
,	O
did	O
go	O
in	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
telling	O
her	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
like	O
one	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Kindness	O
for	O
,	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
grant	O
him	O
one	O
Favour	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
lie	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
not	O
having	O
Money	O
enough	O
then	O
about	O
him	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
Amends	O
,	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
two	O
Watches	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
a	O
Promise	O
to	O
meet	O
him	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Pye	O
Tavern	O
at	O
Bishopsgate	O
.	O
The	O
whole	O
of	O
this	O
was	O
deny	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
ever	O
seen	O
her	O
,	O
before	O
he	O
saw	O
her	O
after	O
her	O
Apprehension	O
by	O
the	O
Constable	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Kennier	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Hundred	O
Weight	O
of	O
Logwood	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Brailsford	I-pers
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Logwood	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Lighter	O
and	O
put	O
into	O
a	O
Boat	O
in	O
the	O
River	O
of	O
Thames	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
by	O
his	O
own	O
Confession	O
.	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Snow	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolph	I-place
's	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Smock	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bass	I-pers
,	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Shift	O
being	O
shew	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
of	O
no	O
Value	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pleading	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
lent	O
her	O
by	O
her	O
Mistress	O
while	O
she	O
nurs	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Belshaw	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
(	O
together	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
who	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
)	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Buckle	I-pers
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
both	O
Boy	O
s	O
:	O
The	O
Proof	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Jonas	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Evan	B-pers
Redworth	I-pers
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Shirt	O
was	O
taken	O
off	O
a	O
Line	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
hung	O
up	O
to	O
dry	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
off	O
the	O
Line	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Aten	I-pers
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Jefferies	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Dial	O
Plate	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Thornton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Watchcase	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Raymund	I-pers
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Row	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
's	I-place
Woodstreet	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
50	O
Yards	O
of	O
Stuff	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Stockwell	I-pers
,	I-pers
and	I-pers
Company	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Company	O
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Katherine	B-pers
Knox	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bible	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Fitzer	I-pers
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Kilmister	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bride	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Tea-kettle	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Timothy	B-pers
Daley	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Spoon	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Arthur	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Isaak	B-pers
Clerk	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
's	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
John	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
having	O
stolen	O
50	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
receive	O
them	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Chiswick	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
4	O
Iron	O
Links	O
of	O
a	O
Chain	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mawson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
to	O
the	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Towers	I-pers
,	O
and	O
George	B-pers
Web	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
and	O
robbing	O
George	B-pers
Westwood	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
Westwood	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
Edward	O
,	O
at	O
King	O
Edward	O
's	O
Stairs	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
there	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
some	O
Name	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
seeing	O
them	O
,	O
ran	O
up	O
Stairs	O
for	O
Fear	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
into	O
a	O
Gallery	O
,	O
and	O
drop	O
'd	O
thence	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Stairs	O
that	O
go	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
seized	O
him	O
,	O
carried	O
him	O
on	O
their	O
Shoulders	O
,	O
afterwards	O
set	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
led	O
and	O
dragg	O
'd	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Mint	B-place
,	O
and	O
as	O
they	O
went	O
along	O
Towers	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
13	O
s.	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
Money	O
if	O
they	O
did	O
design	O
to	O
knock	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
damn	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
meant	O
by	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
kept	O
his	O
Hand	O
shut	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Seven	O
Cities	O
of	O
Refuge	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
his	O
Pocket	O
Book	O
,	O
look	O
'd	O
over	O
his	O
Writs	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
them	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
duck	O
'd	O
him	O
in	O
two	O
nasty	O
stinking	O
Ducking-places	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
stabb	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
beat	O
him	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
almost	O
murthered	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
charge	O
Web	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Cherry	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
saw	O
Capt	O
.	O
Towers	O
with	O
a	O
Cutlass	O
or	O
Backsword	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
lead	O
Westwood	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Back	O
Door	O
of	O
the	O
Seven	O
Cities	O
of	O
Refuge	O
into	O
the	O
Ducking	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
lent	O
him	O
his	O
Hand	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
strike	O
him	O
.	O
Upon	O
a	O
full	O
Hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Deval	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
counterfeiting	O
a	O
Certificate	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
72.	O
in	O
the	O
68th	O
Course	O
of	O
Payment	O
for	O
52	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
for	O
seven	O
Blank	O
Lottery	O
Tickets	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Lottery	O
1723.	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
of	O
Oxford	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cog	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
being	O
invited	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
a	O
Friend	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
applying	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
borrow	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
saying	O
his	O
Father	O
objected	O
against	O
furnishing	O
him	O
with	O
Money	O
for	O
his	O
Journey	O
,	O
he	O
offered	O
to	O
lend	O
him	O
20	O
Guineas	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
sell	O
him	O
a	O
Lottery-Certificate	O
:	O
That	O
asking	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Why	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
sell	O
it	O
himself	O
?	O
He	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
,	O
or	O
it	O
was	O
owned	O
by	O
,	O
one	O
Johnson	O
,	O
and	O
must	O
be	O
so	O
endors	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Clerk	O
in	O
the	O
Lottery-Office	O
it	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
so	O
well	O
for	O
him	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
thereupon	O
did	O
go	O
and	O
sell	O
it	O
for	O
52	O
l.	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
endorsed	O
Johnson	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
his	O
Direction	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
the	O
Money	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
lend	O
him	O
20	O
Guineas	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
bought	O
the	O
Certificate	O
of	O
John	O
Cog	O
.	O
The	O
Commissioners	O
of	O
the	O
Lottery	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
false	O
Certificate	O
:	O
That	O
the	O
true	O
Certificate	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
72	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
68th	O
Course	O
of	O
Payment	O
,	O
was	O
for	O
202	O
l.	O
to	O
one	O
-	O
Curson	O
.	O
That	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Names	O
with	O
which	O
the	O
Certificate	O
was	O
signed	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
written	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
though	O
they	O
were	O
artfully	O
counterfeited	O
.	O
Other	O
Evidences	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
Fellow-Clerks	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Office	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
did	O
believe	O
the	O
filling	O
up	O
of	O
the	O
Certificate	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Hand-writing	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
alledged	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Certificate	O
in	O
Exchange	O
Alley	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
George	O
Robinson	O
had	O
sworn	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Parsons	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
was	O
contradicted	O
that	O
he	O
swore	O
it	O
positively	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
verily	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Ward	B-place
of	I-place
Cheap	I-place
,	O
for	O
counterfeiting	O
and	O
forging	O
one	O
Blank	O
Lottery	O
Ticket	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
No	O
.	O
39	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
65th	O
Course	O
of	O
Payment	O
,	O
to	O
one	O
Solomon	B-pers
Grimstone	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Chappel	O
,	O
in	O
Essex	O
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Gibbons	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
bought	O
the	O
Ticket	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
at	O
John	B-place
's	I-place
Coffee-house	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Exchange	I-place
Alley	I-place
,	O
and	O
paid	O
him	O
for	O
it	O
7	O
l.	O
9	O
s.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
endos	O
'd	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
A.	O
Deval	O
and	O
he	O
sold	O
it	O
again	O
to	O
another	O
Person	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
carrying	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Bank	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
counterfeit	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
filling	O
it	O
up	O
was	O
much	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
verily	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
written	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
they	O
knowing	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
a	O
Clerk	O
in	O
the	O
Lottery	O
Office	O
:	O
And	O
the	O
Commissioners	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
tho	O
'	O
their	O
Names	O
were	O
there	O
,	O
yet	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
believe	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
written	O
by	O
themselves	O
.	O
Several	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
searching	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
they	O
found	O
nothing	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
his	O
Brother	O
in	O
Law	O
Parson	O
's	O
Room	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Quires	O
of	O
Paper	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
that	O
Paper	O
was	O
a	O
Blank	O
Certificate	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Leaves	O
further	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
a	O
Ticket	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Number	O
,	O
Course	O
of	O
Payment	O
,	O
and	O
Sum	O
,	O
and	O
Date	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
counterfeit	O
Certificate	O
,	O
but	O
torn	O
in	O
two	O
Pieces	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Commissioners	O
and	O
Officers	O
did	O
believe	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
true	O
Ticket	O
,	O
and	O
signed	O
by	O
themselves	O
.	O
Upon	O
a	O
full	O
Hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Blueskin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Savoy	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Kneebone	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
108	O
Yards	O
of	O
Woollen	O
Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
36	O
l.	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Kneebone	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
having	O
heard	O
that	O
two	O
of	O
his	O
Neighbours	O
had	O
not	O
long	O
before	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
receiving	O
some	O
Intimation	O
that	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
mark	O
'd	O
down	O
to	O
be	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
the	O
Night	O
that	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
with	O
special	O
Care	O
see	O
all	O
the	O
Doors	O
and	O
Windows	O
fast	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
:	O
That	O
early	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
he	O
found	O
two	O
Bars	O
of	O
his	O
Cellar	O
Window	O
cut	O
,	O
the	O
Cellar	O
Door	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
bolted	O
,	O
and	O
lock	O
'd	O
with	O
a	O
Padlock	O
,	O
broken	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Goods	O
stolen	O
.	O
That	O
thereupon	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
acquainted	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
,	O
telling	O
him	O
he	O
suspected	O
John	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
:	O
That	O
thereupon	O
he	O
procured	O
both	O
Shepherd	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
apprehended	O
.	O
That	O
Shepherd	O
declared	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
after	O
his	O
being	O
apprehended	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
breaking	O
and	O
robbing	O
his	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
afterwards	O
William	B-pers
Field	I-pers
came	O
in	O
as	O
a	O
voluntary	O
Evidence	O
against	O
John	O
Shepherd	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
William	O
Field	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
well	O
acquainted	O
with	O
John	O
Shepherd	O
,	O
having	O
only	O
seen	O
him	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Times	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
Field	O
's	O
House	O
:	O
And	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
to	O
rob	O
Mr.	O
Kneebone	O
.	O
But	O
he	O
refusing	O
to	O
expose	O
himself	O
to	O
any	O
Danger	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
neither	O
would	O
he	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
John	O
Shepherd	O
knew	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
undertake	O
the	O
doing	O
it	O
himself	O
.	O
That	O
thereupon	O
they	O
went	O
from	O
his	O
House	O
in	O
the	O
Mint	O
,	O
cross	O
'd	O
the	O
Water	O
at	O
Lambeth	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Shepherd	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
at	O
Westminster	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
spent	O
the	O
Time	O
together	O
from	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
till	O
about	O
twelve	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
John	O
Shepherd	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
taking	O
out	O
the	O
Bars	O
of	O
the	O
Cellar	O
Window	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
cut	O
a	O
Month	O
or	O
more	O
before	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
provided	O
himself	O
with	O
a	O
Tinder-Box	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Money	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Wax-Candle	O
.	O
That	O
Shepherd	O
opening	O
the	O
Back-Door	O
,	O
(	O
they	O
standing	O
to	O
look	O
out	O
)	O
they	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
carried	O
away	O
his	O
Burden	O
of	O
Goods	O
.	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Broad	O
Cloth	O
was	O
pawned	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
going	O
and	O
standing	O
at	O
some	O
small	O
Distance	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
himself	O
pawned	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Cloth	O
was	O
found	O
where	O
pawned	O
,	O
and	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Mendez	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
going	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Wild	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Wild	O
coming	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
Show	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Wild	O
,	O
say	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
I	O
fear	O
is	O
,	O
after	O
I	O
am	O
dead	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
carried	O
to	O
Surgeons	O
Hall	O
and	O
anatomized	O
:	O
To	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Wild	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
would	O
take	O
Care	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
Coffin	O
.	O
Quilt	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Wild	O
,	O
to	O
apprehend	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
himself	O
going	O
to	O
his	O
Chamber	O
,	O
bid	O
him	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
swearing	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
burst	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
a	O
Pen-knife	O
drawn	O
,	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
kill	O
any	O
Body	O
that	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
it	O
was	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Wild	O
was	O
not	O
far	O
off	O
;	O
saying	O
,	O
throw	O
down	O
your	O
Pen-knife	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
will	O
chop	O
off	O
your	O
Arm	O
:	O
And	O
upon	O
this	O
he	O
threw	O
down	O
the	O
Knife	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
apprehended	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
hear	O
Mr.	O
Wild	O
say	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
Coffin	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
or	O
having	O
any	O
Acquaintance	O
with	O
William	O
Field	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
was	O
proved	O
beyond	O
Contradiction	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
proceeded	O
to	O
object	O
against	O
the	O
Credibility	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
;	O
but	O
had	O
no	O
legal	O
Objection	O
to	O
offer	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
colour	O
his	O
resisting	O
Quilt	O
Arnold	O
with	O
his	O
Penknife	O
,	O
he	O
supposing	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Bailiff	O
coming	O
to	O
arrest	O
him	O
.	O
And	O
having	O
no	O
further	O
Defence	O
to	O
make	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
proceeded	O
to	O
tell	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
Morning	O
last	O
,	O
Jonathan	O
Wild	O
said	O
to	O
Simon	B-pers
Jacobs	I-pers
,	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
bring	O
40	O
l.	O
this	O
Time	O
,	O
I	O
with	O
Joe	O
was	O
in	O
your	O
Case	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
he'sa	O
dead	O
Man	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
will	O
do	O
my	O
endeavour	O
to	O
bring	O
you	O
off	O
as	O
a	O
single	O
Felon	O
.	O
But	O
speaking	O
to	O
him	O
(	O
this	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
must	O
die	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
send	O
you	O
a	O
good	O
book	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
shall	O
not	O
be	O
anatomized	O
;	O
I	O
'll	O
provide	O
you	O
a	O
Coffin	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Account	O
he	O
gave	O
of	O
the	O
discourse	O
between	O
Mr.	O
Wild	O
and	O
himself	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
proceed	O
to	O
tell	O
the	O
Court	O
that	O
he	O
cut	O
his	O
Throat	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
not	O
taken	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
by	O
beating	O
and	O
bruising	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
Breast	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
of	O
Which	O
Bruises	O
and	O
Blows	O
he	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
feloniously	O
killing	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
Roberts	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
a	O
drinking	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Company	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
occasion	O
to	O
call	O
the	O
Deceased	O
a	O
reproachful	O
Name	O
,	O
which	O
giving	O
occasion	O
for	O
more	O
provoking	O
Language	O
,	O
they	O
fell	O
to	O
fighting	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Surgeons	O
deposing	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
perceive	O
any	O
Marks	O
of	O
Violence	O
on	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
;	O
but	O
a	O
great	O
Inflammation	O
of	O
the	O
Pleura	O
and	O
other	O
Parts	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
were	O
occasioned	O
by	O
any	O
Blows	O
given	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
rather	O
died	O
of	O
a	O
Fever	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
was	O
occasioned	O
by	O
the	O
Blows	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bruff	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
brown	O
Mare	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Sneeth	I-pers
the	O
25th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Eustace	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Mug	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
and	I-pers
Thomas	I-pers
Lambert	I-pers
the	O
3rd	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
Fountain-Tavern	B-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Strand	I-place
,	O
to	O
drink	O
in	O
Company	O
of	O
one	O
George	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
a	O
Bricklayer	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
drank	O
3	O
Pints	O
of	O
Wine	O
and	O
din	O
'd	O
there	O
,	O
had	O
3	O
Pints	O
more	O
after	O
dinner	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Mug	O
being	O
carried	O
them	O
with	O
Drink	O
,	O
was	O
immediately	O
missing	O
:	O
That	O
the	O
Drawer	O
having	O
observed	O
her	O
when	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
to	O
stoop	O
and	O
make	O
some	O
Motions	O
with	O
her	O
Hands	O
about	O
her	O
Coats	O
,	O
he	O
suspected	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
at	O
her	O
going	O
away	O
having	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
marry	O
'd	O
Man	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
occasion	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Mantua-maker	O
,	O
and	O
liv	O
'd	O
but	O
over	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
sent	O
out	O
the	O
Porter	O
in	O
quest	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
bringing	O
Word	O
where	O
the	O
Man	O
and	O
she	O
were	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
calling	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Room	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
stooping	O
Posture	O
;	O
and	O
immediately	O
at	O
his	O
entering	O
the	O
Room	O
the	O
Mug	O
drop	O
'd	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
Coats	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
her	O
stealing	O
the	O
Mug	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
George	O
Austin	O
set	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
Room	O
,	O
desiring	O
it	O
might	O
stand	O
there	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
gone	O
down	O
,	O
she	O
having	O
occasion	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
make	O
Water	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Katherine	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
divers	O
Persons	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Butroy	I-pers
the	O
2nd	O
of	O
this	O
present	O
October	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Esther	B-pers
Montgomery	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Pancrass	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Linen	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Montague	I-pers
the	O
24th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
assisted	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
in	O
washing	O
Linen	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
a	O
Washer-woman	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Susannah	B-pers
O	I-pers
Brian	I-pers
the	O
4th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bonshaw	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
60	O
Pounds	O
of	O
Sugar	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
and	I-pers
Company	I-pers
and	O
Company	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Sugar	O
was	O
stolen	O
out	O
of	O
a	B-place
Lighter	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
River	I-place
of	I-place
Thames	I-place
:	O
And	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Austin	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Cartwright	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
in	O
counterfeiting	O
the	O
current	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
indicted	O
the	O
second	O
Time	O
for	O
feloniously	O
having	O
in	O
their	O
Custody	O
,	O
and	O
concealing	O
Utensils	O
for	O
coining	O
,	O
the	O
31	O
st	O
Day	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
1724.	O
Henry	B-pers
March	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Joiner	O
or	O
Cabinet-maker	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
wrought	O
as	O
a	O
Journeyman	O
with	O
Cartwright	O
Richardson	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
both	O
he	O
and	O
Austin	O
sent	O
him	O
away	O
from	O
the	O
Work-house	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
)	O
in	O
Black	O
Raven	O
Court	O
in	O
Chiswell-street	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
latter	O
End	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
pretending	O
they	O
had	O
some	O
Experiments	O
to	O
make	O
,	O
by	O
way	O
of	O
melting	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
their	O
Lodging	O
for	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
Work	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
to	O
it	O
found	O
Embers	O
of	O
Charcoal	O
,	O
some	O
Crucibles	O
and	O
Metal	O
.	O
That	O
Austin	O
Richardson	O
coming	O
about	O
9	O
or	O
10	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
he	O
enquired	O
what	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
doing	O
:	O
That	O
thereupon	O
he	O
answered	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
making	O
some	O
Trials	O
as	O
to	O
coining	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
having	O
melted	O
Brass	O
for	O
that	O
Purpose	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
make	O
it	O
bear	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
told	O
by	O
a	O
Friend	O
of	O
something	O
that	O
would	O
do	O
better	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
try	O
the	O
Experiment	O
with	O
that	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
about	O
the	O
8th	O
or	O
9th	O
of	O
March	O
following	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
coin	O
with	O
Several	O
Metals	O
mixt	O
12	O
Pieces	O
in	O
the	O
Likeness	O
of	O
King	O
Charles	O
the	O
Second	O
's	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
25	O
Pieces	O
in	O
the	O
Likeness	O
of	O
Half	O
Crowns	O
:	O
And	O
that	O
the	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
following	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
Austin	O
Richardson	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
put	O
off	O
one	O
of	O
these	O
Half	O
Crowns	O
at	O
a	O
great	O
Wholesale	O
Grocers	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
some	O
Days	O
after	O
,	O
Cartwright	O
Richardson	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
why	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
to	O
put	O
the	O
Money	O
off	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
put	O
off	O
one	O
of	O
those	O
Half	O
Crowns	O
at	O
a	O
Cheesemonger	O
's	O
Shop	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
over	O
against	O
Covent-Garden	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
no	O
farther	O
concern	O
'd	O
than	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
then	O
they	O
bid	O
him	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
Tools	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
hid	O
them	O
under	O
the	O
Boards	O
of	O
a	O
Floor	O
in	O
the	O
Closet	O
.	O
That	O
afterwards	O
Austin	O
Richardson	O
was	O
arrested	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
he	O
threatned	O
to	O
impeach	O
him	O
(	O
this	O
Witness	O
)	O
of	O
Coining	O
:	O
Whereupon	O
he	O
thought	O
best	O
to	O
secure	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Morgan	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
ordered	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Pinkney	O
,	O
Deputy-Warden	O
of	O
the	O
Mint	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
Affair	O
of	O
Coinage	O
in	O
his	O
Absence	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
gone	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
and	O
acquainted	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Matter	O
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
But	O
being	O
arrested	O
on	O
Monday	O
on	O
an	O
Action	O
of	O
20	O
l.	O
by	O
Cartwright	O
Richardson	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
make	O
out	O
his	O
Information	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
appointed	O
Mr.	O
Morgan	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Marshalsea	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Morgan	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
March	O
did	O
come	O
to	O
him	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
and	O
inform	O
'd	O
him	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
Brothers	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
concerned	O
in	O
Coining	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
proposing	O
to	O
have	O
them	O
apprehended	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
it	O
alone	O
a	O
Day	O
or	O
two	O
longer	O
,	O
because	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Brothers	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
promising	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
to	O
him	O
again	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
a	O
Person	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
Cartwright	O
Richardson	O
had	O
arrested	O
March	O
,	O
thrown	O
him	O
into	O
Prison	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
come	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
advis	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
Justice	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
Examination	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
afterwards	O
he	O
having	O
given	O
an	O
Account	O
where	O
the	O
coining	O
Utensils	O
were	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
with	O
an	O
Officer	O
to	O
apprehend	O
Cartwright	O
Richardson	O
(	O
for	O
Austin	O
Richardson	O
was	O
then	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Counter	O
)	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
in	O
Swan-Alley	O
near	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
,	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
them	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
when	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
sieze	O
the	O
Utensils	O
.	O
And	O
taking	O
up	O
some	O
Boards	O
found	O
them	O
under	O
the	O
Floor	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
Floor	O
and	O
the	O
Cieling	O
in	O
a	O
Closet	O
in	O
Black	B-place
Raven	I-place
Court	I-place
in	I-place
Chiswell-street	I-place
.	O
Mr.	O
Woodman	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
having	O
received	O
a	O
Note	O
from	O
Henry	O
March	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
giving	O
him	O
an	O
Account	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
put	O
in	O
Prison	O
at	O
the	O
Suit	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
not	O
give	O
his	O
Information	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
:	O
He	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Morgan	O
in	O
the	O
Tower	O
,	O
and	O
Measures	O
were	O
concerned	O
to	O
get	O
Justice	O
Nichols	O
to	O
take	O
March	O
's	O
Information	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prison	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
there	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
also	O
went	O
and	O
talk	O
'd	O
with	O
Cartwright	O
Richardson	O
,	O
about	O
arresting	O
March	O
,	O
who	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Lawyer	O
,	O
to	O
answer	O
him	O
;	O
who	O
speaking	O
in	O
the	O
Plural	O
Terms	O
,	O
owned	O
,	O
that	O
March	O
did	O
not	O
owe	O
them	O
20	O
l.	O
but	O
did	O
owe	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
Reasons	O
for	O
arresting	O
him	O
,	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Sum	O
,	O
beyond	O
his	O
Capacity	O
of	O
getting	O
Bail	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
they	O
known	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
done	O
such	O
a	O
Thing	O
to	O
hang	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
hang	O
him	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
when	O
Cartwright	O
saw	O
the	O
Utensils	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
sell	O
into	O
an	O
Agony	O
and	O
Fit	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
The	O
Lord	O
have	O
Mercy	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
enough	O
to	O
hang	O
an	O
hundred	O
People	O
;	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
Brother	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
an	O
ill	O
Character	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Barret	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
apprehend	O
Cartwright	O
,	O
at	O
Austin	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
Swan	O
Alley	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
deny	O
'd	O
;	O
but	O
searching	O
the	O
House	O
they	O
broke	O
open	O
a	O
Chamber	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
not	O
opening	O
it	O
:	O
That	O
when	O
they	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
apprehended	O
him	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
so	O
.	O
The	O
finding	O
the	O
Tools	O
as	O
before	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
several	O
Evidences	O
;	O
and	O
Moulds	O
,	O
Crucibles	O
,	O
and	O
Pieces	O
of	O
melted	O
Mettal	O
were	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
;	O
and	O
also	O
a	O
false	O
Half	O
Crown	O
,	O
which	O
March	O
swore	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
those	O
coined	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
himself	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
utterly	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
or	O
having	O
any	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
the	O
Utensils	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
Utensils	O
being	O
found	O
there	O
,	O
they	O
insinuated	O
they	O
might	O
be	O
put	O
there	O
by	O
March	O
himself	O
,	O
by	O
Way	O
of	O
Revenge	O
,	O
in	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
Difference	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
pawned	O
two	O
of	O
Austin	O
's	O
Clock	O
Cases	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
their	O
Tools	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
they	O
had	O
threatened	O
to	O
arrest	O
him	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
threatened	O
,	O
That	O
if	O
they	O
did	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
hang	O
Austin	O
.	O
That	O
March	O
did	O
come	O
to	O
Cartwright	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
23	O
d	O
of	O
August	O
(	O
the	O
Day	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
and	O
accused	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Morgan	O
in	O
the	O
Tower	O
)	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
in	O
Black	O
Raven	O
Court	O
,	O
(	O
where	O
the	O
Tools	O
were	O
found	O
)	O
under	O
Pretence	O
of	O
showing	O
it	O
to	O
an	O
Acquaintance	O
of	O
his	O
Wife	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
Midwife	O
,	O
in	O
Order	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
the	O
Key	O
two	O
Hours	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
Time	O
he	O
might	O
hide	O
the	O
Tools	O
there	O
,	O
in	O
Order	O
to	O
carry	O
on	O
his	O
Plot	O
against	O
them	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Key	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
by	O
two	O
Evidences	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
kept	O
it	O
near	O
two	O
Hours	O
,	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
though	O
March	O
pretended	O
he	O
brought	O
it	O
again	O
in	O
Half	O
an	O
Hour	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
produce	O
this	O
Midwife	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
Person	O
,	O
that	O
did	O
want	O
to	O
see	O
it	O
,	O
in	O
Order	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
And	O
it	O
was	O
highly	O
probable	O
,	O
the	O
Reason	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Morgan	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
Notice	O
of	O
two	O
Brothers	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
consent	O
to	O
compleat	O
his	O
Information	O
,	O
not	O
go	O
immediately	O
to	O
apprehend	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
put	O
it	O
off	O
till	O
Monday	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
Key	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
Tools	O
there	O
:	O
Which	O
was	O
more	O
probable	O
,	O
in	O
that	O
his	O
Pretence	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
Austin	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
when	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
he	O
knew	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
That	O
as	O
to	O
their	O
arresting	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
to	O
prevent	O
his	O
proceeding	O
in	O
his	O
Impeachment	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
really	O
owe	O
them	O
4	O
l.	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
Evidences	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Reason	O
of	O
arresting	O
him	O
for	O
so	O
much	O
beyond	O
that	O
Sum	O
was	O
,	O
Because	O
they	O
were	O
bound	O
for	O
him	O
in	O
several	O
Sums	O
.	O
And	O
though	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
arrested	O
'till	O
the	O
Monday	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
informed	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
knew	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
so	O
;	O
and	O
though	O
the	O
Process	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
not	O
Serv	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
entred	O
Several	O
Days	O
before	O
.	O
To	O
lessen	O
the	O
Credit	O
of	O
March	O
's	O
Evidence	O
,	O
they	O
urg	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
an	O
infamous	O
Character	O
,	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
their	O
Goods	O
,	O
stole	O
their	O
Tools	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
this	O
in	O
Revenge	O
,	O
because	O
they	O
had	O
threatened	O
to	O
arrest	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
what	O
he	O
stood	O
indebted	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
more	O
than	O
once	O
convicted	O
of	O
Perjury	O
,	O
had	O
stood	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
at	O
Rochester	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
burnt	O
a	O
Ship	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
Records	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
They	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Persons	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
them	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
also	O
observ	O
'd	O
,	O
in	O
Favour	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Proof	O
of	O
the	O
putting	O
off	O
the	O
two	O
Half	O
Crowns	O
,	O
the	O
one	O
by	O
Austin	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
by	O
Cartwright	O
,	O
depended	O
intirely	O
on	O
the	O
Credit	O
of	O
March	O
's	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Persons	O
to	O
whom	O
they	O
were	O
said	O
to	O
be	O
put	O
off	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
living	O
at	O
no	O
great	O
Distance	O
,	O
were	O
not	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
who	O
might	O
probably	O
remember	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
about	O
that	O
Time	O
taken	O
such	O
Money	O
.	O
Upon	O
a	O
full	O
Hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Tyrrel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
's	I-place
Hackney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brown	O
Mare	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
2	O
d	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Mare	O
was	O
stolen	O
from	O
Stoke	B-place
Newington	I-place
,	O
and	O
sold	O
to	O
one	O
Kemp	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
He	O
bought	O
the	O
Mare	O
of	O
one	O
Farmer	O
Whiting	B-pers
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
Evidences	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Faircloth	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dustan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gander	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Cheyney	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
marrying	O
a	O
second	O
Husband	O
,	O
a	O
first	O
Husband	O
being	O
alive	O
.	O
But	O
both	O
Marriages	O
being	O
both	O
before	O
the	O
last	O
Act	O
of	O
Grace	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Moidore	O
,	O
3	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Luke	B-pers
Parot	I-pers
,	O
the	O
22	O
d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
in	O
Gracechurch-street	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
to	O
Hatton	B-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
and	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
What	O
he	O
went	O
there	O
for	O
?	O
He	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
being	O
in	O
Liquor	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
perhaps	O
,	O
to	O
do	O
what	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
do	O
:	O
But	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
yet	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Tailor	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Eli	B-pers
Reed	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Woolley	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Quilt	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Shop	O
was	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
by	O
the	O
Watch	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
John	O
Tailor	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
going	O
Home	O
saw	O
two	O
Men	O
talking	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Things	O
upon	O
the	O
Bulk	O
.	O
Eli	O
Reed	O
pretended	O
,	O
He	O
met	O
with	O
Tailor	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
help	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
Lodging	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
then	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
a	O
Bundle	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
,	I-pers
the	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Miles	I-pers
Allison	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Confession	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cleg	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
pave	O
a	O
Yard	O
with	O
Brick	O
,	O
and	O
perswading	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
lay	O
a	O
Brick	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
doing	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
sent	O
for	O
some	O
Ale	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
drinking	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
the	O
Ring	O
off	O
her	O
Finger	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
Excuses	O
for	O
not	O
returning	O
it	O
,	O
'till	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
swore	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
it	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
deny	O
'd	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
rather	O
a	O
Trespass	O
than	O
a	O
Felony	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
acquitned	O
.	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
4	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
Evidence	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Fredrick	B-pers
Discount	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Butoloph	I-place
's	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Maplesdon	I-pers
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
at	O
the	O
Barber	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
treating	O
about	O
buying	O
the	O
Wig	O
,	O
offering	O
a	O
Guinea	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
Thompson	O
not	O
allowing	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
under	O
25	O
s.	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
hung	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Block	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Box	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
afterwards	O
took	O
the	O
Wig	O
unknown	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
He	O
bought	O
the	O
Wig	O
,	O
that	O
Maplesdon	O
had	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
Maplesdon	O
came	O
to	O
ask	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
25	O
s.	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
Wig	O
he	O
bought	O
of	O
him	O
:	O
And	O
afterwards	O
told	O
him	O
another	O
Time	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
sorry	O
he	O
should	O
take	O
out	O
a	O
Warrant	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
Fault	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
pay	O
him	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bone	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bay	O
Horse	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Polsen	I-pers
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
an	O
Under-Bailiff	O
to	O
the	O
Bishop	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
took	O
it	O
as	O
a	O
Stray	O
Horse	O
:	O
It	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
Pound	O
,	O
publickly	O
apprais	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
publickly	O
sold	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
Ground	O
for	O
a	O
Charge	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
:	O
And	O
the	O
Court	O
granted	O
him	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Murphy	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilbey	I-pers
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
left	O
his	O
Cloaths	O
with	O
his	O
Sister	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Back	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
from	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
sister	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
married	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
three	O
Days	O
after	O
.	O
It	O
not	O
appearing	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
sister	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Tone	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
French	I-pers
,	O
the	O
23	O
d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
James	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Tailor	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
were	O
intimate	O
Acquaintance	O
:	O
And	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Warrant	O
for	O
the	O
apprehending	O
Tailor	O
and	O
Collins	O
,	O
who	O
have	O
been	O
since	O
convicted	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
absconded	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
informed	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
France	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
meet	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
'till	O
he	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
Newgate	O
for	O
another	O
Fact	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Butterworth	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
William	O
Harvey	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
George	O
Tailor	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
Mistress	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Clothes	O
,	O
which	O
French	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
were	O
his	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
entirely	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
he	O
ever	O
was	O
with	O
Tailor	O
at	O
the	O
selling	O
the	O
Suit	O
of	O
Clothes	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hulls	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Precinct	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Katherines	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Prior	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
left	O
in	O
a	O
Chest	O
in	O
a	O
Barge	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
belonged	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
;	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
in	O
Half	O
Pence	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleading	O
he	O
laid	O
out	O
the	O
Money	O
for	O
Mr	O
.	O
Prior	O
's	O
Use	O
the	O
,	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Ellison	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
,	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
,	O
whereas	O
Isaac	B-pers
Deering	I-pers
was	O
at	O
the	O
Sessions	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
convicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
13	O
Hundred	O
Weight	O
of	O
Iron	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Trueman	I-pers
,	I-pers
and	I-pers
Company	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Company	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
receive	O
them	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Isaac	O
Deering	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
sell	O
13	O
Hundred	O
Weight	O
of	O
Iron	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
stolen	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Truman	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
Penny	O
a	O
Pound	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
stolen	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
.	O
And	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
Let	O
him	O
bring	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
he	O
would	O
he	O
would	O
buy	O
it	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
calling	O
several	O
Persons	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
they	O
liv	O
'd	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Edward	B-pers
Lob	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
two	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
having	O
come	O
from	O
his	O
Work	O
at	O
Windsor	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
near	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
weary	O
,	O
he	O
sat	O
down	O
on	O
a	O
Bench	O
in	O
Bear-street	B-place
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
a	O
Man	O
came	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
enter	O
'd	O
into	O
Discourse	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
pretending	O
she	O
had	O
travelled	O
30	O
Miles	O
too	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
weary	O
and	O
dry	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
saying	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
his	O
Purse	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
,	O
but	O
presently	O
suspecting	O
them	O
put	O
it	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Man	O
jump	O
'd	O
up	O
upon	O
the	O
Bench	O
and	O
pulled	O
him	O
down	O
backwards	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
describing	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
30	O
s.	O
of	O
his	O
Money	O
again	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
positive	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
confirmed	O
the	O
return	O
of	O
the	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
knew	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
loose	O
Person	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
seen	O
her	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
about	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
her	O
by	O
his	O
Description	O
.	O
After	O
a	O
full	O
Hearing	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Staining	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Frances	B-pers
Slade	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
2	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
from	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Isham	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
Geneva	O
,	O
and	O
showed	O
him	O
a	O
handful	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
he	O
believes	O
18	O
or	O
20	O
Guineas	O
;	O
and	O
to	O
convince	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
Gold	O
,	O
put	O
2	O
Broad	O
Pieces	O
into	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
-	O
Lion	O
,	O
a	O
Watchman	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
her	O
about	O
12	O
or	O
1	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
She	O
wanted	O
him	O
to	O
light	O
her	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
Shilling	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
handful	O
of	O
Gold	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
gave	O
Notice	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Hare	I-pers
,	O
who	O
acquainted	O
the	O
Constable	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
Lodging	O
they	O
heard	O
her	O
say	O
to	O
a	O
Woman	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
get	O
up	O
,	O
you	O
Bitch	O
,	O
and	O
get	O
me	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
may	O
be	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
get	O
away	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
.	O
John	O
Hare	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
having	O
given	O
the	O
Constable	O
Notice	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
asking	O
her	O
for	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
she	O
replied	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
her	O
private	O
Parts	O
;	O
she	O
dropped	O
2	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
and	O
some	O
Half	O
pence	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Penney	I-pers
the	O
Constable	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Watchman	O
giving	O
him	O
Notice	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
believed	O
she	O
had	O
picked	O
some	O
Body	O
's	O
Pocket	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
some	O
Watchmen	O
to	O
her	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Night	O
being	O
still	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
making	O
no	O
Noise	O
,	O
heard	O
a	O
Woman	O
's	O
Voice	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Room	O
say	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
you	O
have	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Watch	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
for	O
he	O
knew	O
her	O
Voice	O
)	O
answered	O
,	O
no	O
matter	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
all	O
his	O
Gold	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
Bitch	O
,	O
go	O
get	O
me	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
Guinea	O
.	O
That	O
a	O
Person	O
,	O
he	O
supposes	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
in	O
his	O
Staff	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
examining	O
her	O
where	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
own	O
having	O
any	O
Money	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
ordering	O
the	O
Watch	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
her	O
Privy	O
Parts	O
(	O
but	O
she	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
the	O
plain	O
Name	O
.	O
)	O
And	O
saying	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
as	O
she	O
ought	O
to	O
be	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
fit	O
to	O
be	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
let	O
her	O
alone	O
she	O
would	O
search	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
permit	O
her	O
,	O
then	O
she	O
stoop	O
'd	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
her	O
Hand	O
under	O
her	O
Coats	O
,	O
a	O
Guinea	O
dropped	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
afterwards	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
another	O
Guinea	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
saw	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
before	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Half	O
pence	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
which	O
she	O
said	O
was	O
her	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
gave	O
that	O
to	O
her	O
again	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
suspect	O
that	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
that	O
she	O
pretended	O
to	O
pull	O
out	O
the	O
2	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
put	O
the	O
rest	O
further	O
up	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
afterwards	O
owned	O
there	O
were	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
more	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
Stone-Cutters	B-place
Alley	I-place
,	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
what	O
she	O
stood	O
there	O
for	O
?	O
She	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
stood	O
there	O
to	O
wait	O
for	O
Money	O
and	O
good	O
Company	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
laid	O
her	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Stones	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
Doing	O
her	O
over	O
,	O
she	O
put	O
her	O
Hand	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
and	O
took	O
some	O
Silver	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
try	O
farther	O
,	O
she	O
put	O
her	O
Fingers	O
into	O
his	O
Fob	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
his	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
thought	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
stay	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
went	O
away	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
And	O
added	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
never	O
been	O
better	O
pleased	O
by	O
any	O
Woman	O
in	O
his	O
life	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
also	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
put	O
an	O
Advertisement	O
into	O
the	O
News	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Person	O
came	O
and	O
demanded	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
his	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
that	O
would	O
not	O
appear	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Person	O
must	O
come	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
some	O
Satisfaction	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
his	O
,	O
because	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
Expressions	O
between	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Gentleman	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
communicated	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
be	O
Tokens	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Owner	O
thereof	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
before	O
she	O
began	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
demanded	O
the	O
2	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Constable	O
's	O
Hands	O
,	O
promising	O
,	O
that	O
then	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
an	O
Account	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Judge	O
promising	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
give	O
a	O
good	O
Account	O
of	O
it	O
she	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
gave	O
the	O
following	O
Account	O
:	O
That	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
,	O
about	O
8	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
in	O
Great	O
Queen-street	O
and	O
had	O
just	O
been	O
drinking	O
a	O
Dram	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
Stick	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
alone	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
her	O
her	O
Stick	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
was	O
dark	O
sighted	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
home	O
without	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
laid	O
her	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
or	O
Stone	O
at	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Door	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
thrust	O
his	O
Hand	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
whole	O
handful	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
her	O
Hand	O
would	O
hold	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
2	O
Men	O
coming	O
by	O
making	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
went	O
away	O
and	O
left	O
her	O
.	O
Then	O
afterwards	O
she	O
did	O
go	O
to	O
Isham	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
Geneva	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
show	O
the	O
Money	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
being	O
dark	O
sighted	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
glad	O
to	O
hear	O
it	O
was	O
Gold	O
,	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Crown	O
Bowl	O
of	O
Punch	O
,	O
bought	O
a	O
Riding	O
Hood	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Clothes	O
of	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
for	O
her	O
Rigging	O
before	O
was	O
very	O
mean	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
did	O
give	O
the	O
Watchman	O
a	O
Shilling	O
to	O
light	O
her	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
her	O
Landlady	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
she	O
owing	O
her	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
interim	O
of	O
the	O
Time	O
the	O
Constable	O
and	O
Watch	O
came	O
and	O
carried	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
Money	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Towers	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Web	I-pers
with	O
John	B-pers
Bowler	I-pers
,	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Tibs	I-pers
,	O
&	O
c.	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
White-Chappel	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
riotously	O
assaulting	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Brookbank	I-pers
,	O
being	O
in	O
Company	O
of	O
60	O
other	O
Persons	O
arm	O
'd	O
with	O
Swords	O
,	O
Staves	O
,	O
Clubs	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
white	O
Shirts	O
with	O
their	O
Faces	O
black	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
12	O
Pounds	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
14	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
a	O
Stone	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Liquors	O
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
not	O
being	O
to	O
the	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
they	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Towers	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Shadwel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
third	O
Time	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Westwood	I-pers
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hatcher	O
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
was	O
assaulted	O
,	O
the	O
Door	O
burst	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Hatchet	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
's	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
being	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
the	O
Hatchet	O
was	O
carried	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
fourth	O
Time	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
White-Chappel	B-place
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Huggins	I-pers
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
several	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Accomplices	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
not	O
been	O
well	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
eating	O
Broth	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Spoon	O
stood	O
in	O
a	O
Poringer	O
in	O
the	O
Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
Charles	O
Towers	O
took	O
the	O
Spoon	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
called	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
bidding	O
him	O
not	O
carry	O
away	O
the	O
Spoon	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
carry	O
it	O
quite	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Simon	B-pers
Jacobs	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Joseph	I-pers
Guest	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Harcourt	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Desk	O
in	O
the	O
Crown-Office	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
3	O
Times	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
lost	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
enquiring	O
of	O
the	O
Maid	O
who	O
she	O
gave	O
the	O
Key	O
to	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Porter	O
's	O
Son	O
;	O
then	O
examining	O
Thomas	B-pers
Charlton	I-pers
the	O
Porter	O
's	O
Son	O
,	O
he	O
owned	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
gotten	O
the	O
Key	O
at	O
the	O
Desire	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
2	O
more	O
,	O
the	O
one	O
called	O
White	B-pers
Will	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
.	O
He	O
describ	O
'd	O
their	O
Persons	O
and	O
Haunt	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
Boy	O
's	O
Description	O
and	O
Account	O
;	O
That	O
the	O
two	O
Persons	O
before	O
mentioned	O
,	O
and	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Desk	O
with	O
the	O
Poker	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
gave	O
him	O
2	O
Guineas	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
for	O
tearing	O
a	O
Receipt	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
for	O
6	O
l.	O
6	O
s.	O
for	O
the	O
Interest	O
of	O
60	O
l.	O
for	O
6	O
Months	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
Defect	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lowen	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bow	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Ward	I-place
of	I-place
Cheap	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Bland	I-pers
the	O
19th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Cheapside	B-place
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
Suspected	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
having	O
that	O
Handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
more	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
try	O
'd	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Handkerchiefs	O
from	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
:	O
But	O
of	O
this	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Jenkin	B-pers
Bulcock	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
7	O
Yards	O
of	O
Dowlas	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Tooth	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Bradley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bartholomew	I-place
's	I-place
Exchange	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
the	O
19th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
calling	O
for	O
a	O
Gill	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
Sugar	O
in	O
a	O
Spoon	O
,	O
carried	O
away	O
the	O
Spoon	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Corney	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bennet	I-place
's	I-place
Gracechurch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Pounds	O
of	O
Glue	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Plumstead	I-pers
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Walsum	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Walson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Smithson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Lawson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Christopher	I-place
's	I-place
Broadstreet	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Julian	B-pers
,	O
a	O
Black	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
20	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
burning	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Turner	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
his	O
Mother	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Night	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
smelt	O
a	O
Smoke	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
out	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
;	O
and	O
going	O
into	O
one	O
Chamber	O
,	O
found	O
it	O
all	O
on	O
Fire	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
broke	O
forth	O
with	O
such	O
Violence	O
that	O
the	O
Family	O
narrowly	O
escaped	O
with	O
their	O
Lives	O
.	O
That	O
supposing	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
by	O
some	O
Body	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
examined	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
owned	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
did	O
also	O
before	O
Sir	O
Francis	B-pers
Forbes	I-pers
.	O
His	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
wherein	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
Days	O
before	O
taken	O
20	O
or	O
30	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
in	O
Fear	O
left	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
found	O
out	O
,	O
did	O
put	O
a	O
Candle	O
under	O
the	O
Sheets	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
up	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
and	O
left	O
it	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Design	O
to	O
set	O
Fire	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
burn	O
not	O
only	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
all	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
fetch	O
'd	O
down	O
the	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
Canal	O
in	O
the	O
Garden	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
by	O
his	O
own	O
Confession	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Lewis	B-pers
Hussar	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
try	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Appeal	O
of	O
Solomon	B-pers
Rondeau	I-pers
,	O
Brother	O
and	O
Heir	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Hussar	I-pers
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
by	O
cutting	O
her	O
Throat	O
with	O
a	O
Razor	O
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
After	O
some	O
considerable	O
Debate	O
:	O
concerning	O
some	O
Preliminaries	O
between	O
the	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
Appellant	O
and	O
Appellee	O
,	O
they	O
agreed	O
to	O
join	O
Issue	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Plea	O
,	O
which	O
contain	O
'd	O
some	O
Matters	O
in	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
in	O
Abatement	O
.	O
The	O
Matters	O
contained	O
in	O
the	O
Defendant	O
's	O
Plan	O
,	O
were	O
as	O
follows	O
:	O
1	O
.	O
That	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
Appeal	O
(	O
besides	O
that	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
now	O
pleaded	O
)	O
yet	O
depending	O
and	O
undetermin	O
'd	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
A	O
Misnomer	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Name	O
was	O
not	O
Lewis	O
,	O
but	O
Loui	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Addition	O
of	O
Labourer	O
was	O
not	O
right	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Barber	O
Chirurgeon	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
a	O
Labourer	O
.	O
4	O
.	O
That	O
there	O
were	O
no	O
such	O
Persons	O
in	O
rerum	O
natura	O
,	O
as	O
John	B-pers
Doe	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Roe	I-pers
(	O
mentioned	O
as	O
Pledges	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Appeal	O
.	O
)	O
5	O
.	O
That	O
Solomon	B-pers
Rondeau	I-pers
was	O
not	O
the	O
proper	O
Appellant	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
one	O
Henry	B-pers
Rondeau	I-pers
was	O
Brother	O
and	O
Heir	O
to	O
Ann	O
Hussar	O
,	O
and	O
Solomon	O
was	O
her	O
Brother	O
and	O
Heir	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
charged	O
in	O
the	O
Said	O
Appeal	O
.	O
The	O
Defendant	O
failed	O
in	O
the	O
Proof	O
of	O
his	O
Plea	O
:	O
For	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
First	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Records	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
former	O
Appeal	O
was	O
quash	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
not	O
depending	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Defendant	O
had	O
pleaded	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
Second	O
,	O
It	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
own	O
Hand-writing	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
used	O
to	O
