TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice	O
Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
12th	O
,	O
13th	O
,	O
and	O
14th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Eleventh	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
PETER	B-pers
DELME	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Serjeant	O
at	O
Law	O
;	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
JURORS	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
The	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Pargister	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Drinkhill	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
Mark	B-pers
Neuth	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hutton	I-pers
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
May	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Beaton	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Illin	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Winn	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Fish	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hern	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Tailor	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Atley	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fry	I-pers
,	O
Valentine	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hyron	I-pers
,	O
Maurice	B-pers
Boheme	I-pers
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Hutchins	I-pers
,	O
Marmaduke	B-pers
Bramley	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Burchet	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Claxton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Shift	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Clement	I-pers
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Shift	O
was	O
hung	O
out	O
in	O
a	O
Yard	O
to	O
dry	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
off	O
from	O
the	O
Line	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
an	O
outcry	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
down	O
the	O
Shift	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Grimes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Peter	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Newnham	I-pers
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
going	O
thro	O
'	O
Peter	B-place
's	I-place
Alley	I-place
in	I-place
Cornhil	I-place
,	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Person	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
receiv	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
an	O
outcry	O
threw	O
it	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
apprehended	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Hogs	O
,	O
value	O
36	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Hogs	O
were	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Neighbour	O
's	O
Yard	O
,	O
at	O
Westminster	B-place
,	O
and	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
selling	O
them	O
at	O
Smithfield	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
leather	O
Shoes	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Frazier	I-pers
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Shoes	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Stall	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
apprehended	O
between	O
2	O
and	O
3	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
by	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
pleaded	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Midwife	O
,	O
about	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Shoes	O
in	O
a	O
Sack	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
and	I-pers
Ann	I-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
in	O
keeping	O
knowingly	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
in	O
their	O
Possession	O
,	O
a	O
Press	O
and	O
a	O
Mould	O
for	O
Coining	O
,	O
contrary	O
to	O
the	O
Statute	O
in	O
that	O
Case	O
made	O
and	O
provided	O
,	O
they	O
having	O
concealed	O
them	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
to	O
lodge	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
missing	O
two	O
pewter	O
Pots	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
the	O
Pots	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
gone	O
abroad	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
Girl	O
their	O
Daughter	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
under	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Mettle	O
lie	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
which	O
giving	O
her	O
some	O
suspicion	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
Daughter	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Tools	O
under	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
Cords	O
and	O
Marring	O
,	O
bundled	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
some	O
melted	O
Mettle	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
Daughter	O
raking	O
in	O
the	O
Ashes	O
,	O
found	O
a	O
false	O
Shilling	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
hold	O
of	O
a	O
Silk	O
Rag	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Hole	O
of	O
the	O
Chimney	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Andirons	O
used	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
pulling	O
out	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
Silk	O
.	O
5	O
other	O
Shillings	O
sell	O
out	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
false	O
Shillings	O
;	O
the	O
Mould	O
and	O
Money	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
when	O
Ann	O
Lewis	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
being	O
in	O
drink	O
,	O
she	O
gave	O
her	O
Daughter	O
a	O
good	O
and	O
bad	O
Shilling	O
before	O
she	O
lay	O
'd	O
her	O
self	O
down	O
to	O
sleep	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Hannah	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Daughter	O
confessed	O
that	O
one	O
Howel	O
used	O
to	O
make	O
those	O
Shillings	O
,	O
30	O
or	O
40	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
.	O
Margaret	O
Thompson	O
's	O
Daughter	O
depos	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
her	O
Mother	O
had	O
done	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
deny	O
'd	O
their	O
knowing	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
Tools	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Pedlar	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
a	O
Soldier	O
one	O
Night	O
during	O
the	O
time	O
they	O
lodg	O
'd	O
there	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Landlady	O
allowed	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Acquaintance	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
,	O
upon	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
and	I-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
Howel	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
in	O
counterfeiting	O
the	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
and	O
making	O
4	O
Pieces	O
in	O
the	O
resemblance	O
of	O
King	O
William	O
the	O
third	O
's	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Thomas	O
Howel	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
her	O
Father	O
's	O
Cellar	O
,	O
near	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Pound	I-place
,	O
and	O
there	O
did	O
several	O
times	O
with	O
the	O
Moulds	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
being	O
filled	O
with	O
Chalk	O
,	O
and	O
making	O
an	O
impression	O
with	O
a	O
good	O
Shilling	O
,	O
pour	O
in	O
melted	O
Mettle	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
pewter	O
Pots	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
having	O
made	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
pewter	O
Pots	O
melted	O
,	O
they	O
afterwards	O
passed	O
it	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
several	O
times	O
at	O
several	O
Places	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
put	O
off	O
that	O
bad	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
Mould	O
to	O
her	O
Father	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
it	O
there	O
,	O
telling	O
her	O
Mother	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
harm	O
in	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
Piece	O
of	O
Sodder	O
to	O
the	O
Lodging	O
of	O
her	O
Father	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
and	O
her	O
Mother	O
were	O
abroad	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
her	O
rise	O
and	O
lay	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
falling	O
a-sleep	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Landlady	O
coming	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
Pots	O
did	O
find	O
the	O
Sodder	O
,	O
the	O
Moulds	O
and	O
counterfeit	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
intirely	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
objected	O
against	O
the	O
Credit	O
of	O
Hannah	O
Lewis	O
,	O
as	O
being	O
not	O
much	O
above	O
10	O
Years	O
old	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
his	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
behav	O
'd	O
her	O
self	O
very	O
strangely	O
,	O
crying	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
Devil	O
and	O
the	O
Cat	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
them	O
give	O
the	O
Devil	O
and	O
the	O
Cat	O
Geneva	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Proof	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
depending	O
only	O
upon	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
the	O
Girl	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Upton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
of	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Oliver	B-pers
Truelove	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
10	O
Bars	O
of	O
Iron	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
Cellar	O
Window	O
was	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Bars	O
of	O
Iron	O
were	O
stolen	O
.	O
Upton	O
's	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
wherein	O
he	O
confessed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
Harvey	O
did	O
at	O
3	O
several	O
Times	O
steal	O
10	O
Bars	O
of	O
Iron	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
breaking	O
open	O
his	O
Cellar	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
commit	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
.	O
Harvey	O
,	O
upon	O
their	O
being	O
apprehended	O
at	O
work	O
together	O
upon	O
the	O
Iron	O
,	O
pretended	O
that	O
the	O
Iron	O
was	O
bought	O
of	O
one	O
Wilkinson	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
make	O
appear	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
Anthony	O
Upton	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
And	O
acquitted	O
Harvey	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Rainsbury	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Harper	I-pers
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
employed	O
to	O
sit	O
up	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
sick	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
She	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
The	O
Matter	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Miles	B-pers
Allison	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Coatsworth	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Allison	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Damask	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
Holland	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Seneff	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
August	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
pawn	O
'd	O
,	O
by	O
Miles	O
Allison	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
Miles	O
Allison	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
And	O
acquitted	O
Mary	O
Allison	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Garret	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Libra	I-pers
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
as	O
appeared	O
by	O
her	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Candy	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Higginson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
She	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
which	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Durance	B-pers
Bun	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
August	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
sat	O
on	O
a	O
Bench	O
about	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
snatch	O
'd	O
his	O
Hat	O
off	O
from	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
immediately	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
positive	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Frances	B-pers
Sands	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Bellas	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
35	O
l.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
divers	O
Persons	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Barron	I-pers
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
Frances	O
Sands	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Club	O
kept	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
a	O
Box	O
,	O
wherein	O
was	O
35	O
l.	O
which	O
Box	O
was	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Mony	O
was	O
stolen	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
no	O
Body	O
used	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
that	O
Room	O
but	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
and	O
Frances	O
Sands	O
,	O
the	O
Key	O
always	O
was	O
kept	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Bottom	O
of	O
the	O
Box	O
was	O
broken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Dun	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Frances	O
Sands	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
must	O
come	O
to	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
,	O
she	O
must	O
be	O
forced	O
to	O
throw	O
it	O
down	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
go	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Oldcastle	I-pers
's	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
there	O
while	O
Ann	O
Bellas	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Daughter	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
Mother	O
Frances	O
Sands	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
then	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
Gold	O
in	O
a	O
Paper	O
,	O
and	O
Silver	O
in	O
a	O
Bag	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Frances	O
Sands	O
afterwards	O
owned	O
that	O
it	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
Club	O
Box	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
being	O
made	O
drunk	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
became	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Crew	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
fetch	O
Drink	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
perceiving	O
that	O
they	O
spent	O
their	O
Money	O
more	O
profusely	O
than	O
was	O
usual	O
,	O
and	O
beyond	O
their	O
former	O
Ability	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
at	O
length	O
it	O
became	O
a	O
Talk	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
that	O
the	O
Money	O
came	O
from	O
a	O
Box	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Place	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
acquainted	O
Mr.	O
Barron	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
apprehended	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
Frances	O
Sands	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
But	O
acquitted	O
Ann	O
Bellas	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Pancrass	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Jame	B-pers
Vickery	I-pers
near	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
she	O
and	O
her	O
Daughter	O
were	O
going	O
near	O
Kentish	B-place
Town	I-place
,	O
behind	O
Bondstreet	B-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
pulling	O
a	O
Club	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
swearing	O
in	O
a	O
violent	O
Manner	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
deliver	O
immediately	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
murder	O
them	O
that	O
Minute	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
deliver	O
to	O
him	O
a	O
Ring	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
and	O
Robbing	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
,	O
near	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
set	O
with	O
Garnets	O
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
having	O
Lodgings	O
at	O
Kentish	O
Town	O
,	O
her	O
Mother	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
Walk	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
met	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
treated	O
as	O
her	O
Mother	O
Jane	O
Vickery	O
had	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Facts	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
which	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
;	O
nor	O
did	O
he	O
deny	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
.	O
The	O
Facts	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
both	O
indictments	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wakelin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Ebenezer	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Sunday	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Body	O
at	O
Home	O
but	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
Part	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
about	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
after	O
in	O
Shadwell	O
:	O
That	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
sorry	O
for	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
Fact	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Wetherel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Tea	O
,	O
and	O
Chocolate	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
lost	O
his	O
Tea	O
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Spooner	I-pers
,	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Castle	O
and	O
Falcon	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
claimed	O
Acquaintance	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
his	O
Countryman	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
knew	O
his	O
Parents	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
must	O
needs	O
be	O
his	O
Cousin	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
and	O
see	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
come	O
several	O
Times	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
Goods	O
at	O
several	O
Times	O
,	O
sometimes	O
Cloves	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
threatned	O
if	O
he	O
told	O
of	O
it	O
he	O
would	O
murder	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
promised	O
to	O
help	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
good	O
Place	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Morning	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Tea	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Canister	O
with	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Persons	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Auden	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
marrying	O
a	O
Second	O
Wife	O
,	O
while	O
his	O
first	O
Wife	O
was	O
living	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Hoskins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Hannah	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Flaxen	O
Sheet	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Pyner	I-pers
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Richard	O
Hoskins	O
that	O
affected	O
him	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
:	O
But	O
Hannah	O
Jones	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Clay	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Nicolas	I-pers
Arbuthnot	I-pers
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
live	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
,	O
but	O
came	O
there	O
one	O
Sunday	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
abroad	O
,	O
to	O
another	O
Servant	O
that	O
then	O
lived	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
were	O
given	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Maid	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
sold	O
them	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Whitechapel	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Fountain	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
9	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
this	O
present	O
August	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
As	O
she	O
was	O
standing	O
,	O
shewing	O
her	O
Child	O
the	O
Trained	O
Bands	O
,	O
a	O
Boy	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
a	O
Boy	O
had	O
pick	O
'd	O
her	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
pursu	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
Crown	O
Piece	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
dropp	O
'd	O
3	O
s.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
laying	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
clapp	O
'd	O
his	O
Hands	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
giving	O
another	O
Boy	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
afterwards	O
,	O
he	O
dropp	O
'd	O
3	O
s.	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
Boy	O
got	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hutton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Ledew	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
July	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
Vault	O
that	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Alms-houses	O
at	O
Hoxton	B-place
,	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
,	O
and	O
falling	O
asleep	O
,	O
slept	O
'till	O
about	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
awaked	O
he	O
had	O
neither	O
Coat	O
nor	O
Hat	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
of	O
Shoreditch	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
apprehended	O
her	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Hat	O
and	O
Coat	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
stopp	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
before	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Fowles	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Peter	I-place
's	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
46	O
Yards	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
value	O
56	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Jasper	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
,	I-pers
and	I-pers
Company	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Company	O
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
this	O
present	O
August	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Cookson	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
2	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
He	O
bought	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
St.	O
Catherines	O
,	O
for	O
30	O
s.	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Vanderhurst	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolph	I-place
's	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hales	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Faith	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Basket	O
of	O
Cherries	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Eels	I-pers
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Cherries	O
stood	O
at	O
a	O
Stall	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Cherries	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
carrying	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
pursu	O
'd	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
them	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Doe	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Hill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Breeton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
keeping	O
an	O
Eating-house	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
often	O
taken	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
defrauded	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Cheeseman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Baptist	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pocket	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Horn	I-pers
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
going	O
along	O
Dowgate	B-place
Hill	I-place
,	O
she	O
had	O
her	O
Pocket	O
pull	O
'd	O
of	O
,	O
she	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
pursu	O
'd	O
and	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hardy	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Alhallows	B-place
on	I-place
the	I-place
Wall	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
gold	O
Chain	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
Spinster	O
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
Rebecca	O
Jones	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
her	O
Neck	O
was	O
very	O
dirty	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
her	O
take	O
it	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
wash	O
her	O
Neck	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
do	O
so	O
,	O
laid	O
it	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
her	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
Miss	O
,	O
how	O
ugly	O
your	O
Coat	O
sits	O
,	O
and	O
pretending	O
to	O
set	O
it	O
right	O
,	O
she	O
perceived	O
her	O
Hand	O
about	O
her	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
ran	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
;	O
she	O
felt	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
and	O
missing	O
her	O
Chain	O
,	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
where	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
?	O
she	O
replyed	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
half	O
penny	O
worth	O
of	O
pins	O
,	O
run	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
followed	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
Sight	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
came	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
was	O
apprehended	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Zeman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
,	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
Spectacles	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mappleston	I-pers
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Man	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Mistress	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
6	O
Pair	O
of	O
Spectacles	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
other	O
Spectacles	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
besides	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
being	O
pursu	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
having	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
carried	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
threw	O
them	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Counter	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Pancras	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Peter	B-pers
Walter	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
in	O
an	O
open	O
Place	O
near	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
6	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
walking	O
between	O
Kentish	B-place
Town	I-place
and	O
Hampstead	B-place
,	O
going	O
over	O
a	O
Stile	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Ditch	O
,	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
Club	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
if	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
to	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
knock	O
out	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Brains	O
presently	O
,	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
demanded	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
Watch	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
but	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
only	O
his	O
Silver	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
to	O
two	O
other	O
Evidences	O
that	O
apprehended	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hermitage	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Precinct	B-place
of	I-place
the	I-place
Trinity	I-place
,	I-place
Minories	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Crookshall	I-pers
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
with	O
a	O
Paper	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
beg	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
pursu	O
'd	O
,	O
was	O
apprehended	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
her	O
Lap	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
and	I-pers
Francis	I-pers
Brightwell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Pancras	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Pargiter	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
6s	O
.	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
having	O
been	O
at	O
London	O
,	O
going	O
home	O
between	O
Fig	B-place
Lane	I-place
and	O
Half-way-house	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
off	O
his	O
House	O
to	O
make	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Horse	O
going	O
on	O
before	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
walking	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Francis	O
Brightwell	O
met	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
passed	O
him	O
6	O
or	O
8	O
Yards	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Benjamin	O
met	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
into	O
a	O
Ditch	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
Watch	O
,	O
asking	O
him	O
if	O
all	O
the	O
Money	O
he	O
had	O
was	O
in	O
one	O
Pocket	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
yes	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
afterwards	O
bid	O
him	O
give	O
him	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
to	O
lift	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Ditch	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
his	O
Wig	O
that	O
was	O
fallen	O
off	O
by	O
his	O
being	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
for	O
Francis	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
halted	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
standing	O
still	O
a	O
little	O
distance	O
off	O
,	O
while	O
Benjamin	O
was	O
robbing	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
afterwards	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
followed	O
his	O
Horse	O
and	O
went	O
Home	O
;	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
following	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
at	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
with	O
some	O
Farmers	O
his	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
,	O
was	O
telling	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
Place	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
at	O
,	O
and	O
describing	O
the	O
Persons	O
,	O
and	O
riding	O
farther	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
telling	O
the	O
Farmers	O
,	O
that	O
those	O
were	O
the	O
Persons	O
that	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
apprehended	O
them	O
,	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Clothes	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
on	O
when	O
they	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
Francis	O
Brightwell	O
had	O
under	O
his	O
Coat	O
a	O
Cross	O
Bow	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
taking	O
them	O
to	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
,	O
he	O
charg	O
'd	O
them	O
with	O
having	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
under	O
a	O
great	O
Surprize	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
neither	O
own	O
nor	O
deny	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
Francis	O
pretended	O
he	O
was	O
elsewhere	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
upon	O
Guard	O
,	O
but	O
prevaricated	O
in	O
his	O
Account	O
.	O
Two	O
other	O
Evidences	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Manner	O
of	O
their	O
apprehending	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Charge	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
for	O
having	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
,	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
several	O
Persons	O
to	O
prove	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
one	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
on	O
guard	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
when	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
saw	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Brightwell	I-pers
the	O
20th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Brew-house	O
Yard	O
,	O
at	O
3	O
quarters	O
past	O
9	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
going	O
home	O
to	O
lye	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Lomax	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
lay	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Barber	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
Benjamin	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
from	O
3	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
till	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
past	O
8	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
Morning	O
Mr.	O
Pargiter	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
was	O
fuddled	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
.	O
Ann	O
Miller	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
Benjamin	O
Brightwell	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
at	O
work	O
till	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
past	O
9	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
July	O
.	O
Susan	B-pers
Tailor	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
Benjamin	O
Brightwell	O
,	O
at	O
her	O
Stable	O
Door	O
,	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
talk	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
lye	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Lomax	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Purpose	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bever	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
Pargiter	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
much	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
.	O
Several	O
Persons	O
also	O
gave	O
them	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Character	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
a	O
Clergyman	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
Francis	O
Brightwell	O
near	O
20	O
Years	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
always	O
reputed	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
the	O
fairest	O
Character	O
for	O
Sobriety	O
,	O
Justness	O
,	O
and	O
Probity	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Person	O
extraordinary	O
well	O
accomplish	O
'd	O
with	O
Latin	O
and	O
Greek	O
Literature	O
,	O
and	O
good	O
Skill	O
in	O
Roman	O
Antiquities	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
such	O
another	O
Granadier	O
in	O
the	O
Universe	O
,	O
he	O
carrying	O
a	O
large	O
Share	O
of	O
exquisite	O
Learning	O
under	O
his	O
Granadiers	O
Cap	O
.	O
Several	O
other	O
Persons	O
of	O
Character	O
,	O
as	O
Colonels	O
,	O
Majors	O
,	O
Captains	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
Character	O
before	O
mentioned	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Sergeant	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Soldiers	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
July	O
on	O
guard	O
,	O
from	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
past	O
9	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
till	O
past	O
eleven	O
a	O
Clock	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
upon	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
acquitted	O
them	O
both	O
.	O
Christian	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Shoes	O
off	O
the	O
Spikes	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Shop	O
Window	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
pursu	O
'd	O
was	O
apprehended	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
50	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
an	O
Apprentice	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
did	O
use	O
to	O
steal	O
Shoes	O
from	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
sell	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Colethorp	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Wig	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Salt	I-pers
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Webster	I-pers
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
Joseph	O
Webster	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Chiswell-street	B-place
,	O
with	O
two	O
Wig-boxes	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
perceiving	O
some	O
Body	O
to	O
touch	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Wigs	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
he	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
having	O
the	O
Wig	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
deny	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Wig	O
out	O
from	O
between	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Coat	O
and	O
Wastcoat	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
Evidences	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Miles	B-pers
Allison	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Trunk	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Frances	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
pretending	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
in	O
Haste	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
went	O
away	O
very	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Trunk	O
was	O
missing	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Katherine	B-pers
Farley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
taking	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Guy	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
this	O
present	O
August	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Mistress	O
about	O
some	O
Business	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
busy	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
desired	O
to	O
stay	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
'till	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
Leisure	O
,	O
and	O
falling	O
asleep	O
,	O
his	O
Watch	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Watch	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
and	I-pers
Benjamin	I-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Pewter	O
pots	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Copper	O
Pot	O
,	O
Value	O
1	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Wilcox	I-pers
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
two	O
Persons	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
had	O
two	O
Pints	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
into	O
another	O
Room	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
without	O
paying	O
for	O
their	O
Drink	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
Pint	O
Pots	O
and	O
a	O
Copper	O
Pot	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Copper	O
Pot	O
was	O
found	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Wright	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Cloak	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Sheets	O
,	O
Blankets	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Caperil	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
this	O
present	O
August	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
carried	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Norris	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Iron	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Billingay	I-pers
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
each	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Mould	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Leather	O
,	O
Value	O
12	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
this	O
present	O
August	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Mews	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Fetherstone	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Giles	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Best	I-pers
;	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
body	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
being	O
informed	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
ordered	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
her	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Recognizance	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Armstrong	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Armstrong	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
in	O
putting	O
off	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Copper	O
for	O
Six	O
Pences	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
false	O
.	O
One	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
People	O
of	O
the	O
Town	O
of	O
Twickenham	B-place
complained	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
much	O
imposed	O
upon	O
by	O
Copper	O
Pieces	O
like	O
Six	O
Pences	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
quest	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
;	O
he	O
apprehended	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Pieces	O
of	O
the	O
Copper	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Tools	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
Several	O
Persons	O
depos	O
'd	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Copper	O
wash	O
'd	O
of	O
Mary	O
Armstrong	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
fin	O
'd	O
them	O
three	O
Marks	O
apiece	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Cyles	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Spurs	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Guilt	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Spurs	O
were	O
given	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
clean	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
Brother	O
,	O
who	O
pawned	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
again	O
by	O
some	O
unknown	O
Hand	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Mackfedre	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
for	O
assaulting	O
and	O
wounding	O
Mr.	O
Henry	B-pers
Jacomb	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Jacomb	O
having	O
acted	O
as	O
an	O
Attorney	O
in	O
a	O
Suit	O
the	O
Defendant	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
Thaves	B-place
Inn	I-place
,	O
to	O
a	O
Coffee-house	O
,	O
and	O
demand	O
some	O
Writings	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hands	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Right	O
to	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
his	O
refusing	O
to	O
deliver	O
them	O
,	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
with	O
his	O
Cane	O
,	O
and	O
wounded	O
him	O
very	O
much	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
sentenced	O
him	O
to	O
pay	O
a	O
Fine	O
of	O
20	O
Marks	O
,	O
to	O
suffer	O
a	O
Year	O
's	O
Imprisonment	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
find	O
Sureties	O
for	O
his	O
Behaviour	O
for	O
three	O
Years	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Copney	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Cobley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anne	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Pollard	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anne	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Gaunt	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Pancrass	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Martha	B-pers
Mead	I-pers
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
fear	O
of	O
her	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
Value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Hampstead	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
or	O
eleven	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Forenoon	O
,	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
Black	O
Mary	O
's	O
Hole	O
,	O
and	O
inquiring	O
of	O
him	O
the	O
Way	O
to	O
Pancrass	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
thither	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
conduct	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
together	O
through	O
Pancrass-Church-Yard	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
would	O
needs	O
call	O
for	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
urgent	O
upon	O
her	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
refus	O
'd	O
;	O
till	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
sitting	O
down	O
on	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
Bench	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
Drink	O
,	O
he	O
over-perswaded	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
did	O
sit	O
down	O
at	O
the	O
other	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Bench	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
drink	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
he	O
very	O
much	O
pressing	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
telling	O
her	O
there	O
could	O
be	O
no	O
harm	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
constrained	O
her	O
to	O
sit	O
down	O
;	O
that	O
afterwards	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
Kentish-Town	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Black	O
Lion	O
for	O
some	O
Brandy	O
,	O
and	O
urged	O
her	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Dram	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
she	O
inquiring	O
the	O
Way	O
to	O
Hampstead	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
would	O
show	O
her	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
not	O
knowing	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
carry	O
'd	O
her	O
through	O
by-Fields	O
,	O
that	O
went	O
towards	O
Highgate	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
opening	O
her	O
Hand	O
by	O
Force	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Ring	O
off	O
from	O
her	O
Finger	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
into	O
another	O
Field	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
followed	O
him	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
for	O
her	O
Ring	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
replyed	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
it	O
her	O
again	O
presently	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
offered	O
Rudeness	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
carried	O
her	O
round	O
about	O
for	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
,	O
telling	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
her	O
way	O
to	O
Hampstead	O
,	O
till	O
at	O
last	O
she	O
found	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
having	O
a	O
Calamanco	O
Gown	O
in	O
her	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
that	O
from	O
her	O
also	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
now	O
she	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
follow	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
carried	O
her	O
rambling	O
about	O
,	O
calling	O
at	O
several	O
Places	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
afraid	O
to	O
charge	O
him	O
with	O
her	O
Ring	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
for	O
fear	O
he	O
should	O
do	O
her	O
some	O
Injury	O
,	O
because	O
they	O
were	O
People	O
of	O
his	O
Acquaintance	O
,	O
till	O
at	O
last	O
they	O
had	O
wandred	O
till	O
they	O
came	O
into	O
Long	O
Alley	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Dolphin	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
Gown	O
to	O
the	O
Maid	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
her	O
not	O
deliver	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
being	O
resolved	O
not	O
to	O
go	O
without	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Gown	O
was	O
given	O
to	O
her	O
again	O
,	O
that	O
after	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
she	O
lodg	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Landlord	O
being	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
she	O
demanded	O
her	O
Ring	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
deny	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
owned	O
it	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
deny	O
having	O
the	O
Ring	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
over	O
Night	O
,	O
was	O
proved	O
by	O
two	O
Evidences	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
he	O
produc	O
'd	O
it	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
in	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
was	O
depos	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Landlord	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
having	O
some	O
Business	O
at	O
Kentish	O
Town	O
was	O
going	O
thither	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
sitting	O
on	O
a	O
Stile	O
near	O
Pancras	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
Pancras	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
directed	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Adam	O
and	O
Eve	O
,	O
he	O
sat	O
down	O
on	O
one	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Bench	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
sat	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
fumbling	O
with	O
her	O
Hand	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
began	O
to	O
complain	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Misfortune	O
to	O
lay	O
her	O
Money	O
down	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
instead	O
of	O
putting	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
had	O
left	O
it	O
behind	O
her	O
,	O
otherwise	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Ale	O
and	O
a	O
Cake	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
replyed	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
welcome	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
drank	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
drank	O
,	O
edging	O
nearer	O
and	O
nearer	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Bench	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Landlord	O
brought	O
some	O
Cakes	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
one	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
forward	O
to	O
Kentish	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Black	O
Lion	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Pints	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
3	O
half	O
Quarterns	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
which	O
tho	O
'	O
she	O
refused	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
she	O
afterwards	O
drank	O
very	O
freely	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
she	O
enquired	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
Hampstead	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
having	O
staid	O
there	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Hours	O
,	O
he	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
some	O
Farmers	O
about	O
putting	O
2	O
Horses	O
to	O
Grass	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
no	O
By-ways	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
violently	O
take	O
the	O
Ring	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
King	O
as	O
a	O
Pledge	O
,	O
for	O
her	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Expence	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
,	O
in	O
their	O
long	O
Journey	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
also	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Gown	O
to	O
carry	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
that	O
at	O
length	O
,	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
arriving	O
in	O
Town	O
,	O
at	O
Long	O
Alley	O
they	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
3	O
Pots	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
another	O
Place	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
half	O
Quarterns	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
her	O
own	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
about	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
That	O
this	O
was	O
their	O
Progress	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
rob	O
her	O
of	O
her	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
hoped	O
God	O
was	O
above	O
the	O
Devil	O
Still	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
at	O
the	O
Dolphin	O
in	O
Long	O
Alley	O
,	O
about	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
a-Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
there	O
till	O
11	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
three	O
Pints	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
Ring	O
on	O
his	O
Finger	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
no	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
young	O
Women	O
's	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
drank	O
very	O
familiarly	O
together	O
,	O
were	O
very	O
loving	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
kissed	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
again	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
also	O
kissed	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
that	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
drank	O
their	O
Drink	O
with	O
much	O
Pleasaniness	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
lovingly	O
together	O
,	O
she	O
taking	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
hold	O
by	O
the	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
like	O
Man	O
and	O
Wife	O
,	O
or	O
like	O
Whore	O
and	O
Rogue	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
Courtship	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
very	O
familiar	O
and	O
loving	O
,	O
kissing	O
one	O
another	O
with	O
that	O
Freedom	O
,	O
that	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
old	O
Man	O
,	O
it	O
made	O
him	O
blush	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
we	O
shall	O
drink	O
together	O
,	O
we	O
have	O
been	O
together	O
all	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
dry	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
faint	O
,	O
and	O
Brandy	O
was	O
called	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
drank	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
went	O
away	O
very	O
lovingly	O
together	O
.	O
Upon	O
a	O
full	O
bearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
accquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Crofts	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Agnew	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Length	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
Six	O
Inches	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
Breast	O
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
August	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Wound	O
he	O
immediately	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
Second	O
Time	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
.	O
And	O
also	O
a	O
Third	O
Time	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
Stabbing	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Major	O
Harrison	O
and	O
Captain	O
Agnew	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Lubeck	B-place
's	I-place
Head	I-place
in	I-place
Maiden	I-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
about	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Burgundy	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
carried	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
filled	O
out	O
a	O
Glass	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
afterwards	O
asked	O
for	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Master	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
down	O
that	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Burgundy	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
up	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
French	O
Wine	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
afterwards	O
heard	O
the	O
Bell	O
ring	O
in	O
the	O
Lion	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
wanted	O
some	O
Snuff	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
sent	O
the	O
Porter	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
also	O
called	O
for	O
another	O
Bottle	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
carried	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
talking	O
together	O
very	O
friendly	O
,	O
and	O
disputing	O
on	O
some	O
Argument	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
about	O
what	O
,	O
that	O
Capt	O
.	O
Agnew	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
Major	O
Harrison	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
laid	O
his	O
Arm	O
over	O
him	O
very	O
friendly	O
,	O
that	O
near	O
one	O
a	O
Clock	O
he	O
heard	O
in	O
that	O
Room	O
,	O
the	O
Noise	O
of	O
stamping	O
of	O
Feet	O
like	O
2	O
Men	O
parrying	O
and	O
pushing	O
at	O
one	O
another	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
immediately	O
ran	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
the	O
Bell	O
rung	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Major	O
coming	O
towards	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
with	O
two	O
Swords	O
drawn	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Collar	O
,	O
he	O
led	O
him	O
to	O
Capt	O
.	O
Agnew	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
bleeding	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
Dear	O
Sir	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
not	O
draw	O
your	O
Sword	O
first	O
?	O
And	O
Capt	O
.	O
Agnew	O
answered	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Major	O
bid	O
him	O
this	O
Evidence	O
take	O
Notice	O
;	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Swords	O
was	O
bloody	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
thinks	O
was	O
the	O
Major	O
's	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
mourning	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Major	O
's	O
Clothes	O
were	O
light	O
coloured	O
trimm	O
'd	O
with	O
black	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
carried	O
down	O
the	O
Swords	O
,	O
informed	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
for	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
who	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
dressed	O
his	O
Wound	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
laid	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
bidding	O
him	O
get	O
a	O
Chair	O
,	O
he	O
fetch	O
'd	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
carried	O
him	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
and	O
another	O
went	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Chair	O
,	O
holding	O
a	O
Napkin	O
before	O
him	O
to	O
keep	O
him	O
from	O
falling	O
or	O
rocking	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
in	O
Hemming	O
's	O
Row	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
dead	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Thorp	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
a-sleep	O
behind	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
all	O
being	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
Drawer	O
,	O
the	O
Porter	O
,	O
and	O
himself	O
,	O
about	O
one	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
the	O
Drawer	O
brought	O
down	O
two	O
Swords	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
was	O
wounded	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
immediately	O
ran	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
sitting	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
stooping	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
listed	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
him	O
on	O
a	O
Chair	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Drawer	O
ran	O
away	O
for	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
called	O
a	O
Coachman	O
and	O
sent	O
him	O
up	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
taken	O
off	O
the	O
Ground	O
he	O
sighed	O
and	O
groaned	O
very	O
much	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Thorp	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Major	O
and	O
Capt	O
.	O
Agnew	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
then	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Burgundy	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
had	O
;	O
but	O
afterwards	O
would	O
have	O
Claret	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
carried	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
friendly	O
.	O
That	O
be	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
called	O
up	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
Quarter	O
past	O
one	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Deceased	O
till	O
Mr.	O
Small	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
came	O
to	O
dress	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stonystreet	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Apothecary	O
's	O
Apprentice	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
present	O
while	O
Mr.	O
Small	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
dress	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
,	O
that	O
Major	O
Harrison	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Captain	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
himself	O
(	O
the	O
Captain	O
)	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
Aggressor	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
answered	O
he	O
was	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Stone	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
Beedle	O
,	O
was	O
all	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
laid	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Major	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
your	O
own	O
seeking	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Carter	O
the	O
Constable	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
also	O
being	O
call	O
'd	O
,	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Captain	O
was	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
some	O
time	O
stirred	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
raised	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Major	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
already	O
said	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Drawer	O
,	O
say	O
before	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
not	O
draw	O
your	O
8	O
word	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
Capt	O
.	O
Agnew	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
draw	O
my	O
Sword	O
first	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
the	O
third	O
time	O
he	O
had	O
owned	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
said	O
,	O
is	O
there	O
no	O
Body	O
to	O
attend	O
me	O
,	O
no	O
Body	O
to	O
help	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Apothecary	O
's	O
Man	O
wiped	O
the	O
Spittle	O
from	O
his	O
Mouth	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
too	O
weak	O
and	O
saint	O
to	O
discharge	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Small	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
dressed	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
broad	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Inch	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
backwards	O
near	O
the	O
right	O
Pap	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Major	O
Harrison	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
Care	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
if	O
himself	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
answered	O
,	O
ay	O
,	O
ay	O
.	O
The	O
Major	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
pleaded	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
unfortunate	O
Accident	O
had	O
brought	O
upon	O
him	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Grief	O
and	O
Concern	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
and	O
himself	O
were	O
Brother	O
Officers	O
in	O
the	O
Garrison	O
of	O
Dunkirk	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1710.	O
and	O
both	O
of	O
them	O
having	O
an	O
Inclination	O
for	O
Books	O
,	O
it	O
had	O
occasioned	O
their	O
contracting	O
an	O
intimate	O
Acquaintance	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
continued	O
with	O
the	O
strictest	O
Friendship	O
ever	O
since	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Day	O
the	O
Accident	O
happened	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
walking	O
in	O
Lincolns	O
Inn	O
,	O
they	O
bespoke	O
a	O
Rabbet	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
for	O
Supper	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
supped	O
,	O
were	O
together	O
till	O
about	O
11	O
a-Clock	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
thro	O
'	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
heard	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Fire	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
being	O
willing	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
till	O
they	O
were	O
satisfied	O
how	O
and	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Lubeck	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
as	O
had	O
been	O
before	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
at	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
Flask	O
,	O
being	O
in	O
Discourse	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
drawing	O
Parallels	O
between	O
the	O
Roman	O
and	O
English	O
Government	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
thinking	O
carry	O
'd	O
in	O
them	O
Reflections	O
on	O
the	O
latter	O
,	O
it	O
gave	O
him	O
Occasion	O
to	O
oppase	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
Argument	O
.	O
Which	O
put	O
the	O
Deceased	O
out	O
of	O
Temper	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
giving	O
him	O
soft	O
Language	O
,	O
had	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
Temper	O
again	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
thought	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
very	O
friendly	O
;	O
but	O
after	O
the	O
bringing	O
in	O
of	O
the	O
second	O
Bottle	O
,	O
the	O
Captain	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
his	O
ill	O
Temper	O
,	O
and	O
wish	O
'd	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Case	O
of	O
Pistols	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
for	O
what	O
,	O
he	O
hoped	O
not	O
for	O
them	O
to	O
use	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
answered	O
,	O
since	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
,	O
they	O
should	O
decide	O
it	O
another	O
way	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
drew	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
begged	O
of	O
him	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
to	O
sorbear	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
grew	O
violent	O
,	O
and	O
push	O
'd	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
whereupon	O
he	O
retreated	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
for	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
drawn	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
put	O
himself	O
into	O
a	O
Posture	O
of	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Captain	O
made	O
a	O
very	O
violent	O
push	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
happily	O
put	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
believes	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
he	O
ran	O
upon	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
received	O
the	O
Wound	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
wounded	O
till	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
having	O
disarm	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
immediately	O
called	O
for	O
help	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
what	O
care	O
of	O
him	O
he	O
could	O
,	O
sending	O
for	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
and	O
assisting	O
him	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
.	O
Colonel	O
Sinclare	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Persons	O
of	O
Character	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
peaceable	O
,	O
affable	O
,	O
inoffensive	O
Gentleman	O
;	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
,	O
among	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
certain	O
noble	O
Lord	O
,	O
gave	O
the	O
Deceased	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
who	O
was	O
so	O
apt	O
to	O
be	O
tenacious	O
of	O
his	O
Argument	O
,	O
when	O
in	O
Discourse	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
be	O
impatient	O
of	O
Contradiction	O
.	O
Upon	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
all	O
three	O
Indictments	O
,	O
bringing	O
in	O
their	O
Verdict	O
,	O
Se	O
Defendendo	O
.	O
Isaak	B-pers
Dearing	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1300	O
Pound	O
Weight	O
of	O
Iron	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Trueman	I-pers
,	I-pers
and	I-pers
Company	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Company	O
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
Second	O
Time	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
deficient	O
as	O
to	O
this	O
Indictment	O
also	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
the	O
Third	O
Time	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Savoy	I-place
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Williams	B-pers
Kneebone	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-Time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
118	O
Yards	O
of	O
Woollen	O
Cloth	O
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
some	O
Time	O
since	O
been	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
the	O
Time	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
about	O
11	O
a-Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
all	O
the	O
Doors	O
and	O
Windows	O
fast	O
;	O
but	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
up	O
about	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
his	O
House	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
the	O
Bar	O
of	O
a	O
Cellar-Window	O
having	O
been	O
cut	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Bolts	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
that	O
comes	O
up	O
Stairs	O
drawn	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Padlock	O
wrench	O
'd	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Shutter	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
broken	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Goods	O
gone	O
;	O
whereupon	O
suspecting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
committed	O
ill	O
Actions	O
thereabouts	O
before	O
,	O
he	O
acquainted	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
procured	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
apprehended	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
new	O
prison	O
,	O
and	O
asking	O
how	O
he	O
could	O
be	O
so	O
ungrateful	O
to	O
rob	O
him	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
shown	O
him	O
so	O
much	O
Kindness	O
?	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
ungrateful	O
in	O
doing	O
so	O
,	O
informing	O
him	O
of	O
several	O
Circumstances	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Manner	O
of	O
Committing	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
drawn	O
into	O
it	O
by	O
ill	O
Company	O
.	O
Jonathan	O
Wild	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
inquire	O
after	O
his	O
Goods	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
he	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
before	O
committed	O
some	O
Robberies	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
.	O
That	O
inquiring	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
heard	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
informed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
Acquaintance	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Blueskin	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Field	I-pers
:	O
Whereupon	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
William	O
Field	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
If	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
an	O
ingenuous	O
Confession	O
,	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
he	O
could	O
prevail	O
with	O
the	O
Court	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
an	O
Evidence	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
make	O
a	O
Discovery	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
of	O
others	O
since	O
convicted	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
some	O
Parcels	O
of	O
the	O
Cloth	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
accordingly	O
.	O
William	O
Field	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
Joseph	O
Blake	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
a	O
Ken	O
where	O
they	O
might	O
get	O
something	O
of	O
Worth	O
:	O
That	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
View	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
disapprov	O
'd	O
of	O
the	O
Attempt	O
,	O
as	O
not	O
thinking	O
it	O
easy	O
to	O
be	O
performed	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
perswaded	O
them	O
that	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
easily	O
done	O
,	O
he	O
knowing	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
having	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
That	O
thereupon	O
he	O
cut	O
the	O
Cellar	O
Bar	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
out	O
three	O
Parcels	O
of	O
Cloth	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
carried	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
also	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Gouldstone	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Thornycroft	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
in	O
conspiring	O
to	O
defraud	O
Sir	O
James	B-pers
Thornhill	I-pers
,	O
of	O
2001	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Oliver	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
in	O
selling	O
to	O
Joseph	B-pers
Pangford	I-pers
,	O
a	O
false	O
Prize	O
York	O
Lottery	O
,	O
Ticket	O
,	O
for	O
20	O
Guineas	O
,	O
knowing	O
,	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
falsified	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Defendent	O
,	O
Joseph	O
Oliver	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
Ticket	O
Porter	O
,	O
who	O
ply	O
'd	O
at	O
Aldgate	B-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
sell	O
a	O
Ticket	O
to	O
Joseph	O
Pangford	O
for	O
20	O
Guineas	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
Prize	O
,	O
which	O
Ticket	O
,	O
when	O
it	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Office	O
to	O
be	O
checqued	O
,	O
did	O
appear	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
(	O
though	O
a	O
true	O
Ticket	O
)	O
a	O
Blank	O
,	O
the	O
Number	O
of	O
which	O
having	O
originally	O
been	O
1906	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
a	O
Blank	O
,	O
was	O
altered	O
to	O
1908	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
Prize	O
.	O
The	O
Defendant	O
Oliver	O
call	O
'd	O
two	O
of	O
his	O
Brother	O
Porters	O
to	O
prove	O
,	O
That	O
a	O
Person	O
appearing	O
like	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
just	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
lac	O
'd	O
Hat	O
,	O
Boots	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Whip	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
call	O
'd	O
Porter	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
ran	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Defendant	O
being	O
readiest	O
at	O
Hand	O
,	O
got	O
the	O
Jobb	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
saw	O
him	O
pull	O
some	O
Papers	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
some	O
to	O
Oliver	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
afterwards	O
told	O
them	O
what	O
the	O
Jobb	O
was	O
.	O
It	O
also	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
Broker	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Defendant	O
Oliver	O
brought	O
the	O
Ticket	O
to	O
him	O
from	O
such	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
not	O
bargaining	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
afterwards	O
told	O
to	O
the	O
Complainant	O
.	O
So	O
that	O
it	O
plainly	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Porter	O
was	O
impos	O
'd	O
upon	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
not	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
the	O
falsifying	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
only	O
imprudent	O
in	O
endorsing	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Buyer	O
,	O
and	O
parting	O
with	O
the	O
Money	O
to	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
sent	O
him	O
,	O
without	O
taking	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
who	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Receipt	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
followeth	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
Six	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Fowles	I-pers
,	O
Anthony	B-pers
Upton	I-pers
,	O
Frances	O
Sands	O
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Colethorp	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
Nine	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Auden	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Welling	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Quin	I-pers
,	O
Isaak	O
Dearing	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Gay	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
,	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Webster	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Luke	B-pers
Tench	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Two	O
last	O
former	O
Convicts	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
,	O
Thirty	O
One	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Claxton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Grimes	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
John	O
Heath	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Rainsberry	I-pers
,	O
Miles	B-pers
Allison	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Garret	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Candy	I-pers
,	O
Durance	O
Bun	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wakelin	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Wethevel	I-pers
,	O
Hannah	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Clay	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Fountain	I-pers
,	O
Susanna	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hutton	I-pers
,	O
Christian	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Cloak	I-pers
,	O
Norris	O
Hall	O
,	O
William	O
Hall	O
,	O
Williams	O
Mould	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Vanderburst	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hales	I-pers
,	O
Philip	B-pers
Zeman	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Doe	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Cheeseman	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hardy	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Hermitage	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Alice	B-pers
Crofts	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Mackfedre	I-pers
,	O
Fined	O
Twenty	O
Marks	O
,	O
to	O
saffer	O
Twelve	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
find	O
Security	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
,	O
for	O
Three	O
Years	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Armstrong	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Armstrong	I-pers
,	O
Fined	O
each	O
Three	O
Marks	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
Just	O
publish	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Seventh	O
Edition	O
(	O
with	O
many	O
Additions	O
and	O
Amendments	O
)	O
of	O
A	O
Rational	O
and	O
Useful	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Venereal	O
Disease	O
,	O
With	O
Observations	O
on	O
the	O
Nature	O
,	O
Symptoms	O
,	O
and	O
Cure	O
.	O
and	O
the	O
ill	O
Consequences	O
that	O
attend	O
it	O
by	O
ill	O
Management	O
;	O
with	O
proper	O
Admonitions	O
;	O
recommended	O
as	O
a	O
Friendly	O
Instruction	O
to	O
all	O
Person	O
who	O
do	O
,	O
or	O
may	O
,	O
labour	O
under	O
this	O
misfortune	O
.	O
Also	O
,	O
A	O
short	O
Inquiry	O
into	O
Old	O
Gleets	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Weaknesses	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Reason	O
why	O
they	O
are	O
so	O
Seldom	O
cured	O
:	O
With	O
the	O
Auther	O
's	O
Method	O
of	O
Cure	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
are	O
added	O
,	O
Some	O
Hints	O
on	O
the	O
Practical	O
Scheme	O
.	O
The	O
Methods	O
and	O
Medicines	O
therein	O
exported	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
gross	O
Impositions	O
Justly	O
detected	O
:	O
With	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
Specisicks	O
,	O
the	O
Use	O
and	O
Abuse	O
of	O
the	O
Name	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
it	O
covers	O
Ignorance	O
and	O
a	O
Cheat	O
.	O
By	O
Joseph	B-pers
Cam	I-pers
,	O
M.D	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
G.	O
Strahan	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
W.	O
Means	O
,	O
without	O
Temple-Bar	O
,	O
C.King	O
,	O
in	O
Westmister-Hall	O
,	O
T.	O
Norris	O
on	O
London-Bridge	O
,	O
J.	O
Baker	O
against	O
Hatton-Garden	O
in	O
Holborn	O
;	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Author	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Golden	O
Ball	O
and	O
Lamp	O
in	O
Bow-Church-Yard	O
,	O
Chepside	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
A	O
compleat	O
List	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Minters	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
cleared	O
at	O
Guilford	O
,	O
Kingston	O
,	O
Croydon	O
and	O
Ryegate	O
,	O
Amounting	O
to	O
above	O
6000	O
from	O
all	O
Parts	O
of	O
Great	O
Britain	O
and	O
Ireland	O
,	O
with	O
their	O
Names	O
,	O
Trades	O
,	O
Towns	O
and	O
Countries	O
,	O
of	O
their	O
last	O
Abode	O
,	O
Alphabetically	O
done	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
more	O
easy	O
finding	O
out	O
any	O
particular	O
Person	O
.	O
Publish	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
general	O
Information	O
to	O
all	O
Mankind	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
Where	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
also	O
,	O
An	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Lives	O
,	O
Intreagues	O
,	O
and	O
Comical	O
Adventures	O
of	O
Rob	O
Roy	O
alias	O
Robert	B-pers
Mac	I-pers
Gregor	I-pers
,	O
Capt	O
.	O
Stanley	O
,	O
Sally	B-pers
Salisbury	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Sarah	B-pers
Pridden	I-pers
,	O
and	O
near	O
a	O
hunred	O
more	O
,	O
who	O
have	O
either	O
dy	O
'd	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
or	O
been	O
executed	O
for	O
several	O
Villanies	O
and	O
Murders	O
committed	O
by	O
them	O
:	O
Wherein	O
is	O
contained	O
a	O
more	O
full	O
and	O
true	O
Account	O
,	O
than	O
has	O
been	O
publish	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Ordinary	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
other	O
.	O
The	O
Whole	O
being	O
not	O
only	O
very	O
Diverting	O
to	O
read	O
,	O
but	O
very	O
Useful	O
to	O
preserve	O
others	O
from	O
being	O
impos	O
'd	O
upon	O
by	O
Sharpers	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
Both	O
printed	O
for	O
M.	O
Hotham	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Black-Boy	O
on	O
London-Bridge	O
.	O
A	O
Water	O
that	O
perfectly	O
cures	O
the	O
Itch	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
Itching	O
Humour	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
,	O
without	O
Necessity	O
of	O
Purging	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
dangerous	O
Use	O
of	O
Mercury	O
,	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
only	O
is	O
prepared	O
and	O
sold	O
,	O
by	O
A	O
.	O
Downing	O
,	O
Chymist	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
and	O
Ball	O
,	O
in	O
George	O
Court	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
John's-Lane	O
,	O
by	O
Hicks's-Hall	O
,	O
near	O
West-Smithfield	O
.	O
Where	O
also	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
the	O
best	O
Spirits	O
of	O
Scurvy-Grass	O
,	O
by	O
Wholesale	O
or	O
Retale	O
,	O
at	O
S	O
d.	O
a	O
Bottle	O
.	O
A	O
most	O
effectual	O
Remedy	O
for	O
the	O
violent	O
Pain	O
in	O
the	O
Teeth	O
,	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
Also	O
a	O
most	O
excellent	O
Remedy	O
for	O
the	O
Teeth	O
,	O
and	O
clearing	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
.	O
Youth	O
's	O
Introduction	O
to	O
Trade	O
and	O
Business	O
:	O
Containing	B-pers
,	I-pers
I	I-pers
.	I-pers
Tables	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
usual	O
Clerk-like	O
Contractions	O
of	O
Words	O
:	O
A	O
Collection	O
of	O
English	O
Words	O
,	O
alike	O
in	O
Sound	O
,	O
but	O
different	O
in	O
Signification	O
;	O
with	O
proper	O
Directions	O
how	O
to	O
address	O
to	O
Persons	O
of	O
elevated	O
Rank	O
,	O
and	O
those	O
in	O
Office	O
.	O
II	O
.	O
Acquittances	O
and	O
Promissory	O
Notes	O
diversify	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
adapted	O
to	O
such	O
Circumstances	O
as	O
occur	O
in	O
real	O
Business	O
.	O
III	O
.	O
Variety	O
of	O
Bills	O
of	O
Parcels	O
,	O
and	O
Bills	O
on	O
Book	O
Debts	O
,	O
to	O
enter	O
the	O
Learner	O
in	O
the	O
Manner	O
and	O
Methods	O
of	O
Commerce	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
ready	O
at	O
Computation	O
.	O
IV	O
.	O
Bills	O
of	O
Exchange	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
necessary	O
for	O
the	O
right	O
Understanding	O
and	O
Management	O
of	O
Remittances	O
;	O
several	O
Orders	O
for	O
Goods	O
,	O
Letters	O
of	O
Credit	O
,	O
Invoyces	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Merchant-like	O
Examples	O
.	O
V.	O
Authentick	O
Forms	O
of	O
such	O
Law-Precedents	O
as	O
are	O
most	O
frequently	O
to	O
be	O
met	O
with	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Course	O
of	O
Traffick	O
.	O
VI	O
.	O
A	O
Collection	O
of	O
Questions	O
to	O
exemplify	O
the	O
common	O
Rules	O
of	O
Arithmetick	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
reduce	O
them	O
to	O
Practice	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Use	O
of	O
Schools	O
.	O
Done	O
upon	O
the	O
Plan	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
Col.	O
Ayre	B-pers
's	O
Essay	O
.	O
By	O
M.	O
Clare	O
,	O
School-Master	O
in	O
Soho-Square	O
,	O
London	O
.	O
Miscellaneous	O
Essays	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
Of	O
Company	O
and	O
Conversation	O
2	O
.	O
Of	O
Solitatiness	O
and	O
Retirement	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
Of	O
Nobility	O
4	O
.	O
Of	O
Contentment	O
.	O
5	O
.	O
Of	O
Women	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
Of	O
the	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
God	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
Atheison	O
.	O
7	O
.	O
Of	O
Religion	O
.	O
8	O
.	O
Of	O
Kings	O
,	O
Princes	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Education	O
of	O
a	O
Prince	O
.	O
9	O
.	O
Of	O
Greatness	O
of	O
Mind	O
.	O
10	O
.	O
Of	O
the	O
Education	O
of	O
Children	O
11	O
.	O
Of	O
Law	O
.	O
12	O
.	O
Of	O
Man	O
.	O
13	O
.	O
Of	O
Old	O
Age	O
.	O
With	O
the	O
Life	O
and	O
Conversion	O
of	O
St.	O
Mary	O
Magdalen	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Reflections	O
upon	O
the	O
Conversion	O
of	O
the	O
good	O
Thief	O
;	O
also	O
,	O
the	O
Life	O
and	O
Conversion	O
of	O
St.	O
Paul	O
.	O
By	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Bulstrode	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Envoy	O
at	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
Brussels	O
,	O
from	O
King	O
Charles	B-pers
II	I-pers
.	O
and	O
King	O
James	B-pers
II	I-pers
.	O
Publish	O
'd	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Preface	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
Son	O
Whitlock	O
Bulstrode	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
The	O
Second	O
Edition	O
.	O
Both	O
Printed	O
for	O
Edward	B-pers
Symon	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Pope	O
's	O
Head	O
Alley	O
,	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
.	O
