TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice	O
Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
26th	O
,	O
and	O
28th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
,	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
the	O
30th	O
,	O
31st	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
1st	O
,	O
2d	O
,	O
and	O
4th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Tenth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
PETER	B-pers
DELME	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
JURORS	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
.	O
The	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Farrel	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rudley	I-pers
,	O
Obadiah	B-pers
Smart	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Woodhouse	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Simmonds	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bembrick	I-pers
,	O
Philip	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Aubin	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Dear	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Tomlins	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Chandler	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Long	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Forster	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Waddell	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Devenish	I-pers
,	I-pers
John	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Chads	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Chandler	I-pers
,	O
Jacob	B-pers
Broughton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Brighcliff	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Petty	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Vantier	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
Home	O
from	O
a	O
Burying	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
his	O
Hat	O
was	O
snatch	O
'd	O
off	O
from	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Person	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
pursu	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Hat	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
Richard	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
no	O
Defence	O
to	O
make	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
bare	O
Denial	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Skeldon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Christ-Church	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Williams	B-pers
Douglas	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
with	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
riding	O
along	O
a	O
full	O
Gallop	O
,	O
about	O
8	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
being	O
a	O
Carman	O
,	O
was	O
leading	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
riding	O
,	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
threw	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
upon	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
Knees	O
against	O
his	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Horse	O
recovering	O
he	O
rode	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
set	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
he	O
following	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
seized	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
struck	O
him	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Times	O
,	O
in	O
attempting	O
to	O
stop	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
died	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Persons	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
peaceable	O
inoffensive	O
Person	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Witherington	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
Vintrey	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
38	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Anns	I-pers
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
Ann	O
Anns	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
going	O
along	O
Thames	B-place
Street	I-place
,	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
behind	O
her	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
up	O
College-Hill	O
,	O
she	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Son	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
pursuing	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
by	O
the	O
following	O
Evidences	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
hearing	O
a	O
Cry	O
of	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
pursued	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
struck	O
up	O
his	O
Heels	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
fell	O
of	O
his	O
Side	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Pocket	O
was	O
found	O
under	O
him	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Wats	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
coming	O
up	O
when	O
the	O
other	O
Evidence	O
had	O
stopp	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
suspected	O
he	O
would	O
put	O
what	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
stolen	O
down	O
the	O
Cellar	O
Window	O
,	O
against	O
which	O
he	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
endeavour	O
to	O
fall	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
under	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Money	O
was	O
all	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
but	O
believed	O
the	O
two	O
Evidences	O
that	O
apprehended	O
him	O
did	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Peter	I-place
's	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
450	O
Asparagus	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
rather	O
a	O
Trespass	O
than	O
a	O
Felony	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Morrice	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Black	I-place
Friars	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Thorp	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Marriot	I-pers
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
.	O
And	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Vicount	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Forster	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Olave	I-place
's	I-place
Hart-street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
170	O
Pound	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Warehouses	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
,	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
80	O
Pound	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mercer	I-pers
,	O
Humphry	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Hatley	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Warehouses	O
of	O
the	O
Persons	O
before	O
mentioned	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
convicted	O
one	O
Pollard	O
of	O
buying	O
Tobacco	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
some	O
Tobacco	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
acknowledg	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Warehouse	O
.	O
The	O
Facts	O
not	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Shoe	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Strange	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Heslop	I-pers
,	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Shoe	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
Shop	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
given	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
seeming	O
to	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Effects	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Faro	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Queen	I-place
Hithe	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
5	O
Sacks	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
and	O
20	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Malt	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
they	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Hilliard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Randolph	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
various	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
were	O
found	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
in	O
Ratcliff-High-Way	O
;	O
this	O
appear	O
'd	O
plain	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
she	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
her	O
Mother	O
's	O
Room	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Lees	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Hipworth	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Katherine	B-pers
Knapp	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Katherine	O
Knap	O
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Black	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
and	I-pers
Frances	I-pers
Chase	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Hasker	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
depo	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Horse	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Custody	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Extal	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	O
Extal	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
bought	O
the	O
Horse	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bear	O
in	O
Piccadilly	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Goss	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
Boast	O
of	O
having	O
stolen	O
a	O
Horse	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
caused	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
(	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Father	O
in	O
Law	O
,	O
having	O
married	O
his	O
Daughter	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Goslin	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
vouch	O
'd	O
the	O
Horse	O
at	O
Smithfield	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
sold	O
him	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Extal	O
,	O
a	O
Waggoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
He	O
bought	O
the	O
Horse	O
of	O
a	O
Higgler	O
,	O
at	O
or	O
near	O
Bagshot	O
.	O
His	O
Father	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Voucher	O
had	O
paid	O
the	O
Money	O
back	O
again	O
to	O
Extal	O
,	O
the	O
Owner	O
had	O
the	O
Horse	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
Goslin	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
Note	O
of	O
him	O
for	O
5	O
l.	O
The	O
Jury	O
upon	O
considering	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
,	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Spicer	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Precinct	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Catherines	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
value	O
34	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Cornelius	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Cabin	O
on	O
Board	O
of	O
Ship	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Gale	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
Crape	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Season	I-pers
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
over	O
the	O
Hatch	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
out	O
the	O
Crape	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
another	O
Boy	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Christian	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Cheesmore	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
marrying	O
George	B-pers
Mobs	I-pers
,	O
her	O
former	O
Husband	O
John	B-pers
Cheesmore	I-pers
being	O
alive	O
.	O
The	O
Facts	O
not	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
But	O
order	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
give	O
Security	O
for	O
her	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Ashley	I-pers
,	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
Her	O
Husband	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
oblig	O
'd	O
to	O
pawn	O
them	O
,	O
lest	O
he	O
should	O
knock	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Church	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Humble	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Clothes	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
a	O
Watchman	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
apprehended	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Clothes	O
,	O
late	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
several	O
contradictious	O
Stories	O
about	O
coming	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Design	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
from	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Dark	O
,	O
took	O
those	O
Clothes	O
in	O
the	O
Stead	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Matth.ew	B-pers
Deuty	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Finchley	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
5	O
Geese	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Harrard	I-pers
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Osbourne	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White-Chappel	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
Anthony	B-pers
Holman	I-pers
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
Jackson	O
's	O
Confession	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Ann	O
Osbourne	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
James	O
Jackson	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s	O
:	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Snuff	O
Box	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hussey	I-pers
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
his	O
Box	O
in	O
Westminster	O
Hall	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
,	O
and	O
missing	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
the	O
only	O
Person	O
that	O
stood	O
near	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
taxed	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Box	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
up	O
a	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
return	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
That	O
when	O
some	O
Gentlemen	O
went	O
to	O
seize	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
ran	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
hid	O
himself	O
behind	O
a	O
But	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
enquir	O
'd	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
return	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
running	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
hiding	O
himself	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
secure	O
himself	O
from	O
being	O
thrown	O
into	O
the	O
Thames	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Bayne	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
For	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Burbeck	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Lary	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Brandon	I-pers
,	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
along	O
Holborn	B-place
,	O
with	O
two	O
Friends	O
,	O
he	O
stop	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
wanted	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
two	O
Men	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
beat	O
and	O
abused	O
him	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
felt	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Hand	O
at	O
his	O
Thigh	O
,	O
near	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
swear	O
that	O
she	O
picked	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
met	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
and	O
hall	O
'd	O
her	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
her	O
drink	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
refusing	O
,	O
he	O
threatned	O
to	O
charge	O
her	O
with	O
robbing	O
him	O
,	O
whereupon	O
two	O
Men	O
coming	O
to	O
her	O
Assistance	O
,	O
he	O
fought	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
tore	O
one	O
of	O
their	O
Shirts	O
,	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Field	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Wintland	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
Orgars	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Indico	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
7	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
had	O
lost	O
Indico	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
Value	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Wintland	O
brought	O
Indico	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
saying	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
at	O
Wapping	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Holt	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
a	O
Bag	O
of	O
Indico	O
,	O
of	O
25	O
l.	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
recommend	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
Customer	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
taken	O
a	O
Sample	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
Capt	O
.	O
Hodges	O
,	O
a	O
Dyer	O
,	O
and	O
treating	O
with	O
him	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Cook	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
Indico	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Cook	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
searched	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
before	O
Sir	O
Francis	B-pers
Forbes	I-pers
some	O
Persons	O
were	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Wapping	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
bought	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Persons	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
one	O
Ailswel	O
,	O
a	O
Porter	O
,	O
who	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
South	O
Sea	O
Company	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
also	O
did	O
in	O
open	O
Court	O
upon	O
Oath	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Wintland	O
pleaded	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
that	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
sale	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Behalf	O
of	O
Field	O
.	O
Field	O
pleaded	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
.	O
They	O
both	O
called	O
some	O
Persons	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
them	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
work	O
'd	O
on	O
board	O
of	O
Ships	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Dickweed	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
's	I-place
Quern	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
,	O
Value	O
13	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Ring	O
was	O
laid	O
in	O
a	O
Draw	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
upon	O
a	O
Table	O
in	O
a	O
Fore-room	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
living	O
at	O
a	O
publick	O
House	O
,	O
went	O
for	O
Pots	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
,	O
the	O
Ring	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
produc	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
produced	O
his	O
Fellow-Servant	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Evidences	O
,	O
that	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
shew	O
'd	O
them	O
the	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Betty	I-pers
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Hambleton	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Hammond	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
three	O
Hundred	O
Weight	O
of	O
Logwood	O
,	O
Value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Dovy	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
great	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Logwood	O
lay	O
upon	O
Porters-Key	B-place
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
three	O
Hundred	O
Weight	O
of	O
it	O
wanting	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Aldersey	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
working	O
upon	O
the	O
Keys	O
as	O
a	O
Labourer	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
they	O
carried	O
off	O
about	O
three	O
Hundred	O
Weight	O
of	O
Logwood	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
in	O
Tower	O
Ditch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
early	O
,	O
carried	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
at	O
Times	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
Dyer	O
,	O
in	O
Fashion	O
Street	O
,	O
in	O
Brick-Lane	O
,	O
for	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Hundred	O
Weight	O
.	O
The	O
Watchman	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
several	O
Persons	O
loitering	O
about	O
the	O
Logwood	O
,	O
at	O
an	O
unseasonable	O
Time	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Logwood	O
rattle	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
stopped	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
believes	O
it	O
was	O
Aldersey	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
afterwards	O
three	O
Hundred	O
Weight	O
of	O
it	O
missing	O
.	O
Betty	O
had	O
confessed	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
Aldersey	O
had	O
taken	O
about	O
70	O
l.	O
of	O
Logwood	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Mud	O
,	O
at	O
Wiggen's-Key	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
5	O
s.	O
Betty	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
sold	O
70	O
l.	O
of	O
Logwood	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Mud	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
suppos	O
'd	O
had	O
fallen	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Scale	O
in	O
Weighing	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
lain	O
there	O
several	O
Days	O
.	O
Hambleton	O
own	O
'd	O
nothing	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
,	O
some	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
of	O
Tallow	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
Joseph	O
Cooper	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
Basket	O
of	O
Tallow	O
that	O
stood	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
stolen	O
away	O
about	O
Eight	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
Stephen	O
Aldersey	O
sent	O
him	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
others	O
stole	O
it	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Betty	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
spoken	O
to	O
him	O
of	O
Tallow	O
,	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
Tallow	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
.	O
Stephen	O
Aldersey	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
took	O
Tallow	O
off	O
the	O
Shop	O
Window	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Pitts	O
,	O
a	O
Tallow	O
Chandler	O
at	O
St.	O
Catherines	O
.	O
Betty	O
own	O
'd	O
a	O
Letter	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Pitts	O
,	O
wherein	O
he	O
mentions	O
a	O
Person	O
having	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
Tallow	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Hambleton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Buttolph-Lane	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
107	O
Pounds	O
of	O
Raisins	O
,	O
Value	O
29	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Barreau	I-pers
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Barrel	O
of	O
Fruit	O
was	O
taken	O
off	O
the	O
Keys	O
,	O
at	O
Buttolph	B-place
's	I-place
Wharf	I-place
,	O
and	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Cask	O
in	O
his	O
Way	O
,	O
kicking	O
it	O
,	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Leadbeater	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bartholomew	I-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
the	I-place
Exchange	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
quilted	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
Value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Susan	B-pers
Staples	I-pers
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Petticoat	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
Susan	B-pers
Elliot	I-pers
;	O
her	O
Confession	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hutchinson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
marrying	O
William	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
her	O
former	O
Husband	O
Percival	B-pers
Hutchinson	I-pers
being	O
alive	O
.	O
Two	O
Evidences	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
were	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
first	O
Marriage	O
to	O
Hutchinson	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Hutchinson	O
was	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
the	O
last	O
Week	O
;	O
two	O
other	O
Evidences	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
second	O
Marriage	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
either	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
Extenuation	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
alledg	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
Percival	O
Hutchinson	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
her	O
within	O
two	O
Hours	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
never	O
bedded	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Hutchinson	O
had	O
married	O
another	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Nichols	O
knew	O
that	O
Hutchinson	O
had	O
married	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
a	O
Warrant	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
up	O
to	O
prosecute	O
him	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
before	O
he	O
married	O
her	O
himself	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
Nichols	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
acknowledg	O
'd	O
his	O
Folly	O
,	O
and	O
want	O
of	O
Consideration	O
of	O
the	O
Consequences	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolph	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
Value	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
Tankard	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
without	O
either	O
Lid	O
or	O
Handle	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
suspecting	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
stopp	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
prevaricated	O
in	O
his	O
Story	O
,	O
saying	O
one	O
Time	O
he	O
brought	O
it	O
from	O
one	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Time	O
from	O
another	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
of	O
a	O
good	O
Family	O
,	O
but	O
reputed	O
Crazy	O
,	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
Proof	O
he	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Ingersol	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Franklin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Queen-hithe	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold-Chain	O
,	O
Value	O
36	O
s.	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Dunwell	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Chain	O
was	O
taken	O
off	O
a	O
Child	O
's	O
Neck	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
Pawn	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
They	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Several	O
Persons	O
appeared	O
to	O
the	O
Reputation	O
of	O
both	O
the	O
Girles	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
them	O
an	O
honest	O
Character	O
till	O
the	O
Commission	O
of	O
this	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Stew-Pan	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Stew-Pan	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
apprehended	O
immediately	O
with	O
the	O
Pan	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Mead	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Magnus	I-place
the	I-place
Martyr	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Trail	B-pers
Waldron	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
Which	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Mountier	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
Ludgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Headclothes	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Beckington	I-pers
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
three	O
Days	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Sturges	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Fore	O
quarter	O
of	O
Mutton	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Billington	I-pers
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Breeches	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
pursued	O
and	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
drop	O
'd	O
the	O
Breeches	O
upon	O
his	O
being	O
apprehended	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Christian	B-pers
Busbey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
taking	O
a	O
Hat	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
Person	O
she	O
called	O
Husband	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Fleet-Lane	B-place
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
snatch	O
'd	O
his	O
Hat	O
off	O
from	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
both	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
pursued	O
,	O
and	O
caught	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Man	O
made	O
off	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Hat	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Cowley	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Curtis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Noblet	I-pers
,	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Country	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
that	O
Means	O
,	O
had	O
several	O
Times	O
Access	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
carry	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
small	O
Trunk	O
;	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Blew	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White-chapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Basket	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
Half	O
Peck	O
and	O
quartern	O
Loaves	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Riston	I-pers
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Basket	O
and	O
Bread	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
set	O
down	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Leaden-hall	B-place
Market	I-place
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
Rag-Fair	O
,	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
Bread	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Fowles	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Allison	I-pers
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
An	O
Acquaintance	O
of	O
his	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
pawn	O
the	O
Coat	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Clarks	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
Several	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
also	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Tuffey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dolphin	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Shelton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Dolphin	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
he	O
lodg	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
lost	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Purse	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Closet	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Frances	B-pers
Tuffey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Hadley	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Linnen	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
There	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
to	O
convict	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Kirk	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Hadley	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
30	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
It	O
also	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
Father	O
in	O
Law	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
their	O
Mother	O
being	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
said	O
before	O
she	O
died	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
30	O
l.	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
knew	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
because	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
produce	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
therefore	O
indicted	O
them	O
of	O
Robberies	O
,	O
which	O
appearing	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
ordered	O
them	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
their	O
Indictments	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Ferrel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Enfield	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2000	O
Nails	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Pound	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Porter	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
together	O
with	O
2	O
other	O
Persons	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
break	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
take	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
a	O
Box	O
with	O
17	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
24	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Tone	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
French	I-pers
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
of	O
other	O
Persons	O
.	O
There	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Hancock	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bullock	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
deficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Barber	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Abrahams	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4s	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
13	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
There	O
not	O
being	O
Evidence	O
sufficient	O
to	O
affect	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
reputable	O
People	O
appearing	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Badrock	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
an	O
Iron	O
Grate	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Cooling	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Appleby	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Ruscum	I-pers
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Piece	O
of	O
Cloth	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
immediately	O
.	O
He	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
which	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
several	O
Persons	O
of	O
Credit	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
never	O
known	O
any	O
ill	O
Action	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
sober	O
honest	O
Person	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Walkup	I-pers
and	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Clifford	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
Snuff-box	O
,	O
4	O
Guineas	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Forster	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidences	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
did	O
lodge	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
left	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
together	O
in	O
her	O
Room	O
,	O
while	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
supper	O
with	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
Lodgers	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
her	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Lock	O
of	O
her	O
Scriptore	O
was	O
broken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Lid	O
being	O
put	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
being	O
lock	O
'd	O
,	O
fell	O
down	O
and	O
hurt	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
found	O
her	O
Money	O
and	O
Plate	O
gone	O
.	O
And	O
Samuel	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
a	O
Pencil	O
of	O
Ivory	O
(	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
had	O
20	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Book	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Place	O
,	O
was	O
left	O
by	O
Walkup	O
,	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
bought	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
and	O
Stockins	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wilden	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Eleanor	O
Clifford	O
did	O
in	O
the	O
Gaol	O
affirm	O
to	O
the	O
Face	O
of	O
Walkup	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
throw	O
up	O
the	O
Flap	O
of	O
the	O
Scriptore	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
stuck	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
lock	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
Walkup	O
,	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
Clifford	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	I-pers
of	I-pers
the	I-pers
Parish	I-pers
of	I-pers
Hesson	I-pers
,	I-pers
and	I-pers
Dorothy	I-pers
his	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
with	O
one	O
Minton	O
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Trantam	I-pers
,	O
between	O
the	O
Hours	O
of	O
6	O
and	O
8	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Linnen	O
,	O
Plate	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Thomas	O
Williams	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Dowman	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
House	O
between	O
6	O
and	O
8	O
a-Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
Dowman	O
came	O
in	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
Williams	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
Disguise	O
,	O
and	O
Williams	O
had	O
in	O
one	O
Hand	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
a	O
naked	O
Bayonet	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
they	O
came	O
upon	O
a	O
desperate	O
Design	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
for	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
Money	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
;	O
that	O
Williams	O
went	O
up	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Linnen	O
,	O
his	O
Spoons	O
,	O
Cup	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
13	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
bound	O
them	O
all	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dowman	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
lodg	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Williams	O
at	O
Hounsloe	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
often	O
sollicited	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
a	O
Robbing	O
on	O
the	O
High-Way	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
Pistols	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
so	O
;	O
that	O
also	O
he	O
proposed	O
to	O
rob	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Farmer	O
,	O
and	O
none	O
but	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
were	O
old	O
,	O
and	O
worth	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
encouraged	O
him	O
,	O
saying	O
.	O
There	O
must	O
be	O
Money	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
borrow	O
'd	O
Money	O
upon	O
Rings	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
must	O
be	O
also	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Linnen	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
could	O
never	O
wear	O
out	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
all	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
Williams	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
the	O
back	O
Way	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
sitting	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
;	O
that	O
being	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
over	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
he	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
to	O
let	O
Williams	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
consulted	O
how	O
to	O
get	O
them	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
and	O
Williams	O
said	O
that	O
such	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
thereabouts	O
used	O
to	O
entertain	O
Lodgers	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
Eggs	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
should	O
knock	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
say	O
he	O
was	O
that	O
Woman	O
's	O
Son	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
Eggs	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
in	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
open	O
'd	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
Williams	O
follow	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
staid	O
below	O
Stairs	O
,	O
while	O
Williams	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
took	O
he	O
Money	O
and	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Linnen	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
two	O
Guineas	O
and	O
the	O
Cup	O
he	O
conceal	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
But	O
acquitted	O
Dorothy	O
Williams	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
,	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
and	O
Robbing	O
Williams	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
of	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
a	O
Hanger	O
,	O
a	O
Snuff-box	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
at	O
Smallberry	B-place
Green	I-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
Hesson	I-place
,	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Men	O
met	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
struck	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
barbarous	O
Manner	O
with	O
a	O
Hatchet	O
on	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
Snuff-box	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
again	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Information	O
of	O
Dowman	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
hidden	O
under	O
the	O
Boards	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
Dowman	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Minton	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
rob	O
on	O
Smallberry	O
Green	O
,	O
and	O
beat	O
about	O
the	O
Lane	O
,	O
for	O
an	O
Hour	O
;	O
that	O
meeting	O
with	O
no	O
Prey	O
,	O
they	O
at	O
length	O
met	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
related	O
,	O
took	O
those	O
Things	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
William	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
hid	O
them	O
under	O
the	O
Boards	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
upon	O
being	O
apprehended	O
,	O
inform	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
accordingly	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
likewise	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
third	O
Time	O
,	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
High-Way	O
,	O
and	O
Robbing	O
him	O
of	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Stud	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
on	O
the	O
Road	O
near	O
Southal	B-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Windmil-Lane	I-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
two	O
others	O
met	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
off	O
from	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
of	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Stud	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Dowman	I-pers
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Piper	I-pers
,	O
since	O
dead	O
in	O
Newgate	O
.	O
That	O
Williams	O
carried	O
out	O
a	O
Hatchet	O
under	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
been	O
out	O
to	O
rob	O
three	O
Nights	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
met	O
with	O
any	O
Body	O
to	O
rob	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Rage	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
rob	O
the	O
next	O
Man	O
he	O
met	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
if	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
flinch	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
cut	O
him	O
to	O
pieces	O
.	O
That	O
some	O
Time	O
after	O
they	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Newgate	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
committing	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
his	O
Silver	O
Stud	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
not	O
having	O
any	O
Thing	O
material	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
also	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Ware	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White-chapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cane	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Melton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Loyd	I-pers
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
being	O
standing	O
together	O
a	O
pricking	O
at	O
the	O
Garter	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
him	O
have	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
they	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
a	O
Clock	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
to	O
see	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
snatched	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
persued	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Alhallows	B-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Wall	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
Iron	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Ashbourn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Dennis	I-pers
,	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Botfield	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Mare	O
,	O
value	O
33	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Mare	O
;	O
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Crampon	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
bought	O
the	O
Mare	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Mare	O
in	O
exchange	O
for	O
another	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
Persons	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Queen-Hithe	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
having	O
confest	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
And	O
also	O
,	O
She	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Nicholas	I-place
Cole-Abby	I-place
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
This	O
Fact	O
also	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
having	O
also	O
confest	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Beech	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Susan	B-pers
Ruffield	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
having	O
confest	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Leather	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Humes	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
coming	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
they	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Tailor	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Hannah	B-pers
Tailor	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Wig	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
Tea	O
Spoon	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Partington	I-pers
,	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
not	O
thinking	O
the	O
Evidence	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Pitt	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Precinct	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Katherine	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
buying	O
144	O
Pound	O
of	O
Tallow	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
stolen	O
by	O
Robert	B-pers
Betty	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Hambleton	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
convicted	O
for	O
the	O
Fact	O
this	O
present	O
Sessions	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
being	O
inform	O
'd	O
by	O
one	O
Aldersey	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
bought	O
his	O
Tallow	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
for	O
apprehending	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
for	O
8	O
or	O
9	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
burnt	O
the	O
Basket	O
,	O
and	O
described	O
the	O
Basket	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
by	O
his	O
Description	O
it	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Basket	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
such	O
sort	O
of	O
Stuff	O
,	O
that	O
any	O
Tallow-Chandler	O
must	O
needs	O
know	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
stolen	O
.	O
Two	O
other	O
Evidences	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
such	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Tallow	O
and	O
burnt	O
the	O
Basket	O
.	O
Stephen	O
Aldersey	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
and	O
his	O
Accomplices	O
sold	O
the	O
Tallow	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
for	O
9	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
full	O
Pots	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
bring	O
him	O
any	O
Tallow	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
let	O
them	O
in	O
at	O
any	O
Time	O
at	O
his	O
back	O
Door	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Tallow	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Persons	O
that	O
sold	O
him	O
it	O
,	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
honestly	O
come	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
full	O
Value	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
being	O
satisfied	O
in	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Deacon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White-Chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
buying	O
300	O
Weight	O
of	O
Logwood	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Dovey	I-pers
,	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
stolen	O
by	O
Robert	O
Betty	O
,	O
Robert	O
Hambleton	O
,	O
and	O
Stephen	O
Aldersey	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
the	O
2	O
former	O
were	O
convicted	O
this	O
present	O
Sessions	O
.	O
One	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
between	O
2	O
and	O
3	O
Hundred	O
Weight	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
dirty	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
there	O
was	O
2	O
Hundred	O
and	O
Three	O
Quarters	O
of	O
Logwood	O
,	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
Three	B-place
Cranes	I-place
in	I-place
Brick	I-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
them	O
bring	O
it	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
after	O
the	O
Rate	O
of	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Hundred	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
if	O
they	O
could	O
get	O
him	O
any	O
Indico	O
and	O
Sugar	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
buy	O
it	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
dirty	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
weigh	O
'd	O
the	O
heavier	O
,	O
and	O
weigh	O
'd	O
but	O
2	O
Hundred	O
7	O
Pound	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
damag	O
'd	O
and	O
rotten	O
.	O
And	O
John	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Wood	O
was	O
bought	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
publickly	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
damaged	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
there	O
was	O
Allowance	O
made	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
Business	O
to	O
cut	O
the	O
Wood	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Stick	O
of	O
about	O
3	O
Quarters	O
of	O
a	O
Hundred	O
was	O
damag	O
'd	O
and	O
rotten	O
,	O
and	O
good	O
for	O
little	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
had	O
work	O
'd	O
for	O
him	O
Several	O
years	O
,	O
yet	O
he	O
never	O
knew	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
any	O
Logwood	O
but	O
of	O
the	O
Salter	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
him	O
for	O
Cutting	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
Salter	O
's	O
Bill	O
.	O
He	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Trinity	B-place
Minories	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
190	O
Pound	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
of	O
Micajah	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gumes	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Harding	O
and	O
himself	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
Part	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
Ratcliff-High-Way	O
,	O
and	O
Part	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Baldwin	O
in	O
Rosemary	O
Lane	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Baldwin	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
Thomas	O
Gumes	O
the	O
Black	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
him	O
5	O
Pound	O
of	O
the	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
had	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
but	O
that	O
they	O
came	O
honestly	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Whitechapel	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
,	I-pers
and	I-pers
Company	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Company	O
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Southernwood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Magnes	I-place
the	I-place
Martyr	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Chance	I-pers
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
having	O
been	O
at	O
an	O
Entertainment	O
in	O
Southwark	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
much	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
over	O
the	O
Bridge	O
a	O
Woman	O
attack	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
turn	O
'd	O
him	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
at	O
his	O
Watch	O
and	O
broke	O
the	O
String	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
second	O
Attack	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
of	O
his	O
Money	O
and	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
catch	O
at	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
Dirt	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Mackdonnel	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
going	O
over	O
the	O
Bridge	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
much	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
going	O
together	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
apprehensive	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
pick	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
and	O
another	O
Person	O
coming	O
by	O
with	O
a	O
Link	O
,	O
he	O
bid	O
him	O
keep	O
a	O
little	O
back	O
to	O
observe	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
he	O
saw	O
her	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
turn	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
sell	O
down	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Watch	O
glittering	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
they	O
pursu	O
'd	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Oman	I-pers
confirm	O
'd	O
what	O
Mr.	O
Mackdonnel	O
had	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
carrying	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-House	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Watch	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
return	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
afterwards	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
help	O
it	O
if	O
she	O
must	O
cross	O
the	O
Water	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
lead	O
Monkeys	O
to	O
Water	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
a	O
Silver	O
Salt	O
,	O
and	O
Knives	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Dr.	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
stolen	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Yarwood	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
convicted	O
for	O
the	O
Offence	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
former	O
Sessions	O
.	O
There	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
's	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Ring	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Lewis	B-pers
Hussare	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Shoreditch	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Hussare	I-pers
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
on	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquest	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Rondeau	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Mother	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
living	O
in	O
Swan	B-place
Alley	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
a	O
Boy	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
,	O
telling	O
her	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Black	O
Dog	O
within	O
Bishopsgate	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Daughter	O
inquiring	O
of	O
the	O
Boy	O
,	O
what	O
sort	O
of	O
Person	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
the	O
Boy	O
answered	O
,	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
whitish	O
Clothes	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
no	O
Person	O
who	O
wanted	O
her	O
there	O
;	O
that	O
thereupon	O
she	O
return	O
'd	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
whereas	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
she	O
left	O
her	O
Daughter	O
sitting	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
back	O
she	O
found	O
her	O
sitting	O
in	O
her	O
Chair	O
as	O
tho	O
'	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
asleep	O
,	O
with	O
her	O
Hand	O
leaning	O
against	O
the	O
Chimney	O
Piece	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
calling	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
what	O
are	O
you	O
asleep	O
?	O
And	O
she	O
not	O
answering	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
Hands	O
,	O
upon	O
her	O
letting	O
it	O
go	O
it	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
which	O
surprizing	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
Blood	O
,	O
immediately	O
saw	O
her	O
Throat	O
had	O
been	O
cut	O
.	O
Being	O
ask	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
after	O
what	O
Manner	O
he	O
had	O
behav	O
'd	O
himself	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
?	O
She	O
answered	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
married	O
6	O
years	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
little	O
of	O
the	O
Time	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
by	O
Gaming	O
consum	O
'd	O
all	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
2	O
Years	O
after	O
,	O
she	O
having	O
been	O
furnish	O
'd	O
with	O
Household	O
Goods	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
under	O
Presence	O
of	O
behaving	O
himself	O
better	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
had	O
induc	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
live	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
having	O
gotten	O
the	O
Goods	O
into	O
the	O
Cart	O
,	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
different	O
Place	O
than	O
what	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
absconded	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
That	O
since	O
Christmas	O
last	O
,	O
he	O
pretended	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
complaining	O
of	O
some	O
Pain	O
in	O
her	O
Stomach	O
,	O
he	O
pretended	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
something	O
that	O
would	O
do	O
her	O
good	O
,	O
and	O
pretending	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
a	O
Barber	O
,	O
went	O
and	O
fetched	O
what	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
Conserve	O
of	O
Roses	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
in	O
an	O
Hour	O
's	O
Time	O
set	O
her	O
so	O
violently	O
a	O
Vomiting	O
for	O
several	O
Hours	O
,	O
she	O
thought	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
died	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
she	O
lay	O
as	O
in	O
a	O
Swoon	O
,	O
senseless	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
apprehended	O
she	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
she	O
recover	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
;	O
and	O
always	O
after	O
it	O
complain	O
'd	O
of	O
a	O
great	O
Pain	O
in	O
her	O
Stomach	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
should	O
never	O
be	O
well	O
after	O
it	O
.	O
Being	O
ask	O
'd	O
how	O
she	O
left	O
the	O
Door	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
?	O
She	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
upon	O
a	O
French	O
Latch	O
,	O
which	O
open	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
Outside	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
put	O
on	O
the	O
Door	O
himself	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Rupert	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
she	O
thinks	O
,	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
see	O
a	O
Boy	O
and	O
Man	O
,	O
such	O
a	O
one	O
in	O
Person	O
as	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
the	O
Deceased	O
did	O
live	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
whitish	O
Clothes	O
on	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
his	O
Hat	O
flapping	O
over	O
his	O
Face	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Boy	O
and	O
he	O
were	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Man	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Boy	O
which	O
Way	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Boy	O
said	O
that	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Man	O
went	O
towards	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Boy	O
ran	O
towards	O
Shoreditch	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Bread	I-pers
and	I-pers
Wine	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
living	O
within	O
2	O
Doors	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
for	O
a	O
Pail	O
of	O
Water	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
a	O
Boy	O
and	O
a	O
Man	O
running	O
towards	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Man	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
whitish	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Boy	O
in	O
a	O
brown	O
colour	O
'd	O
Coat	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Boy	O
went	O
down	O
the	O
Steps	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
Mother	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Man	O
was	O
as	O
to	O
Height	O
and	O
Person	O
every	O
way	O
like	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Solomon	B-pers
Rondeau	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
about	O
8	O
a	O
Clock	O
his	O
Mother	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
his	O
Sister	O
's	O
Throat	O
was	O
cut	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Wind	O
Pipe	O
was	O
cut	O
clear	O
asunder	O
;	O
that	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
little	O
recover	O
'd	O
his	O
Surprize	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
to	O
the	O
Black	O
Dog	O
,	O
but	O
hearing	O
nothing	O
of	O
any	O
Person	O
,	O
suspecting	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
done	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Lothbury	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
directed	O
from	O
Place	O
to	O
Place	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Blew	O
Ball	O
,	O
in	O
Princes-Street	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
answer	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Maid	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
he	O
got	O
a	O
Constable	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
apprehend	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Maid	O
deny	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
asserting	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
saying	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
Officer	O
,	O
she	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
knocking	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
his	O
second	O
Wife	O
answered	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
Time	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
having	O
slipt	O
on	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Constable	O
telling	O
him	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
apprehend	O
him	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
having	O
murthered	O
his	O
Wife	O
Ann	O
Hussare	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
set	O
up	O
a	O
kind	O
of	O
a	O
Bravado-Laugh	O
,	O
bidding	O
him	O
look	O
in	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
Thing	O
in	O
his	O
Countenance	O
that	O
should	O
induce	O
him	O
to	O
believe	O
he	O
could	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
Fact	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
the	O
Constable	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Solomon	B-pers
Rondeau	I-pers
coming	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
apprehend	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
they	O
were	O
inform	O
'd	O
in	O
Lothbury	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
married	O
another	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
lodge	O
at	O
the	O
Blew	O
Ball	O
,	O
in	O
Princes	O
Street	O
;	O
that	O
going	O
thither	O
,	O
the	O
Maid	O
deny	O
'd	O
his	O
lodging	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
telling	O
her	O
he	O
was	O
well	O
assur	O
'd	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
come	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
what	O
Room	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
apprehended	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Manner	O
before	O
related	O
;	O
that	O
upon	O
telling	O
him	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
he	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
shew	O
but	O
very	O
little	O
Concern	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
was	O
entirely	O
innocent	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Pockets	O
a	O
Razor	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Case	O
of	O
Lancers	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Waldridge	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
a	O
Room	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
in	O
Swan	O
Alley	O
in	O
Coleman-street	O
,	O
without	O
Bed	O
or	O
Furniture	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
used	O
sometimes	O
to	O
work	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
thither	O
that	O
Night	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
about	O
6	O
,	O
or	O
between	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
,	O
staid	O
there	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
had	O
a	O
white	O
Coat	O
on	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
That	O
afterwards	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Condemn	O
'd	O
Hole	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
that	O
Night	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
liv	O
'd	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Waldridge	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
there	O
that	O
Night	O
about	O
6	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
in	O
his	O
shaving	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
Coat	O
on	O
of	O
a	O
whitish	O
Colour	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Cane	O
and	O
Sword	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Deborah	B-pers
Sprag	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
new	O
Wife	O
being	O
her	O
Acquaintance	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Turk	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Workhouse	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-Street	O
,	O
on	O
a	O
Visit	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Apprentice	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
her	O
Husband	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
fetch	O
her	O
Home	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Maid	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
it	O
was	O
past	O
8	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
she	O
might	O
shut	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
out	O
Victuals	O
for	O
the	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
just	O
done	O
his	O
Supper	O
,	O
having	O
eaten	O
the	O
Meat	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
knock	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
If	O
I	O
must	O
not	O
eat	O
with	O
you	O
I	O
will	O
drink	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
eat	O
no	O
Supper	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
in	O
a	O
musing	O
Posture	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
set	O
his	O
Cane	O
in	O
the	O
Chimney	O
Corner	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
on	O
a	O
sudden	O
catch	O
'd	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
gave	O
a	O
great	O
Start	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
Motion	O
she	O
being	O
a	O
little	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
,	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
the	O
Reason	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
,	O
after	O
a	O
Pause	O
,	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
least	O
her	O
Husband	O
should	O
come	O
Home	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
to	O
dirtily	O
dress	O
'd	O
,	O
having	O
just	O
come	O
from	O
his	O
Business	O
.	O
Clarges	B-pers
Fradding	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
About	O
a	O
Year	O
since	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
the	O
Liberty	O
of	O
his	O
Shop	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Wig	O
in	O
,	O
in	O
some	O
Discourse	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
wondered	O
how	O
he	O
could	O
pretend	O
Courtship	O
to	O
so	O
many	O
young	O
Women	O
as	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
when	O
if	O
he	O
gain	O
'd	O
their	O
Consent	O
he	O
knew	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
marry	O
them	O
,	O
having	O
a	O
Wife	O
already	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
well	O
enough	O
as	O
to	O
that	O
;	O
that	O
his	O
Wife	O
was	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
Religion	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
deserv	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
burnt	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
no	O
more	O
Sin	O
to	O
kill	O
her	O
than	O
to	O
kill	O
a	O
Dog	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
Body	O
else	O
:	O
And	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
before	O
Sir	O
Francis	B-pers
Forbes	I-pers
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Socinian	O
.	O
Lewis	B-pers
Marriot	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
talking	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
second	O
Wife	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
married	O
about	O
five	O
Weeks	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
hearing	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
another	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
taxing	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
swore	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Sacrament	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
;	O
that	O
upon	O
this	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
so	O
,	O
he	O
ought	O
to	O
arrest	O
those	O
People	O
,	O
and	O
clear	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
cohabit	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
My	O
Dear	O
,	O
be	O
not	O
uneasy	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
make	O
you	O
sensible	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
Time	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
other	O
Wife	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
asserted	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
his	O
deceased	O
Wife	O
since	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
And	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
following	O
Evidences	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Satchel	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
about	O
six	O
a-Clock	O
,	O
the	O
Chimes	O
at	O
the	O
Change	O
having	O
newly	O
gone	O
,	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
borrow	O
six	O
Pence	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Newgate-Street	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
again	O
about	O
Half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
seven	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
then	O
the	O
Clothes	O
on	O
which	O
he	O
appear	O
'd	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Payton	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
from	O
her	O
Mistress	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
Madam	O
Hern	O
's	O
,	O
to	O
put	O
on	O
some	O
Clothes	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
her	O
Mistress	O
at	O
Madam	O
Sprag	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Turk	O
's	O
Head	O
in	O
Newgate-Street	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
the	O
Second	O
Time	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
eight	O
a-Clock	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Madam	O
Sprag	O
's	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
his	O
Back	O
was	O
white	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
no	O
Matter	O
,	O
went	O
away	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
Home	O
with	O
her	O
Mistress	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Pipe	I-pers
,	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Hern	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
out	O
,	O
came	O
home	O
about	O
five	O
a-Clock	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
he	O
afterwards	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
afterwards	O
went	O
to	O
Madam	O
Sprag	O
's	O
and	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
before	O
related	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
past	O
eight	O
a-Clock	O
.	O
Lucy	B-pers
Stock	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
When	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Sprag	O
's	O
it	O
was	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
a-Clock	O
.	O
Lewis	B-pers
Haynes	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
guess	O
,	O
in	O
Throckmorton	O
Street	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
a-Clock	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Clothes	O
he	O
had	O
on	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
which	O
did	O
not	O
answer	O
in	O
Colour	O
to	O
the	O
whitish	O
Clothes	O
he	O
was	O
suppos	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
seen	O
in	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
the	O
Murther	O
was	O
.	O
Though	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
Presumptions	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
were	O
very	O
strong	O
,	O
yet	O
not	O
amounting	O
to	O
legal	O
Evidence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
;	O
But	O
the	O
Court	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
That	O
though	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Murther	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
prosecuted	O
for	O
Bigamy	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Islington	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
her	O
Child	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
at	O
the	O
Red	B-place
Lion	I-place
at	I-place
Holloway	I-place
;	O
that	O
being	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
tax	O
'd	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
although	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Husband	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
before	O
her	O
Delivery	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
deliver	O
'd	O
privately	O
,	O
afterwards	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
over	O
now	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
had	O
miscarried	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
constrained	O
to	O
tell	O
where	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
buried	O
in	O
a	O
Garden	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
two	O
Stabs	O
in	O
the	O
Belly	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
when	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
A	O
Midwife	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
Child	O
at	O
its	O
full	O
Time	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
wanted	O
three	O
Months	O
of	O
her	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
born	O
dead	O
:	O
But	O
one	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
She	O
had	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
was	O
born	O
alive	O
.	O
But	O
giving	O
no	O
Account	O
how	O
it	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
two	O
Stabs	O
in	O
the	O
Belly	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
such	O
an	O
one	O
that	O
the	O
Bowels	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
upon	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Ravishing	O
and	O
carnally	O
knowing	O
Dorcas	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Infant	O
of	O
five	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
for	O
an	O
Assault	O
upon	O
the	O
said	O
Dorcas	O
Reeves	O
.	O
The	O
Mother	O
of	O
the	O
Child	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
her	O
next	O
Door	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
was	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
when	O
his	O
Sister	O
having	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
then	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
Home	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Child	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
under	O
Pretence	O
of	O
bearing	O
him	O
Company	O
;	O
and	O
some	O
Times	O
after	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
a	O
way	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Half-Penny	O
,	O
bidding	O
her	O
buy	O
some	O
Plumbs	O
:	O
That	O
some	O
Time	O
after	O
the	O
Child	O
complain	O
'd	O
much	O
of	O
her	O
being	O
sore	O
,	O
and	O
pointed	O
to	O
her	O
private	O
Parts	O
.	O
That	O
examining	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
sad	O
Condition	O
,	O
and	O
enquiring	O
of	O
her	O
how	O
it	O
came	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
her	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
made	O
her	O
kneel	O
upon	O
his	O
Knees	O
had	O
taken	O
up	O
her	O
Coats	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
hurt	O
her	O
sadly	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bradbury	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
very	O
much	O
injured	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Parts	O
were	O
much	O
inflamed	O
and	O
excoriated	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
manifest	O
Perforation	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
also	O
had	O
the	O
Assistance	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Fern	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
of	O
his	O
Opinion	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
had	O
been	O
very	O
much	O
damaged	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
child	O
did	O
say	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
done	O
to	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Child	O
being	O
too	O
young	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Rape	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Assault	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hare	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
's	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Brass	O
Coach-Buckles	O
,	O
and	O
Housings	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Nathan	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
were	O
cut	O
off	O
from	O
the	O
Horses	O
Harness	O
as	O
the	O
Coach	O
was	O
standing	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Tea-Table	O
,	O
value	O
30s	O
.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Momford	I-pers
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
groundless	O
and	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
granted	O
them	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Frederick	B-pers
Schmidt	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
erasing	O
and	O
altering	O
a	O
Bank	O
Note	O
.	O
For	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
wickedly	O
,	O
and	O
fraudulently	O
,	O
intending	O
unjust	O
Lucre	O
,	O
to	O
acquire	O
and	O
obtain	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
well	O
the	O
Governor	B-pers
and	I-pers
Company	I-pers
of	I-pers
the	I-pers
Bank	I-pers
of	I-pers
England	I-pers
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
divers	O
other	O
Subjects	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
to	O
Deceive	O
and	O
Defraud	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
publishing	O
of	O
a	O
Statute	O
,	O
in	O
this	O
Case	O
made	O
and	O
provided	O
(	O
that	O
is	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
the	O
16th	O
Day	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
10th	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
by	O
Force	O
of	O
Arms	O
,	O
feloniously	O
,	O
unlawfully	O
and	O
fraudently	O
,	O
Forge	O
and	O
Counterfeit	O
a	O
Note	O
in	O
Form	O
of	O
a	O
Bank	O
Note	O
,	O
bearing	O
Date	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
1723	O
,	O
sign	O
'd	O
in	O
behalf	O
of	O
the	O
Governor	O
and	O
Company	O
of	O
the	O
Bank	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Payment	O
of	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
one	O
hundred	O
Pounds	O
,	O
to	O
Mr.	O
William	O
Richardson	O
,	O
or	O
Bearer	O
;	O
against	O
the	O
Peace	O
of	O
our	O
Sovereign	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
his	O
Crown	O
and	O
Dignity	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Statute	O
in	O
that	O
Case	O
made	O
and	O
provided	O
.	O
The	O
Case	O
was	O
open	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Council	O
,	O
setting	O
forth	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
gotten	O
into	O
the	O
Acquaintance	O
of	O
the	O
Baron	B-pers
de	I-pers
Loden	I-pers
and	O
Eleonora	B-pers
Sophia	I-pers
,	O
Countess	O
of	O
Bostram	O
,	O
he	O
entrusted	O
the	O
Baron	O
with	O
a	O
Bank	O
Note	O
of	O
600	O
l	O
on	O
which	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
200	O
or	O
300	O
l.	O
borrow	O
'd	O
upon	O
,	O
under	O
pretence	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
left	O
by	O
a	O
Person	O
to	O
transact	O
his	O
Affairs	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
gone	O
Abroad	O
for	O
a	O
small	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
willingly	O
return	O
him	O
the	O
self	O
same	O
Note	O
.	O
He	O
thereupon	O
went	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Perrier	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
not	O
readily	O
coming	O
into	O
it	O
,	O
afterwards	O
,	O
he	O
applied	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Minet	O
,	O
a	O
Merchant	O
but	O
he	O
refusing	O
,	O
this	O
Baron	O
goes	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wilday	O
and	O
bought	O
of	O
him	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
200	O
l.	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
600	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
and	O
Notes	O
.	O
That	O
besides	O
this	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
Note	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Note	O
in	O
Question	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
payable	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Williamson	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
originally	O
only	O
a	O
20	O
l.	O
Note	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Messieurs	O
Mallory	O
,	O
and	O
tendered	O
to	O
them	O
as	O
a	O
Note	O
of	O
85	O
l.	O
in	O
Payment	O
for	O
about	O
12	O
Pounds	O
worth	O
of	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
exchange	O
of	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
Baron	O
receiv	O
'd	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Mallory	O
,	O
a	O
Bank	O
Note	O
of	O
20	O
l.	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
85	O
l.	O
which	O
20	O
l.	O
Note	O
was	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
altered	O
to	O
a	O
Note	O
of	O
100	O
l.	O
and	O
negotiated	O
as	O
such	O
to	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
,	O
in	O
buying	O
a	O
Service	O
of	O
Plate	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
demanded	O
a	O
party	O
Jury	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
granted	O
him	O
.	O
Juratores	O
diversarum	O
Linguarum	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Chandler	I-pers
,	O
Noah	B-pers
Moyer	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Forster	I-pers
,	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Vanderhoven	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
,	O
Stephen	B-pers
Saroon	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Shad	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Sennysear	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Long	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Belford	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Delaport	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Allyingham	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Note	O
of	O
85	O
l.	O
was	O
originally	O
a	O
Note	O
of	O
20	O
l.	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
made	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Mr.	O
William	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Mallory	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Baron	O
de	O
Loden	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
the	O
15th	O
or	O
16th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
bought	O
about	O
12	O
Pounds	O
worth	O
of	O
Lace	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
in	O
Exchange	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Money	O
and	O
a	O
Bank	O
Note	O
of	O
20	O
l.	O
The	O
Baron	O
de	O
Loden	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
gave	O
this	O
Note	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
receiv	O
'd	O
of	O
Messieur	O
Mallory	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
desired	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
this	O
Evidences	O
Lodging	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
,	O
they	O
being	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
in	O
the	O
Lodgings	O
of	O
the	O
Countess	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
up	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
by	O
himself	O
alone	O
for	O
some	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
the	O
Sum	O
Twenty	O
was	O
quite	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Note	O
,	O
the	O
Place	O
being	O
blank	O
,	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
drew	O
the	O
Note	O
through	O
a	O
Plate	O
of	O
Gum-water	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
having	O
dried	O
it	O
between	O
Papers	O
,	O
smooth	O
'd	O
it	O
over	O
between	O
Papers	O
with	O
a	O
Box	O
Iron	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
wrote	O
in	O
the	O
Vacancy	O
(	O
where	O
Twenty	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
)	O
One	O
Hundred	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
wrote	O
at	O
the	O
Bottom	O
of	O
the	O
Note	O
100	O
l.	O
instead	O
of	O
20	O
l.	O
and	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
thus	O
altered	O
the	O
Note	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Service	O
of	O
Plate	O
with	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
it	O
and	O
bought	O
Plate	O
to	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
40	O
l.	O
and	O
upwards	O
and	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Interpreter	O
,	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Schmidt	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
he	O
being	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
whether	O
the	O
Interpreter	O
delivered	O
the	O
Plate	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
He	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
could	O
write	O
20	O
sorts	O
of	O
Hands	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
but	O
3	O
or	O
400	O
l.	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
50000	O
l.	O
Eleanora	O
Sophia	O
,	O
the	O
Countess	O
of	O
Bostram	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Note	O
first	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
20	O
l.	O
Note	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
altered	O
in	O
the	O
Manner	O
as	O
had	O
before	O
been	O
depos	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Baron	O
,	O
not	O
varying	O
in	O
the	O
least	O
Circumstance	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Note	O
afterwards	O
blank	O
'd	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Sum	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
with	O
her	O
Eyes	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
him	O
write	O
the	O
Words	O
,	O
On	O
Hundred	O
Pounds	O
;	O
and	O
besides	O
the	O
Oath	O
taken	O
in	O
Court	O
in	O
Form	O
,	O
added	O
this	O
by	O
way	O
of	O
Confirmation	O
,	O
before	O
God	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
produced	O
a	O
Letter	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
as	O
written	O
to	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Baron	O
,	O
the	O
Purpose	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
,	O
to	O
contradict	O
his	O
having	O
charg	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
altering	O
and	O
giving	O
him	O
the	O
Note	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
charge	O
it	O
upon	O
one	O
Collier	O
.	O
The	O
Baron	O
own	O
'd	O
his	O
having	O
given	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
that	O
Letter	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
what	O
good	O
would	O
it	O
do	O
him	O
to	O
hang	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
charg	O
'd	O
it	O
on	O
a	O
Person	O
that	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
found	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
off	O
himself	O
well	O
enough	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
himself	O
did	O
dictate	O
to	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
should	O
write	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
write	O
what	O
he	O
dictated	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
upon	O
his	O
Persuasions	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Frazier	O
depos	O
'd	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
send	O
a	O
Letter	O
to	O
his	O
Correspondent	O
at	O
Amsterdam	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
send	O
him	O
Word	O
whether	O
Notes	O
of	O
the	O
Bank	O
of	O
England	O
for	O
large	O
Sums	O
were	O
current	O
there	O
.	O
Which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
,	O
and	O
pretended	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
Breslau	O
in	O
Silesia	O
,	O
to	O
England	O
,	O
to	O
Negotiate	O
an	O
Affair	O
for	O
the	O
Duke	O
de	O
Alvarez	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
the	O
last	O
of	O
the	O
Family	O
of	O
the	O
Duke	O
de	O
Alva	O
,	O
(	O
so	O
famous	O
for	O
his	O
Cruelty	O
in	O
the	O
Netherlands	O
)	O
in	O
Relation	O
to	O
a	O
large	O
Sum	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Quantity	O
of	O
about	O
a	O
Million	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
owning	O
to	O
him	O
from	O
the	O
Government	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
Executors	O
of	O
the	O
Lord	O
Godolphin	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
some	O
Evidences	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Myer	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Frazier	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
talked	O
to	O
them	O
of	O
such	O
an	O
Affair	O
,	O
and	O
show	O
'd	O
them	O
some	O
Writings	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
pretended	O
were	O
Powers	O
to	O
transact	O
such	O
an	O
Affair	O
;	O
and	O
also	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
there	O
Assistance	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
understand	O
,	O
not	O
had	O
any	O
Opinion	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
being	O
Real	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
excus	O
'd	O
in	O
concerning	O
themselves	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Matter	O
of	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
altering	O
the	O
Bank	O
Note	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Crosby	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Katherine	I-place
's	I-place
Coleman	I-place
Street	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Absalom	B-pers
Norton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Coat	O
was	O
stolen	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
Window	O
.	O
Mary	O
Crosbey	O
had	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
which	O
confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Coustantine	B-pers
Mac-yennis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Frances	B-pers
the	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Richard	I-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
Second	O
Time	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
Stabbing	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Third	O
Time	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquest	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Brumpton	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
living	O
in	O
Essex-Court	O
,	O
was	O
up	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
making	O
a	O
Fire	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
dragging	O
the	O
Deceased	O
along	O
the	O
Passage	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
dragg	O
'd	O
her	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
several	O
Pushes	O
at	O
her	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
dragging	O
her	O
along	O
the	O
Entry	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
Mouth	O
was	O
bloody	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Hand	O
bloody	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
flung	O
her	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Stones	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
strick	O
'd	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
but	O
her	O
Voice	O
was	O
very	O
low	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Witch	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
burn	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
past	O
Six	O
a-Clock	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Morning	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
walking	O
in	O
the	O
Temple	O
,	O
heard	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
into	O
Essex-Court	B-place
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
flourishing	O
his	O
Sword	O
over	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
stick	O
her	O
again	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
Are	O
not	O
you	O
a	O
base	O
Man	O
to	O
abuse	O
a	O
Woman	O
so	O
?	O
that	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
Dog	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
stick	O
you	O
too	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
then	O
on	O
her	O
Hands	O
and	O
Knees	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
stuck	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
some	O
Tub	O
Folks	O
coming	O
up	O
,	O
they	O
surrounded	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
desired	O
them	O
not	O
to	O
use	O
him	O
ill	O
,	O
surrendring	O
himself	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Husband	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
Wife	O
had	O
been	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Laundress	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
to	O
do	O
his	O
Business	O
in	O
the	O
Chambers	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
threatened	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
under	O
some	O
fear	O
of	O
going	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
thereupon	O
he	O
bid	O
her	O
not	O
go	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
always	O
before	O
a	O
civil	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
believ	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
or	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
a	O
Masquerade	O
,	O
or	O
something	O
that	O
had	O
disordered	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
she	O
did	O
venture	O
to	O
go	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ordered	O
her	O
to	O
come	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Fire	O
;	O
she	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
afterwards	O
he	O
had	O
Word	O
brought	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
murthered	O
her	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Offley	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
Thursday	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
bid	O
her	O
come	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
a	O
Fire	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
appeared	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
very	O
sensible	O
and	O
civil	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bouch	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Disturbance	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
secured	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
got	O
to	O
Devereaux	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
no	O
farther	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
catch	O
Cold	O
for	O
Want	O
of	O
his	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
a	O
Witch	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Murder	O
committed	O
in	O
the	O
Tower	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
discover	O
it	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
had	O
be	O
witch	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
thought	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
he	O
smelling	O
very	O
strong	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Mind	O
of	O
what	O
a	O
Crime	O
he	O
had	O
committed	O
,	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
must	O
die	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
were	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
he	O
answered	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
Care	O
of	O
his	O
Chambers	O
,	O
because	O
there	O
were	O
Things	O
of	O
Consequence	O
there	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Glynn	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
a	O
Person	O
came	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
not	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Husband	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
Man	O
stabbing	O
your	O
Wife	O
in	O
the	O
Temple	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ran	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
on	O
her	O
Hands	O
and	O
Knees	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
not	O
ashamed	O
?	O
And	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
bewitch	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
,	O
