TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Jail-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
;	O
On	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
,	O
Monday	O
,	O
and	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
27th	O
,	O
28th	O
,	O
30th	O
,	O
and	O
31st	O
Days	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Twelfth	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
GEORGE	B-pers
MERTTINS	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
Sergeant	O
at	O
Law	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
JURORS	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
The	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Jarman	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hargrave	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Elliot	I-pers
,	O
Ezekiel	B-pers
Plumfield	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Winn	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Edwin	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Read	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Camps	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Jackman	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Maurice	B-pers
Boheme	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Forber	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Harle	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wedgborough	I-pers
,	O
Philip	B-pers
Holden	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Stanly	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harrington	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Forber	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
follows	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
alias	I-pers
Allen	I-pers
Marsden	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Aldgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Holloway	I-pers
,	O
six	O
Yards	O
of	O
Muslin	O
,	O
value	O
32	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Ponds	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
Shop	O
to	O
cheapen	O
Muslin	O
.	O
I	O
shew	O
'd	O
her	O
several	O
Pieces	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
very	O
difficult	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
put	O
a	O
Piece	O
under	O
her	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
presently	O
follow	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
thus	O
defended	O
herself	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Holloway	O
's	O
Shop	O
to	O
buy	O
'ome	O
Muslin-Wm	O
.	O
Ponds	O
perceiving	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
innocent	O
Country	O
Girl	O
,	O
he	O
chuck	O
'd	O
me	O
under	O
the	O
Chin	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
pretty	O
Creature	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
Yorkshire	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
yes	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
back	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
under	O
my	O
Coats	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
Muslin	O
to	O
have	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
because	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
this	O
Robbery	O
.	O
Guilty	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Susan	B-pers
Brockway	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
three	O
Broad	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
from	O
Joseph	B-pers
Richmond	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Richmond	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
:	O
About	O
Nine	O
o'Clock	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
pickt	O
me	O
up	O
upon	O
London-Bridge	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Cross-Key	B-place
Tavern	I-place
upon	I-place
Fish-street-Hill	I-place
,	O
and	O
there	O
we	O
staid	O
about	O
an	O
Hour	O
.	O
I	O
agreed	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
a	O
Crown	O
apiece	O
,	O
to	O
-	O
to	O
-	O
,	O
not	O
to	O
do	O
them	O
over	O
,	O
but	O
for	O
them	O
to	O
strip	O
naked	O
,	O
and	O
show	O
me	O
some	O
Tricks	O
.	O
And	O
to	O
satisfy	O
them	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
Money	O
enough	O
to	O
be	O
as	O
good	O
as	O
my	O
Word	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
three	O
Broad	O
Pieces	O
and	O
three	O
Shillings	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Brockway	O
said	O
,	O
as	O
how	O
she	O
supposed	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
right	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
she	O
took	O
a	O
Piece	O
to	O
look	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
whereas	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
good	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
by	O
and	O
by	O
she	O
snatches	O
all	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
into	O
her	O
Bosom	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
shall	O
never	O
see	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
'll	O
keep	O
it	O
,	O
to	O
learn	O
you	O
more	O
Wit	O
;	O
,	O
that	O
another	O
time	O
you	O
may	O
know	O
an	O
honest	O
Woman	O
a	O
Whore	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
Gardner	O
ran	O
round	O
the	O
Table	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Design	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
supposed	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Money	O
from	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
kept	O
my	O
Eye	O
upon	O
them	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
rang	O
the	O
Bell	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
Drawer	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
.	O
The	O
Drawer	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
This	O
Man	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
coming	O
to	O
our	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
shew	O
'd	O
them	O
into	O
a	O
Ground	O
Room	O
,	O
opposite	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
;	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
three	O
Pints	O
of	O
Mountain	O
:	O
After	O
which	O
,	O
upon	O
hearing	O
the	O
Bell	O
,	O
I	O
stept	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
Brockway	O
presently	O
threw	O
down	O
three	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
There	O
is	O
your	O
Money	O
,	O
Drawer	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Man	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
The	O
Maid	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
undress	O
'd	O
the	O
two	O
Women	O
,	O
and	O
search	O
'd	O
them	O
in	O
every	O
Part	O
,	O
but	O
-	O
but	O
found	O
no	O
Money	O
about	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
then	O
made	O
their	O
Defence	O
:	O
This	O
Man	O
took	O
us	O
to	O
the	O
Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
us	O
a	O
Crown	O
apiece	O
to	O
strip	O
ourselves	O
naked	O
,	O
and	O
stew	O
him	O
Postures	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
Mary	O
Gardner	O
Money	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
Penny-worth	O
of	O
Rods	O
,	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
whip	O
us	O
a-cross	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
us	O
good	O
Girls	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
for	O
us	O
to	O
whip	O
him	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Boy	O
:	O
But	O
we	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
neither	O
a	O
proper	O
Time	O
nor	O
Place	O
for	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
might	O
over-look	O
us	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
we	O
were	O
in	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
the	O
Curtains	O
were	O
drawn	O
.	O
He	O
bid	O
us	O
look	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
for	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
worse	O
for	O
us	O
,	O
if	O
we	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
as	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
us	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
called	O
the	O
Drawer	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
got	O
his	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Harwood	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Church	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
34	O
Yards	O
of	O
Crape	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hanly	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
July	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Holloway	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Breadstreet	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Cheeses	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Norris	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Dowdell	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Two	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Russell	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Holborn	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
val	O
4	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
Silver	O
Salts	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
s.	O
two	O
Tea-Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Head-Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Farnell	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Dwelling-House	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Farnell	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
;	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
two	O
Weeks	O
my	O
Servant	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
(	O
when	O
my	O
Wife	O
was	O
at	O
Market	O
)	O
under	O
Pretence	O
of	O
fetching	O
some	O
Scowering	O
Oil	O
.	O
My	O
Wife	O
coming	O
home	O
,	O
presently	O
mist	O
the	O
Tankard	O
;	O
and	O
wondring	O
the	O
Maid	O
carry	O
'd	O
so	O
long	O
,	O
she	O
sent	O
one	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
.	O
This	O
increased	O
our	O
Suspicion	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
farther	O
Search	O
,	O
we	O
mist	O
the	O
other	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
We	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
her	O
till	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
this	O
Month	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
at	O
the	O
Angel	O
in	O
Hammer	O
Smith	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
Wife	O
's	O
Stays	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
whole	O
Charge	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
disposed	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
we	O
found	O
according	O
to	O
her	O
Direction	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Goldsmith	O
to	O
whom	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
sold	O
the	O
Tankard	O
for	O
45	O
s.	O
deny	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
ever	O
had	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bagnal	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
July	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Val	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Henly	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
36	O
s.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bawler	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Churchill	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Brass	O
Cocks	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Clark	B-pers
and	O
Young	B-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Val	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Madderin	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
Aprons	O
.	O
two	O
Smocks	O
,	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Head-Cloaths	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Ruffles	O
and	O
a	O
Common-Prayer-Book	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Owen	B-pers
Sweny	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
Guilty	O
Val	O
.	O
10d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
six	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
July	O
.	O
Richard	O
Green	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
Between	O
One	O
and	O
Two	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Fleetstreet	B-place
,	O
near	O
Fetter-Lane	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
then	O
thirteen	O
Guineas	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
;	O
she	O
stopt	O
me	O
,	O
whipt	O
her	O
Hand	O
into	O
my	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
mist	O
six	O
Guineas	O
:	O
I	O
called	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
.	O
-	O
She	O
at	O
first	O
deny	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
body	O
searched	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
afterwards	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
My	O
Watchman	O
brought	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
,	O
before	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
both	O
pickt	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
but	O
fix	O
'd	O
the	O
Charge	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
-	O
(	O
She	O
has	O
been	O
brought	O
to	O
our	O
Watch	O
house	O
for	O
a	O
Street-Walker	O
before	O
now	O
.	O
)	O
-	O
She	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Matter	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
searching	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
it	O
would	O
signify	O
nothing	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
question	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
convey	O
'd	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
That	O
Morning	O
we	O
carry	O
'd	O
her	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Vine	O
in	O
Bell-Court	O
in	O
Foster-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Guineas	O
in	O
her	O
Mouth	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Watch	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
thus	O
made	O
her	O
Defence	O
:	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
Flower-de-Luce	O
Court	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
a	O
jostling	O
together	O
against	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
the	O
Man	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
Bitch	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
pickt	O
my	O
Pocket	O
;	O
and	O
seeing	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
Confederate	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
let	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
go	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Moulson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cheslin	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Peirce	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Woollen	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Sieve	O
of	O
Currants	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Holms	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
July	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Street	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
,	O
Ravishing	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
her	O
Will	O
,	O
carnally	O
knowing	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Harvison	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
aged	O
17	O
Years	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
Rebecca	O
Harvison	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
I	O
and	O
this	O
Child	O
of	O
mine	O
being	O
at	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
Church-Lane	O
,	O
near	O
S.	O
Giles	O
's	O
Church	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodges	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
about	O
Seven	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Child	O
in	O
his	O
Arms	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
a	O
kissing	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Child	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
see	O
,	O
is	O
a	O
Dwarf	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Idiot	O
;	O
and	O
what	O
makes	O
the	O
Misfortune	O
the	O
greater	O
,	O
she	O
wants	O
the	O
Use	O
of	O
her	O
Limbs	O
so	O
much	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
is	O
forced	O
to	O
be	O
carried	O
like	O
an	O
Infant	O
.	O
We	O
afterwards	O
went	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
left	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
a	O
little	O
farther	O
:	O
And	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
we	O
heard	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Child	O
out	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
soon	O
brought	O
her	O
home	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
undress	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
put	O
her	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
she	O
was	O
ruin	O
'd	O
,	O
bloody	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
frightful	O
Condition	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
by	O
all	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
ravish	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
he	O
that	O
did	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
sorry	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
and	O
beg	O
'd	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
send	O
him	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
would	O
ruin	O
him	O
.	O
In	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Weeks	O
after	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
had	O
the	O
Foul	O
Disease	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Saxby	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
Mrs.	O
Harvison	O
and	O
her	O
Child	O
Betty	O
being	O
at	O
Supper	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
who	O
is	O
my	O
Lodger	O
)	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
;	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
we	O
all	O
went	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
Dudley	O
's	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Husband	O
carried	O
the	O
Child	O
.	O
We	O
staid	O
there	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
my	O
Husband	O
and	O
I	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Harvison	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Betty	O
.	O
We	O
return	O
'd	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
told	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Child	O
away	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
by	O
the	O
Wall	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Church-yard	I-place
.	O
The	O
Child	O
cried	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
Man	O
had	O
hurt	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
leaning	O
his	O
Head	O
over	O
her	O
Neck	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hurt	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
Dear	O
,	O
did	O
I	O
?	O
A	O
Midwife	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
upon	O
Searching	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
that	O
a	O
Man	O
had	O
entred	O
her	O
Body	O
about	O
three	O
Inches	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Anne	B-pers
Hains	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
The	O
Night	O
as	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
our	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
Dudley	O
Court	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
in	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
indeed	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
strange	O
Sight	O
.	O
They	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
need	O
not	O
be	O
afraid	O
to	O
look	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
her	O
Limbs	O
were	O
as	O
straight	O
as	O
mine	O
;	O
and	O
with	O
that	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
'em	O
took	O
up	O
her	O
Coats	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
see	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
nothing	O
that	O
ail	O
'd	O
her	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
before	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
carried	O
her	O
out	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
called	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
brought	O
her	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
great	O
Alteration	O
:	O
Some	O
Man	O
had	O
certainly	O
abused	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Watchman	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
to	O
apprehend	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
Bed	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
Plaisterer	O
by	O
Trade	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Apron	O
that	O
he	O
usually	O
works	O
in	O
,	O
was	O
then	O
lying	O
upon	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
bloody	O
.	O
Sam	O
.	O
(	O
says	O
I	O
)	O
you	O
must	O
get	O
up	O
and	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
perceived	O
his	O
Shirt	O
was	O
bloody	O
too	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Harvison	O
,	O
he	O
laid	O
his	O
Hand	O
upon	O
her	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
ruined	O
your	O
Child	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
Brignal	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
soon	O
after	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
injured	O
.	O
His	O
Apron	O
and	O
Shirt	O
was	O
bloody	O
.	O
He	O
confest	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
beg	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
What	O
a	O
Stomach	O
you	O
must	O
have	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
to	O
meddle	O
with	O
that	O
Idiot	O
?	O
Why	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
kiss	O
'd	O
twenty	O
Women	O
,	O
and	O
twenty	O
times	O
twenty	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
such	O
a	O
Creature	O
.	O
Says	O
he	O
,	O
The	O
Devil	O
bewitcht	O
me	O
.	O
Frances	B-pers
Lepine	I-pers
,	O
Midwife	O
,	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
I	O
search	O
'd	O
the	O
Child	O
two	O
Days	O
after	O
the	O
Injury	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
a	O
Man	O
had	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
Signs	O
of	O
the	O
French	O
Disease	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
the	O
Parts	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
torn	O
or	O
swell	O
'd	O
.	O
Christiana	B-pers
Bolton	I-pers
,	O
another	O
Midwife	O
,	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
I	O
examined	O
the	O
Child	O
in	O
two	O
Weeks	O
and	O
two	O
Days	O
after	O
the	O
Hurt	O
was	O
received	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
an	O
Attempt	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Penetration	O
;	O
nor	O
was	O
there	O
then	O
any	O
Symptom	O
of	O
a	O
Foul	O
Distemper	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
one	O
Finger	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
perceive	O
that	O
the	O
Parts	O
were	O
much	O
extended	O
.	O
Two	O
Days	O
after	O
I	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Passage	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
much	O
wider	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
Running	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
-	O
Cox	O
,	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
in	O
behalf	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
Being	O
inform	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
had	O
received	O
the	O
Foul	O
Disease	O
,	O
I	O
search	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
very	O
strictly	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
Day	O
after	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
not	O
the	O
least	O
Sign	O
of	O
his	O
having	O
had	O
such	O
a	O
Distemper	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Now	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
a	O
Man	O
could	O
hardly	O
be	O
so	O
perfectly	O
cured	O
in	O
so	O
short	O
a	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
own	O
there	O
may	O
be	O
a	O
Possibility	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
slight	O
Infection	O
;	O
or	O
if	O
the	O
Patient	O
had	O
been	O
under	O
Cure	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
almost	O
well	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
that	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Whole	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
immediately	O
ordered	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
accordingly	O
done	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
Not	O
guilty	O
,	O
and	O
will	O
be	O
try	O
'd	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pocket	O
with	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Headcloaths	O
,	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Burkitt	I-pers
,	O
June	O
16	O
.	O
Guilty	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Munford	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Snuff	O
Box	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Trewicks	I-pers
,	O
Aug	O
5	O
.	O
John	O
Trewicks	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
Alexander	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
(	O
with	O
whom	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
small	O
Acquaintance	O
)	O
brought	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
Visiting	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
one	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
.	O
While	O
she	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
we	O
mist	O
a	O
Snuff	O
Box	O
off	O
the	O
Tea-Table	O
;	O
but	O
thought	O
it	O
improper	O
to	O
take	O
any	O
Notice	O
of	O
it	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Company	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
Wife	O
look	O
'd	O
for	O
it	O
diligently	O
,	O
but	O
all	O
to	O
no	O
purpose	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
again	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
lost	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Stocking	O
off	O
the	O
Back	O
of	O
a	O
Chair	O
.	O
This	O
gave	O
us	O
a	O
strong	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
we	O
invited	O
her	O
to	O
Supper	O
another	O
time	O
,	O
on	O
purpose	O
to	O
detect	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
before-hand	O
had	O
hung	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Turn-over	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Back	O
of	O
a	O
Chair	O
.	O
The	O
Apron	O
was	O
presently	O
mist	O
;	O
we	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
it	O
:	O
She	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
stiffly	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
were	O
resolved	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hill	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
her	O
to	O
my	O
Wife	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
young	O
Women	O
;	O
but	O
first	O
we	O
desired	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
every	O
one	O
else	O
to	O
look	O
narrowly	O
all	O
over	O
the	O
Parlour	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
satisfied	O
that	O
the	O
Apron	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
;	O
which	O
every	O
one	O
did	O
.	O
The	O
Woman	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stript	O
herself	O
to	O
her	O
Under-Petticoat	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Modesty	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
any	O
farther	O
to	O
expose	O
her	O
Nakedness	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
not	O
being	O
satisfy	O
'd	O
with	O
such	O
a	O
Pretence	O
,	O
she	O
lifted	O
up	O
her	O
Petticoat	O
and	O
Smock	O
together	O
.	O
They	O
still	O
insisted	O
upon	O
having	O
the	O
Petticoat	O
quite	O
off	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
unty	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
stooping	O
down	O
they	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
throw	O
something	O
white	O
under	O
the	O
Table	O
:	O
They	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Apron	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
Spight	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Trewicks	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
'd	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
'd	O
either	O
give	O
him	O
30	O
s.	O
or	O
stand	O
stark	O
naked	O
for	O
a	O
Week	O
together	O
at	O
the	O
seven	O
Dials	O
.	O
She	O
called	O
up	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
speak	O
in	O
her	O
Behalf	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
produced	O
others	O
against	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Sum	O
of	O
their	O
Evidence	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
of	O
very	O
good	O
Repute	O
,	O
was	O
industrious	O
and	O
careful	O
in	O
the	O
Maintenance	O
of	O
her	O
Family	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
often	O
been	O
entrusted	O
with	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
Value	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
preserv	O
'd	O
her	O
Credit	O
without	O
Blemish	O
:	O
But	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
greatest	O
Lyars	O
in	O
Life	O
,	O
an	O
idle	O
,	O
lazy	O
,	O
cheating	O
,	O
pilfering	O
,	O
drunken	O
Puss	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
three	O
Husbands	O
;	O
and	O
had	O
in	O
general	O
the	O
worst	O
Character	O
that	O
could	O
be	O
given	O
to	O
a	O
Woman	O
.	O
Guilty	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Riggals	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Euphania	B-pers
Tristam	I-pers
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Pimble	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Cambrick	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Scarf	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Yarrow	I-pers
,	O
July	O
27	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilks	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Peasly	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Picard	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
thence	O
three	O
Smocks	O
,	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
4	O
Yards	O
of	O
Linnen	O
etc	O
.	O
Aug	O
21	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
Transp	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cloth	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
l.	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
Tenters	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Lockwood	B-pers
and	O
Philips	B-pers
Esq	O
s	O
;	O
Aug.	O
9	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Tipping	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Headcloaths	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Minshall	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hodges	I-pers
,	O
June	O
20	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
20	O
s.	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fidoe	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Southernwood	I-pers
,	O
April	O
1	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
3d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
,	O
June	O
14	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
and	O
second	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Turn	O
over	O
,	O
two	O
Mobs	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Necklace	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Leach	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Cumbridge	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
Joseph	B-pers
Needham	I-pers
two	O
Suits	O
of	O
Headcloaths	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
14	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Needham	I-pers
deposed	O
to	O
this	O
effect	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Holland	O
gave	O
me	O
two	O
Suits	O
of	O
Headcloaths	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
my	O
Wife	O
to	O
clear-starch	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
thro	O
'	O
Rag-Fair	O
,	O
this	O
Gentlewoman	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
pick	O
'd	O
me	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
drink	O
together	O
at	O
the	O
Rose	B-place
and	I-place
Crown	I-place
Alehouse	I-place
.	O
We	O
staid	O
there	O
about	O
two	O
Hours	O
:	O
She	O
went	O
away	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
after	O
I	O
mist	O
the	O
Goods	O
is	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
woundy	O
vex	O
'd	O
to	O
think	O
what	O
Account	O
I	O
should	O
give	O
to	O
my	O
Wife	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
But	O
howsoever	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
this	O
House	O
again	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
Enquiry	O
after	O
this	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
thus	O
made	O
her	O
Defence	O
:	O
I	O
met	O
this	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
'd	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
'd	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Twopenny	O
.	O
Why	O
then	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
let	O
's	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
the	O
Way	O
to	O
the	O
Rose	O
and	O
Crown	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
into	O
a	O
Room	O
by	O
ourselves	O
,	O
and	O
both	O
got	O
drunk	O
together	O
.	O
He	O
bid	O
me	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
and	O
so	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
much	O
care	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
.	O
Why	O
,	O
indeed	O
,	O
my	O
Dear	O
,	O
(	O
says	O
he	O
)	O
I	O
ha	O
n't	O
got	O
so	O
much	O
Silver	O
about	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
'll	O
change	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
are	O
afraid	O
of	O
not	O
having	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
hold	O
these	O
Headcloaths	O
the	O
while	O
for	O
your	O
own	O
Security	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
me	O
:	O
But	O
finding	O
myself	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Saying	O
is	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
for	O
staying	O
any	O
longer	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
without	O
my	O
Half-Crown	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Thetford	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bag	O
and	O
70	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davy	I-pers
,	O
July	O
1	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
and	O
Isaac	B-pers
Astlin	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Twedall	I-pers
,	O
July	O
28	O
.	O
Guilty	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Manoroy	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Tea-Kettle	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
Saucepan	O
4	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
Brass	O
Pot	O
16	O
s.	O
May	O
20	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Sikes	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
11	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cotton	O
and	O
Linnen	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ewin	I-pers
,	O
April	O
16	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Temple	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Walter	B-pers
Angus	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
15	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Daniel	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Saucepan	O
,	O
two	O
Plates	O
,	O
a	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
9	O
Pair	O
of	O
Crystal	O
buttons	O
,	O
a	O
Necklace	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Wather	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Buck-Skins	O
and	O
a	O
Calf's-Skin	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Rudshaw	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transp	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Thomson	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
James	I-pers
of	O
Chiswick	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Drugget	O
Suit	O
with	O
Silver	O
Buttons	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
85	O
s.	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mawson	I-pers
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
of	O
Thistleworth	B-place
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coat	O
and	O
Wastecoat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Tibbets	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Cloaths	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
Indictment	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
second	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
Mantle	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ryman	I-pers
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Frances	B-pers
Field	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Field	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Purse	O
and	O
23	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Edward	O
Stone	O
,	O
July	O
16	O
.	O
Edward	O
Stone	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
About	O
11	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
I	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
took	O
Coach	O
near	O
the	O
Queen's-Head	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
then	O
32	O
l.	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
Bow	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
we	O
dined	O
.	O
From	O
thence	O
we	O
drove	O
back	O
to	O
London	O
.	O
Frances	O
Field	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
us	O
somewhere	O
about	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
;	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
we	O
drove	O
to	O
Long-Lane	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
stopt	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
leaving	O
them	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
stept	O
out	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Hat	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
Sight	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
mist	O
my	O
Gold	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
green	O
Purse	O
.	O
I	O
presently	O
taxed	O
them	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
,	O
For	O
God	O
's	O
Sake	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
make	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
for	O
Frances	O
Field	O
has	O
got	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
's	O
gone	O
to	O
Islington	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
her	O
.	O
Ann	O
Smith	O
in	O
particular	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
while	O
we	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
together	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
Frances	O
Field	O
put	O
her	O
Hand	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
into	O
my	O
Fob	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
pull	O
out	O
a	O
green	O
Purse	O
with	O
Gold	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Squire	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
Ann	O
Smith	O
take	O
a	O
green	O
Purse	O
with	O
Money	O
in	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Pocket	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
all	O
being	O
acquainted	O
together	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
nothing	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
thought	O
she	O
was	O
only	O
in	O
jest	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
kept	O
Company	O
with	O
Elizabeth	O
Field	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
Year	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
'd	O
invited	O
them	O
all	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
pretended	O
he	O
'd	O
marry	O
her	O
.	O
They	O
dined	O
at	O
Bow	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
and	O
Tom	O
.	O
Squire	O
got	O
drunk	O
and	O
lay	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
to	O
sleep	O
.	O
As	O
we	O
came	O
back	O
he	O
asked	O
Betty	O
Field	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
an	O
Inn	O
,	O
and	O
lie	O
with	O
Night	O
;	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
Sister	O
Fanny	O
a	O
Shilling	O
But	O
Betty	O
refusing	O
to	O
do	O
as	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
her	O
D	O
-	O
him	O
we	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
'd	O
swear	O
away	O
,	O
if	O
we	O
would	O
not	O
consent	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
Islington	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
drunk	O
the	O
was	O
full	O
of	O
Claret	O
,	O
and	O
something	O
else	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
That	O
they	O
were	O
reputed	O
to	O
be	O
as	O
honst	O
Girls	O
as	O
ever	O
liv	O
'd	O
-	O
as	O
to	O
their	O
Fingers	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
them	O
as	O
to	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
De	I-pers
le	I-pers
Gall	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Broadhurst	I-pers
by	O
giving	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
near	O
the	O
Right	O
Pap	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Length	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
Depth	O
of	O
eight	O
Inches	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
Eleven	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languish	O
'd	O
till	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
Having	O
a	O
Writ	O
for	O
20	O
l.	O
at	O
the	O
Suit	O
of	O
Susanna	B-pers
Crosier	I-pers
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
dwelt	O
at	O
at	O
a	O
Distiller	O
's	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Mackett	B-place
's	I-place
Court	I-place
in	I-place
Piccadilly	I-place
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
being	O
my	O
Assistant	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Oxford	O
Arms	O
Alehouse	O
opposite	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
execute	O
this	O
Writ	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
there	O
long	O
,	O
before	O
we	O
perceived	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
looking	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Window	O
up	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Street-Door	O
being	O
open	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
the	O
Deceased	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
follow	O
'd	O
myself	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Stairs-Head	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
pale	O
and	O
bloody	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
put	O
him	O
into	O
.	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Time	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
Gerrard-street	O
,	O
he	O
died	O
,	O
I	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
receiv	O
'd	O
two	O
Wounds	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
Left	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
deeper	O
in	O
the	O
Right	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
how	O
he	O
could	O
be	O
so	O
barbarous	O
?	O
And	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
kill	O
'd	O
more	O
of	O
us	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Warrant	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Suit	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Clements	O
for	O
30	O
l.	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
execute	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
Mr.	O
Davis	O
,	O
who	O
I	O
found	O
waited	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Man	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
George	O
Alehouse	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Mackert's-Court	O
,	O
opposite	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodged	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Room	O
there	O
that	O
commanded	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Chamber	O
,	O
I	O
watched	O
the	O
Room	O
of	O
the	O
Oxford	O
Arms	O
,	O
where	O
Davis	O
and	O
his	O
Man	O
were	O
waiting	O
;	O
not	O
doubting	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
they	O
saw	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
of	O
taking	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
see	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
come	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
intended	O
to	O
be	O
before-hand	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
But	O
however	O
,	O
Davis	O
's	O
Man	O
stept	O
in	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
aware	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
first	O
Suspicion	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
there	O
,	O
was	O
my	O
hearing	O
a	O
Pistol	O
go	O
off	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
stept	O
up	O
:	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Deceased	O
bloody	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
walking	O
about	O
in	O
his	O
Wastecoat	O
and	O
Slippers	O
;	O
and	O
perceiving	O
him	O
to	O
have	O
no	O
Weapons	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
I	O
presently	O
arrested	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
carrying	O
him	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
Mr.	O
Davis	O
,	O
who	O
assisted	O
me	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Coach	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
could	O
kill	O
the	O
Men	O
?	O
and	O
whether	O
his	O
Door	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
not	O
lock	O
'd	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Deceased	O
coming	O
in	O
without	O
knocking	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
Thief	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
serv	O
'd	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
manner	O
;	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
arrested	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
for	O
30	O
l.	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
thought	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
for	O
150	O
l.	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
as	O
much	O
before	O
,	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
this	O
had	O
never	O
happen	O
'd	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Moor	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
three	O
Wounds	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
only	O
one	O
that	O
he	O
believed	O
mortal	O
,	O
was	O
between	O
the	O
5th	O
and	O
6th	O
Rib	O
,	O
and	O
divided	O
the	O
Arteries	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
then	O
made	O
his	O
Defence	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Souter	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
Nurse	O
to	O
Capt	O
.	O
De	O
le	O
Gall	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
who	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
was	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Expectation	O
of	O
wanting	O
the	O
Midwife	O
's	O
Assistance	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
leaning	O
upon	O
the	O
Captain	O
's	O
Arm	O
to	O
support	O
herself	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
sweeping	O
under	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
Back	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Noise	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
it	O
was	O
forced	O
open	O
,	O
(	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
locked	O
it	O
but	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
before	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
turned	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
,	O
if	O
Capt	O
.	O
De	O
le	O
Gall	O
lived	O
there	O
?	O
The	O
Captain	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
what	O
he	O
wanted	O
?	O
The	O
Deceased	O
made	O
no	O
Answer	O
,	O
but	O
stood	O
learning	O
upon	O
his	O
Cane	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
about	O
the	O
Room	O
.	O
The	O
Captain	O
then	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Rogue	O
,	O
and	O
bade	O
him	O
be	O
gone	O
at	O
his	O
Peril	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
not	O
going	O
,	O
the	O
Captain	O
stept	O
back	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
ran	O
up	O
with	O
his	O
Cane	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
struck	O
the	O
Captain	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
D	O
-	O
ye	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
have	O
ye	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Deceased	O
closed	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
him	O
down	O
in	O
a	O
Corner	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
:	O
They	O
got	O
up	O
again	O
;	O
a	O
Pistol	O
lay	O
upon	O
the	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
;	O
both	O
of	O
them	O
strove	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Struggle	O
it	O
went	O
off	O
;	O
but	O
did	O
no	O
Harm	O
,	O
except	O
burning	O
the	O
deceased	O
's	O
Shirt	O
.	O
The	O
Captain	O
had	O
his	O
Sword	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
ran	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
collar	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
dragg	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
throw	O
him	O
down	O
Stairs	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
both	O
fell	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Stairs-Head	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
being	O
undermost	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Son	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
Our	O
Chamber-Door	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
the	O
Box	O
of	O
the	O
Lock	O
was	O
almost	O
forced	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Nails	O
fell	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
;	O
the	O
Deceased	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
Capt	O
.	O
De	O
le	O
Gall	O
:	O
My	O
Pappa	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
?	O
-	O
Get	O
you	O
gone	O
at	O
your	O
Peril	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
made	O
no	O
Answer	O
,	O
but	O
struck	O
my	O
Pappa	O
with	O
his	O
Cane	O
;	O
my	O
Pappa	O
retreated	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
Sword	O
off	O
the	O
Table	O
;	O
the	O
Deceased	O
ran	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
D	O
-	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
have	O
you	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
collar	O
'd	O
my	O
Pappa	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
him	O
down	O
;	O
and	O
seeing	O
a	O
Pistol	O
on	O
the	O
Drawers	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
dragg	O
'd	O
him	O
thither	O
,	O
and	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
my	O
Pappa	O
strove	O
to	O
hinder	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Struggle	O
it	O
went	O
off	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
hauled	O
my	O
Pappa	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
fell	O
down	O
together	O
.	O
Two	O
or	O
three	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
produced	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
an	O
Account	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Lock	O
on	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Bolt	O
in	O
the	O
Lock	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
Bolt	O
was	O
defective	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
usually	O
kept	O
lock	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Nails	O
of	O
the	O
Lock	O
were	O
forced	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Floor	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
those	O
Nails	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
were	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
It	O
appearing	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
no	O
Officer	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Authority	O
to	O
execute	O
the	O
Process	O
in	O
the	O
Absence	O
of	O
the	O
Officer	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
did	O
declare	O
or	O
tell	O
the	O
Purpose	O
of	O
his	O
coming	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
struck	O
and	O
abus	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sheet	O
and	O
four	O
Plates	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Green	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Hood	O
,	O
three	O
Aprons	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Bodice	O
,	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Baldwin	I-pers
;	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pinks	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Scales	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
,	O
April	O
3	O
.	O
Guilty	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cornish	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Shoreditch	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Tobacco-Box	O
,	O
and	O
12	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Sam	B-pers
.	I-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
,	O
July	O
3	O
.	O
Sam	O
.	O
Wilkinson	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
About	O
Ten	O
at	O
Night	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Shoreditch	B-place
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
help	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
Lodging	O
.	O
She	O
carry	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
her	O
Room	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Shilling	O
to	O
fetch	O
some	O
Drink	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
12	O
s.	O
then	O
left	O
in	O
my	O
Tobacco-Box	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
put	O
under	O
my	O
Pillow	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
out	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
persuading	O
her	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
Bed	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
again	O
about	O
Two	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
feeling	O
for	O
my	O
Box	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
.	O
She	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
own	O
d	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
gave	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
Soldier	O
to	O
stand	O
by	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
offer	O
'd	O
me	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
thus	O
made	O
her	O
Defence	O
:	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
help	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
Lodging	O
:	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
my	O
Landlady	O
's	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
having	O
no	O
Bed	O
to	O
spare	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
into	O
mine	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
Room	O
enough	O
for	O
him	O
and	O
me	O
too	O
:	O
Whereupon	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
and	O
sat	O
at	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
hopes	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
gone	O
.	O
And	O
so	O
finding	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
as	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
this	O
Fact	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Massy	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Chiswick	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Ivory	O
Snuff-Box	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
d.	O
three	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Isinglass	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
d.	O
20	O
Yards	O
of	O
Ribbon	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
d.	O
and	O
1090	O
Glass	O
Beads	O
waxed	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
28	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
,	O
July	O
22	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Cliff	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Van	I-pers
Tromp	I-pers
alias	I-pers
the	I-pers
Mad	I-pers
Sailor	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
Noble	O
Peregrine	B-pers
Duke	I-pers
of	I-pers
Leedes	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
thence	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Salt-Seller	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
d.	O
a	O
Cloak	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Hat	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Fredrick	B-pers
Neuf	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
Ten	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Best	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Duchess	O
of	O
Leedes	O
.	O
Between	O
Nine	O
and	O
Ten	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
as	O
her	O
Grace	O
was	O
at	O
Supper	O
in	O
the	O
Back-Parlour	O
,	O
(	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
in	O
Pall-mall	B-place
)	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
little	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
Fore-Parlour	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
the	O
Candle	O
burning	O
:	O
I	O
stept	O
in	O
and	O
saw	O
Cliff	O
standing	O
there	O
.	O
He	O
presently	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Sash-Window	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
Sash	O
was	O
then	O
thrown	O
up	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
shut	O
close	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
pursuing	O
him	O
,	O
this	O
Cloak	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Jarvis	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
I	O
struck	O
Cliff	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
running	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Pewter	O
Salt-Seller	O
fell	O
from	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
got	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
was	O
quickly	O
stopt	O
by	O
another	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
carry	O
'd	O
before	O
Justice	O
Ellis	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
made	O
a	O
Confession	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
)	O
that	O
himself	O
and	O
Price	O
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Sparks	I-pers
,	O
(	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
having	O
stole	O
a	O
Hat	O
and	O
a	O
Coat	O
out	O
of	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
together	O
to	O
the	O
Duchess	O
of	O
Leedes	O
's	O
.	O
They	O
look	O
'd	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Window	O
next	O
Pall-mall	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
a	O
Candle	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Person	O
there	O
,	O
Price	O
lifted	O
up	O
the	O
Sash	O
,	O
and	O
himself	O
(	O
James	B-pers
Cliff	I-pers
)	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
gave	O
out	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
to'em	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
the	O
Price	O
escaped	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
this	O
Confession	O
,	O
a	O
Search	O
was	O
made	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Days	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
Price	O
near	O
Southampton-street	O
about	O
Nine	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
He	O
offer	O
'd	O
me	O
all	O
the	O
Money	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
accessary	O
any	O
farther	O
than	O
in	O
opening	O
the	O
Window	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
none	O
but	O
Cliff	O
went	O
in	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Bealing	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
,	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
That	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
Price	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
Cliff	O
and	O
Sparks	O
at	O
the	O
Duchess	O
of	O
Leedes	O
's	O
Window	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
consulting	O
to	O
rob	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
advised	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
;	O
which	O
they	O
not	O
approving	O
left	O
them	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Fidoe	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Beadle	O
,	O
deposed	O
:	O
That	O
in	O
Bealing	O
's	O
House	O
he	O
heard	O
Price	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
himself	O
;	O
and	O
also	O
persuaded	O
them	O
against	O
it	O
.	O
Cliff	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Defence	O
;	O
and	O
Price	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
Cliff	O
and	O
Sparks	O
at	O
the	O
Duchess	O
's	O
Rails	O
,	O
and	O
only	O
spoke	O
to	O
them	O
as	O
he	O
past	O
by	O
;	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
about	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
and	O
Matth.ew	B-pers
Mollineux	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
12	O
lb	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Horseman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
July	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Paris	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Table-Cloth	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Burgess	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1	O
st	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Val	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Rany	I-pers
and	O
Roger	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
three	O
Napkins	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Nugent	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Woldridge	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Holborn	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Fell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
Twelve	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Elizabeth	O
Fell	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Fell	O
;	O
and	O
my	O
Lodging	O
is	O
in	O
her	O
Garret	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
about	O
Ten	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
made	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
my	O
Garret	O
fast	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
fell	O
asleep	O
.	O
About	O
Midnight	O
(	O
as	O
I	O
afterward	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
)	O
I	O
was	O
waked	O
by	O
the	O
creaking	O
of	O
my	O
Chest	O
,	O
which	O
stood	O
by	O
the	O
Bed-Side	O
.	O
-	O
Who	O
's	O
there	O
?	O
says	O
I	O
.	O
-	O
No	O
body	O
answer	O
'd	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
jumpt	O
out	O
of	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
.	O
Who	O
are	O
ye	O
?	O
says	O
I	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
a	O
Word	O
would	O
he	O
speak	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
beat	O
him	O
about	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
.	O
He	O
still	O
remain	O
'd	O
Silent	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
no	O
Resistance	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
wondring	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
when	O
,	O
all	O
on	O
a	O
sudden	O
,	O
he	O
cut	O
me	O
across	O
the	O
Face	O
with	O
this	O
Pocket	O
Knife	O
.	O
The	O
Stroke	O
I	O
believed	O
was	O
aim	O
'd	O
at	O
my	O
Throat	O
,	O
but	O
luckily	O
mist	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Blood	O
ran	O
into	O
my	O
Mouth	O
,	O
and	O
almost	O
strangled	O
me	O
.	O
However	O
,	O
I	O
held	O
him	O
fast	O
,	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
who	O
quickly	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Assistance	O
,	O
being	O
let	O
in	O
by	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Family	O
,	O
whom	O
the	O
Disturbance	O
had	O
by	O
this	O
alarm	O
'd	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Light	O
came	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
surprized	O
that	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
had	O
treated	O
me	O
thus	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
,	O
not	O
long	O
since	O
,	O
been	O
a	O
Fellow-Servant	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
this	O
very	O
House	O
;	O
which	O
makes	O
me	O
think	O
that	O
his	O
not	O
speaking	O
,	O
was	O
for	O
fear	O
his	O
Tongue	O
should	O
betray	O
him	O
.	O
His	O
Penknife	O
was	O
found	O
hard	O
by	O
my	O
Chest	O
;	O
which	O
,	O
I	O
fancy	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
feeling	O
for	O
when	O
he	O
made	O
no	O
Resistance	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
finding	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
other	O
(	O
that	O
he	O
cut	O
me	O
with	O
)	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Crouch	I-pers
,	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Directions	O
,	O
to	O
fetch	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
by	O
the	O
Common-Sewer	O
that	O
is	O
betwixt	O
our	O
Warehouse	O
(	O
as	O
we	O
call	O
it	O
)	O
and	O
Workhouse	O
;	O
and	O
by	O
that	O
Means	O
we	O
discover	O
'd	O
the	O
Way	O
by	O
which	O
he	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Fell	O
's	O
Business	O
is	O
boiling	O
of	O
Tripe	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
that	O
Place	O
called	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
we	O
put	O
Offal	O
and	O
odd	O
Things	O
of	O
little	O
Value	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
an	O
open	O
Place	O
over	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
this	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
a	O
Man	O
may	O
easily	O
get	O
in	O
.	O
There	O
had	O
been	O
wooden	O
Rails	O
nail	O
'd	O
across	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
sure	O
whether	O
they	O
were	O
broke	O
down	O
that	O
Night	O
as	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
enter	O
'd	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
time	O
before	O
.	O
This	O
,	O
however	O
,	O
I	O
take	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Place	O
of	O
his	O
Entrance	O
.	O
Then	O
going	O
a	O
cross	O
the	O
Common-Sewer	O
,	O
he	O
comes	O
to	O
the	O
Workhouse	O
,	O
which	O
has	O
two	O
Folding-Doors	O
;	O
and	O
whether	O
these	O
were	O
fasten	O
'd	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
certain	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
is	O
the	O
Kitchen-Door	O
;	O
and	O
this	O
has	O
a	O
Light	O
over	O
it	O
almost	O
like	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
Door	O
;	O
at	O
which	O
we	O
presume	O
he	O
enter	O
'd	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
greasy	O
Marks	O
of	O
his	O
Shooes	O
upon	O
the	O
Dresser	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Grease	O
is	O
another	O
Sign	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
he	O
must	O
go	O
up	O
Three	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
to	O
the	O
Garret	O
;	O
but	O
how	O
he	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
that	O
Door	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
thus	O
made	O
his	O
Defence	O
:	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
Brooks	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
lie	O
with	O
him	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
might	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
.	O
I	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
some	O
Friends	O
at	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
a	O
pretty	O
way	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
kept	O
me	O
till	O
Twelve	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
directly	O
from	O
them	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Fell	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
Brooks	O
himself	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
let	O
me	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
got	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Words	O
passing	O
betwixt	O
us	O
,	O
it	O
occasion	O
'd	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
.	O
All	O
this	O
was	O
positively	O
contradicted	O
by	O
Brooks	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
continued	O
to	O
assert	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
made	O
his	O
Garret	O
fast	O
about	O
Ten	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
just	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
its	O
being	O
open	O
'd	O
again	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
his	O
Chest	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sauntring	O
about	O
Mr.	O
Fell	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Time	O
her	O
Family	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
till	O
almost	O
Midnight	O
:	O
Besides	O
which	O
,	O
were	O
repeated	O
the	O
Circumstances	O
of	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
greasy	O
Marks	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
's	O
Shooes	O
upon	O
the	O
Dresser	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Bevon	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
val	O
.	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
16	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Gardener	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
James	O
Gardener	O
,	O
July	O
16	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Val	O
.	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Herrickson	I-pers
and	O
Andrew	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
48	O
Yards	O
of	O
Fustian	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Schewin	B-pers
Witte	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
Kettle	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
nine	O
Yards	O
of	O
Stuff	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Wildy	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
Transp	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
ten	O
Yards	O
of	O
Printed	O
Linnen	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Ingram	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
July	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
val	O
.	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
Transp	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Grey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Aldgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
(	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
James	B-pers
Tisdal	I-pers
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
60	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Frances	B-pers
Sanders	I-pers
,	O
July	O
27	O
.	O
And	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
White	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stoln	O
.	O
Frances	B-pers
Sanders	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Shop	O
in	O
Church-Row	B-place
,	I-place
by	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
but	O
my	O
Dwelling	O
house	O
is	O
in	O
another	O
Place	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
Daughter	O
(	O
Sarah	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
)	O
were	O
called	O
up	O
about	O
Midnight	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
Shop	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
sixty	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
Sarah	O
Nichols	O
deposed	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
both	O
swore	O
to	O
the	O
Bundle	O
of	O
Stockings	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
there	O
still	O
being	O
their	O
Marks	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
Elizabeth	O
White	O
offered	O
me	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
these	O
Stockings	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
She	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
Pair	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
fell	O
to	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
that	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
fetch	O
the	O
whole	O
Bundle	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
own	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
This	O
made	O
me	O
believe	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
honestly	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
therefore	O
I	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
for	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
bring	O
them	O
as	O
privately	O
as	O
she	O
could	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
;	O
but	O
White	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
Grey	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
Bundle	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
were	O
with	O
me	O
before	O
him	O
.	O
In	O
order	O
to	O
detain	O
them	O
till	O
the	O
Constable	O
came	O
,	O
I	O
made	O
them	O
tell	O
over	O
the	O
Stockings	O
,	O
set	O
down	O
the	O
Prices	O
separately	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
cast	O
them	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
Men	O
's	O
he	O
allow	O
'd	O
at	O
2	O
s.	O
Boys	O
at	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
Childrens	O
at	O
3	O
d.	O
At	O
these	O
Prices	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
4	O
l.	O
16	O
s.	O
in	O
all	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
they	O
must	O
abate	O
the	O
odd	O
16	O
s.	O
but	O
Grey	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
afford	O
it	O
.	O
You	O
can	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
.	O
But	O
who	O
do	O
they	O
belong	O
to	O
?	O
Perhaps	O
I	O
may	O
come	O
into	O
Trouble	O
about	O
them	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
no	O
Fear	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
says	O
Grey	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
are	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
bear	O
you	O
Harmless	O
.	O
By	O
this	O
time	O
,	O
my	O
Husband	O
and	O
the	O
Constable	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
Grey	O
look	O
'd	O
very	O
shy	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
whisper	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
at	O
my	O
own	O
Price	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
But	O
we	O
secured	O
them	O
both	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
Eleven	O
o'Clock	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
Grey	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Tisdale	O
,	O
broke	O
open	O
Mrs.	O
Sanders	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
these	O
Goods	O
.	O
Grey	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Stockings	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
Elizabeth	O
White	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Grey	O
and	O
Templeman	O
brought	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
sell	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Grey	O
Death	O
,	O
and	O
White	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Templeman	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
whereas	O
William	B-pers
Grey	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Tisdale	I-pers
did	O
privately	O
steal	O
sixty	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Frances	B-pers
Sanders	I-pers
,	O
he	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Templeman	O
,	O
did	O
receive	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stoln	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
,	O
(	O
Sister	O
to	O
Blake	O
,	O
alias	O
Blueskin	O
,	O
of	O
Enterprizing	O
Memory	O
)	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Billers	I-pers
and	I-pers
Comp	I-pers
.	O
12	O
Yards	O
of	O
Callico	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
36	O
s.	O
d	O
August	O
3d	O
Edward	B-pers
and	I-pers
Joseph	I-pers
Clarv	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
lived	O
Servant	O
in	O
a	O
Coffee-house	O
over	O
against	O
us	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
often	O
in	O
our	O
Shop	O
.	O
The	O
Callico	O
was	O
mist	O
one	O
Friday	O
Morning	O
;	O
and	O
hearing	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
suddenly	O
gone	O
from	O
her	O
Place	O
,	O
we	O
suspected	O
her	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Girl	O
had	O
a	O
pretty	O
good	O
Character	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
'Prentice	O
to	O
Mr.Wilford	O
in	O
Alhallows-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
since	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
Service	O
at	O
this	O
Coffee-house	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
Commission	O
of	O
his	O
Fact	O
.	O
Guilty	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
alias	I-pers
Mabell	I-pers
Careless	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Bishopsgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
20	O
lb	O
of	O
Thread	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Caney	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
July	O
16	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Dudley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
19	O
s.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Bailis	I-pers
,	O
July	O
21	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
Whipt	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Partridge	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Miles	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
Trans	O
.	O
Magdalen	B-pers
Gainer	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Iron	O
Fender	O
and	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Gladhall	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bland	I-pers
,	O
a	O
bundle	O
of	O
Cork	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
Nine	O
Iron	O
Bars	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
36	O
s.	O
July	O
31	O
.	O
Guilty	O
each	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Little	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Rans	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
thence	O
a	O
Gown	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
l.	O
a	O
Velvet	O
Scarf	O
val	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Gown	O
val	O
10	O
s.	O
Ten	O
Napkins	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Table	O
Cloth	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Headcloths	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
s.	O
240	O
Wig	O
Cauls	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	O
Rans	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Camlet	O
Ridinghood	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Damask	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
And	O
.	O
John	O
Little	B-pers
,	I-pers
was	I-pers
a	I-pers
2d	I-pers
time	I-pers
indicted	I-pers
,	I-pers
with	I-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
his	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hedges	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
night	O
Shirts	O
val	O
3	O
l.	O
Four	O
Smocks	O
val	O
.	O
25	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	O
Hedges	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
Twelve	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
And	O
Susan	B-pers
Belcher	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Kempster	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Fowell	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stoln	O
.	O
John	O
Little	O
,	O
of	O
Shadwell	B-place
,	O
was	O
a	O
3d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dear	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
a	O
Quilt	O
val	O
.	O
25	O
s.	O
a	O
Hat	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dear	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
Mary	O
Rans	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
June	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
about	O
Twelve	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
all	O
my	O
Doors	O
and	O
Windows	O
fast	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
up	O
about	O
four	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
House	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
two	O
Panes	O
of	O
Glass	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
front	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
Windows	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
Shutters	O
without	O
Side	O
and	O
within	O
;	O
but	O
both	O
were	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
Not	O
long	O
ago	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Everet	I-pers
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
apply	O
to	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Bewle	I-pers
in	O
New	O
Prison	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
hear	O
of	O
my	O
Goods	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
:	O
Bewle	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
such	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
Susan	O
Belcher	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Lear	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
About	O
ten	O
Weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
about	O
Eleven	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
all	O
fast	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
up	O
again	O
about	O
Two	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
House	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
the	O
middle	O
Shutter	O
taken	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Sash	O
thrown	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
lost	O
this	O
Quilt	O
,	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
;	O
and	O
recovered	O
it	O
again	O
by	O
the	O
Means	O
of	O
Bewle	O
,	O
who	O
directed	O
John	O
Everet	O
and	O
Quilt	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
where	O
to	O
fetch	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hedges	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
between	O
Ten	O
and	O
Eleven	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
made	O
all	O
fast	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
;	O
and	O
rising	O
about	O
Five	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
both	O
the	O
outer	O
and	O
inner	O
Doors	O
of	O
my	O
Cellar	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
several	O
Shirts	O
,	O
Smocks	O
,	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
were	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Tub	O
of	O
Water	O
;	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
I	O
got	O
again	O
by	O
the	O
Instructions	O
of	O
Bewle	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bewle	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Jack	O
Little	O
about	O
three	O
Months	O
:	O
My	O
first	O
Acquaintance	O
with	O
him	O
was	O
by	O
means	O
of	O
his	O
Wife	O
Betty	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
longer	O
.	O
Jack	O
,	O
(	O
says	O
she	O
to	O
me	O
one	O
Wednesday	O
)	O
I	O
know	O
a	O
young	O
Fellow	O
that	O
wants	O
a	O
Companion	O
to	O
go	O
a	O
House-breaking	O
with	O
:	O
Do	O
ye	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
?	O
Why	O
then	O
I	O
am	O
his	O
Man	O
.	O
Let	O
me	O
see	O
him	O
.	O
She	O
soon	O
brought	O
us	O
together	O
.	O
We	O
presently	O
struck	O
a	O
Bargain	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
open	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Houses	O
that	O
very	O
Night	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Friday	O
Night	O
following	O
,	O
betwixt	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
,	O
we	O
entred	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Rans	O
,	O
over	O
against	O
the	O
Sugar-Loaf	B-place
in	I-place
Virginia-Street	I-place
.	O
I	O
remember	O
there	O
was	O
double	O
Shutters	O
to	O
the	O
Windows	O
.	O
I	O
hoisted	O
Jack	O
Little	O
upon	O
my	O
Shoulder	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
several	O
Panes	O
of	O
Glass	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
opened	O
the	O
shutters	O
,	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
two	O
Gowns	O
,	O
a	O
Velvet	O
Scarf	O
,	O
several	O
Dozens	O
of	O
Wig	O
Cauls	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
Week	O
after	O
we	O
broke	O
open	O
Mr.	O
Dear	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
Gravel-Lane	B-place
about	O
One	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
We	O
cut	O
away	O
with	O
a	O
Hatcher	O
,	O
the	O
Runner	O
so	O
far	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Shutters	O
fell	O
upon	O
my	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
killed	O
me	O
.	O
We	O
only	O
took	O
a	O
Quilt	O
,	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
from	O
thence	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
Watch	O
coming	O
their	O
Rounds	O
,	O
prevented	O
us	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Week	O
we	O
broke	O
open	O
Hedgers	O
's	O
House	O
about	O
Midnight	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
,	O
Linnen	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Tub	O
of	O
Water	O
.	O
The	O
Linnen	O
,	O
the	O
Cauls	O
;	O
and	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
we	O
sold	O
to	O
Mother	O
Belcher	O
,	O
who	O
very	O
well	O
knew	O
how	O
we	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
Belcher	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
deny	O
d	O
that	O
she	O
ever	O
bought	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
either	O
Little	O
or	O
Bewle	O
;	O
but	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Bewle	O
had	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
sold	O
those	O
Goods	O
to	O
one	O
Roger	O
.	O
In	O
Answer	O
to	O
which	O
.	O
Bewle	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
some	O
things	O
to	O
Roper	O
;	O
but	O
insisted	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
sold	O
the	O
greatest	O
Part	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Belcher	O
.	O
John	O
Little	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
Acquaintance	O
with	O
Bewle	O
.	O
But	O
this	O
was	O
proved	O
otherwise	O
by	O
Quilt	O
Arnold	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Everet	I-pers
.	O
Quilt	O
Arnold	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
While	O
Bewle	O
was	O
in	O
New-Prison	O
,	O
I	O
and	O
Everet	O
found	O
these	O
two	O
Pick-lock	O
Keys	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
expecting	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Little	O
,	O
desired	O
us	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
take	O
him	O
in	O
Ratcliff	O
.	O
Bewle	O
's	O
Wife	O
(	O
with	O
a	O
Child	O
in	O
her	O
Arms	O
)	O
went	O
with	O
us	O
to	O
set	O
him	O
.	O
And	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
we	O
had	O
taken	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
sorry	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
kill	O
Bewle	O
's	O
Wife	O
and	O
Child	O
,	O
for	O
his	O
Life	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
now	O
Bewle	O
was	O
made	O
an	O
Evidence	O
.	O
John	O
Everet	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
When	O
we	O
took	O
Little	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
fain	O
have	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
New-Prison	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
saw	O
Bewle	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
little	O
thought	O
,	O
Jack	O
Bewle	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
would	O
have	O
served	O
me	O
so	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
this	O
Handkerchief	O
upon	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Little	I-pers
's	O
Neck	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
that	O
that	O
was	O
stoln	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Hedges	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Little	I-pers
,	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
Bewles	O
's	O
Wife	O
.	O
John	O
Little	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
three	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Susan	O
Belcher	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
Indictments	O
for	O
Receiving	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
But	O
Elizabeth	O
Little	O
being	O
under	O
the	O
Influence	O
and	O
Direction	O
of	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Patience	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Tea	O
Kettle	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Potter	I-pers
,	O
March	O
12	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Barns	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Panton	I-pers
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Swaris	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Smock	O
,	O
three	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Riding	O
Hood	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Adam	B-pers
Hale	I-pers
;	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Figdure	B-pers
Abrahams	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
Jew	O
)	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Bohea	O
Tea	O
,	O
val	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
and	I-pers
Emanuel	I-pers
Abrahams	I-pers
,	O
in	O
their	O
Dwelling-House	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
England	I-pers
,	I-pers
and	I-pers
Sarah	I-pers
his	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Sarah	I-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Sarah	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
alias	O
Sarah	O
Smith	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Curtains	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
a	O
Looking-Glass	O
,	O
two	O
Plates	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Gatfield	I-pers
,	O
July	O
29	O
.	O
John	O
England	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
But	O
his	O
Wife	O
acting	O
by	O
the	O
Consent	O
,	O
and	O
under	O
the	O
Authority	O
of	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Harrington	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sheet	O
,	O
a	O
Curtain	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pillowbier	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Hester	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Hester	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Woolnoth	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Conspiracy	O
against	O
John	B-pers
Cockerell	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
of	O
1400	O
l.	O
per	O
Ann	O
.	O
For	O
that	O
they	O
(	O
together	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
)	O
did	O
induce	O
and	O
persuade	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
Cockerell	O
to	O
marry	O
Abigail	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Person	O
whom	O
they	O
pretended	O
was	O
a	O
Lady	O
that	O
had	O
an	O
Estate	O
of	O
1000	O
l.	O
per	O
Ann	O
in	O
Barbadoes	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
well	O
knew	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
ill	O
Fame	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
no	O
Fortune	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
great	O
Disparagement	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
Cockerell	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
great	O
Discomposure	O
of	O
his	O
Mind	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
lessen	O
his	O
Estate	O
and	O
Substance	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
John	O
Cockerell	O
deposed	O
to	O
this	O
Effect	O
:	O
About	O
the	O
Middle	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Eccleton	O
in	O
Lombard	B-place
street	I-place
,	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
her	O
Mother	O
Mrs.	O
Gregory	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
Elder	O
of	O
the	O
Defendants	O
.	O
)	O
My	O
Business	O
with	O
her	O
was	O
to	O
demand	O
a	O
Debt	O
that	O
was	O
due	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
then	O
unprovided	O
to	O
answer	O
my	O
Demand	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
however	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
something	O
to	O
propose	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
might	O
be	O
very	O
much	O
to	O
my	O
Advantage	O
.	O
-	O
Sir	O
,	O
(	O
continued	O
she	O
)	O
are	O
you	O
disposed	O
for	O
Matrimony	O
?	O
Do	O
you	O
want	O
a	O
good	O
Wife	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
Fortune	O
?	O
If	O
you	O
do	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
introduce	O
you	O
to	O
a	O
very	O
agreeable	O
young	O
Lady	O
that	O
is	O
lately	O
come	O
from	O
Barbadoes	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
a	O
vast	O
Plantation	O
there	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Hundred	O
Negroes	O
upon	O
it	O
:	O
Her	O
Estate	O
is	O
worth	O
1000	O
or	O
1100	O
l.	O
a	O
Year	O
.	O
She	O
likes	O
England	O
so	O
well	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
's	O
resolved	O
to	O
live	O
here	O
and	O
marry	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
can	O
meet	O
with	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
of	O
a	O
suitable	O
Fortune	O
.	O
Why	O
,	O
really	O
Madam	O
,	O
(	O
says	O
I	O
)	O
provided	O
Things	O
are	O
as	O
you	O
represent	O
them	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
any	O
Aversion	O
to	O
Marriage	O
;	O
-	O
I	O
would	O
willingly	O
have	O
an	O
Heir	O
.	O
-	O
But	O
-	O
a	O
-	O
Madam	O
,	O
-	O
are	O
you	O
sure	O
that	O
this	O
Lady	O
is	O
indeed	O
worth	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
you	O
speak	O
of	O
?	O
Am	O
I	O
sure	O
,	O
Sir	O
?	O
(	O
says	O
Mrs.	O
Gregory	O
again	O
)	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
manages	O
all	O
her	O
Affairs	O
.	O
-	O
You	O
know	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
,	O
he	O
lives	O
at	O
my	O
Cousin	O
Tryon	O
's	O
;	O
-	O
He	O
's	O
worth	O
300	O
l.	O
a	O
Year	O
;	O
he	O
lives	O
in	O
very	O
good	O
Credit	O
;	O
and	O
you	O
ca	O
n't	O
think	O
that	O
such	O
a	O
Man	O
as	O
he	O
would	O
impose	O
upon	O
any	O
body	O
.	O
This	O
Discourse	O
was	O
only	O
betwixt	O
me	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Gregory	O
.	O
It	O
ran	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
my	O
Mind	O
all	O
that	O
Night	O
;	O
and	O
next	O
day	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Eccleton	O
's	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
found	O
there	O
not	O
only	O
Mrs.	O
Gregory	O
,	O
but	O
her	O
Daughter	O
Miss	O
Gregory	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
other	O
Defendant	O
)	O
and	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
John	O
Smith	O
.	O
Our	O
chief	O
Talk	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
same	O
Subject	O
as	O
before	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
assured	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
what	O
Mrs.	O
Gregory	O
had	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
this	O
Lady	O
's	O
Fortune	O
,	O
was	O
all	O
true	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
desirous	O
of	O
coming	O
into	O
this	O
pretended	O
Lady	O
's	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
beg	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
when	O
and	O
where	O
I	O
should	O
enjoy	O
that	O
Favour	O
.	O
They	O
promis	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
Enquiry	O
,	O
and	O
send	O
me	O
Word	O
.	O
We	O
parted	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
being	O
Sunday	O
,	O
a	O
Letter	O
was	O
brought	O
me	O
,	O
(	O
as	O
I	O
suppose	O
from	O
Miss	O
Gregory	O
)	O
appointing	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
that	O
evening	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Eales	O
's	O
in	O
Ely-Court	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
might	O
see	O
this	O
Berbadias	O
Lady	O
.	O
I	O
want	O
accordingly	O
.	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
drinking	O
Tea	O
with	O
the	O
two	O
Defendants	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
dress	O
'd	O
in	O
a	O
rich	O
Brocade	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
and	O
Diamond	O
Pendants	O
.	O
The	O
Conversation	O
turn	O
'd	O
up	O
on	O
this	O
Lady	O
's	O
Plantation	O
Miss	O
Gregory	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
(	O
as	O
her	O
Mother	O
had	O
said	O
before	O
)	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Cole	O
was	O
worth	O
at	O
least	O
1000	O
l.	O
a	O
Year	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
100	O
Negroes	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
mention	O
'd	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
an	O
Attorney	O
of	O
my	O
Acquaintance	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Counterfeit	O
Lady	O
if	O
she	O
knew	O
him	O
?	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
any	O
Personal	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
of	O
his	O
Name	O
.	O
Then	O
pray	O
,	O
Madam	O
,	O
(	O
says	O
I	O
)	O
how	O
long	O
may	O
you	O
have	O
had	O
this	O
Plantation	O
?	O
About	O
three	O
Years	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
,	O
And	O
,	O
Dear	O
Madam	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
may	O
be	O
so	O
bold	O
,	O
how	O
-	O
a	O
-	O
might	O
you	O
at	O
first	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
Possession	O
of	O
this	O
Plantation	O
?	O
-	O
Why	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
(	O
say	O
she	O
)	O
it	O
was	O
left	O
me	O
by	O
my	O
own	O
Brother	O
.	O
Of	O
all	O
my	O
Relations	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
only	O
one	O
Sister	O
living	O
:	O
She	O
's	O
about	O
9	O
Years	O
old	O
;	O
-	O
but	O
such	O
a	O
poor	O
sickly	O
thing	O
-	O
My	O
Uncle	O
left	O
her	O
1500	O
l.	O
which	O
will	O
be	O
mine	O
if	O
I	O
survive	O
her	O
.	O
With	O
such	O
like	O
Discourse	O
we	O
pass	O
'd	O
away	O
the	O
Time	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
Company	O
broke	O
up	O
.	O
Next	O
Morning	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Miss	O
Gregory	O
,	O
to	O
enquire	O
how	O
the	O
Lady	O
liked	O
me	O
.	O
O	O
!	O
Mr.	O
Cockerell	O
,	O
(	O
says	O
she	O
)	O
you	O
are	O
certainly	O
the	O
most	O
fortunate	O
Man	O
living	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
o'my	O
Conscience	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
bewitched	O
the	O
Lady	O
.	O
-	O
She	O
's	O
so	O
Charm	O
'd	O
!	O
So	O
Captivated	O
!	O
-	O
She	O
no	O
sooner	O
saw	O
you	O
,	O
than	O
she	O
felt	O
your	O
Power	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
something	O
in	O
you	O
so	O
engaging	O
!	O
so	O
irresistible	O
!	O
that	O
you	O
immediately	O
gain	O
'd	O
a	O
perfect	O
Conquest	O
.	O
-	O
Her	O
Heart	O
!	O
her	O
Soul	O
!	O
her	O
Fortune	O
!	O
all	O
is	O
yours	O
!	O
-	O
Look	O
ye	O
,	O
Miss	O
Gregory	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Lady	O
's	O
Heart	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
under	O
no	O
Apprehensions	O
of	O
being	O
deceived	O
;	O
but	O
me	O
.	O
thinks	O
the	O
Report	O
of	O
her	O
Fortune	O
wants	O
a	O
little	O
Confirmation	O
.	O
Well	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
the	O
strangest	O
Man	O
!	O
so	O
incredulous	O
!	O
-	O
I	O
thought	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
had	O
satisfy	O
'd	O
you	O
:	O
But	O
if	O
he	O
that	O
has	O
the	O
Management	O
of	O
all	O
her	O
Affairs	O
can	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
how	O
I	O
should	O
.	O
Well	O
!	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
to	O
talk	O
with	O
him	O
seriously	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
Sir	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
beg	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
ingenuous	O
,	O
-	O
Has	O
Mrs.	O
Cole	O
really	O
got	O
so	O
good	O
a	O
Fortune	O
as	O
is	O
reported	O
?	O
Why	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
tell	O
you	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
since	O
you	O
press	O
me	O
so	O
closely	O
;	O
she	O
has	O
not	O
quite	O
so	O
much	O
:	O
Fame	O
is	O
apt	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
little	O
extravagant	O
;	O
Eighty	O
Negroes	O
is	O
the	O
outside	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Annual	O
Income	O
is	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
800	O
l.	O
Upon	O
this	O
Fall	O
of	O
at	O
least	O
200	O
l.	O
a	O
Year	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
Negroes	O
,	O
I	O
returns	O
to	O
Miss	O
Gregory	O
,	O
and	O
tells	O
her	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Laud	O
!	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
perceive	O
the	O
Trick	O
?	O
'T	O
is	O
all	O
an	O
Artifice	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
:	O
He	O
designs	O
to	O
try	O
for	O
the	O
Lady	O
himself	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
but	O
this	O
day	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
really	O
made	O
some	O
Tenders	O
of	O
Service	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
'us	O
no	O
wonder	O
then	O
if	O
he	O
endeavours	O
to	O
lessen	O
your	O
Opinion	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
indeed	O
that	O
at	O
present	O
she	O
prefers	O
you	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
you	O
are	O
in	O
the	O
Sixty	O
sixth	O
Year	O
of	O
your	O
Age	O
;	O
but	O
yet	O
if	O
she	O
finds	O
you	O
neglect	O
her	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
may	O
chance	O
to	O
supplant	O
you	O
.	O
Therefore	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
design	O
to	O
pursue	O
the	O
Amour	O
,	O
be	O
quick	O
!	O
dispatch	O
!	O
the	O
sooner	O
the	O
better	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
desired	O
Miss	O
Gregory	O
to	O
ask	O
this	O
Lady	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
be	O
marry	O
'd	O
next	O
day	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
brought	O
me	O
Word	O
,	O
Yes	O
:	O
And	O
Preparation	O
was	O
made	O
accordingly	O
.	O
As	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Sham	O
Lady	O
,	O
Madam	O
,	O
-	O
do	O
n't	O
deceive	O
me	O
;	O
-	O
Have	O
you	O
really	O
such	O
a	O
Plantation	O
?	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
.	O
In	O
short	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
marry	O
'd	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
together	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
-	O
a	O
-	O
I	O
need	O
say	O
nothing	O
about	O
throwing	O
the	O
Stocking	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
after	O
Dinner	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
my	O
Return	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
Barbadian	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
another	O
Woman	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
(	O
says	O
this	O
pretended	O
Lady	O
of	O
mine	O
)	O
that	O
it	O
's	O
now	O
high	O
time	O
to	O
undeciive	O
you	O
:	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
question	O
but	O
that	O
you	O
think	O
you	O
have	O
marry	O
'd	O
a	O
rich	O
Lady	O
of	O
Barbadoes	O
;	O
when	O
,	O
indeed	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
quite	O
mistaken	O
.	O
Mistaken	O
!	O
(	O
says	O
I	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
Surprize	O
)	O
Why	O
,	O
pray	O
Madam	O
,	O
what	O
are	O
ye	O
?	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
your	O
Wife	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
;	O
but	O
before	O
you	O
made	O
me	O
so	O
I	O
was	O
Mrs.	O
Eccleton	O
's	O
Maid	O
;	O
and	O
this	O
is	O
my	O
Mother	O
,	O
a	O
good	O
honest	O
Woman	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
she	O
keeps	O
a	O
Chandler	O
's	O
Shop	O
.	O
Mercy	O
on	O
me	O
!	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
what	O
have	O
I	O
done	O
?	O
Done	O
?	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
Why	O
you	O
have	O
marry	O
'd	O
Abigail	O
Cole	O
.	O
Away	O
went	O
I	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Gregory	O
:	O
I	O
wonder	O
,	O
Madam	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
how	O
you	O
could	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
so	O
vile	O
an	O
Action	O
,	O
as	O
thus	O
to	O
impose	O
upon	O
a	O
Man	O
that	O
has	O
always	O
been	O
your	O
Friend	O
?	O
What	O
could	O
induce	O
you	O
to	O
so	O
much	O
Wickedness	O
?	O
Lord	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Cockerell	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
?	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
very	O
suitable	O
Wife	O
:	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
great	O
Fortune	O
indeed	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
may	O
save	O
you	O
one	O
by	O
her	O
good	O
Management	O
:	O
You	O
had	O
Money	O
enough	O
before	O
;	O
you	O
only	O
wanted	O
an	O
Heir	O
to	O
enjoy	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
due	O
time	O
she	O
may	O
bring	O
you	O
one	O
.	O
Thus	O
far	O
the	O
Plaintiff	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
prove	O
his	O
Wife	O
(	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Indictment	O
)	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
Woman	O
of	O
Ill	O
Fame	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
his	O
Counsel	O
called	O
Abigail	B-pers
Holms	I-pers
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Cockerell	O
had	O
been	O
Cook-Maid	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Eccleton	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
Father	O
was	O
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pensioner	O
in	O
Chelsea-College	O
.	O
To	O
answer	O
this	O
,	O
by	O
proving	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Woman	O
of	O
a	O
Vertuous	O
Character	O
,	O
the	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
Defendants	O
call	O
'd	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fog	I-pers
,	O
who	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Eccleton	O
's	O
the	O
Sadlers	O
.	O
The	O
Morning	O
after	O
the	O
Wedding	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
Mr.	O
Cockerell	O
say	O
to	O
my	O
Master	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
my	O
Wife	O
was	O
a	O
Maid	O
.	O
And	O
then	O
,	O
(	O
says	O
my	O
Master	O
)	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
that	O
you	O
have	O
been	O
dabbling	O
.	O
-	O
As	O
for	O
the	O
Management	O
in	O
bringing	O
this	O
Wedding	O
about	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
Mrs.	O
Gregory	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
our	O
People	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
at	O
first	O
they	O
only	O
talked	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
Banter	O
,	O
and	O
little	O
thought	O
of	O
bringing	O
it	O
to	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
they	O
saw	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Cockerell	O
was	O
so	O
quickly	O
in	O
Love	O
,	O
they	O
carried	O
on	O
the	O
Jest	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
married	O
in	O
Earnest	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Eccleton	O
thus	O
deposed	O
,	O
Mr.Cockerell	O
has	O
sworn	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Mother	O
on	O
Account	O
of	O
a	O
Debt	O
;	O
I	O
dont	O
know	O
that	O
my	O
Mother	O
owes	O
him	O
a	O
Shilling	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
very	O
Often	O
upon	O
another	O
Account	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
may	O
safely	O
swear	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
teiz	O
'd	O
my	O
Mother	O
500	O
times	O
to	O
help	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
Wife	O
:	O
I	O
myself	O
have	O
recommended	O
him	O
to	O
at	O
least	O
20	O
Women	O
,	O
all	O
whom	O
he	O
left	O
when	O
he	O
found	O
their	O
fortunes	O
fell	O
short	O
of	O
his	O
Expectation	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
so	O
continually	O
importuning	O
us	O
to	O
introduce	O
him	O
to	O
Ladies	O
,	O
that	O
at	O
last	O
we	O
contrived	O
to	O
get	O
rid	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
by	O
dressing	O
up	O
my	O
Maid	O
in	O
a	O
young	O
Lady	O
's	O
Apparel	O
,	O
and	O
recommending	O
her	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
Barbadoes	O
fortune	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Plot	O
succeeded	O
beyond	O
Expectation	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
's	O
as	O
modest	O
a	O
Woman	O
as	O
ever	O
lived	O
:	O
Nor	O
is	O
she	O
any	O
thing	O
below	O
him	O
,	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
her	O
Father	O
's	O
being	O
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
for	O
his	O
Father	O
served	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Quality	O
under	O
Oliver	B-pers
Cromwell	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Monday	O
after	O
his	O
Wedding	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
Bit	O
.	O
Bit	O
?	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
What	O
a	O
Man	O
or	O
your	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
well	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
Town	O
too	O
?	O
'T	O
is	O
very	O
strange	O
!	O
Well	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
't	O
was	O
my	O
own	O
Fault	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
rash	O
Old	O
Fool	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
blame	O
nobody	O
but	O
myself	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
bit	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
so	O
Rich	O
as	O
I	O
expected	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
made	O
over	O
all	O
my	O
Estate	O
to	O
my	O
Brother	O
's	O
Son	O
,	O
except	O
130	O
l.	O
a	O
Year	O
,	O
a	O
Third	O
of	O
which	O
is	O
all	O
that	O
she	O
can	O
come	O
in	O
for	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
whether	O
he	O
did	O
this	O
before	O
Marriage	O
or	O
since	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
desired	O
both	O
me	O
and	O
my	O
Sister	O
(	O
the	O
Defendant	O
)	O
to	O
persuade	O
his	O
Wife	O
to	O
consent	O
to	O
a	O
Divorce	O
,	O
upon	O
Condition	O
of	O
his	O
allowing	O
her	O
a	O
handsome	O
Reward	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
thought	O
no	O
Woman	O
would	O
be	O
so	O
much	O
a	O
Fool	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
swear	O
herself	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Whore	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
to	O
lose	O
her	O
Husband	O
for	O
a	O
little	O
Money	O
.	O
Sh	O
o	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
occasion	O
for	O
all	O
that	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
manage	O
it	O
a	O
much	O
better	O
way	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
can	O
but	O
get	O
her	O
to	O
comply	O
;	O
I	O
'll	O
provide	O
a	O
Pre-Contracts	O
betwixt	O
me	O
and	O
another	O
Lady	O
,	O
and	O
get	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
swear	O
it	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Tea	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Cockerell	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
Wedding	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Mistress	O
Eccleton	O
's	O
,	O
appear	O
'd	O
very	O
well	O
pleas	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
Mrs.	O
Gregory	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
charg	O
'd	O
a	O
Constable	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
desired	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
to	O
dress	O
herself	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
took	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Shoulders	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
thrown	O
her	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
prevented	O
.	O
-	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Reason	O
why	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Hurry	O
to	O
be	O
married	O
,	O
without	O
making	O
any	O
farther	O
enquiry	O
about	O
the	O
Woman	O
's	O
Estate	O
,	O
was	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
she	O
should	O
Enquire	O
after	O
his	O
Estate	O
and	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Singleton	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
On	O
Thursday	O
Morning	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Wedding-Day	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Cockerell	O
telling	O
me	O
what	O
a	O
great	O
Fortune	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
marry	O
,	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
take	O
Care	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
bit	O
.	O
Bit	O
!	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
No	O
no	O
,	O
I	O
'm	O
too	O
old	O
for	O
that	O
,	O
they	O
must	O
have	O
good	O
Luck	O
that	O
can	O
bite	O
me	O
.	O
And	O
are	O
you	O
really	O
certain	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Money	O
:	O
Ay	O
,	O
ay	O
(	O
says	O
he	O
)	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
well	O
satisfied	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hammond	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
after	O
the	O
Wedding	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Cockerell	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
well	O
satisfied	O
with	O
his	O
Bride	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
having	O
summ	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Pleading	O
of	O
the	O
Counsel	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
last	O
of	O
which	O
we	O
have	O
not	O
Room	O
to	O
insert	O
)	O
observed	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Marriage	O
Vow	O
of	O
the	O
Plaintiff	O
over-turn	O
'd	O
the	O
whole	O
Indictment	O
,	O
for	O
in	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
acknowledged	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
depend	O
upon	O
the	O
Report	O
of	O
her	O
Fortune	O
,	O
when	O
in	O
a	O
most	O
solemn	O
manner	O
he	O
protest	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
her	O
for	O
Richer	O
for	O
Poorer	O
.	O
-	O
That	O
he	O
took	O
her	O
(	O
not	O
for	O
the	O
Sake	O
of	O
a	O
Barbadoes	O
Plantation	O
)	O
but	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
her	O
after	O
God	O
's	O
Ordinance	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Procreation	O
of	O
Children	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
the	O
mutual	O
Society	O
and	O
Help	O
of	O
each	O
other	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Defendants	O
.	O
George	B-pers
English	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
Boy	O
)	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
25	O
Bobbins	O
,	O
and	O
60	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Partan	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Sydenham	I-pers
;	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
English	I-pers
,	O
(	O
his	O
Mother	O
)	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
George	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
val	O
.	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stubbs	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
Bobbins	O
,	O
and	O
26	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hophny	I-pers
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Table-Cloths	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Dutton	I-pers
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Holloway	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Duncomb	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
14	O
s.	O
&	O
c.	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
May	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Brecknell	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
Watchman	O
)	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Smocks	O
,	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
4	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Rawlins	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
,	O
from	O
Joseph	B-pers
Forward	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Half	O
Broadpiece	O
,	O
and	O
Two-Pence	O
,	O
Guilty	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Baily	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
19	O
Guineas	O
,	O
3	O
Broadpieces	O
and	O
a	O
Half	O
;	O
two	O
Moidores	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Shilling	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
and	O
7	O
Guineas	O
,	O
a	O
Canvas	O
Bag	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
William	O
Smith	O
.	O
Win	O
.	O
Smith	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
Between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
Night	O
,	O
July	O
21	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
got	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
asleep	O
upon	O
a	O
Bulk	O
near	O
Widegate-Alley	B-place
in	I-place
Bishopsgate-Street	I-place
;	O
I	O
had	O
then	O
34	O
l.	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
my	O
Coat	O
Pocket	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
ty	O
'd	O
in	O
a	O
Bag	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Bag	O
wrapt	O
in	O
this	O
Handkerchief	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
waked	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
gone	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
seen	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
examined	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Handkerchief	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Field	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
receiving	O
Goods	O
that	O
were	O
stoln	O
by	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
he	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stoln	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Fined	O
20	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
suffer	O
12	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
an	O
old	O
Offender	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Sheppard	O
and	O
Blueskin	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Pierce	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Mulzer	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
Common-Prayer-Book	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
Aquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
with	O
William	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
assault	O
,	O
ravish	O
and	O
against	O
her	O
Will	O
,	O
carnally	O
know	O
Sarah	B-pers
Tate	I-pers
July	O
6	O
.	O
Sarah	O
Tate	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Hay-making	O
at	O
Hammersmith	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
coming	O
Home	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
Kensington	O
,	O
where	O
my	O
Master	O
lived	O
,	O
Will	O
.	O
West	O
took	O
my	O
Fork	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Wheatsheaf	O
at	O
Kensington	B-place
;	O
and	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
after	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
they	O
kept	O
me	O
till	O
it	O
was	O
late	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
West	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
Lobb	O
's	O
Field	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Point	O
of	O
Ravishing	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
just	O
made	O
an	O
Entrance	O
into	O
my	O
-	O
my	O
-	O
Body	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
seeming	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
angry	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
no	O
farther	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
offered	O
to	O
bear	O
me	O
Company	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
civiler	O
Man	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
West	O
followed	O
us	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
a	O
private	O
Place	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
me	O
down	O
and	O
committed	O
a	O
Rape	O
upon	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
got	O
off	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
on	O
and	O
ravished	O
me	O
again	O
.	O
They	O
made	O
me	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
frightful	O
Condition	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
would	O
have	O
bless	O
'd	O
yourself	O
to	O
have	O
seen	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
Blood	O
gush	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Nose	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
into	O
my	O
Mouth	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
lay	O
upon	O
my	O
Back	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
strangled	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
all	O
over	O
bloody	O
,	O
from	O
Head	O
to	O
Foot	O
,	O
both	O
within	O
and	O
without	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
such	O
an	O
Agony	O
!	O
-	O
I	O
struggled	O
and	O
strove	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
all	O
that	O
a	O
Woman	O
could	O
do	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
was	O
quite	O
spent	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
just	O
ready	O
to	O
die	O
away	O
:	O
And	O
at	O
last	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
home	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
they	O
left	O
me	O
about	O
Midnight	O
.	O
My	O
Mistress	O
came	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
dark	O
and	O
let	O
me	O
in	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
how	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
abused	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
called	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Sarah	O
Tate	O
and	O
Will	O
.	O
West	O
had	O
been	O
,	O
that	O
Evening	O
,	O
at	O
several	O
Alehouses	O
together	O
in	O
and	O
about	O
Kensington	O
:	O
That	O
she	O
appointed	O
to	O
meet	O
him	O
in	O
Emerson	O
's	O
Field	O
:	O
That	O
there	O
are	O
Houses	O
all	O
the	O
Way	O
betwixt	O
the	O
Wheatsheaf	O
(	O
near	O
the	O
Church	O
)	O
and	O
her	O
Master	O
Lockwood	O
's	O
House	O
(	O
near	O
Kensington-Square	O
:	O
)	O
So	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
Occasion	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
a	O
private	O
round-about	O
Way	O
over	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
being	O
ravished	O
in	O
the	O
Publick	O
Street	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Norris	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Fulham	B-place
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Goddard	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
of	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
12	O
Inches	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
I	O
keep	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
at	O
Hammersmith	B-place
.	O
Mr.	O
