TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bayly	O
:	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
,	O
Monday	O
and	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
9th	O
,	O
10th	O
,	O
11th	O
,	O
13th	O
,	O
and	O
14th	O
,	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
1725.	O
in	O
the	O
Twelfth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
FORBES	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Fortescue	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Page	I-pers
;	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
,	O
Serjeant	O
at	O
Law	O
;	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Roger	B-pers
Street	I-pers
John	B-pers
Snee	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Trott	I-pers
John	B-pers
Branch	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
George	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
Daniel	B-pers
Jevon	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
William	B-pers
Buckmaster	I-pers
James	B-pers
Cannel	I-pers
William	B-pers
Thomason	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Goddard	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Stanley	I-pers
George	B-pers
Stanford	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
King	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Marlow	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Percival	I-pers
Eleazer	B-pers
Malory	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Peacock	I-pers
Dawbry	B-pers
Turberville	I-pers
John	B-pers
Metcalf	I-pers
William	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Billingsgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
in	O
the	O
Ware-House	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Ashton	I-pers
,	O
119	O
l.	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Will	B-pers
.	I-pers
Tryon	I-pers
.	O
Dec.	O
2	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Wharfinger	O
,	O
at	O
Lyon's-Key	B-place
;	O
and	O
was	O
entrusted	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
Ware-Houses	O
,	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
Sugar	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Hogshead	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Tryon	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
Bag	O
in	O
the	O
Passage	O
on	O
the	O
Stair-Head	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Cliff	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hamson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Aldgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
and	O
Chain	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
Trans	O
.	O
Katherine	B-pers
Dunster	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
;	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Bowers	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
alias	O
Wife	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Bowers	I-pers
;	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Canvas	O
Bag	O
,	O
with	O
Money	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
fell	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
lost	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
made	O
enquiry	O
after	O
it	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
Constable	O
who	O
search	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
only	O
the	O
Bag	O
was	O
found	O
empty	O
under	O
Dunster	O
's	O
Chair	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
confest	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Company	O
,	O
but	O
deny	O
'd	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
his	O
Money	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
39	O
Shillings	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
was	O
indicted	O
with	O
James	B-pers
Sherrard	I-pers
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Tolson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
Value	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Field	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
know	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stoln	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
Night	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
Captain	O
Tolson	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
Steele	O
,	O
who	O
lay	O
in	O
Newgate	O
for	O
returning	O
from	O
Transportation	O
,	O
confest	O
that	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
Foster	O
,	O
and	O
Sherrard	O
committed	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
and	O
sold	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Field	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Dun	I-pers
in	O
Southwark	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
apprehended	O
in	O
Moses	O
and	O
Aaron	O
's	O
Alley	O
,	O
White-Chappel	O
.	O
Mary	O
Dun	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Foster	O
brought	O
Captain	O
Tolson	O
's	O
Shirts	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
pawn	O
'd	O
at	O
his	O
Wife	O
's	O
desire	O
.	O
Foster	O
's	O
Information	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
wherein	O
he	O
confest	O
this	O
Fact	O
among	O
other	O
Felonies	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
Field	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
Foster	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Astill	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Cloths	O
,	O
a	O
Riding-Hood	O
,	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
defrauding	O
Mary	B-pers
Lestrange	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
under	O
Pretence	O
of	O
getting	O
her	O
21	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
Value	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Pepper	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Covent-Garden	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
China	O
Sugar	O
Dish	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
China	O
Mug	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Shadwell	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Head	O
of	O
a	O
Cain	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Ingledew	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hodges	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
September	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pillowbier	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Evan	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Marshal	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Ewins	I-pers
,	O
Two	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
Value	O
2	O
s.	O
October	O
14	O
.	O
Guilty	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Pew	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
60	O
Ells	O
of	O
Mantua	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Foreman	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Brachstone	I-pers
,	O
November	O
21	O
.	O
Several	O
Witnesses	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Months	O
past	O
,	O
has	O
been	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Brachstone	O
;	O
she	O
left	O
a	O
Box	O
at	O
the	O
Lodging	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
in	O
Coleman	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
call	O
for	O
it	O
in	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Days	O
.	O
Harrison	O
searched	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
several	O
Goods	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Brachstone	O
dealt	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
Notice	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Brackstone	O
came	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Scurrier	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Cripplegate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Firkin	O
of	O
Butter	O
,	O
value	O
24	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hamlet	I-pers
.	O
October	O
29	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
pursu	O
'd	O
,	O
threw	O
the	O
Firkin	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
the	O
Evidence	O
cross	O
the	O
Wrist	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
escap	O
'd	O
from	O
his	O
Keepers	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
on	O
Board	O
for	O
Transportation	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
broke	O
out	O
of	O
Newgate	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Ker	B-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Carr	I-pers
Halbert	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Hainsworth	B-pers
Dent	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
Halbert	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Silver	O
Salts	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
2	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Peat	I-pers
;	O
and	O
Dent	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stoln	O
.	O
September	O
8	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
Dent	O
offering	O
to	O
sell	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Goods	O
,	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
having	O
stoln	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
Fire	O
on	O
London-Bridge	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
a	O
strict	O
Examination	O
,	O
he	O
confest	O
that	O
Carr	O
Halbert	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
Apprentice	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Brother-in-law	O
)	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Garret	O
Window	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
him	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
.	O
Halbert	O
confest	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
that	O
Dent	O
perswaded	O
him	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Halbert	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Dent	O
:	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Books	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Reason	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Reason	O
had	O
lost	O
several	O
Books	O
,	O
and	O
missing	O
Dr.	O
Taylor	O
's	O
Living	O
and	O
Dying	O
from	O
his	O
Window	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
loitering	O
thereabouts	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
before	O
took	O
2	O
other	O
Books	O
,	O
entitled	O
Antiochus	O
and	O
Stratonice	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Apology	O
,	O
for	O
Antonia	B-pers
Bourignon	I-pers
;	O
all	O
which	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
sworn	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Vandereiken	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Hat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Douglas	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Byrn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hampstead	B-place
;	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Iron	O
Jack	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Shuter	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
in	O
taking	O
the	O
said	O
Jack	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Freehold	O
of	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Shuter	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Jack	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
an	O
unhabited	O
House	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Shuter	O
;	O
that	O
Edw	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
,	O
meeting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Jack	O
in	O
his	O
Arms	O
,	O
he	O
suspected	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
honestly	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
Upon	O
Examination	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
Mrs.	O
Shutor	O
's	O
Kitchen	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Misdemeanor	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Barge-Head	O
Fast-Rope	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Bouch	I-pers
.	O
Junior	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
And	O
William	B-pers
Lunn	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Leonard	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stoln	O
.	O
Lunn	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Carter	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
Value	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Goddard	B-pers
Orwin	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
;	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Tea	O
Spoon	O
,	O
as	O
Apron	O
,	O
a	O
Sheet	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Mohun	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Showbridge	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
several	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Elias	B-pers
Mordecai	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
Each	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Swingler	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cheese	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Harrowbin	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Chetain	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Long	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
2	O
Petticoats	O
.	O
a	O
Smock	O
and	O
a	O
Frock	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Will	B-pers
.	I-pers
Harding	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
Novem	O
.	O
Acquit	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Timberlock	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Gross	O
of	O
Thread	O
Laces	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Arrowsmith	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
Acquit	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Lovingham	I-pers
,	I-pers
Martha	I-pers
his	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
,	O
Martha	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Lamb	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Samuel	O
James	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
thence	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
a	O
Pawn	O
Brokers	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
traced	O
from	O
Lamb	O
to	O
Lovingham	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
her	O
to	O
her	O
Husband	O
.	O
He	O
confest	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Jackson	O
(	O
which	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
)	O
that	O
about	O
5	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
Geo	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Will	B-pers
Lasingby	I-pers
,	O
and	O
himself	O
,	O
went	O
together	O
to	O
Mr.	O
James	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
Mincing-Lane	B-place
.	O
That	O
himself	O
stood	O
to	O
watch	O
,	O
while	O
his	O
Companions	O
climb	O
'd	O
over	O
two	O
Walls	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
back	O
a	O
Bundle	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
carried	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
Goods	O
were	O
afterwards	O
pawn	O
'd	O
by	O
Mary	O
Lamb	O
.	O
The	O
Women	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
,	O
but	O
Richard	O
Lovingham	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	I-pers
and	I-pers
Isabell	I-pers
her	I-pers
Daughter	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Isabell	O
her	O
Daughter	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
36	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Beal	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
Ann	O
Hall	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Isabell	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
Ann	O
Hall	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stoln	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Shales	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
William	I-pers
Baily	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ashford	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
10	O
Guineas	O
,	O
a	O
quarter	O
Moidore	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Ellit	I-pers
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Ellit	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
I	O
had	O
Occasion	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
my	O
Chamber	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
my	O
Servant	O
had	O
been	O
just	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
Drawers	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
ten	O
Guineas	O
missing	O
.	O
I	O
taxed	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
afterwards	O
told	O
me	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
making	O
my	O
Bed	O
,	O
Sarah	O
(	O
who	O
had	O
lately	O
been	O
my	O
Servant	O
)	O
came	O
down	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Clarks	O
,	O
(	O
who	O
lodged	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
higher	O
)	O
and	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Drawers	O
,	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
her	O
say	O
nothing	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
Clark	O
again	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
she	O
gave	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
bidding	O
her	O
pay	O
her	O
Landlady	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
she	O
'd	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Lodging	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Fenn	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cheese	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
3	O
Pound	O
of	O
Bacon	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Greenwood	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
Novem	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
Whipt	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Vandesman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hankerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Cust	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Firkin	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
Firkin	O
of	O
Butter	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hurlock	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
.	O
Acquit	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Fielder	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Emmet	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
6	O
Cow-Hides	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Ware-House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Light	I-pers
.	O
Emmet	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Fielder	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Value	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harrop	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Half	O
a	O
Firkin	O
of	O
Soap	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Plumridge	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Ebdon	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Pretland	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Hemp	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Wapping	B-place
;	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
Mary	B-pers
Sutherland	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Bodice	O
,	O
a	O
Stomacher	O
,	O
a	O
Camblet	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
15	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
Mary	O
Sutherland	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
betwixt	O
1	O
and	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Ratcliff-Highway	B-place
to	O
wash	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Savages	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
Ladder	O
rais	O
'd	O
against	O
the	O
Side	O
of	O
a	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Man	O
going	O
up	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
gone	O
far	O
before	O
Hemp	O
over	O
took	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
whither	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
to	O
my	O
Daily	O
Labour	O
.	O
What	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
is	O
it	O
a	O
rich	O
House	O
?	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
much	O
to	O
that	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
they	O
pay	O
me	O
very	O
honestly	O
.	O
Have	O
they	O
Men	O
Servants	O
or	O
Maids	O
.	O
Both	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
off	O
is	O
it	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
ye	O
.	O
O	O
God	O
bless	O
ye	O
Master	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
(	O
in	O
hopes	O
to	O
get	O
rid	O
of	O
him	O
)	O
't	O
is	O
a	O
great	O
Way	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
should	O
you	O
give	O
your	O
self	O
that	O
Trouble	O
.	O
By	O
this	O
Time	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
Bird	O
,	O
was	O
come	O
up	O
to	O
us	O
.	O
D	O
-	O
ye	O
for	O
an	O
Old	O
Bitch	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
what	O
makes	O
ye	O
carry	O
a	O
Candle	O
at	O
this	O
Time	O
of	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
stript	O
me	O
of	O
all	O
my	O
Cloths	O
but	O
my	O
Shift	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
pull	O
'd	O
over	O
my	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
tore	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Woman	O
's	O
Voice	O
,	O
say	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
D	O
-	O
ye	O
,	O
kill	O
the	O
Bitch	O
,	O
if	O
ye	O
think	O
she	O
knows	O
ye	O
.	O
They	O
beat	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
me	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
barbarous	O
and	O
indecent	O
Manner	O
.	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
Murder	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
tye	O
my	O
Head	O
betwixt	O
my	O
Legs	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Cart-Way	O
;	O
but	O
a	O
Watchman	O
's	O
Dog	O
coming	O
up	O
,	O
they	O
stampt	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
me	O
for	O
dead	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
so	O
weak	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
speak	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
Roberts	O
the	O
Watchman	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
Woman	O
's	O
Evidence	O
,	O
as	O
did	O
Richard	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
who	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
seeing	O
Bird	O
and	O
Hemp	O
in	O
the	O
Watch-House	O
,	O
and	O
conceiving	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Persons	O
that	O
had	O
committed	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
he	O
look	O
'd	O
stedfastly	O
at	O
them	O
,	O
says	O
Bird	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
do	O
ye	O
know	O
me	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
do	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
was	O
you	O
not	O
near	O
Well-Close	O
Square	O
'tother	O
Night	O
.	O
Hemp	O
changed	O
colour	O
,	O
and	O
faintly	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
Yes	O
.	O
-	O
And	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
strip	O
a	O
poor	O
Woman	O
there	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
.	O
Why	O
Yes	O
,	O
Says	O
Bird	O
,	O
we	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
is	O
it	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
Son	O
of	O
a	O
Bitch	O
alive	O
?	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
Mrs.	O
Sutherland	O
saw	O
Bird	O
,	O
-	O
Ay	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
That	O
's	O
the	O
Rogue	O
that	O
I	O
scratch	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
.	O
Bird	O
immediately	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
D	O
-	O
in	O
the	O
old	O
Bitch	O
,	O
is	O
she	O
not	O
dead	O
yet	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
had	O
done	O
her	O
Business	O
.	O
As	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
Hemp	O
appeared	O
inclinable	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
full	O
Discovery	O
,	O
which	O
Bird	O
perceiving	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
Oath	O
,	O
have	O
ye	O
a	O
Mind	O
to	O
hang	O
us	O
both	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Watchman	O
;	O
deposed	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Princes-Street	O
,	O
in	O
Wood-Street	O
,	O
Spittle-Fields	O
;	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
for	O
a	O
long	O
Time	O
suspected	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Harbour	O
of	O
Rogues	O
.	O
And	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
about	O
1	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
this	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
great	O
Noise	O
of	O
Quarrelling	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
inform	O
'd	O
the	O
Parish	O
Watch	O
and	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
came	O
back	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
when	O
a	O
Woman	O
squawl	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
in	O
a	O
vile	O
Manner	O
;	O
Ye	O
Son	O
of	O
a	O
Bitch	O
,	O
you	O
know	O
ye	O
I	O
can	O
hang	O
ye	O
when	O
I	O
will	O
;	O
-	O
How	O
often	O
have	O
I	O
saved	O
ye	O
from	O
the	O
Gallows	O
and	O
be	O
d	O
-	O
'd	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
-	O
you	O
have	O
well	O
enough	O
ye	O
Day	O
,	O
how	O
you	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
shelter	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
had	O
murder	O
'd	O
the	O
Man	O
upon	O
Tower-Hill	O
.	O
-	O
Hush	O
!	O
Hush	O
!	O
says	O
somebody	O
else	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
repeated	O
the	O
Words	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
it	O
was	O
nothing	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
true	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
broke	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-House	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Hemp	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
another	O
Place	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
contradicted	O
themselves	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
another	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Colston	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Hannah	B-pers
Humphries	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hampstead	B-place
;	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Radford	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
2	O
Shirts	O
,	O
a	O
Smock	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
.	O
June	O
3	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Cloths	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
September	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
Colston	O
,	O
upon	O
her	O
Confession	O
,	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
Radford	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
among	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Headcloths	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
sold	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Cook	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
stole	O
them	O
from	O
her	O
again	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
Hamphries	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
;	O
and	O
Colston	O
found	O
guilty	O
on	O
the	O
First	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
Second	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Oney	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Honey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Exton	I-pers
alias	I-pers
John	I-pers
Slum	I-pers
;	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
20	O
Hogs	O
,	O
value	O
27	O
l	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Harwood	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Sheep	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Phillip	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
3d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
8	O
Hogs	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Harwood	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
July	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
acquitted	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
and	O
3d	O
Indictments	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Ainsley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Savoy	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
15	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Elder	O
Wine	O
,	O
value	O
28	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Lewis	B-pers
Delafay	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
Decem	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Frost	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Queen-Hith	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Cox	O
lost	O
2	O
Spoons	O
,	O
markt	O
ICM	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
sold	O
to	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
2	O
Spoons	O
,	O
with	O
Mr	O
Cox	O
's	O
Mark	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
the	O
Spoons	O
were	O
given	O
him	O
by	O
his	O
Grand-Mother	O
Mary	B-pers
Curl	I-pers
(	O
his	O
Grand-Fathers	O
Name	O
being	O
John	O
)	O
for	O
a	O
Proof	O
of	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
his	O
Grand-Mother	O
and	O
her	O
Maid	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
her	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
who	O
all	O
confirm	O
'd	O
his	O
Assertion	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
the	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Rodd	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
17	O
Plates	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Fenton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Whipt	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Pinn	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Coals	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
;	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Ware-House	O
of	O
Ballard	B-pers
and	I-pers
Best	I-pers
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intention	O
to	O
steal	O
.	O
Guilty	O
both	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Aaron	B-pers
Depaz	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Jew	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Helens	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Avery	B-pers
Hobbs	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
Barbara	B-pers
Hobbs	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
drinking	O
in	O
my	O
Kitchin	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Spoon	O
lay	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
I	O
miss	O
it	O
.	O
Being	O
brought	O
back	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
private	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
the	O
Spoon	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
several	O
others	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
they	O
saw	O
him	O
deliver	O
the	O
Spoon	O
.	O
In	O
his	O
Defence	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
;	O
that	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
he	O
felt	O
somebody	O
ruffling	O
about	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
,	O
he	O
wonder	O
'd	O
to	O
find	O
the	O
Spoon	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Soloman	B-pers
de	I-pers
Costa	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Aaron	B-pers
Paris	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
some	O
Intervals	O
of	O
something	O
like	O
Madness	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Broker	O
in	O
Exchange-Alley	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
believ	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
as	O
honest	O
a	O
Man	O
as	O
any	O
of	O
that	O
Profession	O
.	O
That	O
Part	O
relating	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Lunacy	O
was	O
contradicted	O
by	O
others	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Dobbs	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Hilted	O
Sword	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Ash	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
John	O
Ash	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
Between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
within	O
20	O
Yards	O
of	O
that	O
End	O
of	O
Chancery-Lane	B-place
,	O
next	O
Fleet-street	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
jostled	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
snatch	O
away	O
my	O
Sword	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
get	O
5	O
Yards	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
nor	O
at	O
all	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Sight	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
stopt	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
seize	O
any	O
other	O
Person	O
,	O
for	O
indeed	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
Person	O
near	O
me	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
.	O
I	O
thrust	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
Sword-Cutlers	O
Shop	O
in	O
Fleet	O
Street	O
,	O
just	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
the	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
kept	O
him	O
there	O
;	O
a	O
Woman	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
brought	O
my	O
Sword	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
took	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
.	O
Being	O
asked	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
certain	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
rob	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
How	O
can	O
I	O
be	O
sure	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
has	O
got	O
a	O
Wig	O
now	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
wore	O
his	O
own	O
Hair	O
then	O
?	O
Being	O
further	O
demanded	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
positive	O
that	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
took	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
did	O
then	O
wear	O
a	O
Wig	O
or	O
not	O
;	O
What	O
Colour	O
his	O
Cloths	O
were	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
Coat	O
or	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
could	O
give	O
no	O
direct	O
Answer	O
.	O
But	O
however	O
he	O
was	O
positive	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
and	O
no	O
other	O
)	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
in	O
Chancery-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
thrust	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Sword-Cutlers	O
Shop	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
call	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Farish	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
sent	O
from	O
his	O
Shop	O
to	O
Serjeants-Inn	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
gone	O
but	O
about	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
Minutes	O
,	O
before	O
Word	O
was	O
brought	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
then	O
wore	O
a	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
close	O
shaved	O
.	O
That	O
there	O
was	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
for	O
near	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
before	O
,	O
a	O
great	O
Throng	O
of	O
People	O
at	O
Chancery-Lane	O
End	O
,	O
occasion	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
Stop	O
of	O
Coaches	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wist	O
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
.	O
Edmund	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
from	O
Temple-Bar	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
that	O
a	O
Stop	O
of	O
Coaches	O
,	O
had	O
gather	O
'd	O
a	O
Crowd	O
of	O
30	O
or	O
40	O
People	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Chancery-Lane	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
Chancery-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
follow	O
'd	O
at	O
a	O
small	O
Distance	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
,	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Fellows	O
came	O
shoving	O
along	O
,	O
pusht	O
down	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
People	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
towards	O
St.	O
Dunstan	O
's	O
Church	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
hardly	O
got	O
by	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
hastily	O
turning	O
about	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Reach	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
seiz	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
who	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
had	O
a	O
Pamphlet	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
)	O
and	O
thrust	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Cutler	O
's	O
Shop	O
.	O
A	O
Woman	O
brought	O
in	O
the	O
Sword	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
How	O
could	O
you	O
charge	O
me	O
with	O
taking	O
your	O
Sword	O
,	O
when	O
this	O
Women	O
has	O
found	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
O	O
says	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
do	O
ye	O
begin	O
to	O
be	O
saucy	O
?	O
I	O
'll	O
prosecute	O
you	O
closely	O
for	O
that	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Hayloft	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
upon	O
my	O
Coach-Box	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
Crowd	O
of	O
People	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
turn	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
Chancery-Lane	O
,	O
not	O
having	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
then	O
mist	O
his	O
Sword	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
not	O
far	O
off	O
,	O
a	O
Fellows	O
that	O
I	O
took	O
to	O
be	O
Pick	O
Pockets	O
,	O
they	O
thrust	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Crowd	O
and	O
run	O
off	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
turn	O
'd	O
about	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
seize	O
Davis	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
getting	O
away	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
-	O
They	O
went	O
in	O
my	O
Coach	O
to	O
the	O
Justices	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
told	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
of	O
these	O
two	O
idle	O
Fellows	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
wonder	O
'd	O
how	O
he	O
could	O
swear	O
so	O
hard	O
against	O
the	O
young	O
Man	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
no	O
more	O
valueto	O
hang	O
50	O
or	O
60	O
such	O
Fellows	O
,	O
than	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Wine	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Coles	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
with	O
the	O
Constable	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
when	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
brought	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
say	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
his	O
Sword	O
;	O
who	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
No	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
neither	O
did	O
I	O
see	O
it	O
on	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
none	O
by	O
but	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
took	O
bold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Sword	O
was	O
dropt	O
.	O
Several	O
Persons	O
of	O
Credit	O
appear	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
behalf	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Coffee	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Guines	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Oddy	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Walter	B-pers
Ray	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Coats	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hackney	B-place
:	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10d	O
.	O
Whipt	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Majoram	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Goose	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Mattocks	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Islington	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
17	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Harry	O
the	O
8th	O
's	O
Sixpence	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
George	B-pers
Allgood	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Robbing	O
him	O
of	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
coming	O
in	O
a	O
Chariot	O
along	O
the	O
Cross	B-place
Road	I-place
from	I-place
Newington	I-place
to	I-place
Islington	I-place
;	O
on	O
Monday	O
about	O
7	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
were	O
attack	O
'd	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
by	O
2	O
Persons	O
on	O
Horse-back	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
discern	O
the	O
Highway-mens	O
Faces	O
;	O
but	O
thought	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
rode	O
on	O
a	O
dark	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
on	O
a	O
grey	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Sells	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
himself	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
committed	O
this	O
Robbery	O
;	O
himself	O
on	O
a	O
grey	O
Mare	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
a	O
bey	O
Gelding	O
;	O
both	O
which	O
they	O
hired	O
on	O
the	O
preceding	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
,	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Horn	I-pers
in	O
Finsbury	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Horn	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
his	O
Remembrance	O
,	O
one	O
Sunday-Night	O
(	O
but	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
the	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
Month	O
)	O
he	O
let	O
such	O
a	O
Gelding	O
and	O
Mare	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
except	O
Sells	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Holman	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Crofts	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
he	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Leaden	O
Flower	O
Pots	O
,	O
value	O
4l	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hucks	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stoln	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
,	O
he	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Pewter	O
Ale-house	O
Pots	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Moor	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stoln	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
3d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
Cane	O
Chairs	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
April	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stoln	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Holman	O
,	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Vincent	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
White	I-pers
(	O
who	O
was	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
)	O
stole	O
a	O
Ladder	O
from	O
the	O
New	O
Buildings	O
in	O
Tyburn	O
Road	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
which	O
they	O
got	O
over	O
a	O
Wall	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Huck	O
's	O
Garden	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
two	O
Leaden	O
Pots	O
;	O
that	O
at	O
other	O
Times	O
they	O
stole	O
6	O
Chairs	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Huck	O
's	O
Summer	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
2	O
Ale-house	O
Pots	O
from	O
Joseph	O
Moor	O
;	O
all	O
which	O
(	O
as	O
White	O
depos	O
'd	O
)	O
they	O
sold	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Margaret	O
Crofts	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
gave	O
them	O
a	O
Groat	O
a	O
Pound	O
for	O
the	O
Alehouse	O
Pots	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
must	O
melt	O
them	O
for	O
fear	O
the	O
owners	O
Name	O
upon	O
them	O
should	O
occasion	O
a	O
Discovery	O
,	O
that	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Reason	O
she	O
order	O
'd	O
the	O
Leaden	O
Flower	O
Pots	O
which	O
were	O
gilded	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
cut	O
to	O
pieces	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
7	O
s.	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
weigh	O
'd	O
a	O
Hundred	O
Weight	O
.	O
She	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
of	O
her	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
of	O
the	O
Three	O
Indictments	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Holman	O
guilty	O
of	O
each	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Plowman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Gowns	O
,	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Marriot	I-pers
,	O
in	O
July	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pocket	O
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
and	O
Chain	O
,	O
3	O
Guineas	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutors	O
Wife	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
Coachman	O
set	O
me	O
down	O
at	O
my	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
his	O
Hand	O
to	O
help	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
.	O
My	O
Pocket	O
was	O
on	O
that	O
Side	O
next	O
him	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
stept	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
switch	O
as	O
if	O
some	O
part	O
of	O
my	O
Cloths	O
had	O
catch	O
'd	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
.	O
My	O
Maid	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
with	O
a	O
Candle	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
drive	O
away	O
without	O
his	O
Fare	O
.	O
I	O
mist	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
insisting	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
he	O
look	O
'd	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
We	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
;	O
my	O
Maid	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
pusht	O
his	O
Arm	O
forward	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
was	O
dirty	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
could	O
say	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
plain	O
that	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
Dirt	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
Coach	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
indeed	O
take	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
throw	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
thought	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
his	O
Corn	O
Bag	O
.	O
Then	O
turning	O
the	O
Pocket	O
upside	O
down	O
,	O
he	O
shook	O
my	O
Watch	O
and	O
Money	O
into	O
the	O
Street	O
upon	O
which	O
Words	O
arising	O
,	O
my	O
Husband	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutors	O
Maid	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
latter	O
Part	O
of	O
is	O
Evidence	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
began	O
to	O
be	O
uneasy	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Parlour	O
;	O
but	O
my	O
Wife	O
and	O
Maid	O
following	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
Nothing	O
,	O
but	O
taking	O
the	O
Candle	O
,	O
went	O
round	O
to	O
the	O
farther	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
open	O
'd	O
that	O
Door	O
,	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
look	O
under	O
the	O
Cushion	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
but	O
yet	O
having	O
an	O
Eye	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
stoop	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Times	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
my	O
thinking	O
lay	O
something	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Coach	O
Floor	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
immediately	O
holding	O
the	O
Candle	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
his	O
Hand	O
had	O
been	O
,	O
See	O
Sir	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
here	O
lies	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
a	O
Mob	O
began	O
to	O
gather	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
from	O
me	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
in	O
about	O
two	O
Hours	O
after	O
,	O
he	O
return	O
'd	O
and	O
demanded	O
his	O
Fare	O
.	O
At	O
one	O
Time	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
examin	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Money	O
dropt	O
into	O
his	O
Shoes	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
another	O
Time	O
that	O
they	O
fell	O
only	O
upon	O
his	O
Shoes	O
;	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
how	O
they	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Coach	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Several	O
Witnesses	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
3	O
Shirts	O
,	O
a	O
Frock	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Money	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Mony	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wollaston	I-pers
,	O
July	O
10	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
House	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
.	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
and	O
a	O
French	O
Six-pence	O
.	O
November	O
5	O
.	O
Daniel	O
Hill	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Baker	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
who	O
formerly	O
kept	O
a	O
Chandler	O
's	O
Shop	O
)	O
was	O
my	O
Customer	O
,	O
and	O
ow	O
'd	O
me	O
12	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
for	O
Bread	O
;	O
for	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
his	O
Note	O
to	O
be	O
paid	O
at	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Week	O
.	O
He	O
made	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Payments	O
and	O
then	O
neglected	O
for	O
several	O
Weeks	O
.	O
I	O
dunn	O
'd	O
him	O
often	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
put	O
me	O
off	O
with	O
one	O
Pretence	O
or	O
other	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
Middle	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
a	O
Friend	O
in	O
Hertfordshire	O
had	O
left	O
him	O
50	O
l.	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
early	O
next	O
Morning	O
to	O
fetch	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
beg	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
lend	O
him	O
my	O
great	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
Guines	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
'd	O
bear	O
him	O
Company	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
In	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Days	O
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
a	O
Letter	O
without	O
Date	O
or	O
Superscription	O
;	O
the	O
Contents	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
had	O
met	O
with	O
two	O
Highwaymen	O
upon	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
almost	O
killed	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
some	O
Weeks	O
before	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
come	O
Home	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
however	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
sure	O
to	O
have	O
my	O
Money	O
;	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
her	O
several	O
Times	O
,	O
and	O
once	O
or	O
twice	O
I	O
did	O
get	O
a	O
small	O
Matter	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
commonly	O
made	O
Excuses	O
,	O
and	O
appointed	O
me	O
to	O
call	O
another	O
Time	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
again	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
again	O
about	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
;	O
for	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
should	O
hardly	O
come	O
in	O
again	O
before	O
that	O
Time	O
.	O
And	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Hill	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
You	O
have	O
often	O
promis	O
'd	O
me	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Wine	O
when	O
I	O
paid	O
you	O
any	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
you	O
never	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
yet	O
;	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
would	O
bring	O
it	O
with	O
you	O
to	O
Night	O
,	O
for	O
now	O
my	O
Husband	O
is	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
I	O
have	O
most	O
need	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
a	O
Deed	O
of	O
Charity	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
appointed	O
return	O
'd	O
with	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Wine	O
.	O
I	O
knockt	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
look	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
.	O
What	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
to	O
Bed	O
?	O
If	O
you	O
are	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
come	O
to	O
Morrow	O
.	O
She	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
stay	O
a	O
Minute	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
Husband	O
's	O
Voice	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
certain	O
;	O
however	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
let	O
me	O
in	O
;	O
Now	O
,	O
Says	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
see	O
you	O
are	O
as	O
good	O
as	O
your	O
Word	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
drink	O
except	O
I	O
eat	O
a	O
Bit	O
first	O
;	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
'd	O
step	O
to	O
the	O
Chandler	O
's	O
Shop	O
and	O
fetch	O
a	O
Roll	O
and	O
Cheese	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
turning	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
glimpse	O
of	O
Somebody	O
go	O
from	O
her	O
Door	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
we	O
sat	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchin	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
a	O
Glass	O
or	O
two	O
.	O
Now	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
suppose	O
my	O
Husband	O
should	O
come	O
and	O
catch	O
us	O
,	O
-	O
Why	O
what	O
if	O
he	O
should	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
the	O
first	O
Time	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
seen	O
me	O
in	O
this	O
House	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
that	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
but	O
yet	O
he	O
'd	O
certainly	O
Murder	O
as	O
both	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
would	O
stay	O
no	O
longer	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
up	O
to	O
go	O
,	O
when	O
presently	O
Somebody	O
knock	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
O	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
my	O
Sister	O
Molly	O
,	O
step	O
up	O
Stairs	O
a	O
Minute	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
send	O
her	O
away	O
again	O
presently	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
dont	O
know	O
what	O
she	O
may	O
think	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
us	O
here	O
together	O
at	O
this	O
Time	O
of	O
Night	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Stair-head	O
,	O
she	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
bade	O
him	O
welcome	O
Home	O
;	O
G	O
-	O
D	O
-	O
ye	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
.	O
What	O
Business	O
have	O
ye	O
with	O
my	O
Wife	O
?	O
And	O
so	O
knock	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
with	O
his	O
Cane	O
,	O
and	O
beat	O
me	O
unmercifully	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
while	O
his	O
Wife	O
took	O
a	O
Couple	O
of	O
Spike	O
Nails	O
,	O
and	O
nail	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
-	O
Then	O
he	O
swore	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
my	O
Rings	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
pull	O
'd	O
then	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
rising	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
then	O
clos	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
him	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
his	O
Wife	O
catch	O
'd	O
up	O
a	O
knife	O
and	O
swore	O
she	O
'd	O
Murder	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
got	O
the	O
Knife	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Fire	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
fell	O
upon	O
me	O
again	O
,	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
by	O
abusing	O
me	O
thus	O
?	O
Do	O
you	O
intend	O
to	O
murder	O
me	O
?	O
If	O
I	O
have	O
done	O
you	O
any	O
wrong	O
,	O
send	O
for	O
an	O
Officer	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
surrender	O
my	O
self	O
peaceably	O
.	O
By	O
G	O
-	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
be	O
your	O
butcher	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
immediately	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
Note	O
for	O
50	O
l.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
'd	O
never	O
do	O
that	O
.	O
Why	O
then	O
look	O
ye	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
make	O
but	O
one	O
Word	O
with	O
you	O
;	O
if	O
you	O
wont	O
return	O
me	O
my	O
Note	O
for	O
12	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
give	O
me	O
another	O
Note	O
for	O
5	O
l.	O
You	O
shall	O
never	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
this	O
House	O
alive	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
that	O
Note	O
about	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
search	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
thrusting	O
his	O
Hand	O
into	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
French	O
Six-pence	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
all	O
I	O
had	O
about	O
me	O
then	O
.	O
And	O
then	O
they	O
let	O
me	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
White-Horse-Alley	B-place
in	I-place
Cow-Cross	I-place
to	O
apprehend	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
he	O
fell	O
to	O
Fighting	O
,	O
I	O
follow	O
'd	O
to	O
part	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Wife	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
the	O
Spikes	O
with	O
which	O
she	O
nail	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
kept	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
in	O
and	O
I	O
for	O
fear	O
she	O
intended	O
to	O
do	O
the	O
same	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
run	O
into	O
the	O
Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
forced	O
her	O
Husband	O
away	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
thus	O
made	O
his	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
about	O
3	O
Weeks	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
and	O
returning	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
about	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
to	O
my	O
Habitation	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
Light	O
below	O
,	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
but	O
No-body	O
answering	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
my	O
Wife	O
had	O
been	O
asleep	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
knock	O
'd	O
harder	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
with	O
only	O
one	O
Petticoat	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Gown	O
wrapt	O
.	O
loosely	O
about	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
surprised	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
Bottle	O
,	O
a	O
Glass	O
,	O
and	O
Watch	O
upon	O
the	O
Table	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
who	O
those	O
Things	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hill	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
he	O
?	O
says	O
I	O
:	O
Above	O
says	O
she	O
And	O
what	O
Business	O
has	O
he	O
there	O
with	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
Dark	O
?	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
ran	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
standing	O
in	O
his	O
Shirt	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
suppose	O
he	O
was	O
just	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
really	O
find	O
his	O
Cloaths	O
in	O
the	O
Dark	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
,	O
for	O
before	O
this	O
Accident	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
as	O
virtuous	O
a	O
Wife	O
as	O
any	O
in	O
England	O
But	O
having	O
a	O
Cane	O
in	O
my	O
Hand	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
hot	O
,	O
I	O
'd	O
cool	O
his	O
Courage	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
to	O
giving	O
him	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Strokes	O
across	O
the	O
Shoulders	O
,	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
House	O
;	O
however	O
,	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
put	O
on	O
his	O
Cloths	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
came	O
down	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
Constable	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
and	O
beg	O
'd	O
of	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
;	O
for	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
ruin	O
'd	O
,	O
if	O
ever	O
it	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Father-in-law	O
's	O
Ear	O
;	O
and	O
therefore	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
but	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
'd	O
give	O
me	O
any	O
Satisfaction	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
desir	O
'd	O
nothing	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
Bond	O
never	O
to	O
come	O
into	O
my	O
Wife	O
's	O
Company	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
his	O
Rings	O
for	O
a	O
Pledge	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
such	O
a	O
Bond	O
.	O
As	O
for	O
the	O
French	O
Six-pence	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
Mug	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
that	O
we	O
might	O
drink	O
and	O
be	O
Friends	O
at	O
parting	O
.	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Terry	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
Rings	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
how	O
could	O
you	O
swear	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
you	O
by	O
force	O
,	O
Why	O
,	O
says	O
be	O
again	O
,	O
If	O
Swearing	O
will	O
do	O
his	O
Business	O
he	O
shall	O
not	O
want	O
for	O
that	O
.	O
Others	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
If	O
hanging	O
will	O
do	O
his	O
Business	O
,	O
be	O
shant	O
want	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Several	O
Witnesses	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Williamson	B-pers
Goodbarn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
17	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Receipt	O
for	O
10	O
Shares	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Subscriptions	O
of	O
the	O
London	O
Assurance	O
,	O
value	O
92	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Bains	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
James	O
Bains	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
James	O
Bains	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Angel	B-place
Inn	I-place
behind	I-place
St.	I-place
Clement	I-place
Church	I-place
,	I-place
and	I-place
the	I-place
Chequer	I-place
Inn	I-place
upon	I-place
Dowgate-Hill	I-place
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
lodged	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
for	O
several	O
Months	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
10	O
Guineas	O
at	O
one	O
time	O
,	O
2	O
at	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
at	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
one	O
Tuesday	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
standing	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
Occasion	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
something	O
in	O
my	O
Scrutore	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
and	O
mist	O
my	O
Subscriptions	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
home	O
all	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Day	O
I	O
acquainted	O
my	O
Broker	O
with	O
my	O
Loss	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
his	O
Advice	O
,	O
I	O
stuck	O
up	O
Advertisements	O
in	O
Jonathan	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
Change-Alley	O
.	O
That	O
Evening	O
Mr.	O
Woodly	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
those	O
Subscriptions	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
since	O
seen	O
advertis	O
'd	O
;	O
by	O
his	O
Description	O
of	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
sold	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
judged	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Woodly	O
to	O
his	O
Bankers	O
,	O
on	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
Draught	O
.	O
The	O
Banker	O
told	O
us	O
that	O
he	O
paid	O
part	O
of	O
that	O
Draught	O
with	O
a	O
50	O
l.	O
Bank	O
Bill	O
(	O
Numb	O
.	O
211	O
)	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
in	O
Gold	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Bank	O
to	O
stop	O
Payment	O
of	O
that	O
Bill	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
home	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
another	O
Man	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
no	O
Notice	O
of	O
any	O
Loss	O
,	O
but	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
we	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
a	O
Bowl	O
of	O
Punch	O
together	O
.	O
He	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
with	O
all	O
his	O
Heart	O
.	O
While	O
the	O
Punch	O
was	O
making	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
privately	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Woodly	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
as	O
he	O
afterwards	O
told	O
me	O
)	O
mistrusting	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
Design	O
against	O
him	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
no	O
more	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Day	O
which	O
was	O
Thursday	O
,	O
about	O
noon	O
,	O
a	O
Porter	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
some	O
Gentleman	O
wanted	O
me	O
at	O
my	O
other	O
Inn	O
upon	O
Dowgate-Hill	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
must	O
come	O
immediately	O
.	O
I	O
suspected	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
Trick	O
in	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
desir	O
'd	O
John	O
Hitchcock	O
to	O
dog	O
that	O
Porter	O
where	O
ever	O
he	O
went	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
at	O
a	O
proper	O
Distance	O
.	O
The	O
Potter	O
instead	O
of	O
going	O
to	O
Dowgate-Hill	O
went	O
to	O
Charing-Cross	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
in	O
a	O
Trunk	O
Makers	O
Shop	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
in	O
the	O
Angel-Inn	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Woody	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Sheppard	O
and	O
another	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Woodly	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
sold	O
him	O
the	O
Subscriptions	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
Men	O
were	O
positive	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
In	O
order	O
to	O
secure	O
him	O
till	O
I	O
could	O
find	O
a	O
Justice	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
(	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
several	O
of	O
their	O
Houses	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Way	O
)	O
.	O
I	O
arrested	O
him	O
in	O
an	O
Action	O
of	O
40	O
l.	O
for	O
his	O
Board	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
my	O
Friend	O
Collet	O
,	O
having	O
first	O
(	O
by	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
accommodate	O
the	O
Difference	O
)	O
got	O
from	O
him	O
the	O
same	O
50	O
l.	O
Bank	O
Bill	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
receiv	O
'd	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Woodly	O
's	O
Banker	O
.	O
Whilst	O
he	O
was	O
under	O
this	O
Arrest	O
,	O
he	O
promis	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
me	O
any	O
Satisfaction	O
and	O
give	O
me	O
good	O
Security	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
'd	O
give	O
my	O
Friend	O
a	O
Note	O
on	O
demand	O
for	O
100	O
l.	O
I	O
'd	O
discharge	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
that	O
Night	O
withdrew	O
my	O
Action	O
for	O
40	O
l.	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
arrested	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
10	O
d.	O
John	B-pers
Hitchcock	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Guineas	O
at	O
three	O
Times	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
when	O
I	O
first	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
pressing	O
closely	O
,	O
he	O
confest	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
himself	O
with	O
a	O
Key	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
opened	O
Mr.	O
Bain	O
's	O
Scrutore	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
17	O
Guineas	O
at	O
3	O
Times	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
another	O
Time	O
took	O
the	O
Subscriptions	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
ask	O
him	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
if	O
Mr.	O
Bains	O
's	O
Sister	O
,	O
or	O
his	O
Maid	O
were	O
at	O
all	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Person	O
but	O
my	O
self	O
that	O
was	O
any	O
Way	O
Concern	O
'd	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
God	O
forbid	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
accuse	O
the	O
Innocent	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
300l	O
.	O
I	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
And	O
yet	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
Bains	O
's	O
Sister	O
did	O
give	O
him	O
that	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
those	O
Subscriptions	O
,	O
and	O
assured	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Familiarity	O
betwixt	O
himself	O
and	O
her	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Conner	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
himself	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Scrutore	O
with	O
a	O
Key	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
Subscriptions	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
neither	O
Mr.	O
Bain	O
's	O
Sister	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
other	O
Person	O
had	O
any	O
Hand	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
thus	O
made	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Guineas	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
own	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
Subscriptions	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Woodly	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
given	O
me	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Bains	O
's	O
Sister	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
saying	O
one	O
Day	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
wonder	O
'd	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
receiv	O
'd	O
Money	O
from	O
my	O
Father	O
as	O
usual	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
help	O
me	O
to	O
something	O
that	O
would	O
fetch	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
Subscriptions	O
which	O
she	O
could	O
easily	O
come	O
at	O
;	O
for	O
she	O
was	O
intrusted	O
with	O
the	O
whole	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
all	O
the	O
Keys	O
.	O
The	O
Monday	O
before	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
his	O
Sister	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Account	O
of	O
his	O
having	O
lost	O
the	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
sent	O
the	O
Maid	O
away	O
before	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
Suspicion	O
.	O
He	O
knew	O
that	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
some	O
great	O
Freedoms	O
betwixt	O
me	O
and	O
his	O
Sister	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
press	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
marry	O
her	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
Night	O
I	O
was	O
arrested	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
some	O
mention	O
to	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Favours	O
she	O
had	O
granted	O
me	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
rather	O
have	O
given	O
100	O
l.	O
than	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
said	O
any	O
such	O
Thing	O
of	O
his	O
Sister	O
.	O
Since	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
under	O
this	O
Trouble	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
requir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
procure	O
his	O
Sister	O
to	O
appear	O
upon	O
my	O
Tryal	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
has	O
refus	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
To	O
this	O
Mr.Bains	O
thus	O
reply	O
'd	O
.	O
My	O
Sister	O
never	O
was	O
trusted	O
with	O
the	O
keys	O
of	O
my	O
Scrutore	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
least	O
Affair	O
betwixt	O
her	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
dont	O
believe	O
that	O
he	O
ever	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
touch	O
'd	O
her	O
Lips	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
had	O
no	O
Opportunities	O
of	O
being	O
alone	O
together	O
.	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
her	O
away	O
because	O
she	O
was	O
saucy	O
;	O
for	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
sent	O
the	O
Maid	O
away	O
,	O
truly	O
my	O
Sister	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
Maid	O
went	O
,	O
she	O
'd	O
go	O
too	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
might	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
she	O
took	O
Huff	O
,	O
and	O
away	O
she	O
went	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
some	O
Freedoms	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Indeed	O
,	O
(	O
I	O
wonder	O
you	O
should	O
say	O
so	O
of	O
my	O
Sister	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
dont	O
believe	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
ever	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
such	O
Thing	O
in	O
her	O
Life	O
.	O
Other	O
Witnesses	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
Bains	O
's	O
Sister	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Subscriptions	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
his	O
Note	O
or	O
do	O
any	O
Thing	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
Matter	O
up	O
rather	O
than	O
his	O
Father	O
should	O
hear	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Notice	O
was	O
left	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Bains	O
for	O
his	O
Sister	O
to	O
appear	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
produce	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
.	O
Several	O
Witnesses	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Pinner	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Picart	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Merregeot	I-pers
,	O
November	O
17	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Blewit	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Layton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
two	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
2	O
Suits	O
of	O
Laced	O
Head-cloths	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
November	O
7	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
an	O
Apothecary	O
;	O
Blewit	O
was	O
his	O
Journeyman	O
and	O
Layton	O
a	O
Cobler	O
that	O
clean	O
'd	O
Shoes	O
for	O
the	O
Family	O
.	O
Between	O
4	O
and	O
5	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Evening	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
order	O
'd	O
Blewit	O
to	O
carry	O
some	O
Vials	O
of	O
Physick	O
to	O
a	O
Patient	O
at	O
Islington	O
.	O
Blewit	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Black	O
Lyon	O
Ale-house	O
,	O
known	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Follards	I-pers
;	O
from	O
whence	O
he	O
sent	O
Layton	O
with	O
the	O
Physic	O
,	O
who	O
deliver	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
mean	O
Time	O
,	O
a	O
Woman	O
enquiring	O
for	O
Blewit	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecuor	O
's	O
Maid	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Ale-house	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Key	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
went	O
in	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
shut	O
the	O
Maid	O
out	O
,	O
they	O
staid	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Ale-house	O
where	O
Layton	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
Home	O
about	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
that	O
his	O
House	O
had	O
been	O
rob	O
'd	O
.	O
Layton	O
confest	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
Blewit	O
finding	O
a	O
Ladder	O
,	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
Wall	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Door	O
being	O
open	O
they	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
Blewit	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Layton	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
John	O
Blewit	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Scales	O
,	O
a	O
Smock	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
Pound	O
of	O
Brass	O
Weights	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	O
Rogers	O
,	O
October	O
2	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
suspect	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
till	O
Vandereikin	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
try	O
'd	O
this	O
Session	O
for	O
another	O
Felony	O
)	O
impeach	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Gore	O
;	O
before	O
whom	O
he	O
confest	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Scales	O
and	O
Weights	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
Vandereikin	O
who	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
his	O
Mistresses	O
Smock	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hatch	I-pers
(	O
a	O
Woman	O
of	O
the	O
Town	O
)	O
but	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
must	O
have	O
it	O
again	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
Time	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Agnes	B-pers
,	I-pers
the	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Richard	I-pers
Layton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Apron	O
.	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
September	O
:	O
8	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Preston	I-pers
.	O
November	O
16	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Gurnell	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
.	O
October	O
28	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Moses	B-pers
Gladwin	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Golding	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
24	O
Silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Slater	I-pers
,	O
December	O
8	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Dukes	I-pers
,	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
cheapen	O
'd	O
the	O
Handkerchiefs	O
at	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
Shop	O
.	O
The	O
Woman	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
one	O
End	O
of	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Man	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Man	O
with	O
his	O
other	O
Hand	O
,	O
draw	O
a	O
Parcel	O
from	O
under	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
held	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
betwixt	O
his	O
Legs	O
.	O
I	O
let	O
them	O
go	O
out	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
who	O
pursued	O
them	O
with	O
a	O
Cry	O
of	O
Stopthief	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
presently	O
brought	O
back	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Bolten	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Bennet	O
confirm	O
'd	O
this	O
Evidence	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
[	O
Golding	O
:	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Freckwell	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Susan	B-pers
Cotten	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
11	O
Yards	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
.	O
November	O
25	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hals	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
defrauding	O
Joseph	B-pers
Mosthouse	I-pers
of	O
4	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
by	O
selling	O
him	O
two	O
Brunswick	O
Lottery	O
Tickets	O
,	O
in	O
July	O
1720	O
,	O
in	O
Reality	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
such	O
Lottery	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Defendant	O
was	O
not	O
any	O
Way	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Fraud	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
acted	O
in	O
the	O
Capacity	O
of	O
a	O
Broker	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Prior	I-pers
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Prior	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Box	O
Iron	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Leg	O
of	O
Mutton	O
.	O
December	O
4	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Abigail	B-pers
Foot	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Bishopsgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
l.	O
16	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Herbert	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Wilful	O
and	O
corrupt	O
Perjury	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Colecraft	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Burgess	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
40	O
Bobbins	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
Pound	O
of	O
Silk	O
wound	O
on	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Stallard	I-pers
.	O
November	O
26	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
Second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Gowns	O
4	O
Petticoats	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Venables	I-pers
,	O
April	O
26	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
each	O
.	O
Value	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Whoran	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Redman	B-pers
Dearing	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Key	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Watch	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
l.	O
2	O
Watch	O
Cafes	O
,	O
a	O
Coat	O
and	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
November	O
25	O
.	O
Each	O
guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Richard	B-pers
Perrin	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Coat	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
November	O
2	O
Richard	O
Perrin	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
over	O
Stepney-Fields	B-place
,	O
about	O
Seven	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
met	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
passing	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
knockt	O
me	O
down	O
with	O
a	O
Club	O
as	O
thick	O
as	O
my	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
Coat	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
presently	O
recover	O
'd	O
my	O
self	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
crying	O
Stopthief	O
.	O
He	O
just	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Sight	O
,	O
by	O
turning	O
the	O
Road	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
stopt	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Baston	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
running	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Lane	O
's	O
End	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
Man	O
that	O
impos	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
whereof	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
running	O
from	O
a	O
Bailiff	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
supposing	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Rogue	O
,	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
reprehend	O
him	O
,	O
whereof	O
he	O
broke	O
my	O
Head	O
.	O
Other	O
Witnesses	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Purpose	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drop	O
the	O
Coat	O
.	O
The	O
Club	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
little	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
John	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Pease	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
two	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
4	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
November	O
11	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
about	O
7	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
dash	O
'd	O
his	O
Hand	O
through	O
the	O
Glass	O
of	O
the	O
Shop-window	O
,	O
snatch	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
ran	O
across	O
the	O
Way	O
into	O
a	O
dark	O
Entry	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
dropt	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
afterwards	O
found	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
,	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Wooden	O
Quilt	O
,	O
with	O
9	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Silk	O
and	O
Silver	O
Twist	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bowden	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Heatstone	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Easton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
House	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Mullet	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
2	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
3	O
Broad	O
Pieces	O
,	O
7	O
Guineas	O
and	O
18	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
Katherine	B-pers
Mullet	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
my	O
Lodger	O
about	O
a	O
Month	O
.	O
When	O
one	O
Night	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
Bed	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Noise	O
below	O
Stairs	O
where	O
my	O
Chest	O
stood	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
who	O
's	O
there	O
!	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
'T	O
is	O
I	O
Landlady	O
I	O
am	O
only	O
looking	O
for	O
a	O
Pot	O
to	O
warm	O
some	O
Beer	O
.	O
By	O
and	O
by	O
he	O
comes	O
up	O
into	O
my	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
takes	O
all	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Closer	O
,	O
cut	O
a	O
Slice	O
of	O
Mutton	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
Stairs	O
again	O
;	O
next	O
Morning	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
Chest	O
broke	O
open	O
and	O
my	O
Money	O
gone	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
thus	O
made	O
his	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
what	O
I	O
am	O
charged	O
with	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
honestly	O
.	O
For	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
lodge	O
with	O
this	O
old	O
Women	O
,	O
she	O
fell	O
in	O
Love	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
has	O
got	O
a	O
Husband	O
indeed	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
's	O
at	O
Carolina	O
.	O
One	O
Day	O
she	O
invited	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
Stepney	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
Treat	O
of	O
Cakes	O
and	O
Ale	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
;	O
and	O
while	O
we	O
were	O
drinking	O
together	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
Occasion	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Necessary	O
House	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
farther	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
Yard	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
no	O
sooner	O
got	O
thither	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
after	O
me	O
-	O
and	O
we	O
were	O
very	O
merry	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
Rings	O
for	O
my	O
Pains	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
came	O
home	O
again	O
.	O
At	O
Night	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
follow	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
several	O
hot	O
Pots	O
together	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
undrest	O
herself	O
,	O
came	O
into	O
Bed	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
because	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
satisfied	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
swore	O
this	O
Robbery	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
an	O
ill	O
Thing	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Ivory	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
at	O
Stepney	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
Ale	O
and	O
Cakes	O
,	O
and	O
Pigeon	O
Pyes	O
together	O
;	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
Son	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
come	O
to	O
make	O
merry	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Necessary	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
follow	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
talking	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
in	O
.	O
They	O
came	O
away	O
together	O
,	O
the	O
walking	O
with	O
her	O
Arm	O
round	O
his	O
Neck	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Burt	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Newstead	I-pers
were	O
,	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Newstead	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
did	O
steal	O
2	O
Dishes	O
,	O
10	O
Plates	O
and	O
a	O
Sauce-Pan	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Tarlton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
1724	O
.	O
Henry	O
Burt	O
was	O
2d	O
of	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
with	O
Thomas	O
Newstead	O
and	O
Mary	O
Newstead	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
and	O
20	O
Pound	O
of	O
Feathers	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
North	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
Newstead	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Burt	O
guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictment	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Underwood	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Wastecoat	O
,	O
a	O
half	O
Smock	O
,	O
and	O
14	O
Pound	O
of	O
Candles	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
October	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Coach	O
Seats	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Denny	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Drydell	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Meadows	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Galter	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Simmons	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Cloths	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
2	O
Wigs	O
,	O
a	O
Hat	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Horn	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
October	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Cumbert	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Gowns	O
,	O
2	O
Petticoats	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ruth	B-pers
Denton	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Clerk	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Rachael	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coral	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Ditow	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Stephen	B-pers
Tuner	I-pers
on	O
the	O
River	O
Thames	O
,	O
(	O
being	O
a	O
Common	O
Highway	O
)	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
Wastecoat	O
,	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
The	O
King	O
's	O
Witnesses	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
in	O
drink	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
invited	O
him	O
to	O
lie	O
on	O
Board	O
his	O
Vessel	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
undrest	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
arose	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
threaten	O
'd	O
to	O
throw	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
over	O
Board	O
.	O
In	O
his	O
Defence	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
mistook	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Cloaths	O
for	O
his	O
own	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Stringer	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Cornwall	I-pers
of	O
Wapping	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
(	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hartwell	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Hartly	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Nowers	I-pers
)	O
four	O
Turkey-Cocks	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Turkey	O
Hen	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
The	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jeffery	B-pers
Adamson	I-pers
,	O
December	O
3	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Shed	O
in	O
Black-Horse-Alley	B-place
Nightingale-Lane	I-place
;	O
and	O
being	O
apprehended	O
,	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
John	O
Cornwall	O
of	O
Shadwell	B-place
,	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
(	O
with	O
Hartwell	O
and	O
Nowers	O
)	O
seventeen	O
Turkey	O
Cocks	O
and	O
two	O
Hens	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
December	O
5	O
.	O
The	O
Witnesses	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
On	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
December	O
;	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
the	O
Fowls	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Warehouse	O
.	O
Whereupon	O
he	O
put	O
a	O
new	O
Padlock	O
to	O
his	O
Door	O
;	O
but	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
Instant	O
,	O
the	O
Watchman	O
sending	O
part	O
of	O
that	O
Padlock	O
ript	O
open	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
Time	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Rogues	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
wrench	O
the	O
Padlock	O
open	O
,	O
he	O
filled	O
it	O
with	O
Gun-powder	O
,	O
blew	O
it	O
to	O
Pieces	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
enter	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
bolted	O
the	O
Door	O
within-side	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
the	O
Watchman	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
but	O
his	O
two	O
Companions	O
escaped	O
.	O
And	O
they	O
left	O
two	O
Sacks	O
behind	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
they	O
stole	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Lyter	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
thither	O
to	O
put	O
the	O
Turkeys	O
in	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Forden	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coat	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Headly	I-pers
November	O
6	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Acton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
a	O
Night-cap	O
,	O
a	O
Bobbin	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Ounce	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
November	O
4	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
Somebody	O
got	O
over	O
Mr.	O
Adam	O
's	O
Wall	O
,	O
threw	O
up	O
his	O
Sash	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
run-a-way	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
pursued	O
with	O
a	O
Cry	O
of	O
Stopthief	O
;	O
which	O
some	O
others	O
hearing	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
,	O
they	O
pursued	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Dorrington	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Second	O
Volume	O
of	O
Caryl	O
upon	O
Job	O
Folio	O
;	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
the	O
First	O
Volume	O
of	O
Rushworth	O
's	O
Collections	O
,	O
Folio	O
;	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Green	I-pers
.	O
October	O
25	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Green	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Servant	O
shutting	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Fellow	O
had	O
taken	O
two	O
Books	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
pursued	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Books	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Baxter	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
Books	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Plates	O
,	O
2	O
Porringers	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
,	O
November	O
20	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sheet	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Blanket	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
our	O
Sovereign	B-pers
Lord	I-pers
the	I-pers
King	I-pers
.	O
November	O
13	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
the	B-place
Barracks	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Savoy	I-place
;	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
her	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
off	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Jarvis	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Mackeness	I-pers
,	O
November	O
1	O
.	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Tomson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Iron	O
Poker	O
.	O
value	O
5	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Broom	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
High	O
Treason	O
,	O
in	O
Coining	O
10	O
counterfeit	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
10	O
counterfeit	O
half	O
Guineas	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
.	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
making	O
10	O
counterfeit	O
Schelings	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
April	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Ellard	I-pers
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
West	I-pers
.	O
Acquit	O
.	O
Frances	B-pers
Boswell	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Slippers	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nockels	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Chandler	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Gates	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Frock	O
and	O
Wastecoat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
Guilty	O
both	O
.	O
4	O
s	O
10	O
d.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Moses	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Jew	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
.	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
November	O
22	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Boswell	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
Sheets	O
,	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
October	O
13	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Love	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
.	O
August	O
3	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Colston	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Costan	I-pers
,	O
was	O
a	O
3d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Eustace	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Ring	O
,	O
a	O
Buckle	O
and	O
16	O
Guineas	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Hansly	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Hausly	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
James	B-pers
Major	I-pers
14	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Vincent	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
returning	O
from	O
Transportation	O
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Pretty	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
(	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Lewin	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Munday	I-pers
)	O
2	O
Necks	O
,	O
2	O
Breasts	O
,	O
2	O
Shoulders	O
,	O
2	O
Loins	O
and	O
1	O
Leg	O
of	O
Mutton	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
The	O
Printer	O
of	O
the	O
News	O
Paper	O
,	O
intitled	O
the	O
Postman	O
,	O
being	O
required	O
to	O
attend	O
this	O
Court	O
,	O
on	O
Account	O
of	O
his	O
Printing	O
and	O
publishing	O
in	O
his	O
Postman	O
of	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
2	O
d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
Paper	O
intitled	O
the	O
Cafe	O
of	O
Foster	B-pers
Snow	I-pers
,	O
&	O
c.	O
which	O
was	O
subscribed	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Foster	O
Snow	O
,	O
and	O
representing	O
his	O
Cafe	O
very	O
different	O
from	O
what	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Evidence	O
given	O
at	O
his	O
Tryal	O
;	O
thereby	O
to	O
extenuate	O
his	O
own	O
Guilt	O
,	O
and	O
reflect	O
upon	O
the	O
Justice	O
of	O
the	O
Nation	O
;	O
the	O
said	O
Printer	O
acknowledging	O
himself	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Printer	O
and	O
Publisher	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Libel	O
was	O
committed	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
called	O
upon	O
to	O
discover	O
the	O
Person	O
from	O
whom	O
he	O
received	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
to	O
give	O
Evidence	O
;	O
upon	O
his	O
Promise	O
so	O
to	O
do	O
if	O
required	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
his	O
humble	O
Submission	O
and	O
begging	O
Pardon	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
for	O
his	O
Offence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
Katherine	B-pers
Blackbourn	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Sanders	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Pemble	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
.	O
The	O
4	O
last	O
were	O
former	O
Convicts	O
.	O
John	B-pers
James	I-pers
find	O
20	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
;	O
for	O
extorting	O
Money	O
from	O
.	O
Aaron	B-pers
de	I-pers
Costa	I-pers
Abendena	I-pers
;	O
upon	O
Pretence	O
of	O
concealing	O
the	O
Crime	O
of	O
Buggery	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
convicted	O
last	O
Sessions	O
at	O
Guild-Hall	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
followeth	O
;	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
10.	O
Richard	B-pers
Scurrier	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ashford	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hemp	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
,	O
Moses	B-pers
Gladwin	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Golding	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Vincent	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Golding	I-pers
pleaded	O
her	O
Belly	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
being	O
impanneld	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
with	O
quick	O
Child	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
,	O
7.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Ebden	I-pers
n	O
John	B-pers
Rodd	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
,	O
Heavy	O
Carter	O
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
Martha	B-pers
Fenn	I-pers
,	O
Alice	B-pers
Calorast	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Barges	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
6	O
.	O
Carr	O
Halbert	O
,	O
Aaron	B-pers
Depaz	I-pers
,	O
Katherine	B-pers
Blackbourn	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Sanders	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Pemble	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
.	O
The	O
4	O
last	O
were	O
former	O
Convicts	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
,	O
60.	O
William	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
Katherine	B-pers
Dunster	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Bowers	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Marshal	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Pew	I-pers
.	O
Hainsworth	O
Dent	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
Ann	O
Hall	O
,	O
Isabel	O
Hall	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Showbridge	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Louingham	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Shales	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Baily	O
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Fielder	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harrop	I-pers
,	O
Hannah	B-pers
Colston	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Colton	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Ansly	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Tucker	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Pinx	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Aday	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hoiman	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Plowman	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Planne	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Layton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Blewit	I-pers
Agnes	B-pers
Layton	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Whoran	I-pers
,	O
Redman	O
Dearing	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Oury	I-pers
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Exton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Astill	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Easton	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Burt	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Simmons	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Horn	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hadsex	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Stringer	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Cornwall	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Fordex	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Dorrington	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Chandler	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Moses	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Boswell	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
.	O
James	B-pers
Byrn	I-pers
to	O
suffer	O
one	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
John	B-pers
James	I-pers
find	O
20	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
;	O
for	O
extorting	O
Money	O
from	O
.	O
Aaron	B-pers
de	I-pers
Costa	I-pers
Abendena	I-pers
;	O
upon	O
Pretence	O
of	O
concealing	O
the	O
Crime	O
of	O
Buggery	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
convicted	O
last	O
Sessions	O
at	O
Guild-Hall	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
A	O
Water	O
that	O
perfectly	O
cures	O
the	O
Itch	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
itching	O
Humour	O
in	O
a	O
short	O
time	O
,	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Bottle	O
.	O
Prepared	O
and	O
sold	O
only	O
by	O
A	O
.	O
Drawing	O
Chymist	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
and	O
Ball	O
in	O
George	O
Court	O
in	O
St.	O
John	O
's	O
Lane	O
by	O
Hick's-Hall	O
,	O
near	O
West-Smithfield	O
.	O
Where	O
also	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
Spirits	O
of	O
Scurvy-Grass	O
purging	O
and	O
plain	O
at	O
8	O
d.	O
a	O
Bottle	O
.	O
And	O
a	O
Remedy	O
generally	O
successful	O
in	O
easing	O
the	O
violent	O
Pain	O
of	O
the	O
Teeth	O
,	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
Just	O
Published	O
.	O
A	O
Compleat	O
Collection	O
of	O
Remarkable	O
Tryals	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
Notorious	O
Malefactors	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Sessions-House	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Baily	O
,	O
for	O
near	O
Fifty	O
Years	O
past	O
:	O
Together	O
with	O
a	O
particular	O
Account	O
of	O
their	O
Behaviour	O
under	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
and	O
their	O
Dying	O
Speeches	O
.	O
Faithfully	O
collected	O
from	O
the	O
Book	O
of	O
Tryals	O
,	O
and	O
Papers	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Allen	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Wikes	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Lorrain	O
,	O
Ordinaries	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
first	O
Printing	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
down	O
to	O
this	O
present	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
other	O
Authentick	O
Narratives	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
Brotherton	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
over-against	O
the	O
Royal-Exchange	O
,	O
Cornhill	O
.	O
Price	O
Bound	O
Ten	O
Shillings	O
.	O
Just	O
publish	O
'd	O
the	O
Second	O
Edition	O
of	O
THE	O
Life	O
and	O
Actions	O
of	O
LEWIS	B-pers
DOMINIQUE	I-pers
CARTOUCHE	I-pers
,	O
the	O
famous	O
French	O
Robber	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
broken	O
alive	O
upon	O
the	O
Wheel	O
at	O
Paris	O
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
Giving	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
his	O
Education	O
in	O
the	O
College	O
of	O
Jusuits	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Pranks	O
he	O
play	O
'd	O
there	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
several	O
Robberies	O
he	O
committed	O
alone	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
his	O
turning	O
Thief-taker	O
;	O
how	O
after	O
several	O
and	O
various	O
escapes	O
he	O
put	O
himself	O
at	O
the	O
Head	O
of	O
a	O
Gang	O
,	O
which	O
desy	O
'd	O
the	O
publick	O
Justice	O
of	O
France	O
above	O
Seven	O
Years	O
;	O
with	O
a	O
particular	O
Relation	O
how	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Manner	O
of	O
his	O
Execution	O
.	O
Also	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
his	O
bold	O
and	O
undaunted	O
Behaviour	O
under	O
Consinement	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
Scaffold	O
.	O
The	O
whole	O
being	O
a	O
Series	O
of	O
Adventures	O
and	O
Incidents	O
,	O
remarkable	O
,	O
entertaining	O
and	O
full	O
of	O
variety	O
.	O
Translated	O
from	O
the	O
Original	O
just	O
arriv	O
'd	O
from	O
France	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
Roberts	O
in	O
Warwick-Lane	O
.	O
Where	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
,	O
CARTOUCHE	O
or	O
the	O
ROBBERS	O
,	O
a	O
Comedy	O
.	O
As	O
it	O
was	O
Acted	O
many	O
Times	O
with	O
great	O
Applause	O
at	O
Paris	O
.	O
By	O
Mousieur	O
Le	O
Grand	O
.	O
Comedian	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
.	O
Translated	O
from	O
the	O
French	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
THe	O
Town	O
being	O
still	O
imposed	O
upon	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
publick	O
Prints	O
daily	O
cramm	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
fulsome	O
Praises	O
of	O
infallible	O
Specificks	O
,	O
Areana	O
's	O
,	O
Italian	O
Bolus	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
other	O
Quack	O
Medicines	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
thought	O
necessary	O
to	O
caution	O
the	O
Unwary	O
against	O
them	O
;	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Danger	O
that	O
the	O
judicious	O
Part	O
of	O
Mankind	O
should	O
be	O
deceived	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
Why	O
are	O
these	O
Medicines	O
exposed	O
to	O
Sale	O
at	O
Toys-Shops	O
,	O
unless	O
to	O
skreen	O
the	O
Preparers	O
of	O
such	O
notorious	O
Cheats	O
from	O
the	O
Resentment	O
of	O
injured	O
People	O
?	O
Are	O
the	O
bell	O
Physicians	O
,	O
or	O
most	O
eminent	O
Surgeons	O
,	O
ashamed	O
of	O
their	O
Prescriptions	O
and	O
Preparations	O
?	O
Must	O
the	O
Severe	O
Affiction	O
of	O
an	O
Impostor	O
's	O
Pocket	O
induce	O
Men	O
to	O
ruin	O
their	O
Constitutions	O
?	O
Can	O
we	O
believe	O
that	O
Charity	O
for	O
others	O
deplorable	O
Circumstances	O
will	O
prevail	O
on	O
such	O
a	O
one	O
to	O
publish	O
what	O
he	O
dare	O
not	O
own	O
?	O
Are	O
not	O
the	O
Degrees	O
of	O
the	O
Veneral	O
Disease	O
various	O
?	O
Are	O
not	O
Mens	O
Constitutions	O
vastly	O
different	O
?	O
Was	O
there	O
ever	O
a	O
Remedy	O
always	O
infallible	O
?	O
Do	O
not	O
the	O
same	O
things	O
agree	O
with	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
prove	O
Poison	O
to	O
another	O
?	O
Or	O
are	O
there	O
not	O
a	O
sufficient	O
Number	O
of	O
able	O
and	O
experienced	O
Physicians	O
and	O
surgons	O
,	O
who	O
practice	O
in	O
Publick	O
,	O
and	O
whose	O
Credit	O
depend	O
upon	O
their	O
skill	O
and	O
Success	O
?	O
The	O
most	O
ingenions	O
Prescription	O
may	O
sometimes	O
fail	O
:	O
And	O
will	O
any	O
one	O
depend	O
upon	O
the	O
Apparatus	O
,	O
or	O
an	O
unknown	O
Author	O
,	O
who	O
never	O
sies	O
you	O
,	O
or	O
consults	O
your	O
Distemper	O
,	O
and	O
who	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
has	O
sufficiently	O
cheated	O
you	O
,	O
will	O
refer	O
you	O
to	O
the	O
Advice	O
of	O
some	O
able	O
Surgeon	O
?	O
Shall	O
a	O
Man	O
's	O
Misery	O
incline	O
him	O
to	O
he	O
credulous	O
,	O
and	O
prevail	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
make	O
himself	O
more	O
miserable	O
?	O
Or	O
can	O
any	O
one	O
foolishly	O
fear	O
that	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
will	O
expose	O
his	O
Patient	O
?	O
For	O
your	O
own	O
Sales	O
,	O
therefore	O
apply	O
to	O
some	O
Man	O
of	O
skill	O
and	O
Probity	O
who	O
appears	O
to	O
justify	O
his	O
Practice	O
,	O
and	O
answer	O
for	O
its	O
Success	O
;	O
such	O
a	O
one	O
invites	O
you	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
on	O
the	O
Right-hand	O
in	O
Crane-Court	O
near	O
Fetter	O
Lane	O
