TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Jail-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
;	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
13th	O
,	O
14th	O
,	O
and	O
15th	O
,	O
Days	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Twelfth	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
GEORGE	B-pers
MERTTINS	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Rt	O
.	O
Hon	O
.	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
Raymond	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Price	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
Serjeant	O
at	O
Law	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
JURORS	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
The	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Row	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
Gilbert	B-pers
Whitaker	I-pers
,	O
Nathanael	B-pers
Bently	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Sanderson	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
Caleb	B-pers
Flower	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Wall	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
,	O
Roger	B-pers
Renshaw	I-pers
,	O
Timothy	B-pers
Branwell	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ingram	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Tame	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Richmond	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Lacy	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Gilmore	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Frith	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Durson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Timbrell	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Ben	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sams	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
follows	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Day	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
24	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
48	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Burnham	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Gibbons	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dun	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
1	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Value	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Belcher	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Wint	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Box	O
with	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Head-Cloaths	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
five	O
Tea-Spoons	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Tongs	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
gilt	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
eight	O
Yards	O
of	O
Velvet	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
with	O
other	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
to	O
near	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
100	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
about	O
a	O
Year	O
ago	O
,	O
a	O
Box	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
Bristol	B-place
by	O
the	O
Waggon	O
,	O
directed	O
For	O
Mrs.	O
Thomson	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
left	O
till	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
.	O
And	O
Mary	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
going	O
to	O
the	O
Inn	O
,	O
and	O
enquiring	O
for	O
a	O
Box	O
so	O
directed	O
,	O
the	O
Carrier	O
deliver	O
'd	O
that	O
Box	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
took	O
it	O
home	O
to	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
and	O
they	O
together	O
broke	O
it	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
in	O
it	O
several	O
valuable	O
Goods	O
,	O
about	O
40	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
some	O
Bonds	O
and	O
other	O
Writings	O
.	O
They	O
pawned	O
and	O
sold	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
spent	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
burnt	O
the	O
Writings	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
London	O
;	O
where	O
quarrelling	O
about	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
they	O
let	O
slip	O
some	O
Words	O
that	O
discover	O
'd	O
'em	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Particulars	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
The	O
Woman	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
expected	O
a	O
Box	O
to	O
come	O
by	O
the	O
Bristol	O
Carrier	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
had	O
brought	O
this	O
Box	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
did	O
not	O
belong	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
carry	O
'd	O
it	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Inn	O
;	O
but	O
her	O
Husband	O
swore	O
he	O
'd	O
stab	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
.	O
The	O
Man	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
thought	O
the	O
Box	O
had	O
been	O
his	O
Wife	O
's	O
;	O
for	O
having	O
been	O
lately	O
marry	O
'd	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
such	O
a	O
Box	O
,	O
with	O
Money	O
and	O
Goods	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
coming	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
Waggon	O
.	O
The	O
Box	O
being	O
deliver	O
'd	O
to	O
Mary	O
Thomson	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
directed	O
the	O
Jury	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
did	O
not	O
feloniously	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
,	O
in	O
defrauding	O
Ann	B-pers
Harman	I-pers
,	O
by	O
pretending	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
true	O
Proprietors	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Box	O
;	O
of	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
order	O
'd	O
that	O
they	O
should	O
suffer	O
12	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
,	O
and	O
pay	O
a	O
Fine	O
of	O
20	O
Marks	O
each	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Flood	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
James	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Wig	O
val	O
.	O
9	O
s.	O
a	O
Ring	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Turnover	O
,	O
Oct.	O
6	O
.	O
James	O
Burton	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
Minories	B-place
betwixt	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
met	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Nichols	O
;	O
he	O
jostled	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
he	O
struck	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
and	O
kick	O
'd	O
up	O
my	O
Heels	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Fall	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
,	O
but	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
who	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Robert	O
Flood	O
,	O
who	O
stood	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
bide	O
Nichols	O
beat	O
me	O
within	O
an	O
Inch	O
of	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Nichols	O
threw	O
me	O
down	O
again	O
:	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
catch	O
'd	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
my	O
Ring	O
off	O
my	O
Finger	O
,	O
threw	O
me	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
tore	O
my	O
Turnover	O
off	O
.	O
Several	O
People	O
were	O
by	O
this	O
time	O
got	O
about	O
us	O
;	O
but	O
Flood	O
bade	O
them	O
stand	O
off	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
no	O
body	O
assisted	O
me	O
:	O
However	O
,	O
I	O
made	O
shift	O
to	O
drag	O
Nichols	O
by	O
the	O
Collar	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
about	O
200	O
Yards	O
off	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
follow	O
'd	O
in	O
by	O
Robert	O
Flood	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
both	O
secured	O
.	O
Nathanael	B-pers
Sanderson	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
Hearing	O
a	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
holding	O
Nichols	O
by	O
the	O
Collar	O
.	O
Flood	O
bade	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
let	O
Nichols	O
go	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
wo	O
n't	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
has	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
Then	O
Flood	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
rescue	O
Nichols	O
,	O
and	O
bade	O
him	O
beat	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
then	O
made	O
their	O
Defence	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
been	O
(	O
says	O
Nichols	O
)	O
at	O
Supper	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Adams	O
's	O
in	O
Whitegate-Alley	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
home	O
along	O
the	O
Minories	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
stood	O
up	O
at	O
a	O
Cutler	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
at	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
meant	O
by	O
it	O
?	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
fell	O
to	O
fighting	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
fuddled	O
,	O
and	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
whether	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
or	O
no	O
.	O
Several	O
Witnesses	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Reputation	O
of	O
both	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Pattison	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
18	O
Yards	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
Yards	O
of	O
Sattin	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Martell	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
10	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Chairwoman	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
trusted	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
she	O
broke	O
open	O
a	O
Chest	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
soon	O
miss	O
'd	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
at	O
Places	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Watch	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Oliver	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
2	O
.	O
Robert	O
Oliver	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
I	O
lost	O
this	O
Watch	O
one	O
Night	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
Months	O
ago	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Side	O
of	O
my	O
Hammock	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Sea	O
near	O
Jamaica	B-place
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
then	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
same	O
Ship	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
mistrusted	O
him	O
,	O
till	O
t'other	O
day	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
such	O
a	O
Watch	O
for	O
40	O
s.	O
Mary	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
this	O
Watch	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
my	O
Lodging	O
in	O
King	O
Edward	O
Street	O
in	O
Wapping	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
it	O
for	O
30	O
or	O
40	O
s.	O
I	O
got	O
40	O
s.	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
pawn	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
by	O
a	O
Woman	O
in	O
Jamaica	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hogg	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
six	O
Pound	O
of	O
Tea	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
half	O
a	O
Pound	O
of	O
Almonds	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
Pound	O
of	O
candy	O
'd	O
Lemon	O
and	O
Orange-Peel	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Coxeter	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Coxeter	I-pers
,	O
July	O
4	O
.	O
Richard	O
Coxeter	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
his	O
Servant	O
three	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
often	O
found	O
a	O
greater	O
Decrease	O
in	O
his	O
Stock	O
than	O
he	O
could	O
account	O
for	O
.	O
Beatrice	O
(	O
his	O
Wife	O
)	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
Morning	O
as	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
opening	O
Shop	O
,	O
she	O
heard	O
the	O
Lid	O
of	O
a	O
Canister	O
taken	O
off	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
look	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
her	O
Petticoat	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Hand	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
putting	O
something	O
in	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
next	O
Week	O
she	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Coffee	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
several	O
times	O
seen	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
give	O
small	O
Parcels	O
of	O
Tea	O
,	O
Raisons	O
,	O
Almonds	O
,	O
and	O
Orange-Peel	O
to	O
Susan	B-pers
Ashton	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
with	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Alehouse	O
and	O
Gin-Shops	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Parr	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
often	O
seen	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
meet	O
Ashton	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
her	O
something	O
in	O
small	O
Papers	O
,	O
but	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
believed	O
that	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
Ashton	O
a	O
Pound	O
of	O
Tea	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Ashton	O
knew	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
Ashton	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
Betty	O
,	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
give	O
me	O
any	O
of	O
your	O
Master	O
's	O
Tea	O
?	O
And	O
after	O
a	O
little	O
Pause	O
,	O
she	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
Yes	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
then	O
call	O
'd	O
Witnesses	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
Defence	O
.	O
Susan	B-pers
Ashton	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
never	O
in	O
her	O
Life	O
gave	O
me	O
any	O
Tea	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
that	O
her	O
Master	O
deals	O
in	O
.	O
My	O
Girl	O
used	O
to	O
go	O
thither	O
every	O
Morning	O
to	O
fetch	O
me	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Ounce	O
of	O
Tea	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
always	O
sent	O
Money	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
one	O
Night	O
with	O
some	O
Fish	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
something	O
wrapt	O
up	O
in	O
three	O
Papers	O
.	O
She	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
dropt	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
Papers	O
;	O
and	O
therefore	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
Fish	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Papers	O
,	O
while	O
she	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
into	O
the	O
Papers	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
little	O
Sugar	O
'd	O
Kings	O
in	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
again	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
them	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
whether	O
she	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
Customer	O
,	O
or	O
did	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Coxeter	O
had	O
laid	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Charge	O
,	O
till	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
a	O
Fortune-teller	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Baily	O
,	O
who	O
described	O
a	O
little	O
black	O
Woman	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
has	O
been	O
my	O
Servant	O
about	O
six	O
Weeks	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
ever	O
since	O
she	O
came	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Coxeter	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
found	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
honest	O
,	O
industrious	O
and	O
faithful	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
all	O
Respects	O
such	O
a	O
good	O
Servant	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
now	O
at	O
liberty	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
immediately	O
take	O
her	O
into	O
my	O
House	O
again	O
.	O
Several	O
others	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Cotton	I-pers
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Bullice	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
40	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Man	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
1	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
Cotton	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Rings	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
afterward	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
said	O
that	O
Bullice	O
advised	O
her	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
Bullice	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Cotton	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Cusy	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Mackecky	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stoke	B-place
Newington	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Cows	O
,	O
each	O
of	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
3	O
l.	O
3.	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Fields	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
Cattle	O
;	O
and	O
not	O
finding	O
the	O
two	O
Cows	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
Master	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
hearing	O
that	O
this	O
Man	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
upon	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
Cow-stealing	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
accused	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sleath	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
Between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
on	O
Monday	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
two	O
Cows	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
Master	O
Barns	O
's	O
at	O
Totenham	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
sold	O
them	O
accordingly	O
:	O
and	O
after	O
Market	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
sold	O
them	O
myself	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
be	O
seen	O
in	O
the	O
Market	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
should	O
have	O
arrested	O
me	O
.	O
This	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
little	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
Fellow	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
before	O
I	O
paid	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
stept	O
over	O
to	O
my	O
Father	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
his	O
Advice	O
.	O
I	O
'll	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
if	O
this	O
is	O
not	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
stole	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
Cows	O
that	O
were	O
sold	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
Whereupon	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
Smith	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
again	O
next	O
Week	O
,	O
and	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
himself	O
and	O
Collin	B-pers
Luff	I-pers
stole	O
the	O
Cows	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Lloyd	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Hunter	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Farmer	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Blankets	O
,	O
seven	O
Napkins	O
,	O
six	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
sixteen	O
Clouts	O
,	O
four	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Head-Cloaths	O
,	O
a	O
Fender	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
a	O
Fan	O
,	O
Hood	O
,	O
Stomacher	O
,	O
two	O
Yards	O
of	O
Damask	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
6	O
l.	O
14	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Purcell	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	O
Purcell	O
.	O
John	O
Purcell	O
deposed	O
thus	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
Servant	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
her	O
(	O
with	O
two	O
Children	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
Eleven	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Nine	O
Years	O
old	O
)	O
in	O
Charge	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
Wife	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
return	O
'd	O
,	O
we	O
miss	O
'd	O
several	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
two	O
Trunks	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
tax	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
robbing	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
stiffly	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Purcell	I-pers
(	O
a	O
Child	O
aged	O
Eleven	O
Years	O
)	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
broke	O
open	O
two	O
Trunks	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
me	O
give	O
her	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
out	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
she	O
took	O
out	O
herself	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
Caps	O
,	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
Childbed-Linnen	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
worked	O
Stomacher	O
,	O
a	O
Child	O
's	O
Frock	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
Woman	O
that	O
crys	O
old	O
Iron	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
thus	O
made	O
her	O
Defence	O
:	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
I	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Purcell	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
Girl	O
there	O
,	O
his	O
Daughter	O
Mary	O
;	O
for	O
as	O
young	O
as	O
she	O
is	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
Thieving	O
from	O
her	O
Father	O
for	O
several	O
Years	O
.	O
One	O
Day	O
she	O
sold	O
her	O
Father	O
's	O
Shooes	O
and	O
my	O
black	O
Peticoat	O
to	O
an	O
old	O
Rag-Woman	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
Mother	O
say	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
ashamed	O
to	O
take	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
again	O
,	O
because	O
a	O
Silver	O
Buckle	O
had	O
been	O
lost	O
at	O
the	O
School	O
where	O
she	O
used	O
to	O
go	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
l.	O
twelve	O
Yards	O
of	O
Callico	O
,	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Head-Cloaths	O
,	O
a	O
Ridinghood	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
,	O
August	O
16	O
.	O
The	O
Witnesses	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
Says	O
Margaret	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
,	O
these	O
are	O
my	O
Goods	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
again	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Macleland	I-pers
.	O
Says	O
Thomas	O
Macleland	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
these	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Roods	I-pers
;	O
and	O
says	O
Thomas	O
Roods	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Guilty	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Copper-Pot	O
and	O
a	O
Saucepan	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Barton	I-pers
,	O
Sep.	O
23	O
.	O
Herbert	O
was	O
acquitted	O
and	O
Turner	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
val	O
.	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transp	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Escutcheon	O
,	O
(	O
from	O
a	O
Hearse	O
)	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Sherwood	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
30	O
.	O
-	O
Ellis	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
At	O
the	O
Desire	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
,	O
I	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Constables	O
attended	O
a	O
Funeral	O
to	O
S.	O
Clement	O
Danes	O
Church	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
we	O
came	O
through	O
Temple-Bar	B-place
,	O
the	O
Mob	O
began	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
rude	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
us	O
Names	O
;	O
for	O
they	O
took	O
us	O
to	O
be	O
City	O
Constables	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
we	O
had	O
no	O
Power	O
without	O
the	O
Gate	O
,	O
when	O
indeed	O
our	O
Authority	O
took	O
Place	O
where	O
they	O
thought	O
it	O
ended	O
,	O
for	O
we	O
were	O
not	O
City	O
Constables	O
.	O
Just	O
without	O
Temple-Bar	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Hackney-Coachman	O
)	O
was	O
fitting	O
upon	O
his	O
Box	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
left	O
his	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
follow	O
'd	O
the	O
Hearse	O
.	O
I	O
guess	O
'd	O
at	O
his	O
Design	O
,	O
and	O
caution	O
'd	O
him	O
several	O
times	O
not	O
to	O
meddle	O
with	O
the	O
Escutcheons	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
still	O
push	O
'd	O
forward	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
Burying	O
was	O
over	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
great	O
Mobbing	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
snatch	O
the	O
Escutcheon	O
from	O
the	O
Hearse	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
stood	O
by	O
the	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Hearse	O
,	O
the	O
Mob	O
push	O
'd	O
him	O
against	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Escutcheons	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
it	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
only	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
from	O
S.	O
Clement	O
's	O
Church	O
to	O
the	O
New	O
Church	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Draper	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
'Scutcheon	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Banner	O
val	O
.	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Sherwood	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
30	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
,	O
during	O
the	O
Funeral	O
Procession	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
several	O
times	O
warned	O
not	O
to	O
meddle	O
with	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Ornaments	O
of	O
the	O
Hearse	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
notwithstanding	O
,	O
he	O
reach	O
'd	O
over	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
(	O
the	O
Horse-page	O
)	O
and	O
snatch	O
'd	O
away	O
a	O
Banner	O
and	O
a	O
Scutcheon	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Iron	O
Bars	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Katharine	B-pers
Lady	I-pers
Dowager	I-pers
Abergaveny	I-pers
,	O
September	O
23	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Tongason	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Head-Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
Yards	O
of	O
Lace	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Phillis	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
and	O
two	O
Suits	O
of	O
Head-Cloaths	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Garret	I-pers
,	O
and	O
3	O
d.	O
10	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Gervison	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Irwin	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
Gervison	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
rest	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Rachel	B-pers
Coe	I-pers
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Keaton	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Candlesticks	O
and	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
3	O
.	O
Keaton	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Coe	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Cows	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Barret	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
11	O
.	O
The	O
Witnesses	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
James	O
Barret	O
:	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
Cows	O
from	O
Grass	O
at	O
Stamford-Hill	B-place
last	O
Monday	O
Morning	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Nutt	I-pers
:	O
I	O
bought	O
two	O
Cows	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
for	O
Five	O
Guineas	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ivory	I-pers
:	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Cows	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Nutt	O
bought	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
know	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Cows	O
that	O
my	O
Master	O
lost	O
from	O
Stamford-Hill	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
those	O
two	O
Cows	O
from	O
his	O
Brother-in-Law	O
Joseph	B-pers
Cusy	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
convicted	O
this	O
Morning	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Cows	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Longmire	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Thomas	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
Sept.	O
1	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Warren	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
Crossing	O
Lincoln's-Inn-Fields	O
,	O
between	O
Nine	O
and	O
Ten	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
turn	O
'd	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
me	O
full	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
.	O
I	O
pass	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
follow	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
White	O
Dragon	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
soon	O
came	O
in	O
after	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
tarry	O
long	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
till	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Leather-Lane	B-place
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
suddenly	O
stept	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
knock	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
snatch	O
'd	O
off	O
my	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
down	O
the	O
Lane	O
.	O
He	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
take	O
my	O
Wig	O
too	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
made	O
shift	O
to	O
hold	O
it	O
fast	O
;	O
and	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
quickly	O
taken	O
and	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
again	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
I	O
heard	O
somebody	O
cry	O
,	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
whereupon	O
I	O
and	O
another	O
pursued	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
fell	O
down	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Warren	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
coming	O
to	O
meet	O
us	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
disguis	O
'd	O
in	O
Drink	O
;	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
way	O
we	O
found	O
Mr.	O
Warren	O
's	O
Hat	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Noblet	I-pers
swore	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Susan	B-pers
Isaacson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
72	O
Iron	O
Bellows	O
Pipes	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
24	O
s.	O
Sept.	O
26	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
Transp	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Fleming	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Tilbury	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Filewood	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Haselhurst	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
Oct.	O
8	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Little	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Pancras	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Lionel	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
in	O
an	O
open	O
Field	O
near	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
three	O
Keys	O
,	O
a	O
Turnover	O
,	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
16	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Richard	B-pers
Hatton	I-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
in	O
an	O
open	O
Field	O
near	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Cane	O
,	O
three	O
Keys	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
August	O
7	O
.	O
Lionel	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
About	O
7	O
o'Clock	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Evening	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
from	O
Hampstead	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
2d	O
Field	O
beyond	O
Fig-Lane	B-place
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
two	O
other	O
Men	O
standing	O
together	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
forward	O
with	O
a	O
Pistol	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Your	O
Money	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
some	O
Silver	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
where	O
my	O
Watch	O
was	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
took	O
my	O
Handkerchief	O
and	O
Neckcloth	O
,	O
and	O
bade	O
me	O
good	O
Night	O
.	O
The	O
Tuesday	O
following	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
that	O
such	O
a	O
Man	O
was	O
in	O
Custody	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
presently	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Edward	O
Hatton	O
Evans	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
Coming	O
over	O
the	O
Fields	O
from	O
Kentish-Town	B-place
,	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
my	O
little	O
Boy	O
being	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Man	O
,	O
both	O
arm	O
'd	O
with	O
Pistols	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Companion	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
bade	O
me	O
stand	O
,	O
demanded	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
search	O
'd	O
my	O
Pockets	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
20	O
s.	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
My	O
Child	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
O	O
!	O
my	O
Dear	O
Father	O
!	O
Upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
kiss	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Do	O
n't	O
be	O
afraid	O
,	O
my	O
Dear	O
,	O
we	O
wo	O
n't	O
hurt	O
your	O
Father	O
.	O
They	O
bade	O
me	O
good	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
turn	O
'd	O
back	O
again	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
Cane	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
Mr.	O
Hatton	O
's	O
Child	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
Child	O
presently	O
knew	O
him	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
stood	O
among	O
several	O
others	O
.	O
That	O
's	O
the	O
Man	O
(	O
says	O
the	O
Child	O
)	O
that	O
kiss	O
'd	O
me	O
while	O
the	O
other	O
Man	O
robb	O
'd	O
my	O
Father	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
got	O
the	O
same	O
Wastecoat	O
on	O
now	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
:	O
10	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
prove	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
another	O
Wastecoat	O
on	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Pattin	O
's	O
Alley	O
in	O
Newtoner	O
's	O
Lane	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Bess	B-pers
Lion	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Edgworth	I-pers
Bess	I-pers
,	O
(	O
an	O
old	O
Acquaintance	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
Jack	B-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
's	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
suppose	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Bed	O
with	O
her	O
when	O
I	O
first	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
found	O
his	O
Breeches	O
and	O
Stockings	O
upon	O
her	O
Bed	O
below	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
catch	O
'd	O
him	O
above	O
with	O
nothing	O
on	O
but	O
his	O
Coat	O
.	O
He	O
confess	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
two	O
Robberies	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
now	O
stands	O
indicted	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Jefferison	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
Chimney-Sweeper	O
)	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
Sacks	O
val	O
.	O
9	O
s.	O
and	O
25	O
Bushels	O
and	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Spot	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Kitchen	I-pers
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
;	O
and	O
two	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Soot	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Spurr	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
27	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
being	O
all	O
Chimney-Sweeper	O
s	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Work	O
in	O
Wapping	B-place
,	O
and	O
had	O
left	O
their	O
Soot	O
in	O
an	O
old	O
Woman	O
's	O
Yard	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
,	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
it	O
off	O
by	O
Water	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
suspected	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
examin	O
'd	O
,	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
discover	O
'd	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
concealed	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Katharine	B-pers
Blackbourn	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
with	O
a	O
Gold	O
Chain	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Janeway	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
20	O
.	O
John	O
Janeway	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
having	O
Occasion	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
,	O
he	O
left	O
his	O
Watch	O
in	O
the	O
Hands	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Taylor	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
it	O
was	O
lost	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
laid	O
up	O
Mr.	O
Janeway	O
's	O
Watch	O
in	O
my	O
Bed-Chamber	O
;	O
but	O
having	O
lost	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
let	O
any	O
body	O
know	O
that	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
Possession	O
:	O
But	O
however	O
,	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
it	O
in	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Days	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
violent	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Southwark-Fair	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
home	O
a	O
Couple	O
of	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
small	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Plate	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
her	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
found	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
Watch	O
.	O
The	O
Chain	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
to	O
Richard	B-pers
Peters	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
her	O
Son	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
pawn	O
'd	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Morgan	O
for	O
30	O
s.	O
Guilty	O
Val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Foster	B-pers
Snow	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rawlins	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
in	O
the	O
Left	O
Breast	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Length	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
Depth	O
of	O
seven	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
Stabbing	O
.	O
And	O
a	O
3d	O
time	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Waterman	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
The	O
Deceased	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Feathers	B-place
Alehouse	I-place
in	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
a	O
Couple	O
of	O
Rabbits	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
order	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
roasted	O
for	O
Supper	O
;	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
walk	O
'd	O
about	O
,	O
appear	O
'd	O
very	O
uneasy	O
,	O
and	O
mutter	O
'd	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Curses	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
began	O
to	O
turn	O
his	O
Discourse	O
to	O
a	O
Porter	O
;	O
and	O
betwixt	O
them	O
some	O
Mention	O
was	O
made	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
.	O
Why	O
,	O
it	O
seems	O
(	O
says	O
I	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
)	O
it	O
's	O
you	O
that	O
my	O
Landlord	O
is	O
so	O
disturb	O
'd	O
about	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
to	O
prevent	O
Words	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
thought	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
curs	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
ill	O
Words	O
pass	O
'd	O
betwixt	O
them	O
.	O
They	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
Supper	O
was	O
ready	O
;	O
the	O
Deceased	O
desired	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
to	O
sit	O
down	O
and	O
eat	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
turn	O
'd	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
Eat	O
the	O
Davil	O
!	O
and	O
then	O
struck	O
his	O
Wife	O
;	O
which	O
the	O
Deceased	O
seeing	O
,	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
stept	O
betwixt	O
them	O
to	O
part	O
them	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
reach	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Dresser	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
something	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
suppose	O
was	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
(	O
for	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
distinctly	O
,	O
because	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Candle	O
upon	O
the	O
Dresser	O
;	O
)	O
but	O
be	O
it	O
what	O
it	O
would	O
,	O
he	O
stretch	O
'd	O
out	O
his	O
Arm	O
in	O
this	O
manner	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
the	O
Deceased	O
thus	O
;	O
who	O
thereupon	O
immediately	O
sunk	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
died	O
.	O
-	O
Middleton	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
appeared	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
morose	O
and	O
quarrelsome	O
Humour	O
when	O
he	O
first	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
.	O
-	O
You	O
're	O
a	O
sorry	O
Dog	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
.	O
And	O
you	O
're	O
another	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Deceased	O
again	O
.	O
Sirrah	O
,	O
you	O
're	O
a	O
Rogue	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
-	O
Call	O
me	O
Rogue	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
lay	O
you	O
behind	O
the	O
Fire	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
we	O
sat	O
down	O
to	O
Supper	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
quarrel	O
'd	O
with	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
part	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
something	O
from	O
the	O
Dresser	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
such	O
a	O
Stroke	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
dead	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Rude	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
About	O
a	O
Month	O
ago	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
enquired	O
for	O
the	O
Deceased	O
Mr.	O
Rawlins	O
.	O
Rawlins	O
is	O
a	O
Rogue	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
owes	O
me	O
Money	O
:	O
-	O
He	O
's	O
a	O
Villain	O
!	O
a	O
Rascal	O
!	O
I	O
'd	O
make	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
killing	O
him	O
,	O
than	O
of	O
killing	O
a	O
Toad	O
or	O
a	O
Dog	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Byas	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
uneasy	O
What	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
must	O
I	O
be	O
abused	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
House	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
Man	O
that	O
was	O
ones	O
me	O
Money	O
?	O
Do	O
you	O
mean	O
me	O
?	O
says	O
the	O
Deceased	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
you	O
,	O
reply	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Wife	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
quiet	O
.	O
He	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
be	O
at	O
quiet	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Slap	O
o'the	O
Face	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
said	O
,	O
Are	O
not	O
you	O
a	O
Rogue	O
for	O
that	O
?	O
The	O
Woman	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
would	O
have	O
follow	O
'd	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Deceased	O
hinder	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
presently	O
after	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Maid	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
following	O
my	O
Mistress	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Deceased	O
stopt	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
strike	O
her	O
in	O
his	O
Presence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
just	O
before	O
laid	O
this	O
Case-Knife	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Dresser	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
give	O
the	O
Blow	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Deceased	O
sunk	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
Dresser	O
,	O
and	O
died	O
before	O
we	O
could	O
get	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
We	O
afterwards	O
found	O
this	O
same	O
Knife	O
,	O
all	O
bloody	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Floor	O
.	O
The	O
Surgeon	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
in	O
the	O
Left	O
Breast	O
,	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
Inches	O
deep	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
believed	O
it	O
was	O
given	O
with	O
such	O
a	O
Knife	O
as	O
that	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
;	O
but	O
call	O
'd	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Acquaintance	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
,	O
quiet	O
,	O
good-natur	O
'd	O
Man	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
did	O
use	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
fractious	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
most	O
troublesome	O
Man	O
in	O
Nature	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Guilty	O
of	O
each	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Bredon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hornsey	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Portmantean	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
two	O
Wastecoats	O
,	O
two	O
Shirts	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
a	O
Wig	O
,	O
Several	O
Books	O
,	O
twelve	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pearson	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Portmanteau	O
was	O
left	O
at	O
the	O
Windmill	O
in	O
S.	O
John-Street	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
to	O
Aston	O
in	O
Hertfordshire	O
.	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
tied	O
upon	O
the	O
Ladder	O
at	O
the	O
Tail	O
of	O
the	O
Waggon	O
,	O
and	O
lost	O
between	O
Highgate	B-place
and	O
Barnet	B-place
,	O
and	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
Highgate	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
thus	O
made	O
her	O
Defence	O
:	O
Upon	O
the	O
Road	O
betwixt	O
Mims	O
and	O
Barnet	O
,	O
I	O
fell	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
a	O
Man	O
that	O
sells	O
Fifth	O
:	O
We	O
rode	O
together	O
thro	O
'	O
Barnet	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
off	O
my	O
Horse	O
to	O
piss	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
,	O
the	O
Man	O
got	O
a	O
pretty	O
way	O
before	O
me	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
See	O
here	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
just	O
found	O
a	O
Portmanteau	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
come	O
too	O
late	O
to	O
cry	O
Halves	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
'll	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
Shilling	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
take	O
it	O
upon	O
your	O
Horse	O
so	O
far	O
as	O
Highgate	O
,	O
because	O
my	O
Horse	O
's	O
Back	O
is	O
sore	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
agreed	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
left	O
it	O
two	O
Days	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
at	O
Highgate	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
and	O
open	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
as	O
many	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
it	O
as	O
came	O
to	O
3	O
l.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Wilks	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilks	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gun	O
,	O
eleven	O
Plates	O
,	O
a	O
Bed	O
,	O
two	O
Quilts	O
,	O
two	O
Blankets	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Tongs	O
,	O
a	O
Pot	O
,	O
a	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
a	O
Saucepan	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
10	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
Edward	O
Wilks	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Lodgings	O
of	O
his	O
Brother	O
Thomas	O
Wilks	O
,	O
in	O
Shadwell	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Thomas	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
found	O
Edward	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Swale	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hendon	B-place
,	O
(	O
aged	O
12	O
Years	O
)	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bohun	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Kiff	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Wooden	O
Drawer	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
7	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
15	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
about	O
Eight	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
having	O
just	O
served	O
a	O
Customer	O
,	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
heard	O
a	O
Noise	O
behind	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
turning	O
back	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Drawer	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
He	O
ran	O
out	O
;	O
she	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
pursued	O
by	O
some	O
Neighbours	O
;	O
and	O
finding	O
himself	O
in	O
Danger	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
the	O
Drawer	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
they	O
;	O
but	O
then	O
it	O
was	O
of	O
no	O
Service	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
presently	O
taken	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Sculthorp	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
thence	O
three	O
Pewter	O
Chamber	O
Pots	O
,	O
a	O
Saucepan	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
William	O
Turner	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Horns	B-place
Alehouse	I-place
at	I-place
Essex-Stairs	I-place
:	O
My	O
Back-Window	O
looks	O
into	O
the	O
Thames	O
.	O
My	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Saucepan	O
stole	O
away	O
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
July	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
suppose	O
the	O
Entrance	O
was	O
made	O
at	O
that	O
Sash-Window	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
sure	O
whether	O
or	O
no	O
I	O
had	O
made	O
fast	O
the	O
Shutter	O
of	O
that	O
Window	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
that	O
Night	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
did	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Month	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
Night	O
my	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
Chamber-Pots	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Sculthorp	O
was	O
a	O
Waterman	O
,	O
and	O
ply	O
'd	O
at	O
my	O
Door	O
.	O
He	O
usually	O
drank	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
where	O
every	O
thing	O
lay	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
I	O
ply	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Stairs	O
.	O
Sculthorp	O
took	O
me	O
aside	O
one	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
'd	O
go	O
upon	O
the	O
Account	O
.	O
What	O
Account	O
?	O
says	O
I	O
.	O
Why	O
the	O
Account	O
of	O
what	O
we	O
can	O
get	O
in	O
Turner	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
But	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
is	O
there	O
no	O
Danger	O
?	O
No	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
and	O
Jack	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
have	O
been	O
there	O
twice	O
before	O
:	O
You	O
shall	O
come	O
to	O
no	O
Trouble	O
.	O
Do	O
but	O
bring	O
year	O
Boat	O
under	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
you	O
need	O
not	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
any	O
ways	O
concern	O
'd	O
;	O
but	O
only	O
take	O
what	O
I	O
bring	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
Sculthorp	O
own	O
'd	O
before	O
him	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
House	O
twice	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
intend	O
the	O
next	O
time	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
general	O
Sweep	O
,	O
and	O
clear	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Silver	O
Tankards	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
handy	O
Moveables	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
I	O
heard	O
Sculthorp	O
own	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
Turner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
design	O
to	O
rob	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
up	O
a	O
Boat	O
's	O
full	O
Cargo	O
.	O
As	O
for	O
Rogers	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
most	O
impudent	O
Fellow	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
ever	O
I	O
saw	O
.	O
He	O
stood	O
a	O
strut	O
,	O
cock	O
'd	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
giving	O
a	O
Fillup	O
with	O
his	O
Finger	O
,	O
Now	O
,	O
(	O
says	O
he	O
to	O
his	O
Worship	O
)	O
do	O
your	O
worst	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
but	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
;	O
my	O
Neck	O
is	O
but	O
short	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
wants	O
to	O
be	O
stretch	O
'd	O
.	O
Rogers	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Sculthorp	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Spurs	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Acton	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
27	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
his	O
Spurs	O
to	O
clean	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
presently	O
left	O
his	O
Service	O
,	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Val	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Rachel	B-pers
Pearson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bible	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
S.	O
Martin	O
's	O
Alms-house	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
Service	O
)	O
lived	O
with	O
her	O
Grandmother	O
in	O
Hog-Lane	B-place
Alms-houses	I-place
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Ballinger	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
one	O
Sunday	O
)	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
fetch	O
her	O
down	O
the	O
Bible	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
She	O
sat	O
down	O
to	O
read	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
left	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
neither	O
saw	O
nor	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Bible	O
till	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
with	O
it	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
put	O
it	O
upon	O
her	O
Partner	O
's	O
Bed	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
Morning	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
found	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
her	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
thinking	O
that	O
might	O
bring	O
her	O
to	O
confess	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
stiffly	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Justice	O
discharged	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Day	O
she	O
arrested	O
me	O
for	O
Scandal	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
carry	O
my	O
Cloaths	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Charges	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
'd	O
of	O
the	O
Pawnbroker	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
ever	O
she	O
could	O
upon	O
my	O
Things	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
was	O
arrested	O
.	O
She	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
for	O
what	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
it	O
was	O
for	O
charging	O
a	O
Woman	O
with	O
taking	O
a	O
Bible	O
that	O
was	O
lost	O
.	O
A	O
Bible	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
;	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
Woman	O
's	O
Name	O
?	O
Rachel	O
,	O
says	O
I.	O
Rachel	O
!	O
And	O
what	O
besides	O
Rachel	O
?	O
says	O
she	O
.	O
Why	O
Pearson	O
,	O
says	O
I.	O
Ay	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
;	O
And	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Bible	O
when	O
you	O
see	O
it	O
?	O
Yes	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
.	O
Why	O
then	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
shew	O
you	O
a	O
Bible	O
that	O
was	O
pawn	O
'd	O
here	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Rachel	B-pers
Pearson	I-pers
:	O
So	O
she	O
brings	O
me	O
a	O
Bible	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
very	O
same	O
that	O
we	O
had	O
lost	O
.	O
The	O
Pawnbroker	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pawn	O
'd	O
that	O
Bible	O
to	O
her	O
for	O
6	O
s.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hughs	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Hobson	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
1	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Baron	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Spatterdashers	O
,	O
6	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Wax-Candles	O
,	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
Table-Cloths	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Baron	I-pers
;	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Baron	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
Frock	O
and	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Baron	I-pers
Jun	I-pers
.	I-pers
Jun	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
Philip	O
Baron	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
I	O
keep	O
an	O
Undertaker	O
's	O
Shop	O
near	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
in	O
Holborn	B-place
:	O
My	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
three	O
times	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
,	O
the	O
13th	O
,	O
and	O
22d	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
From	O
several	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
Reason	O
to	O
think	O
that	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
done	O
by	O
somebody	O
that	O
was	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
suspected	O
nobody	O
more	O
than	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
's	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
and	O
lived	O
a	O
very	O
loose	O
,	O
idle	O
Life	O
.	O
In	O
about	O
a	O
Week	O
after	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
I	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
S.	O
Sepulchre	O
's	O
Watch-house	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Game-Cock	O
.	O
Edward	O
Baron	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
Shirts	O
upon	O
his	O
Back	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
left	O
that	O
Night	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Game-Cock	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Abbot	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
1	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Sybilla	B-pers
alias	I-pers
Isabella	I-pers
Hanshaw	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Fanshaw	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Aprons	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Hugh	B-pers
Humphries	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
21	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
Transp	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Sergeant	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Edmonton	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Coats	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hands	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
6	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elias	B-pers
Sharp	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Hannah	B-pers
Bignell	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Breeches	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edw	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
11	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
Hannah	O
Bignell	O
(	O
a	O
Child	O
)	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Moon-light	O
Night	O
going	O
over	O
Tower	B-place
Hill	I-place
with	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
under	O
her	O
Arm	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
snatch	O
'd	O
them	O
from	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
closely	O
pursu	O
'd	O
,	O
upon	O
her	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
the	O
Breeches	O
into	O
Tower	O
Ditch	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
presently	O
stopt	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Breeches	O
taken	O
up	O
again	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Saddle	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Shirts	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Price	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Trunk	O
,	O
two	O
Silver	O
Tea-Spoons	O
,	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
,	O
(	O
her	O
Father	O
)	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Henry	O
Booth	O
,	O
Oct.	O
7	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
order	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Recognisance	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Ferguson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cherry	O
Derry	O
Gown	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Lustring	O
Gown	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Poulter	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
put	O
in	O
a	O
Bundle	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
Bar	O
at	O
the	O
Nag's-Head	B-place
Alehouse	I-place
in	I-place
Aldersgate-Street	I-place
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
by	O
the	O
Highgate	O
Coach	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
so	O
privately	O
as	O
to	O
escape	O
unobserved	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
immediately	O
pursued	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
Noble-Street	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Higgs	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
50	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Iron	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Turney	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
150	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Iron	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
upon	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
was	O
stopt	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
at	O
Dorset	O
Stairs	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
Bars	O
of	O
Iron	O
in	O
his	O
Boat	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
took	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Turney	O
's	O
Door	O
at	O
the	O
Old	B-place
Swan	I-place
:	O
That	O
John	B-pers
Gun	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Smith	O
near	O
Fleet-Ditch	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Gander	I-pers
,	O
another	O
Smith	O
,	O
had	O
often	O
been	O
concern	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
stealing	O
Iron	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
worked	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
sold	O
several	O
Quantities	O
of	O
Iron	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Bryley	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Smith	O
on	O
the	O
Bank-side	O
,	O
who	O
well	O
knew	O
that	O
they	O
stole	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Nicolas	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Joseph	O
Blower	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Blower	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
19	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Apprentice	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
a	O
Turner	O
,	O
in	O
Beach	B-place
Lane	I-place
;	O
and	O
while	O
his	O
Master	O
was	O
taking	O
a	O
Nap	O
in	O
the	O
Chair	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
Chamber-Door	O
,	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
the	O
Keys	O
in	O
the	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
,	O
he	O
opend	O
them	O
,	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
directly	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
News	O
they	O
heard	O
of	O
him	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
Bridewell	O
at	O
Ware	O
for	O
breeding	O
a	O
Riot	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
this	O
Fact	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Barry	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edith	B-pers
Barwell	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Coat	O
and	O
Wastecoat	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Cash	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Edith	O
Barnell	O
,	O
April	O
27	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
in	O
April	O
last	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
just	O
come	O
over	O
from	O
Ireland	O
,	O
took	O
a	O
Lodging	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Barwells	O
,	O
who	O
kept	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
lodged	O
there	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
Weeks	O
,	O
when	O
one	O
Afternoon	O
Mr.	O
Cash	O
,	O
who	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
,	O
went	O
abroad	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Key	O
in	O
his	O
Chamber	O
Door	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
some	O
Excuse	O
for	O
staying	O
above	O
Stairs	O
,	O
pretended	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
Accounts	O
to	O
settle	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
desired	O
his	O
Landlady	O
to	O
lend	O
him	O
her	O
Pen	O
and	O
Ink	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
;	O
tho	O
'	O
she	O
afterwards	O
found	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
write	O
his	O
own	O
Name	O
.	O
While	O
the	O
People	O
were	O
busy	O
below	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
of	O
going	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Cash	O
's	O
Chambers	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
his	O
Mourning	O
Coat	O
and	O
Wastecoat	O
;	O
both	O
which	O
he	O
put	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
button	O
'd	O
his	O
own	O
old	O
Coat	O
over	O
them	O
.	O
At	O
Night	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
full	O
Tankard	O
of	O
Beer	O
;	O
and	O
before	O
he	O
had	O
empty	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Cash	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
perceive	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
more	O
Cloaths	O
upon	O
his	O
Back	O
than	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
either	O
seeing	O
,	O
or	O
pretending	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
an	O
Acquaintance	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
Hah	O
!	O
Paul	O
,	O
won	O
t	O
ye	O
drink	O
with	O
me	O
?	O
And	O
so	O
stept	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
with	O
the	O
Tankard	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
quite	O
off	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Barwell	O
heard	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
till	O
an	O
Advertisement	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
News-Papers	O
informed	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
such	O
a	O
Tankard	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
was	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
Sale	O
by	O
such	O
a	O
Person	O
as	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Lake	O
,	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
in	O
Portsmouth	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
stopt	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
taken	O
into	O
Custody	O
for	O
not	O
giving	O
a	O
good	O
Account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
Edith	B-pers
Barwell	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
upon	O
reading	O
this	O
Advertisement	O
,	O
she	O
wrote	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Lake	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
his	O
Answer	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
Portsmouth	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
soon	O
found	O
her	O
Tankard	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
fell	O
upon	O
his	O
Knees	O
,	O
and	O
beg	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
favourable	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
She	O
heard	O
there	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
a	O
Mourning	O
Coat	O
and	O
Wastecoat	O
,	O
which	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
Mr.	O
Cash	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
redeem	O
'd	O
'em	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lake	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Tankard	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
Sale	O
at	O
my	O
Shop	O
in	O
Portsmouth	O
:	O
I	O
examin	O
'd	O
who	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
?	O
My	O
Name	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
is	O
John	B-pers
Barry	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
left	O
me	O
by	O
my	O
Uncle	O
Edward	B-pers
Barry	I-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
lately	O
dead	O
in	O
Ireland	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
two	O
Letters	O
E	O
and	O
B	O
stand	O
for	O
his	O
Name	O
.	O
Not	O
thinking	O
this	O
Account	O
satisfactory	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Mayor	O
,	O
who	O
committed	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Town	O
Prison	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
my	O
publishing	O
an	O
Advertisement	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Barwell	O
came	O
down	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
her	O
?	O
And	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
Yes	O
,	O
Madam	O
,	O
to	O
my	O
Shame	O
,	O
-	O
my	O
Life	O
is	O
in	O
your	O
Hands	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
thus	O
made	O
his	O
Defence	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
Tankard	O
it	O
's	O
true	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
how	O
I	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
than	O
the	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
Moon	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
drunk	O
over	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
next	O
Morning	O
I	O
found	O
myself	O
asleep	O
in	O
S.	O
James	O
's	O
Park	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Tankard	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
(	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Corrie	I-pers
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
did	O
privately	O
steal	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
and	O
Chain	O
,	O
value	O
22	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Febr	O
.	O
5	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Smith	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
Some	O
Months	O
ago	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
Chancery-Lane	B-place
,	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
Watch	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
who	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
Men	O
and	O
Women	O
surrounded	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
too	O
much	O
frighten	O
'd	O
to	O
take	O
Notice	O
of	O
any	O
particular	O
Person	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
there	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Holms	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
On	O
Shrove-Tuesday	O
Eve	O
,	O
I	O
and	O
William	O
Corrie	O
,	O
and	O
Robert	O
Anderson	O
,	O
met	O
together	O
,	O
as	O
usual	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
Newtoner	O
's	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
we	O
agreed	O
to	O
go	O
a	O
Thieving	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
with	O
us	O
;	O
we	O
rais	O
'd	O
a	O
Mobb	O
in	O
Chancery-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pick	O
'd	O
this	O
Gentlewoman	O
's	O
Pocket	O
of	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
after	O
sold	O
for	O
12	O
Guineas	O
to	O
two	O
Jews	O
that	O
lived	O
in	O
Duke's-Place	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
their	O
Names	O
is	O
John	B-pers
Barnet	I-pers
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
forgot	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
has	O
stole	O
Watches	O
out	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Churches	O
in	O
London	O
.	O
She	O
took	O
my	O
Lady	O
Coventry	O
's	O
Watch	O
set	O
with	O
Diamonds	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Lady	O
Rainbow	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
more	O
.	O
Her	O
House	O
is	O
a	O
Place	O
of	O
Entertainment	O
for	O
none	O
but	O
Whores	O
and	O
Thieves	O
.	O
Several	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Neighbours	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
civil	O
Woman	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
kept	O
an	O
orderly	O
House	O
.	O
A	O
Jew	O
being	O
present	O
,	O
inform	O
'd	O
the	O
Court	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
such	O
Name	O
among	O
the	O
Jews	O
as	O
John	B-pers
Barnet	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
val	O
.	O
25	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Jumps	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Rowny	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
30	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
as	O
Mary	O
Rowny	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
One	B-place
Swan	I-place
Yard	I-place
in	I-place
Bishopsgate-Street	I-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pulled	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
her	O
crying	O
,	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Revel	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
val	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Gascoyn	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
12	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Mann	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Billingsgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Jackets	O
val	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Loan	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
12	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Ship	O
lay	O
in	O
Billingsgate	B-place
Dock	I-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Waterman	O
,	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Cabbin	O
about	O
Midnight	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
perceived	O
just	O
as	O
he	O
went	O
off	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
he	O
dropt	O
the	O
Jackets	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
Thames-Street	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Wastecoat	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
three	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
seven	O
Shirts	O
val	O
.	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Watford	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Gerrard	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
1	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Gerrard	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
Budge-Row	B-place
,	O
(	O
with	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
a	O
Convict	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
who	O
lay	O
for	O
Transportation	O
)	O
and	O
found	O
Means	O
to	O
go	O
off	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
pursued	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
in	O
Newgate-Street	O
with	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Croxton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Nixon	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
8	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Hester	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Bampton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Acton	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Table-Cloth	O
,	O
a	O
Sarcenet-hood	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Stockings	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Lock	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
3	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Pack-Horse	O
at	O
Turnham-Green	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Lydia	B-pers
Pancrage	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Isabella	B-pers
James	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Leggy	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Steel-Box	O
,	O
two	O
Moidores	O
,	O
two	O
Bags	O
,	O
14	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
l.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
James	O
Thomas	O
,	O
Sept.	O
29	O
.	O
James	O
Thomas	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Publick-House	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Lydia	O
was	O
my	O
Servant	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
out	O
one	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
under	O
Pretence	O
of	O
fetching	O
in	O
the	O
Pots	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
no	O
more	O
that	O
day	O
.	O
Next	O
Morning	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
Drawers	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
20	O
l.	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Drawers	O
with	O
this	O
Iron	O
Skewer	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Isabel	O
James	O
,	O
who	O
put	O
her	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
afterwards	O
got	O
Part	O
of	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
took	O
Isabel	O
James	O
,	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
I	O
examined	O
Lydia	O
where	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
fell	O
a-sleep	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
Sibby	O
James	O
and	O
the	O
Coachman	O
got	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
went	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
together	O
to	O
the	O
Musick	O
House	O
in	O
S.	O
George	O
's	O
Fields	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
the	O
Fact	O
by	O
herself	O
.	O
By	O
her	O
Directions	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
Box	O
with	O
a	O
Guinea	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
hid	O
in	O
her	O
Bed	O
at	O
the	O
Ax	O
in	O
Aldermanbury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
two	O
Guineas	O
in	O
the	O
Bottom	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
box	O
in	O
Lydia	O
's	O
Hand	O
;	O
't	O
is	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
box	O
.	O
Isabel	O
James	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Lydia	O
Pancrage	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Whalebone	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Wellbone	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
returning	O
from	O
Transportation	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Expiration	O
of	O
Seven	O
Years	O
.	O
The	O
Record	O
was	O
read	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
thus	O
deposed	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
:	O
About	O
two	O
Years	O
ago	O
I	O
apprehended	O
him	O
for	O
robbing	O
Mr.	O
Moor	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
Try	O
'd	O
,	O
Convicted	O
,	O
and	O
Transported	O
.	O
I	O
afterwards	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
thither	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
how	O
he	O
dared	O
appear	O
again	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
as	O
much	O
Mischief	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
first	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Forward	I-pers
:	O
This	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
ship	O
'd	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Forward	O
Galley	O
,	O
Oct.	O
5	O
.	O
1723	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
him	O
well	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
unruly	O
,	O
that	O
we	O
were	O
forced	O
to	O
put	O
him	O
in	O
double	O
Irons	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Brian	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Lawson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hackney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
val	O
.	O
9	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Can	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
l.	O
Six	O
Shirts	O
val	O
.	O
16	O
s.	O
a	O
Quilt	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
Napkins	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Delamarie	I-pers
,	O
in	O
her	O
Dwelling-House	O
,	O
Sept.	O
24	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
Servant	O
to	O
Capt	O
.	O
Delamarie	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Husband	O
:	O
)	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
lived	O
a-part	O
from	O
her	O
Husband	O
several	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
imagined	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
too	O
familiar	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
died	O
suddenly	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
took	O
Possession	O
of	O
his	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
and	O
Effects	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
finding	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
remember	O
'd	O
had	O
formerly	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
she	O
accused	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
appearing	O
the	O
least	O
Colour	O
of	O
a	O
Proof	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
granted	O
her	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
her	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Chiswick	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
150	O
lb	O
of	O
Lead	O
val	O
.	O
22	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Pankeman	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
24	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Lead	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
being	O
proved	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Lead	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sack	O
and	O
four	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Malt	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
8	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Winifred	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Head-Cloaths	O
val	O
.	O
7s	O
.	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Theade	B-pers
Cleave	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
25	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Breaking	O
and	O
Entering	O
(	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rowden	I-pers
already	O
convicted	O
)	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
14	O
Pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
Nov.	O
6	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Flemmer	I-pers
(	O
who	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
convicted	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
)	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
there	O
wanted	O
sufficient	O
Proof	O
to	O
fix	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Matson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
,	O
in	O
Cursing	O
and	O
speaking	O
several	O
false	O
and	O
seditious	O
Words	O
against	O
his	O
Majesty	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
drinking	O
the	O
Pretender	O
's	O
Health	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Oct.	O
1	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Murrel	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
Last	O
Friday	O
Night	O
,	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Tobacco-Roll	B-place
and	I-place
Sugar	I-place
Loaf	I-place
in	I-place
Winford-Street	I-place
in	I-place
Petticoat-Lane	I-place
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
drank	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
another	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Marshal	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ralph	I-pers
(	O
two	O
Soldiers	O
)	O
were	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
.	O
Some	O
Difference	O
arising	O
betwix	O
them	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
them	O
King	O
George	O
's	O
Bull-Dogs	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
King	O
James	O
the	O
Third	O
had	O
more	O
Right	O
to	O
the	O
Crown	O
than	O
King	O
George	O
.	O
Somebody	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
Constable	O
and	O
Watch	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
another	O
Pint	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
ye	O
altogether	O
;	O
Here	O
's	O
a	O
good	O
Health	O
to	O
King	O
James	O
the	O
Third	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
drank	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Marshal	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ralph	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Here	O
's	O
God	O
bless	O
King	O
James	O
the	O
Third	O
,	O
and	O
G	O
-	O
D	O
-	O
King	O
George	O
.	O
he	O
has	O
no	O
Right	O
to	O
the	O
Crown	O
;	O
and	O
G	O
-	O
D	O
-	O
all	O
King	O
George	O
's	O
Bull-Dogs	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
drank	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Denton	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Murrel	O
's	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
stay	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
:	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
,	O
King	O
James	O
has	O
more	O
right	O
than	O
King	O
George	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
that	O
he	O
curs	O
'd	O
his	O
Majesty	O
,	O
or	O
drank	O
any	O
Health	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hambleton	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drink	O
the	O
Pretender	O
's	O
Health	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
King	O
James	O
the	O
Third	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
carrying	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
D	O
-	O
King	O
George	O
and	O
his	O
Country	O
too	O
;	O
and	O
bade	O
the	O
Soldiers	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Rogue	O
their	O
Master	O
.	O
Several	O
Persons	O
appear	O
'd	O
in	O
Behalf	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
many	O
Years	O
,	O
had	O
often	O
been	O
in	O
his	O
Company	O
,	O
drunk	O
and	O
sober	O
;	O
but	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
swearing	O
,	O
or	O
meddling	O
with	O
the	O
Government	O
one	O
way	O
or	O
other	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
order	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
pay	O
a	O
Fine	O
of	O
twenty	O
Marks	O
,	O
suffer	O
a	O
Year	O
's	O
Imprisonment	O
,	O
and	O
stand	O
twice	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
,	O
once	O
near	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
the	O
Crime	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
once	O
at	O
Charing-cross	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Hughs	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Gether	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Salt	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Hood	O
,	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Headcloaths	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Jane	O
Iverson	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Iverson	I-pers
.	O
July	O
26	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
Girl	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
who	O
keeps	O
the	O
Bull	B-place
Alehouse	I-place
in	I-place
Sherborn-Lane	I-place
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
happening	O
to	O
leave	O
the	O
Key	O
in	O
her	O
Chamber-Door	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
lock	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
directly	O
with	O
the	O
Key	O
.	O
She	O
took	O
Coach	O
for	O
Bristol	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Fortune	O
worth	O
500	O
l.	O
and	O
40	O
l.	O
per	O
annum	O
;	O
but	O
having	O
no	O
Success	O
,	O
she	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
fell	O
into	O
Company	O
with	O
a	O
Waterman	O
last	O
Wednesday	O
Night	O
,	O
was	O
marry	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
Country	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Val	O
.	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Simmons	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
(	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Morrison	I-pers
)	O
eight	O
Hundred	O
Weight	O
of	O
Sugar	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
l.	O
and	O
60	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Henry	O
Allen	O
,	O
Aug.	O
30	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Morrison	O
(	O
who	O
is	O
since	O
dead	O
)	O
were	O
Apprentice	O
s	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
a	O
Confectioner	O
in	O
Lombard-Street	B-place
.	O
John	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
In	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sold	O
2	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Candy	O
'd	O
Orange-Peel	O
for	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
he	O
and	O
Morrison	O
shared	O
the	O
Money	O
betwixt	O
them	O
.	O
On	O
April	O
25	O
,	O
he	O
sold	O
6	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Biskets	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
time	O
4	O
lb	O
.	O
and	O
put	O
but	O
half	O
the	O
Money	O
into	O
the	O
Till	O
,	O
and	O
parted	O
the	O
other	O
half	O
betwixt	O
himself	O
and	O
Morrison	O
.	O
At	O
another	O
time	O
,	O
he	O
sold	O
4	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Citron	O
for	O
10	O
s.	O
kept	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
of	O
it	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
another	O
Half	O
Crown	O
to	O
Morrison	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
can	O
reckon	O
up	O
about	O
15	O
s.	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
taken	O
in	O
this	O
manner	O
.	O
One	O
Day	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
had	O
done	O
so	O
,	O
they	O
brought	O
a	O
Shilling	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
a	O
naked	O
Knife	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Shilling	O
.	O
One	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
they	O
both	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
rob	O
an	O
Orchard	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
them	O
where	O
the	O
Apples	O
were	O
?	O
D	O
-	O
ye	O
,	O
says	O
Morrison	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
tell	O
ye	O
where	O
they	O
are	O
;	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
rip	O
me	O
up	O
with	O
his	O
Knife	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
prevented	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Allen	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
Leave	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Bartholomew	O
Fair	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
not	O
being	O
very	O
busy	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
Leave	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
no	O
more	O
till	O
next	O
Week	O
,	O
when	O
his	O
Father	O
brought	O
him	O
home	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
him	O
backwards	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
his	O
Father	O
to	O
the	O
Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
his	O
Father	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
his	O
Son	O
had	O
wrong	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
We	O
sent	O
for	O
him	O
over	O
;	O
he	O
seem	O
'd	O
very	O
much	O
concern	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
Morrison	O
had	O
drawn	O
him	O
into	O
such	O
a	O
Combination	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
would	O
be	O
the	O
utter	O
Ruin	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
had	O
made	O
a	O
Practice	O
of	O
sending	O
out	O
Sugar	O
in	O
Boxes	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Quantity	O
of	O
about	O
Eight	O
Hundred	O
Weight	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
sold	O
for	O
4	O
d.	O
a	O
Pound	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
it	O
was	O
worth	O
7	O
d.	O
His	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Steele	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
returning	O
from	O
Transportation	O
before	O
the	O
Expiration	O
of	O
Seven	O
Years	O
.	O
The	O
Record	O
being	O
read	O
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Ely	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
Man	O
that	O
was	O
transported	O
for	O
stealing	O
Mr.	O
Walker	O
's	O
Coat	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
try	O
'd	O
here	O
and	O
convicted	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
aboard	O
the	O
Lighter	O
for	O
Transportation	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
this	O
Chissel	O
and	O
a	O
Pistol	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
thus	O
made	O
his	O
Defence	O
:	O
I	O
faithfully	O
served	O
my	O
Master	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
above	O
six	O
Years	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
:	O
He	O
died	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Mistress	O
discharged	O
me	O
before	O
the	O
Governor	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
wanting	O
but	O
a	O
few	O
Months	O
of	O
the	O
seven	O
Years	O
being	O
expired	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
come	O
home	O
to	O
see	O
my	O
Wife	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
found	O
that	O
since	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
transported	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
marry	O
'd	O
this	O
Isaac	B-pers
Ely	I-pers
,	O
who	O
apprehended	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
swears	O
against	O
me	O
only	O
to	O
get	O
rid	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
may	O
have	O
my	O
Wife	O
to	O
himself	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Hand	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Busby	I-pers
a	O
Wastecoat	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
Shirt	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
Knives	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Will	O
.	O
Busby	O
,	O
Sept.	O
15	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
(	O
with	O
Joseph	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
)	O
a	O
Coat	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Winslow	I-pers
Sept.	O
21	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
2d	O
to	O
the	O
Val	O
.	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Street	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
assaulting	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
ravish	O
,	O
and	O
(	O
against	O
her	O
Will	O
)	O
carnally	O
know	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Harvison	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Infant	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Age	O
of	O
17	O
Years	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
the	O
same	O
in	O
effect	O
as	O
was	O
given	O
last	O
Sessions	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
try	O
'd	O
for	O
ravishing	O
the	O
said	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Harvison	I-pers
,	O
we	O
shall	O
not	O
repeat	O
it	O
here	O
,	O
but	O
referr	O
the	O
Reader	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
Paper	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
,	O
order	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
pay	O
a	O
Fine	O
of	O
20	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
suffer	O
6	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
follows	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
Seven	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Longmire	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Steele	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Little	I-pers
,	O
Foster	B-pers
Snow	I-pers
,	O
Lydia	B-pers
Pancrage	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Whalebone	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
Whipt	O
,	O
Two	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Draper	I-pers
;	O
from	O
S.	O
Clement	O
's	O
Church	O
to	O
the	O
New	O
Church	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
One	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Simmons	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
,	O
Forty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Day	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Gibbons	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Pattison	I-pers
,	O
Laurence	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Cotton	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Cusy	I-pers
,	O
Alice	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Moor	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Tongason	I-pers
,	O
Rachel	B-pers
Coe	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Jefferson	I-pers
,	O
Katharine	B-pers
Blackbourn	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Wilks	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Kiff	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Sculthorp	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
,	O
Rachel	B-pers
Pearson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hughs	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
Isabella	B-pers
Hanshaw	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Sargeant	I-pers
,	O
Elias	B-pers
Sharp	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Holms	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Ferguson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Higgs	I-pers
,	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Revel	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Mann	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Croxton	I-pers
,	O
Hester	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
,	O
Winifred	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Hughs	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Philip	B-pers
Hand	I-pers
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Matson	I-pers
fined	O
Twenty	O
Marks	O
,	O
to	O
suffer	O
a	O
Year	O
's	O
Imprisonment	O
,	O
and	O
stand	O
twice	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
to	O
pay	O
Twenty	O
Marks	O
each	O
,	O
and	O
suffer	O
a	O
Year	O
's	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
Samuel	O
Street	O
to	O
pay	O
Twenty	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
suffer	O
six	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
Just	O
publish	O
'd	O
,	O
A	O
PRACTICAL	O
TREATISE	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
Second	O
Thoughts	O
on	O
the	O
Consequences	O
of	O
the	O
VENEREAL	O
DISEASE	O
.	O
In	O
Three	O
Parts	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Simple	O
Gonorrhoea	O
,	O
Gleets	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Weaknesses	O
,	O
whether	O
from	O
Venereal	O
Embraces	O
,	O
Self-Pollution	O
,	O
improperly	O
call	O
'd	O
Onanism	O
,	O
or	O
Natural	O
Imbecillity	O
.	O
II	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Vinulent	O
Gonorrhoea	O
,	O
or	O
Clap	O
.	O
III	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Venereal	O
Lues	O
,	O
or	O
Grand	O
Pox	O
.	O
Wherein	O
are	O
plainly	O
shew	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
exact	O
Degrees	O
of	O
Difference	O
;	O
with	O
their	O
Signs	O
,	O
Symptoms	O
,	O
Prognosticks	O
,	O
and	O
Cures	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
Cases	O
;	O
their	O
Beginnings	O
,	O
Progress	O
,	O
and	O
fatal	O
Periods	O
,	O
when	O
neglected	O
,	O
or	O
unskilfully	O
managed	O
;	O
and	O
how	O
their	O
absolute	O
Cure	O
,	O
without	O
Violence	O
,	O
or	O
Injury	O
,	O
is	O
completed	O
.	O
With	O
proper	O
and	O
effectual	O
Remedies	O
,	O
in	O
their	O
several	O
Stages	O
,	O
prescribed	O
and	O
recommended	O
therein	O
.	O
With	O
some	O
Remarks	O
on	O
that	O
preposterous	O
Way	O
of	O
Venery	O
,	O
with	O
Machine	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
a	O
plain	O
Discovery	O
of	O
the	O
Dangers	O
(	O
tho	O
'	O
little	O
expected	O
)	O
which	O
attend	O
that	O
vile	O
Practice	O
.	O
And	O
many	O
other	O
useful	O
Discoveries	O
relating	O
to	O
Infections	O
in	O
both	O
Sexes	O
,	O
not	O
before	O
taken	O
Notice	O
of	O
.	O
The	O
Whole	O
fitted	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
for	O
the	O
Advantage	O
of	O
Patients	O
,	O
as	O
young	O
Practisers	O
.	O
By	O
Joseph	B-pers
Cam	I-pers
,	O
M	O
D.	O
Printed	O
for	O
the	O
Author	O
;	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
W.	O
Mears	O
without	O
Temple-Bar	O
,	O
G.	O
Strahan	O
against	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
C.	O
King	O
in	O
Westminster-Hall	O
,	O
T.	O
Norris	O
on	O
London-bridge	O
,	O
and	O
J.	O
Baker	O
over-against	O
Hatton-Garden	O
in	O
Holborn	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
Lately	O
made	O
publick	O
,	O
BASIL	B-pers
VALENTINE	I-pers
's	O
Tinctura	O
Mirabilis	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
AN	O
admirable	O
Tincture	O
for	O
the	O
Tooth-Ach	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
Disorders	O
and	O
Defects	O
of	O
the	O
Teeth	O
and	O
Gums	O
When	O
once	O
used	O
,	O
it	O
gives	O
present	O
Ease	O
in	O
the	O
most	O
tormenting	O
Pain	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
only	O
takes	O
it	O
away	O
in	O
a	O
Moment	O
,	O
but	O
absolutely	O
cures	O
the	O
Tooth-Ach	O
,	O
so	O
as	O
certainly	O
to	O
prevent	O
its	O
return	O
:	O
It	O
certainly	O
preserves	O
the	O
Teeth	O
from	O
growing	O
rotten	O
,	O
and	O
those	O
that	O
are	O
a	O
little	O
decay	O
'd	O
from	O
becoming	O
worse	O
:	O
It	O
makes	O
the	O
foulest	O
Teeth	O
as	O
white	O
as	O
Ivory	O
:	O
At	O
once	O
using	O
it	O
fastens	O
those	O
that	O
are	O
loose	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
an	O
admirable	O
and	O
wonderful	O
Medicine	O
against	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
in	O
the	O
Gums	O
;	O
for	O
by	O
the	O
simple	O
Application	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Directions	O
,	O
it	O
cures	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
be	O
it	O
never	O
so	O
violent	O
,	O
or	O
of	O
long	O
continuance	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
no	O
Quack	O
Medicine	O
to	O
blind	O
the	O
Eyes	O
of	O
the	O
Publick	O
,	O
but	O
is	O
certainly	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
best	O
chymical	O
Medicines	O
that	O
ever	O
was	O
made	O
publick	O
for	O
that	O
Purpose	O
:	O
It	O
causes	O
the	O
Gums	O
to	O
grow	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Teeth	O
again	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
full	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
those	O
who	O
have	O
occasion	O
to	O
use	O
it	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
neither	O
disagreeable	O
to	O
the	O
Smell	O
or	O
Taste	O
,	O
but	O
really	O
preserves	O
the	O
Teeth	O
and	O
Gums	O
from	O
all	O
manner	O
of	O
Foulness	O
,	O
Corruption	O
,	O
and	O
Putrefaction	O
.	O
The	O
many	O
Numbers	O
that	O
daily	O
use	O
it	O
,	O
never	O
miss	O
of	O
a	O
perfect	O
Cure	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
Bottle	O
is	O
enough	O
for	O
any	O
one	O
Person	O
for	O
their	O
whole	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
may	O
be	O
depended	O
upon	O
to	O
answer	O
the	O
Character	O
here	O
given	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
every	O
respect	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
had	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Garaway	O
's	O
the	O
South	O
Gate	O
of	O
the	O
Royal-Exchange	O
;	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Neal	O
's	O
Toy-shop	O
over-against	O
the	O
White	O
Hart	O
Inn	O
,	O
Southwark	O
;	O
at	O
Francis	B-pers
Robotham	I-pers
's	O
Toy-shop	O
next	O
the	O
Gridiron	O
,	O
without	O
the	O
Bars	O
,	O
Whitechappel	O
;	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Greggs	O
,	O
Bookseller	O
,	O
next	O
Northumber-land-House	O
,	O
Charing-Cross	O
;	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Aishmale	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
Buckle-shop	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Albemarle-street	O
,	O
Pickadilly	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
Widow	O
Trent	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
upper	O
End	O
of	O
King-street	O
,	O
next	O
the	O
Golden	O
Lion	O
,	O
Westminster	O
;	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Sotro	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Indian	O
Queen	O
,	O
Great	O
Turn-stile	O
.	O
Holborn	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
Mitre	O
in	O
Jewin	O
street	O
,	O
near	O
Aldersgate-street	O
;	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Walford	O
's	O
,	O
Picture	O
Frame-maker	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Angel	O
and	O
Crown	O
in	O
New-Rent	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Harrow	O
Corner	O
,	O
Southwark	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Barbara	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
's	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Crown	O
,	O
in	O
Harlow	O
,	O
in	O
Essex	O
;	O
at	O
One	O
Shilling	O
the	O
Bottle	O
,	O
with	O
Directions	O
,	O
sealed	O
with	O
the	O
Lion	O
Rampant	O
.	O
Any	O
Merchants	O
,	O
or	O
Travellers	O
by	O
Sea	O
or	O
Land	O
,	O
may	O
be	O
furnish	O
'd	O
with	O
it	O
Wholesale	O
,	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Garraway	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
South-Gate	O
of	O
the	O
Royal-Exchange	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Robotham	O
's	O
above-said	O
,	O
at	O
reasonable	O
Rates	O
,	O
with	O
Allowance	O
to	O
them	O
that	O
sell	O
it	O
in	O
any	O
place	O
of	O
the	O
Kingdom	O
.	O
It	O
will	O
keep	O
its	O
Virtue	O
Time	O
out	O
of	O
Remembrance	O
.	O
Beware	O
of	O
Counterfeits	O
.	O
Each	O
Bottle	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
is	O
sealed	O
as	O
above	O
.	O
As	O
it	O
is	O
needless	O
to	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
the	O
behalf	O
of	O
a	O
Book	O
,	O
that	O
has	O
pass	O
'd	O
with	O
universal	O
Approbation	O
thro	O
'	O
nine	O
Editions	O
of	O
2000	O
each	O
,	O
the	O
Booksellers	O
it	O
is	O
printed	O
for	O
only	O
give	O
Notice	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
Day	O
is	O
publish	O
'd	O
the	O
Tenth	O
Edition	O
of	O
,	O
ONANIA	O
,	O
Or	O
the	O
Heinous	O
Sin	O
of	O
Self-Pollution	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
its	O
frightful	O
Consequences	O
in	O
both	O
Sexes	O
consider	O
'd	O
,	O
with	O
Spiritual	O
and	O
Physical	O
Advice	O
to	O
those	O
who	O
have	O
already	O
injur	O
'd	O
themselves	O
by	O
that	O
abominable	O
Practice	O
.	O
In	O
which	O
are	O
many	O
very	O
remarkable	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
even	O
astonithing	O
Letters	O
from	O
Persons	O
of	O
both	O
Sexes	O
,	O
young	O
and	O
old	O
,	O
single	O
and	O
marry	O
'd	O
,	O
concerning	O
their	O
Self-Abuses	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Also	O
Letters	O
from	O
Clergymen	O
,	O
Physicians	O
,	O
School-masters	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
Casuistical	O
,	O
of	O
Cases	O
of	O
Conscience	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
with	O
Answers	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
from	O
a	O
Lady	O
very	O
curious	O
,	O
concerning	O
the	O
lawful	O
Use	O
and	O
sinful	O
Abuse	O
of	O
the	O
Marriage	O
Bed	O
,	O
with	O
Histories	O
or	O
Cases	O
and	O
Cures	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
And	O
one	O
from	O
another	O
young	O
marry	O
'd	O
Lady	O
who	O
by	O
that	O
detestable	O
Practice	O
became	O
barren	O
and	O
diseased	O
.	O
A	O
learned	O
Divine	O
and	O
Physician	O
has	O
recommended	O
this	O
Book	O
in	O
these	O
Words	O
:	O
This	O
little	O
Book	O
ought	O
to	O
be	O
read	O
by	O
all	O
Sorts	O
of	O
People	O
,	O
of	O
both	O
Sexes	O
,	O
of	O
what	O
Age	O
,	O
Degree	O
,	O
Profession	O
or	O
Condition	O
soever	O
,	O
Guilty	O
or	O
not	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Sin	O
declaim	O
'd	O
against	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Sold	O
by	O
T.	O
Crouch	O
at	O
the	O
Bell	O
in	O
Pater-noster-Row	O
near	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
and	O
J.	O
Isted	O
at	O
the	O
Golden	O
Ball	O
by	O
S.	O
Dunstan	O
's	O
Church	O
,	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
Booksellers	O
.	O
Price	O
stitch	O
'd	O
Two	O
Shillings	O
.	O
BOOKS	O
just	O
publish	O
'd	O
,	O
I.	O
ONANIA	O
Examin	O
'd	O
and	O
Detected	O
;	O
or	O
,	O
the	O
Ignorance	O
,	O
Error	O
,	O
Impertinence	O
and	O
Contradiction	O
of	O
a	O
Book	O
call	O
'd	O
ONANIA	O
,	O
discover	O
'd	O
and	O
detected	O
;	O
wherein	O
also	O
is	O
consider	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Differences	O
and	O
sundry	O
Degrees	O
of	O
Self-Pollution	O
in	O
both	O
Sexes	O
;	O
with	O
Choice	O
of	O
suitable	O
Remedies	O
both	O
for	O
extinguishing	O
excessive	O
Desires	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
for	O
strengthening	O
the	O
Bodies	O
of	O
such	O
as	O
have	O
been	O
hurt	O
by	O
Voluntary	O
or	O
Nocturnal	O
Emissions	O
.	O
Together	O
with	O
some	O
Thoughts	O
on	O
the	O
Use	O
of	O
the	O
Marriage	O
Bed	O
,	O
whether	O
there	O
can	O
be	O
sinful	O
Excesses	O
therein	O
,	O
or	O
it	O
can	O
be	O
defiled	O
without	O
a	O
third	O
Person	O
;	O
with	O
the	O
Opinions	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
Learned	O
and	O
Approved	O
Authors	O
,	O
as	O
Divines	O
,	O
Physicians	O
and	O
Surgeons	O
,	O
and	O
suitable	O
Observations	O
added	O
by	O
the	O
Author	O
.	O
The	O
whole	O
interspers	O
'd	O
with	O
Variety	O
of	O
Subjects	O
,	O
both	O
serious	O
and	O
jocose	O
.	O
The	O
2d	O
Edition	O
.	O
By	O
Philo	O
Castitatis	O
;	O
price	O
stitcht	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
II	O
.	O
Authentick	O
Memoits	O
of	O
the	O
Life	O
and	O
surprizing	O
Adventures	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
executed	O
at	O
Tyburn	O
,	O
November	O
16	O
,	O
1724	O
.	O
The	O
2d	O
Edition	O
.	O
Adorn	O
'd	O
with	O
Variety	O
of	O
Copper	O
Cuts	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
1	O
s.	O
III	O
.	O
The	O
Order	O
of	O
Causes	O
of	O
God	O
's	O
Foreknowledge	O
,	O
Election	O
,	O
Predestination	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
Man	O
's	O
Salvation	O
and	O
Damnation	O
;	O
as	O
also	O
whether	O
Christ	O
died	O
for	O
all	O
,	O
or	O
not	O
for	O
all	O
.	O
By	O
Henry	B-pers
Haggar	I-pers
.	O
The	O
6th	O
Edition	O
.	O
price	O
6	O
d.	O
IV	O
.	O
The	O
Art	O
of	O
Spelling	O
.	O
By	O
J.	O
P.	O
M.	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
5th	O
Edition	O
,	O
with	O
Additions	O
.	O
V.	O
La	O
Plume	O
Volante	O
;	O
or	O
.	O
The	O
Art	O
of	O
Short-Hand	O
improved	O
;	O
being	O
the	O
most	O
swift	O
,	O
regular	O
,	O
and	O
easy	O
Method	O
of	O
Short-Hand-Writing	O
yet	O
extant	O
:	O
Composed	O
after	O
40	O
Years	O
Practice	O
and	O
Improvement	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Art	O
.	O
By	O
William	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
;	O
price	O
bound	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
VI	O
.	O
An	O
Essay	O
concerning	O
the	O
Infinite	O
Wisdom	O
of	O
God	O
.	O
manifested	O
in	O
the	O
Continuance	O
and	O
Structure	O
of	O
the	O
Skin	O
of	O
Human	O
Bodies	O
;	O
price	O
1	O
s.	O
VII	O
.	O
The	O
young	O
Man	O
's	O
Guide	O
;	O
being	O
a	O
plain	O
Discovery	O
of	O
the	O
Art	O
of	O
Drawing	O
,	O
Engraving	O
in	O
Copper	O
to	O
the	O
Life	O
.	O
The	O
to	O
each	O
Pictures	O
or	O
other	O
things	O
with	O
Aqua	O
fortis	O
;	O
price	O
1	O
s.	O
VIII	O
.	O
The	O
Agreement	O
of	O
the	O
Customs	O
of	O
the	O
East-Indians	O
,	O
with	O
those	O
of	O
the	O
Jews	O
and	O
other	O
Ancient	O
People	O
;	O
with	O
Cuts	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
are	O
added	O
,	O
Instructions	O
to	O
young	O
Gentlemen	O
that	O
intend	O
to	O
travel	O
;	O
price	O
bound	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
All	O
printed	O
for	O
Jof	O
.	O
Marshall	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
in	O
Newgate-street	O
