TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Fail-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
a	O
Special	O
Commission	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
pursuant	O
to	O
a	O
Statute	O
made	O
in	O
the	O
33d	O
of	O
Hen	O
.	O
VIII	O
.	O
for	O
trying	O
Offences	O
committed	O
beyond	O
the	O
Seas	O
,	O
and	O
out	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
;	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
1	O
st	O
,	O
and	O
2d	O
Days	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Eleventh	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
GEORGE	B-pers
MERTTINS	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Lord	O
Chief	B-pers
Baron	I-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Dormer	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
Sergeant	O
at	O
Law	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
JURORS	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
The	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pestell	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Cowdry	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Horton	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mayhew	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Logar	I-pers
,	O
Roger	B-pers
Oram	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Milwell	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
King	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hull	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Phipps	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Champion	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Coombs	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Team	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Boyd	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
follows	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Badger	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
Boy	O
)	O
of	O
the	O
Old	B-place
Jewry	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Frances	B-pers
Gill	I-pers
,	O
4	O
l.	O
13	O
s.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
F.	O
Gill	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
Francis	O
Gill	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Shoomaker	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
found	O
him	O
,	O
several	O
times	O
guilty	O
of	O
Pilfering	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
turn	O
'd	O
him	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
his	O
father	O
giving	O
me	O
a	O
Bond	O
for	O
his	O
Honesty	O
,	O
I	O
consented	O
to	O
try	O
him	O
a	O
little	O
longer	O
.	O
But	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
soon	O
after	O
found	O
my	O
Drawers	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
mist	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Father	O
's	O
Bond	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
about	O
two	O
Weeks	O
after	O
,	O
with	O
two	O
green	O
Purses	O
,	O
and	O
38	O
s.	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
were	O
my	O
Purses	O
,	O
and	O
Part	O
of	O
my	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
burnt	O
his	O
Father	O
's	O
Bond	O
.	O
Guilty	O
val	O
.	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Ithell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Alhallows	B-place
Staining	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
30	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Lead	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
Singleton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
May	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Eastcheap	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Wyat	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Bishopsgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
14	O
lb	O
.	O
Brass	O
Weight	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
William	O
Andrews	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Bludwick	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Aldgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Callimanco	O
Shoos	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Clogs	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dunce	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
who	O
sold	O
them	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
him	O
entrusted	O
to	O
sell	O
such	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
informed	O
the	O
Jury	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Offence	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
Felony	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
thereupon	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	I-pers
Spinster	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Bostock	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Bostock	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Swithin	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Petty	O
Treason	O
and	O
Murder	O
,	O
by	O
feloniously	O
and	O
traiterously	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
giving	O
Rich	B-pers
.	I-pers
Bostock	I-pers
her	O
Husband	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
in	O
the	O
left	O
Side	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
short	O
Ribs	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Breadth	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
six	O
Inches	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Rich	O
.	O
Bostock	O
.	O
Tho	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
Watchman	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Door	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
Jumbling	O
:	O
I	O
answer	O
'd	O
first	O
with	O
my	O
Staff	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
by	O
word	O
of	O
Mouth	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
her	O
Husband	O
at	O
the	O
Cock	O
Alehouse	O
;	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
must	O
needs	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
never	O
suspected	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
lived	O
an	O
abominable	O
Life	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
after	O
,	O
when	O
my	O
Hour	O
was	O
fulfill	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
the	O
Door	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Deccased	O
standing	O
with	O
the	O
Door	O
a-jar	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
light	O
his	O
Candle	O
;	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
down	O
Stars	O
with	O
no	O
kind	O
of	O
thing	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
her	O
Cap	O
and	O
her	O
Smock	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
just	O
had	O
a	O
Glimpse	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
threw	O
the	O
Door	O
against	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
force	O
of	O
it	O
beat	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Street	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
the	O
Deceased	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
shut	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
Lumbering	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Deceased	O
cry	O
,	O
Lord	O
!	O
Lord	O
!	O
Lord	O
!	O
Whereupon	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
were	O
got	O
to	O
their	O
old	O
Trade	O
of	O
Quarrelling	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
pass	O
'd	O
on	O
to	O
my	O
Stand	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
after	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
somebody	O
call	O
Watch	O
!	O
Watch	O
!	O
And	O
upon	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
out	O
and	O
heard	O
that	O
the	O
poor	O
Man	O
was	O
departed	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
willing	O
to	O
go	O
upon	O
my	O
own	O
Head	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
inform	O
'd	O
the	O
Constable	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
his	O
Instruction	O
for	O
keeping	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Constable	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
he	O
a-lying	O
upon	O
the	O
Floor	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
stab	O
'd	O
into	O
the	O
Body	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Coat	O
,	O
Wastecoat	O
,	O
and	O
Shirt	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Blood	O
lay	O
guthing	O
out	O
upon	O
the	O
Floor	O
under	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
much	O
Discourse	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
As	O
I	O
came	O
thro	O
'	O
Dover	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stood	O
at	O
her	O
Door	O
with	O
a	O
Candle	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Watch	O
:	O
But	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
she	O
saw	O
me	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
Pray	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Cooper	O
,	O
come	O
in	O
and	O
help	O
my	O
Husband	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
stept	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
lying	O
upon	O
the	O
Floor	O
,	O
with	O
nothing	O
upon	O
his	O
Back	O
but	O
his	O
Shirt	O
.	O
See	O
there	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
how	O
he	O
lies	O
dead	O
drunk	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
lift	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Life	O
in	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
whether	O
he	O
's	O
drunk	O
or	O
no	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
's	O
dead	O
.	O
Lord	O
!	O
What	O
shall	O
I	O
do	O
?	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
threw	O
something	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
I	O
have	O
given	O
him	O
an	O
unhappy	O
Blow	O
.	O
-	O
For	O
God	O
's	O
Sake	O
call	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
'T	O
is	O
too	O
late	O
now	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
had	O
better	O
call	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
of	O
your	O
Neighbours	O
.	O
And	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
in	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
People	O
thereabouts	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
,	O
upon	O
removing	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
we	O
perceived	O
a	O
great	O
Wound	O
in	O
his	O
Left	O
Side	O
.	O
Nathanael	B-pers
West	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
Constable	O
:	O
It	O
was	O
just	O
past	O
One	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
when	O
my	O
Watchman	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Man	O
dead	O
at	O
the	O
Pastry-Cook	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sitting	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
in	O
a	O
melancholy	O
Posture	O
;	O
the	O
Deceased	O
sitting	O
on	O
the	O
Floor	O
at	O
her	O
Feet	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
Head	O
leaning	O
in	O
her	O
Lap	O
.	O
I	O
quickly	O
perveiv	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
stab	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
as	O
much	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
About	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Yards	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
Wastecoat	O
,	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
sharp	O
pointed	O
Case-Knife	O
:	O
It	O
was	O
greasy	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
look	O
'd	O
a	O
little	O
tarnish	O
'd	O
with	O
Blood	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
rub	O
'd	O
the	O
Tarnish	O
with	O
my	O
Finger	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
not	O
come	O
off	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Coat	O
and	O
Wastecoat	O
,	O
and	O
here	O
's	O
the	O
Shirt	O
.	O
-	O
You	O
may	O
perceive	O
that	O
they	O
're	O
all	O
bloody	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Left	O
Side	O
of	O
each	O
of	O
'em	O
you	O
may	O
see	O
the	O
Holes	O
where	O
the	O
Knife	O
went	O
thro	O
'	O
.	O
-	O
Before	O
this	O
Accident	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
several	O
times	O
been	O
call	O
'd	O
off	O
my	O
Watch	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
crying	O
out	O
Murder	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
quarrelling	O
.	O
Swarton	O
(	O
another	O
Watchman	O
)	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
upon	O
Duty	O
at	O
my	O
Stand	O
,	O
(	O
near	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
House	O
)	O
having	O
just	O
been	O
beating	O
Eleven	O
o'Clock	O
;	O
and	O
not	O
long	O
after	O
,	O
comes	O
the	O
Deceased	O
and	O
knocks	O
at	O
his	O
own	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
stood	O
knocking	O
for	O
the	O
Space	O
of	O
a	O
considerable	O
time	O
;	O
but	O
no-body	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
Mythinks	O
,	O
Master	O
Bostock	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
they	O
ca	O
n't	O
,	O
choose	O
but	O
hear	O
you	O
.	O
Hear	O
me	O
!	O
Yes	O
,	O
L	O
-	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
hears	O
me	O
well	O
enough	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
'll	O
give	O
it	O
her	O
by	O
and	O
by	O
:	O
And	O
so	O
at	O
last	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
that	O
lodges	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
let	O
him	O
in	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
beat	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
severely	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
suppose	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
cry	O
out	O
Murder	O
!	O
And	O
then	O
down	O
he	O
comes	O
again	O
.	O
Doctor	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
(	O
for	O
so	O
he	O
always	O
call	O
'd	O
me	O
)	O
I	O
have	O
given	O
it	O
her	O
,	O
to	O
her	O
Heart	O
's	O
Content	O
.	O
The	O
more	O
Shame	O
for	O
you	O
then	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
to	O
beat	O
your	O
Wife	O
at	O
such	O
a	O
rate	O
.	O
My	O
Wife	O
!	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
her	O
,	O
a	O
Bitch	O
,	O
she	O
's	O
none	O
of	O
my	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
turn	O
her	O
a-drift	O
to-morrow	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
for	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
again	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
my	O
dear	O
Creature	O
is	O
dead	O
.	O
-	O
Dead	O
!	O
Ay	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
be	O
's	O
murder	O
'd	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
himself	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
.	O
And	O
this	O
is	O
all	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
a-bed	O
with	O
my	O
Wife	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
great	O
Jumbling	O
below	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
usual	O
betwixt	O
the	O
Deceased	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
mind	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
quickly	O
over	O
.	O
Being	O
afterwards	O
call	O
'd	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
stab	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
himself	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Scot	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
I	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Breast	O
and	O
lower	O
Belly	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
.	O
He	O
received	O
the	O
Wound	O
betwixt	O
the	O
7th	O
and	O
8th	O
Ribs	O
,	O
counting	O
from	O
above	O
downwards	O
;	O
it	O
pass	O
'd	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Midriff	O
and	O
the	O
Left	O
Lobe	O
of	O
the	O
Lungs	O
to	O
the	O
Left	O
Ventricle	O
of	O
the	O
Heart	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
it	O
terminated	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
thus	O
made	O
her	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
work	O
late	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
very	O
much	O
tir	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
fell	O
into	O
a	O
sound	O
Sleep	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
beat	O
me	O
in	O
a	O
violent	O
and	O
barbarous	O
manner	O
,	O
pull	O
'd	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
Bed	O
,	O
tore	O
all	O
my	O
Linnen	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
down	O
Stairs	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
served	O
me	O
so	O
several	O
times	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
always	O
used	O
to	O
humour	O
him	O
,	O
by	O
going	O
down	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
giving	O
him	O
good	O
Words	O
to	O
coax	O
him	O
to	O
Bed	O
again	O
;	O
tho	O
'	O
indeed	O
I	O
was	O
never	O
married	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Now	O
I	O
suppose	O
that	O
I	O
not	O
coming	O
to	O
fetch	O
him	O
up	O
so	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
expected	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
vex	O
'd	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
stab	O
'd	O
himself	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
not	O
(	O
I	O
believe	O
)	O
with	O
a	O
Design	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
his	O
own	O
Life	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
to	O
territy	O
me	O
,	O
by	O
making	O
me	O
think	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
himself	O
a	O
greater	O
Mischief	O
than	O
he	O
really	O
had	O
:	O
But	O
I	O
suppose	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
found	O
himself	O
wounded	O
deeper	O
than	O
he	O
intended	O
,	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
towards	O
the	O
Cock	O
to	O
wash	O
himself	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
too	O
weak	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
fall	O
down	O
.	O
I	O
staid	O
above	O
a	O
pretty	O
while	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
up	O
again	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
Accord	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
not	O
coming	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
as	O
naked	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
was	O
born	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
and	O
seeing	O
him	O
lie	O
all	O
along	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
either	O
in	O
Fitts	O
,	O
or	O
feign	O
'd	O
himself	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
.	O
-	O
Speak	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
Dickey	O
,	O
(	O
says	O
I	O
)	O
My	O
dear	O
Dickey	O
speak	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
do	O
n't	O
lie	O
so	O
to	O
frighten	O
me	O
:	O
But	O
he	O
made	O
no	O
Answer	O
.	O
-	O
As	O
to	O
what	O
Mr.	O
Cooper	O
swore	O
about	O
my	O
saying	O
I	O
had	O
given	O
the	O
Deceased	O
an	O
unhappy	O
Blow	O
,	O
he	O
mistook	O
my	O
Words	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
given	O
me	O
many	O
an	O
unhappy	O
Blow	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
second	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
my	O
Compter-Drawer	O
,	O
ty	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Glove	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Small-Beer	O
;	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
An	O
Acquaintance	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
inform	O
'd	O
me	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
8	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
his	O
Stockings	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Drawer	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Bride	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Iron	O
Linch-Pins	O
of	O
a	O
Cart	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gilmore	I-pers
,	O
9	O
Iron	O
Washes	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Linch-Pins	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Value	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Smock	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Head-Cloaths	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
four	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Rich	B-pers
.	I-pers
Chetham	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
Guilty	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Margery	B-pers
Thackum	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver-handled	O
Knife	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charlotte	B-pers
Burrows	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Smock	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
Guilty	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Emery	B-pers
alias	I-pers
Uriah	I-pers
Parry	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminter	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Siver-hilted	O
Sword	O
val	O
.	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edmund	B-pers
Fitzgerald	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
Instalment	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Friends	O
,	O
hired	O
a	O
Room	O
to	O
themselves	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Lloyd	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Old	B-place
Palace-Yard	I-place
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
waited	O
upon	O
'em	O
;	O
he	O
being	O
hired	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Lloyd	O
to	O
assist	O
in	O
attending	O
Company	O
for	O
that	O
Day	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
laid	O
his	O
Sword	O
in	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
without	O
it	O
.	O
Some	O
other	O
of	O
the	O
Servants	O
going	O
to	O
clear	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
that	O
Sword	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
;	O
they	O
told	O
him	O
whose	O
Sword	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
carry	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
assured	O
them	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
for	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
'd	O
keep	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
nothing	O
by	O
his	O
Master	O
that	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
was	O
resolved	O
to	O
take	O
Care	O
of	O
himself	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Mony	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Muns	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Val	O
.	O
30	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Gosling	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Islington	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Plough	O
Wheels	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Sett	O
of	O
Iron	O
Wiles	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Plough	O
Hooks	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Guidot	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Masters	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
King	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
in	O
Westminster	B-place
Hall	I-place
;	O
which	O
the	O
Constable	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Giles	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
having	O
Notice	O
given	O
him	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Pick-pocket	O
,	O
he	O
watch	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
he	O
found	O
one	O
Handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
twenty	O
three	O
in	O
his	O
Codpiece	O
;	O
all	O
which	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Moorsam	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stratford-le-Bow	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
bay	O
Mare	O
val	O
.	O
7	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
John	O
Brown	O
,	O
has	O
deposed	O
:	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
Mare	O
from	O
a	O
Common	O
near	O
Spalding	B-place
.	O
After	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sent	O
me	O
Word	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
her	O
to	O
Tho	B-pers
Lankton	I-pers
near	O
Barking	O
in	O
Essex	O
;	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
at	O
Bow	O
in	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Brown	O
's	O
Daughter	O
rode	O
the	O
Mare	O
up	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
order	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
Lankton	O
not	O
appearing	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Mare	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hogg	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
(	O
a	O
Girl	O
of	O
about	O
ten	O
Years	O
old	O
)	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hogg	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Hogg	I-pers
,	O
(	O
the	O
Girl	O
's	O
Mother	O
)	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Hogg	O
(	O
the	O
Daughter	O
)	O
for	O
stealing	O
40	O
Bobbins	O
,	O
and	O
16	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Legee	O
Silk	O
val	O
.	O
72	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	O
Hogg	O
(	O
the	O
Mother	O
)	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Girl	O
had	O
been	O
employ	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
wind	O
Silk	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
at	O
Night	O
she	O
frequently	O
used	O
to	O
steal	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Bobbins	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
them	O
home	O
to	O
her	O
Mother	O
,	O
who	O
advised	O
her	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Her	O
Mother	O
sold	O
the	O
Silk	O
to	O
Anne	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
in	O
Drury	B-place
's	I-place
Rents	I-place
in	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
for	O
16	O
d.	O
a	O
Pound	O
:	O
Anne	O
Moore	O
knowing	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
stolen	O
.	O
Their	O
Confessions	O
were	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Picart	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Gandon	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
marrying	O
Philip	B-pers
Bouchain	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
her	O
former	O
Husband	O
John	B-pers
Gandon	I-pers
being	O
then	O
living	O
;	O
to	O
whom	O
she	O
was	O
marry	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Sixth	O
Year	O
of	O
King	O
William	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Paul	B-pers
Gandon	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
Mine	O
Broder	O
Jean	O
,	O
and	O
dis	O
Voman	O
,	O
de	O
Preesoner	O
,	O
was	O
marie	O
togader	O
at	O
Stapaney	O
Shursh	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
vas	O
den	O
prasant	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
vary	O
long	O
time	O
ago	O
,	O
-	O
me	O
no	O
remember	O
ho	O
'	O
long	O
;	O
-	O
't	O
is	O
more	O
dan	O
twanty	O
Year	O
.	O
-	O
Dare	O
vas	O
de	O
Ministre	O
Anglois	O
,	O
dare	O
vas	O
de	O
putting	O
de	O
Ring	O
upon	O
de	O
feenger	O
,	O
dare	O
vas	O
de	O
putting	O
de	O
Hands	O
togader	O
,	O
and	O
de	O
oder	O
tings	O
,	O
dat	O
be	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
in	O
de	O
Mariage	O
;	O
don	O
after	O
dis	O
,	O
dey	O
live	O
a	O
togader	O
so	O
as	O
de	O
Man	O
and	O
de	O
Vife	O
;	O
and	O
mine	O
Broder	O
get	O
von	O
,	O
two	O
,	O
tree	O
Shild	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
now	O
mine	O
Broder	O
be	O
grown	O
von	O
old	O
Man	O
,	O
-	O
he	O
no	O
make	O
more	O
Shild	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
marie	O
dis	O
oder	O
Man	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Bouchain	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
Me	O
vas	O
marie	O
to	O
dis	O
Voman	O
,	O
dat	O
is	O
true	O
,	O
de	O
twanty	O
fourt	O
of	O
dis	O
Mont	O
,	O
a	O
six	O
Heures	O
after	O
de	O
Noon	O
,	O
a	O
l'Enseigne	O
de	O
Hand	O
and	O
de	O
Pen	O
in	O
de	O
Fleet-Lane	B-place
,	O
and	O
me	O
give	O
tree	O
Shilling	O
to	O
de	O
Parsoon	O
;	O
but	O
me	O
vas	O
vary	O
much	O
elevate	O
vid	O
de	O
Liquor	O
,	O
and	O
dis	O
,	O
and	O
dat	O
,	O
and	O
toder	O
,	O
so	O
dat	O
me	O
no	O
could	O
tell	O
vat	O
I	O
did	O
ven	O
de	O
ting	O
was	O
done	O
.	O
But	O
me	O
no	O
go	O
to	O
Bed	O
vid	O
mine	O
Vife	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
for	O
in	O
were	O
,	O
four	O
Heures	O
after	O
de	O
Ceremonie	O
was	O
over	O
,	O
dare	O
come	O
in	O
some	O
Relationg	O
of	O
mine	O
Spouse	O
,	O
and	O
dey	O
make	O
de	O
grand	O
None	O
and	O
de	O
Uproar	O
,	O
dat	O
me	O
no	O
could	O
tink	O
vat	O
a	O
Drable	O
vas	O
de	O
Matter	O
vid	O
dem	O
;	O
but	O
in	O
a	O
leetel	O
time	O
dey	O
tell	O
a	O
me	O
dat	O
I	O
must	O
no	O
do	O
vid	O
mine	O
Vife	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
vas	O
belong	O
to	O
anoder	O
Man	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
dey	O
take	O
her	O
quite	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
me	O
vas	O
force	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Bed	O
vid	O
mine	O
self	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
thus	O
made	O
her	O
Defence	O
:	O
Me	O
have	O
but	O
von	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
dat	O
is	O
Jean	B-pers
Gandon	I-pers
;	O
tor	O
dis	O
Man	O
,	O
Philip	O
Bouchain	O
,	O
be	O
none	O
Husband	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Vat	O
signifie	O
de	O
Parsoon	O
,	O
and	O
de	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
de	O
Ceremonie	O
,	O
vy	O
dat	O
no	O
make	O
de	O
Husband	O
,	O
dare	O
be	O
no	O
Husband	O
,	O
no	O
Vife	O
,	O
till	O
dey	O
go	O
to	O
Bed	O
togader	O
.	O
But	O
Monsieur	O
Benchain	O
,	O
he	O
no	O
do	O
vid	O
me	O
in	O
de	O
Bed	O
,	O
he	O
do	O
nothing	O
in	O
de	O
Varld	O
;	O
-	O
noting	O
but	O
de	O
Ceremonie	O
;	O
-	O
vy	O
den	O
dat	O
be	O
no	O
Husband	O
.	O
There	O
not	O
being	O
a	O
legal	O
Proof	O
of	O
the	O
second	O
Marriage	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Broad-Piece	O
val	O
.	O
23	O
s.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Drury	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
keeps	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
at	O
Mile-End	B-place
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Lodger	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
Ten	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
fell	O
asleep	O
together	O
in	O
the	O
Chimney	O
Corner	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
awake	O
till	O
after	O
Eleven	O
,	O
when	O
feeling	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
a	O
Broad-Piece	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
there	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
sleep	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
suspected	O
,	O
was	O
examined	O
;	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
lying	O
upon	O
the	O
Dresser	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Henly	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sheet	O
,	O
four	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
a	O
Box-Iron	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
Shirts	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Trinder	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Stockton	I-pers
of	O
S.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Colme	I-pers
;	O
Cha	O
.	O
Smith	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
near	O
the	O
Right	O
Breast	O
of	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
four	O
Inches	O
,	O
and	O
Breadth	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
;	O
and	O
John	O
Stockton	O
for	O
being	O
present	O
,	O
aiding	O
and	O
abetting	O
the	O
said	O
Smith	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Maccauley	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
The	O
Deceased	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Smith	O
were	O
Comrades	O
,	O
and	O
lodg	O
'd	O
together	O
at	O
the	O
Bell	B-place
Alehouse	I-place
in	I-place
Bell-Yard	I-place
in	I-place
King-Street	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
.	O
At	O
this	O
Place	O
they	O
and	O
Stockton	O
(	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
were	O
drinking	O
together	O
upon	O
the	O
Saturday	O
Evening	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
kill	O
'd	O
.	O
Some	O
Words	O
pass	O
'd	O
betwixt	O
them	O
in	O
Dutch	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
understand	O
;	O
but	O
afterwards	O
the	O
Deceased	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
challeng	O
'd	O
Smith	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Privy-Garden	O
and	O
fight	O
him	O
.	O
Smith	O
appeared	O
very	O
unwilling	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Deceased	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
fight	O
with	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Smith	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
last	O
.	O
Stockton	O
follow	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
did	O
I	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
more	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Privy-Garden	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
stript	O
,	O
and	O
drew	O
first	O
;	O
but	O
Smith	O
said	O
,	O
We	O
had	O
better	O
let	O
Fighting	O
alone	O
,	O
Peter	O
:	O
-	O
The	O
Point	O
of	O
my	O
Sword	O
is	O
broke	O
:	O
-	O
We	O
have	O
seen	O
old	O
Comrades	O
,	O
and	O
why	O
should	O
we	O
fall	O
out	O
?	O
However	O
,	O
Peter	O
would	O
needs	O
fight	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
shook	O
Hands	O
and	O
made	O
several	O
Pushes	O
at	O
one	O
another	O
.	O
Smith	O
wounded	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
surgeon	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
dead	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Lamb	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
Peter	O
Colme	O
(	O
the	O
Deceased	O
)	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
quarrelling	O
at	O
the	O
Bell	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
says	O
Peter	O
to	O
Stockton	O
,	O
You	O
think	O
yourself	O
a	O
brave	O
Fellow	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
you	O
fancy	O
you	O
're	O
a	O
better	O
Man	O
than	O
me	O
,	O
come	O
out	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
fight	O
you	O
.	O
Stockton	O
declin	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
Peter	O
grew	O
very	O
passionate	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
challeng	O
'd	O
either	O
of	O
'em	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
quickly	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
,	O
that	O
Peter	O
and	O
Smith	O
were	O
gone	O
to	O
the	O
Privy-Garden	O
to	O
fight	O
.	O
Stockton	O
was	O
still	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
meddle	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
intend	O
it	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
shall	O
get	O
no	O
Credit	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
and	O
I	O
follow	O
'd	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Deceased	O
stript	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
naked	O
Sword	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
rather	O
forbear	O
Fighting	O
,	O
said	O
Smith	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Point	O
of	O
my	O
Sword	O
is	O
blunted	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Ogden	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
the	O
Privy	O
Garden	O
,	O
Stockton	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
Gate-way	O
,	O
thro	O
'	O
which	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
Men	O
in	O
a	O
Posture	O
of	O
fighting	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
have	O
gone	O
in	O
that	O
Way	O
;	O
but	O
Stockton	O
having	O
a	O
Stick	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
very	O
sower	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
to	O
venture	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
ran	O
round	O
another	O
Way	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
wounded	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
then	O
made	O
their	O
Defence	O
.	O
While	O
we	O
were	O
drinking	O
with	O
Peter	O
,	O
(	O
said	O
Smith	O
)	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
Maid	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
to	O
change	O
for	O
some	O
Meat	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
Peter	O
bid	O
her	O
take	O
all	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
out	O
of	O
that	O
Money	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
meant	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
.	O
What	O
Man	O
is	O
that	O
?	O
says	O
I	O
.	O
Why	O
,	O
a	O
Rascally	O
Fellow	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
again	O
.	O
But	O
if	O
you	O
are	O
so	O
bright	O
a	O
Man	O
as	O
you	O
think	O
yourself	O
,	O
come	O
out	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
see	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
mind	O
to	O
quarrel	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
said	O
but	O
little	O
more	O
.	O
Then	O
Stockton	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Cards	O
;	O
Peter	O
won	O
several	O
Games	O
,	O
and	O
Stockton	O
would	O
play	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
Peter	O
then	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
play	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
deny	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
some	O
other	O
Words	O
arising	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
Come	O
out	O
if	O
you	O
dare	O
fight	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
quiet	O
.	O
He	O
put	O
up	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
beckoned	O
me	O
to	O
follow	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
to	O
the	O
Privy	O
Garden	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
drew	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
strips	O
himself	O
.	O
Comrade	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
What	O
makes	O
you	O
so	O
quarrelsome	O
?	O
You	O
do	O
n't	O
use	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
.	O
If	O
I	O
have	O
offended	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
beg	O
your	O
Pardon	O
.	O
-	O
You	O
are	O
a	O
Coward	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
to	O
ask	O
a	O
Man	O
's	O
Pardon	O
,	O
before	O
you	O
have	O
ty	O
'd	O
what	O
he	O
can	O
do	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
post	O
you	O
for	O
such	O
as	O
one	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
fight	O
.	O
The	O
Thames	O
was	O
just	O
behind	O
me	O
and	O
a	O
Wall	O
on	O
each	O
Side	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
stept	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
fight	O
now	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
Point	O
of	O
my	O
Sword	O
was	O
broke	O
;	O
but	O
all	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
say	O
to	O
prevent	O
the	O
Engagement	O
,	O
signify	O
'd	O
nothing	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
we	O
would	O
shake	O
Hands	O
first	O
,	O
which	O
with	O
much	O
ado	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
Stockton	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Smith	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Aldgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
two	O
Yards	O
of	O
Lace	O
val	O
.	O
10s	O
.	O
two	O
Suits	O
of	O
Headcloaths	O
val	O
.	O
10s	O
.	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Francis	O
Lloyd	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
val	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dicks	I-pers
,	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoos	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Tho	O
.	O
Dicks	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
val	O
.	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Aldgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tea-Spoon	O
val	O
.	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
Guilty	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Mead	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
Girl	O
)	O
of	O
Wapping	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coat	O
and	O
Wastecoat	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Dobbins	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
at	O
a	O
Trap-Door	O
on	O
the	O
House	O
Top	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Chest	O
,	O
and	O
hid	O
herself	O
and	O
them	O
under	O
a	O
Bed	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
discovered	O
by	O
a	O
Chairwoman	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Pennington	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
blanket	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
two	O
Contains	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Susan	B-pers
Higgons	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
Guilty	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Teeling	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Job	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
,	O
by	O
violently	O
beating	O
and	O
throwing	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languish	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
saying	O
the	O
said	O
Job	O
Dixon	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
About	O
Three	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Deceased	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
were	O
playing	O
at	O
Cards	O
in	O
a	O
Brandy	O
Shop	O
by	O
Stocks	B-place
Market	I-place
,	O
I	O
tipt	O
the	O
Wink	O
upon	O
the	O
Deceased	O
;	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
perceiving	O
,	O
he	O
challenged	O
me	O
to	O
fight	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Pest-Fields	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
accepted	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
thither	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
fought	O
for	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
Minutes	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
gave	O
out	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
fight	O
any	O
one	O
that	O
takes	O
your	O
Part	O
.	O
-	O
Will	O
you	O
?	O
(	O
said	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
)	O
Then	O
I	O
am	O
your	O
Man	O
:	O
Whereupon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
struck	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
stript	O
and	O
fell	O
to	O
it	O
ding	O
dong	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Knocks	O
together	O
:	O
The	O
Deceased	O
was	O
thrown	O
twice	O
,	O
and	O
appeared	O
not	O
at	O
all	O
to	O
be	O
hurt	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
kick	O
'd	O
up	O
his	O
Heels	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Grass	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
lay	O
stretch	O
'd	O
out	O
like	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
.	O
He	O
complain	O
'd	O
of	O
his	O
Back	O
and	O
Neck	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
for	O
fetching	O
a	O
Coach	O
to	O
carry	O
him	O
Home	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
his	O
Game	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
dead	O
already	O
?	O
-	O
Ill	O
carry	O
you	O
Home	O
upon	O
my	O
Back	O
;	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
we	O
got	O
a	O
Chair	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
died	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Burdon	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
foul	O
Play	O
,	O
not	O
any	O
Stones	O
where	O
the	O
Deceased	O
fell	O
.	O
'T	O
is	O
a	O
Place	O
of	O
Trees	O
and	O
Grass	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Sort	O
of	O
Burying	O
Ground	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
a	O
capable	O
Judge	O
how	O
the	O
Man	O
came	O
by	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Clements	I-pers
the	O
Surgeon	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
put	O
to	O
Bed	O
:	O
I	O
could	O
perceive	O
no	O
Fracture	O
,	O
no	O
Wound	O
,	O
no	O
Dislocation	O
,	O
nor	O
even	O
any	O
Discolouring	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
the	O
Use	O
of	O
all	O
his	O
Limbs	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
no	O
more	O
Strength	O
than	O
a	O
New-born	O
Child	O
.	O
I	O
suspected	O
indeed	O
that	O
his	O
Skull	O
was	O
fractured	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
otherwise	O
by	O
putting	O
something	O
in	O
his	O
Mouth	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
held	O
fast	O
with	O
his	O
Teeth	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
think	O
what	O
could	O
be	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
,	O
except	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Distortion	O
of	O
the	O
Spinal	O
Marrow	O
,	O
which	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Use	O
of	O
his	O
Limbs	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Sanson	I-pers
,	O
Apothecary	O
,	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
informed	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
fell	O
backwards	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
Neck	O
almost	O
double	O
;	O
by	O
which	O
Fall	O
't	O
is	O
likely	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Ligament	O
that	O
holds	O
the	O
Vertebrae	O
of	O
the	O
Neck	O
was	O
extended	O
;	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
great	O
Concussion	O
of	O
the	O
Bones	O
,	O
the	O
Spinal	O
Marrow	O
was	O
distorted	O
,	O
which	O
might	O
be	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Wilding	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
The	O
Deceased	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
were	O
such	O
great	O
Cronies	O
before	O
this	O
Boxing	O
Bout	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
but	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Bread	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
wanted	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
his	O
Wife	O
go	O
without	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
Court	O
demanded	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
any	O
way	O
distemper	O
'd	O
before	O
this	O
Misfortune	O
happened	O
?	O
To	O
which	O
this	O
Evidence	O
thus	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
a	O
confident	O
Judge	O
of	O
such	O
Matters	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
disease	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
some	O
that	O
are	O
left	O
behind	O
are	O
the	O
worse	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
-	O
Dixon	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Father	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Deceased	O
say	O
,	O
The	O
Rogue	O
that	O
I	O
loved	O
so	O
well	O
has	O
killed	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Calighan	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
a	O
Ring	O
,	O
two	O
Moidores	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
l.	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Aldred	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dowler	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jefferies	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
(	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
did	O
assault	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
,	I-pers
the	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Patrick	I-pers
Lion	I-pers
,	O
and	O
take	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
and	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Elizabeth	O
Lion	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
who	O
are	O
Bailiff	O
s	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
about	O
Five	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
.	O
Richardson	O
threw	O
me	O
upon	O
my	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
'd	O
be	O
my	O
Death	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Then	O
Dowler	O
took	O
me	O
a	O
Slap	O
o'the	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
dash	O
'd	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
Teeth	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
his	O
Penknife	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
stick	O
my	O
Heart	O
's	O
Blood	O
out	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
let	O
Richardson	O
do	O
so	O
and	O
so	O
.	O
Whereof	O
he	O
took	O
away	O
my	O
Pocket-Apron	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Ring	O
and	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
but	O
the	O
Ring	O
dropt	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
got	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
sha	O
n't	O
mind	O
what	O
they	O
say	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
as	O
good	O
a	O
Character	O
as	O
any	O
Woman	O
in	O
my	O
Business	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
White	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Chelsea	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Jefferies	O
a	O
making	O
Water	O
at	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Lion	O
's	O
Door	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Jefferies	O
?	O
said	O
I	O
.	O
Will	O
you	O
go	O
in	O
and	O
drink	O
with	O
me	O
?	O
No	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
Couple	O
of	O
Friends	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
expect	O
a	O
little	O
Fun	O
by	O
and	O
by	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Shower	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
Lodger	O
in	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Lion	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
Richardson	O
threw	O
her	O
down	O
;	O
Jefferies	O
held	O
her	O
Hands	O
;	O
and	O
Douler	O
with	O
a	O
Penknife	O
cut	O
her	O
across	O
the	O
Forehead	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
stick	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Heart	O
if	O
She	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
quietly	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
--	O
--	O
What	O
d	O
'ye	O
call	O
it	O
?	O
--	O
--	O
her	O
Pocket-Apron	O
;	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
it	O
quite	O
off	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
then	O
made	O
their	O
Defence	O
.	O
This	O
Good-Woman	O
(	O
says	O
Dowler	O
)	O
keeps	O
a	O
Bawdy-House	O
in	O
Chelsea	B-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
and	O
I	O
going	O
thither	O
to	O
arrest	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
Plyers	O
,	O
a	O
whole	O
Heap	O
of	O
them	O
fell	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
narrowly	O
escaped	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
shall	O
prove	O
by	O
good	O
Witness	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
I	O
live	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
Mother	O
Lion	O
's	O
.	O
-	O
Dowler	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
came	O
thither	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
Betty	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
advised	O
them	O
not	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
People	O
were	O
quarrelsome	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
would	O
go	O
in	O
:	O
Whereupon	O
Mother	O
Lion	O
took	O
and	O
thrust	O
Betty	O
Palmer	O
into	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
Backsides	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
dare	O
swear	O
she	O
has	O
got	O
twenty	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
calls	O
out	O
to	O
two	O
Irish	O
Hay-makers	O
that	O
belong	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
Come	O
out	O
ye	O
Sons	O
of	O
Bitches	O
,	O
for	O
here	O
's	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Thieving	O
Bailiffs	O
.	O
They	O
fell	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
tore	O
their	O
Shirts	O
off	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
knock	O
down	O
Dowler	O
with	O
a	O
Quart	O
Bottle	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
prevented	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
who	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
got	O
his	O
Pitch-Fork	O
,	O
and	O
Dowler	O
ran	O
for	O
a	O
Mop-Stick	O
:	O
One	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Poker	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
the	O
Tongs	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
went	O
at	O
it	O
to	O
some	O
Tune	O
,	O
and	O
Dowler	O
nointed	O
the	O
Haymaker	O
handsomely	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Herring	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Herring	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Buckles	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
Mother	O
of	O
Pearl	O
Snuff-Box	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Massia	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
at	O
the	O
Fire	O
in	O
Little	B-place
Suffolk	I-place
Street	I-place
.	O
Guilty	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Le	I-pers
Count	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Peter	B-pers
Covington	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Kettle	O
,	O
a	O
Pot	O
,	O
a	O
Cullender	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Hough	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Henly	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
,	O
in	O
unlawfully	O
removing	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
a	O
Copper	O
from	O
the	O
Freehold	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Hough	I-pers
.	O
To	O
both	O
which	O
Indictments	O
Covington	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Le	O
Count	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Rowly	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Tooly	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Lofty	I-pers
,	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Eady	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bledall	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Blakely	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Brewer	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
Shirts	O
,	O
two	O
Caps	O
,	O
and	O
six	O
Pillowbers	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Gaffington	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Curtains	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
Bledall	O
brought	O
the	O
Goods	O
into	O
a	O
Room	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
sitting	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
found	O
and	O
apprehended	O
together	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
all	O
except	O
Bledall	O
,	O
who	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
in	O
his	O
Tryal	O
upon	O
the	O
first	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Aberdeen	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
,	I-pers
the	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Cammel	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Pocket	O
,	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Scurrel	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Carrol	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Beds	O
,	O
four	O
Pillows	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Bolsters	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Carcass	O
of	O
a	O
Lamb	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Parr	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
Marshall	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
Stevens	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transp	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Miles	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Fir	O
Timber	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Gill	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Edmonds	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
He	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rawlins	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
thirteen	O
Cocks	O
,	O
two	O
Hens	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
Chickens	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Hains	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
He	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
Ludgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Purse	O
,	O
7	O
Broad-Pieces	O
,	O
4	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
set	O
with	O
Diamonds	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
from	O
Alexander	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
Alexander	O
Ross	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
invited	O
her	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
Glass	O
.	O
She	O
perceiving	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Foreigner	O
,	O
spoke	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
French	O
;	O
and	O
we	O
agreed	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Dog	B-place
Tavern	I-place
upon	I-place
Ludgate-Hill	I-place
.	O
While	O
we	O
were	O
drinking	O
there	O
,	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
lend	O
her	O
some	O
Money	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
to	O
lend	O
;	O
and	O
putting	O
my	O
Hand	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
Two	O
Shillings	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
;	O
therefore	O
I	O
must	O
give	O
her	O
more	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
took	O
out	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
it	O
a	O
Silk	O
Purse	O
that	O
I	O
brought	O
from	O
Berlin	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
green	O
or	O
blue	O
.	O
She	O
took	O
the	O
Half	O
Crown	O
,	O
and	O
pray	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
look	O
upon	O
the	O
Purse	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
very	O
much	O
admired	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
emptied	O
it	O
into	O
her	O
Lap	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
7	O
Broad	O
Pieces	O
,	O
4	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
set	O
with	O
Diamonds	O
.	O
She	O
look	O
'd	O
them	O
all	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
my	O
Purse	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
return	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
my	O
Pocket	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
long	O
before	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
(	O
knowing	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
little	O
busy	O
about	O
my	O
Breeches	O
)	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
taken	O
it	O
in	O
Jest	O
?	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
never	O
saw	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
for	O
going	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
stopt	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Drawer	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
bring	O
another	O
Bottle	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
her	O
so	O
unwilling	O
to	O
stay	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
bring	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
look	O
well	O
about	O
the	O
Room	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
dropt	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
unwilling	O
to	O
take	O
my	O
Eye	O
off	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
might	O
have	O
no	O
Opportunity	O
of	O
conveying	O
the	O
Purse	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Drawer	O
then	O
told	O
us	O
,	O
if	O
we	O
would	O
not	O
agree	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
away	O
quietly	O
,	O
he	O
'd	O
fetch	O
a	O
Constable	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
did	O
I	O
charged	O
the	O
Constable	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
excused	O
himself	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
'd	O
let	O
any	O
Woman	O
search	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Man	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
search	O
'd	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Constable	O
carry	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
Prison	O
;	O
but	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Solomon	B-pers
Southall	I-pers
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
Southall	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Humphries	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
a	O
Brass	O
Pot	O
,	O
6	O
Plates	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pewter-Dish	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
;	O
and	O
Edward	O
Vaughan	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stoln	O
.	O
Vaughan	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Southall	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Emerson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
May	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
defrauding	O
Richard	B-pers
Wattorfe	I-pers
of	O
96	O
Yards	O
of	O
Sacking	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
defrauding	O
Hamlet	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
of	O
90	O
Yards	O
of	O
Sacking	O
.	O
Richard	O
Wattorfe	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
A	O
Man	O
bought	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Sacking	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
order	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
bring	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
White-Hart	B-place
Alehouse	I-place
in	I-place
Gracechurch-street	I-place
,	O
and	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
paid	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
Man	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
bid	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
for	O
the	O
Money	O
to	O
his	O
Uncle	O
Strange	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Salutation	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Lombard	O
Street	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
Goods	O
at	O
the	O
White-Hart	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
Salutation	O
.	O
He	O
stept	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
his	O
Uncle	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
the	O
Coffee-House	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
began	O
to	O
mistrust	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
lay	O
hold	O
on	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
aware	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
took	O
to	O
his	O
Heels	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
go	O
look	O
my	O
Cloth	O
and	O
be	O
damn	O
'd	O
.	O
Hamlet	O
Johnson	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
A	O
Man	O
bought	O
some	O
Sacking	O
of	O
me	O
at	O
Hoxton	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
bring	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Hercules	B-place
Pillars	I-place
near	O
Temple	O
Bar	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
Chapman	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sat	O
drinking	O
by	O
himself	O
;	O
and	O
my	O
Chap	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
the	O
Cloth	O
for	O
his	O
Uncle	O
Strange	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
Cloth	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
'em	O
both	O
to	O
the	O
Horseshoo	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
lighted	O
his	O
Pipe	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Man	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
after	O
,	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
were	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
?	O
Why	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
's	O
gone	O
to	O
a	O
Brother	O
of	O
mine	O
at	O
the	O
Hercules	O
Pillars	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
'll	O
go	O
and	O
see	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
walks	O
out	O
leisurely	O
with	O
his	O
Pipe	O
in	O
his	O
Mouth	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
came	O
back	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
up	O
with	O
a	O
Search-Warrant	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Pillory	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Brace	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Beak	I-pers
;	O
and	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
and	O
17	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Barbara	B-pers
Pomfret	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hancock	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Froome	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
once	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
two	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Bodice	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoos	O
and	O
Clog	O
's	O
,	O
four	O
Brass	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
L'Estange	I-pers
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Carton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
20	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
John	B-pers
Burbeck	I-pers
Senior	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Mitchell	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Gown	O
val	O
.	O
20s	O
.	O
a	O
Night-Gown	O
10	O
d	O
,	O
a	O
Smock	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Ruffles	O
5	O
s.	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Sylvester	I-pers
.	O
Mary	O
Sylvester	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
lodged	O
about	O
a	O
Month	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
with	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
Servants	O
;	O
and	O
sometimes	O
had	O
Let	O
Victuals	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
in	O
out	O
of	O
Charity	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
Return	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
of	O
going	O
away	O
with	O
my	O
Goods	O
,	O
one	O
Day	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
a	O
visiting	O
:	O
But	O
upon	O
Enquiry	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
Long-Acre	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
saw	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
fell	O
on	O
her	O
Knees	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
my	O
Pardon	O
,	O
and	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
brought	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
indeed	O
lent	O
her	O
a	O
Smock	O
or	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
or	O
so	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
that	O
she	O
stands	O
indicted	O
for	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
Sylvester	O
keeps	O
a	O
notorious	O
Bawdy	O
House	O
in	O
Bond	O
street	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
taken	O
Whores	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
House	O
many	O
a	O
time	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Bawdy	O
three	O
Sessions	O
ago	O
.	O
-	O
She	O
served	O
her	O
Time	O
with	O
Mother	O
Needham	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
Sylvester	O
decoy	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
she	O
put	O
these	O
Cloaths	O
upon	O
her	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
receive	O
Company	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
too	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Note	O
for	O
15	O
l.	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
allow	O
her	O
12	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Week	O
for	O
her	O
Board	O
.	O
And	O
tho	O
'	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
yet	O
but	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
Clap	O
'd	O
and	O
Pox	O
'd	O
again	O
and	O
again	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
from	O
whence	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Hospital	O
,	O
and	O
gone	O
thro	O
'	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Salivations	O
;	O
and	O
now	O
this	O
wicked	O
Bawd	O
wants	O
to	O
hang	O
the	O
poor	O
Creature	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
has	O
run	O
away	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
granted	O
her	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
her	O
Indictment	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Carron	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
val	O
.	O
40	O
s.	O
two	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Webster	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Warn	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Val	O
.	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Abell	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Dabell	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
bay	O
Gelding	O
val	O
.	O
8l	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Yarrow	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Calf	O
val	O
.	O
16	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Hughs	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Pinners	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Bridget	B-pers
Barrington	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Barrington	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Gile	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Goodman	I-pers
52	O
s.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Thomas	O
Goodman	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
excessive	O
Modesty	O
not	O
suffering	O
him	O
to	O
appear	O
and	O
give	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
directed	O
the	O
Jury	O
to	O
acquit	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
his	O
Recognizance	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Blaithwaite	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Braithwait	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Wapping	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
two	O
Gowns	O
val	O
.	O
27	O
s.	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
three	O
Scarves	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
s.	O
three	O
Hoods	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
s.	O
thirty	O
Yards	O
of	O
Lace	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mitchell	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Mitchell	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
a	O
Shop	O
(	O
or	O
a	O
Stall	O
)	O
on	O
the	O
Backside	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	B-place
,	O
there	O
being	O
only	O
a	O
thin	O
Deal	O
Partition	O
betwixt	O
them	O
,	O
Part	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
removed	O
into	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Shop	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Field	I-pers
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Iron	O
Chissel	O
,	O
value	O
One	O
Penny	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
Margaret	B-pers
Mortimer	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coat	O
and	O
Wastecoat	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bartlet	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Birmingham	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Shirt	O
val	O
.	O
12d	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Fossar	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Elliot	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Dimity	O
Mantles	O
val	O
.	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
6th	O
Year	O
of	O
King	O
George	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Katharine	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
,	I-pers
of	O
Covent	B-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
an	O
Apron	O
val	O
.	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Proof	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Macamurrel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Ounce	O
of	O
Human	O
Hair	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Caleb	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
Caleb	O
Smith	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
I	O
bought	O
my	O
Wig	O
of	O
the	O
Widow	O
Grey	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
Hair	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
Shop	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Groves	I-pers
is	O
her	O
Journyman	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
helps	O
them	O
to	O
shave	O
now	O
and	O
then	O
,	O
upon	O
a	O
Saturday	O
or	O
so	O
;	O
and	O
between	O
whiles	O
he	O
does	O
odd	O
Jobbs	O
for	O
himself	O
.	O
I	O
tax	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
Hair	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
sign	O
his	O
Confession	O
;	O
but	O
a	O
Woman	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
.	O
Several	O
Persons	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Elston	I-pers
,	O
Mariner	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
(	O
on	O
a	O
Special	O
Commission	O
for	O
trying	O
Offences	O
beyond	O
the	O
Seas	O
)	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
at	O
Guinea	B-place
,	O
by	O
beating	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Cane	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
Breast	O
,	O
Back	O
and	O
Sides	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
10th	O
Year	O
of	O
King	O
George	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languish	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
Feburary	O
following	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
at	O
Guinea	O
,	O
by	O
beating	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Cane	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
Back	O
,	O
Breast	O
and	O
Sides	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
10th	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
present	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languish	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Month	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Bush	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
Surgeon	O
in	O
the	O
Christopher	O
Galley	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Captain	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
1723.	O
we	O
went	O
with	O
our	O
Boats	O
up	O
the	O
River	O
Andona	O
to	O
buy	O
Slaves	O
and	O
Palm	O
Oil	O
.	O
Atkinson	O
(	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
)	O
happened	O
to	O
set	O
a	O
small	O
jar	O
of	O
Palm	O
Oil	O
(	O
about	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
s.	O
)	O
upon	O
some	O
Bars	O
of	O
Iron	O
that	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
Fore	O
Sheets	O
of	O
the	O
Long	O
Boat	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
soon	O
after	O
ordered	O
West	O
(	O
the	O
other	O
Deceased	O
)	O
to	O
hand	O
some	O
of	O
those	O
Bars	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Boat	O
;	O
and	O
West	O
,	O
in	O
taking	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Bars	O
up	O
,	O
threw	O
down	O
the	O
Jar	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
flew	O
into	O
a	O
violent	O
Passion	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
who	O
set	O
the	O
Jar	O
in	O
that	O
Place	O
?	O
And	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Crew	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
Jack	O
Atkinson	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
swore	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
for	O
ever	O
D	O
-	O
'em	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
beat	O
them	O
both	O
alike	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
knotted	O
Cane	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
about	O
an	O
Inch	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
thick	O
;	O
(	O
we	O
call	O
it	O
a	O
Bamboo	O
Cane	O
)	O
and	O
with	O
this	O
Cane	O
he	O
knock	O
'd	O
them	O
both	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
a	O
beating	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
furious	O
manner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
another	O
Boat	O
about	O
three	O
Fathom	O
from	O
the	O
Long	O
Boat	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
heard	O
and	O
saw	O
all	O
that	O
pass	O
'd	O
betwixt	O
'em	O
.	O
I	O
haul	O
'd	O
up	O
my	O
Boat	O
close	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
intended	O
to	O
kill	O
the	O
Men	O
?	O
G	O
-	O
D	O
-	O
you	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
kill	O
ye	O
all	O
before	O
I	O
go	O
aboard	O
the	O
Ship	O
.	O
But	O
then	O
,	O
Captain	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
how	O
will	O
you	O
get	O
your	O
Boats	O
aboard	O
?	O
(	O
for	O
we	O
were	O
then	O
Ten	O
Leagues	O
up	O
the	O
River	O
Andona	O
.	O
)	O
He	O
Scratch	O
'd	O
his	O
Ears	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
Why	O
then	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
you	O
all	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
kill	O
you	O
when	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
ye	O
aboard	O
.	O
He	O
still	O
kept	O
beating	O
the	O
two	O
Men	O
till	O
his	O
Cane	O
was	O
broke	O
all	O
to	O
Pieces	O
:	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
gave	O
them	O
a	O
Hundred	O
Blows	O
apiece	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
lay	O
down	O
,	O
he	O
stampt	O
upon	O
their	O
Breasts	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
Blood	O
gush	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
Mouths	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
left	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
miserable	O
Condition	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
ordered	O
any	O
Care	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
on	O
Board	O
,	O
I	O
apply	O
'd	O
a	O
Seton	O
to	O
each	O
of	O
their	O
Poles	O
.	O
Each	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
seized	O
with	O
a	O
violent	O
Fever	O
:	O
They	O
spit	O
Blood	O
daily	O
,	O
and	O
Atkinson	O
grew	O
delirous	O
Their	O
Heads	O
especially	O
were	O
black	O
with	O
Bruises	O
,	O
very	O
much	O
swell	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soft	O
as	O
an	O
Apple	O
.	O
Yet	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
they	O
were	O
so	O
extremely	O
ill	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
never	O
Shew	O
'd	O
the	O
least	O
Regard	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
as	O
they	O
lay	O
upon	O
the	O
Deck	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
kick	O
them	O
,	O
stamp	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
strike	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
with	O
his	O
Fist	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
them	O
get	O
up	O
to	O
work	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
the	O
second	O
day	O
after	O
their	O
Beating	O
,	O
that	O
West	O
was	O
put	O
to	O
the	O
Helm	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
coming	O
upon	O
the	O
Deck	O
,	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
For	O
God	O
's	O
Sake	O
,	O
Doctor	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
take	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Helm	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
stand	O
;	O
and	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
.	O
They	O
both	O
died	O
in	O
Calabar	O
River	O
;	O
Atkinson	O
in	O
fifteen	O
days	O
,	O
and	O
West	O
in	O
nineteen	O
days	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
beat	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
verily	O
believe	O
that	O
that	O
Beating	O
threw	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
Fever	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
their	O
Death	O
.	O
Before	O
they	O
died	O
,	O
they	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
write	O
their	O
Wills	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
some	O
Intimation	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
called	O
me	O
down	O
between	O
Decks	O
one	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
clapping	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
my	O
Breast	O
,	O
I	O
understand	O
,	O
Doctor	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
the	O
Wills	O
of	O
these	O
Fellows	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
deliver	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
or	O
let	O
me	O
see	O
you	O
tear	O
it	O
,	O
by	O
G	O
-	O
I	O
'll	O
shoot	O
you	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Body	O
this	O
Minute	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
fetch	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
tore	O
it	O
before	O
his	O
Face	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
thus	O
made	O
his	O
Defence	O
:	O
Atkinson	O
and	O
West	O
died	O
of	O
a	O
violent	O
Flux	O
and	O
Fever	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
common	O
Distemper	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
)	O
which	O
they	O
brought	O
upon	O
themselves	O
by	O
drinking	O
Palm	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
eating	O
Plantanes	O
.	O
My	O
Gunner	O
and	O
Jerry	B-pers
Clampet	I-pers
,	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
more	O
,	O
died	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Distemper	O
,	O
much	O
about	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
;	O
and	O
whatever	O
the	O
Doctor	O
swears	O
now	O
about	O
Atkinson	O
and	O
West	O
,	O
he	O
then	O
turned	O
them	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
over	O
to	O
the	O
Boatswain	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
they	O
were	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
lazy	O
Sons	O
of	O
Bitches	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
able	O
enough	O
to	O
work	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
but	O
willing	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
afterwards	O
did	O
their	O
Duty	O
.	O
To	O
this	O
the	O
Doctor	O
thus	O
answered	O
:	O
The	O
two	O
deceased	O
Men	O
were	O
free	O
from	O
the	O
Country	O
Distemper	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
'em	O
indeed	O
had	O
a	O
small	O
Looseness	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
like	O
a	O
Flux	O
:	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
did	O
drink	O
some	O
Palm	O
Wine	O
during	O
their	O
Illness	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
to	O
excess	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
they	O
eat	O
any	O
Plantanes	O
As	O
for	O
turning	O
them	O
over	O
to	O
the	O
Boatswain	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Gunner	O
and	O
Jerry	O
Clampet	O
;	O
nor	O
did	O
they	O
do	O
Duty	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
beat	O
them	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
able	O
;	O
only	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
said	O
before	O
,	O
he	O
forced	O
them	O
to	O
do	O
something	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
his	O
Witnesses	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Elms	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
Carpenter	O
and	O
Second	O
Mate	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
Staid	O
on	O
board	O
while	O
the	O
Boats	O
went	O
up	O
Andona	O
River	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
the	O
two	O
deceased	O
Men	O
and	O
the	O
Doctor	O
had	O
got	O
drunk	O
and	O
tumbled	O
over-board	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Captain	O
had	O
given	O
the	O
two	O
Deceased	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Blows	O
with	O
a	O
Rattan	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
them	O
complain	O
of	O
being	O
beat	O
;	O
they	O
did	O
their	O
Duty	O
aboard	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
that	O
they	O
ail	O
'd	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
-	O
not	O
but	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
Setons	O
and	O
Blisters	O
upon	O
'em	O
:	O
But	O
then	O
they	O
had	O
such	O
a	O
violent	O
Flux	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
run	O
from	O
'em	O
all	O
over	O
the	O
Deck	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
thrust	O
my	O
Hand	O
up	O
their	O
Fundaments	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
grown	O
so	O
very	O
wide	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
,	O
that	O
14	O
or	O
15	O
days	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
beat	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Doctor	O
turn	O
'd	O
'em	O
over	O
to	O
the	O
Boatswain	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
lazy	O
Dogs	O
,	O
and	O
able	O
enough	O
to	O
work	O
;	O
-	O
tho	O
'	O
indeed	O
they	O
were	O
then	O
in	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
Fever	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
several	O
Blisters	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
'em	O
died	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
t'other	O
in	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
then	O
there	O
were	O
seven	O
more	O
that	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
Flux	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
that	O
Country	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
that	O
Plantanes	O
are	O
apt	O
to	O
give	O
a	O
Flux	O
;	O
-	O
and	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
but	O
they	O
may	O
cause	O
Spitting	O
of	O
Blood	O
.	O
The	O
Palm	O
Wine	O
will	O
seldom	O
keep	O
24	O
Hours	O
;	O
't	O
is	O
like	O
Canary	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
Syder	O
at	O
Noon	O
,	O
and	O
Vinegar	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
It	O
being	O
so	O
pleasant	O
in	O
a	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
Sailors	O
are	O
commonly	O
so	O
fond	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
drink	O
to	O
Excess	O
,	O
the	O
Consequence	O
of	O
which	O
is	O
commonly	O
a	O
great	O
Flux	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
not	O
always	O
attended	O
with	O
a	O
Fever	O
.	O
Several	O
Witnesses	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
heard	O
the	O
Doctor	O
say	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
that	O
the	O
Captain	O
did	O
any	O
Hurt	O
to	O
any	O
Man	O
:	O
-	O
He	O
turn	O
'd	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Place	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
Shore	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
come	O
on	O
board	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
therefore	O
I	O
swore	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
clapt	O
in	O
Irons	O
at	O
Barbadoes	O
.	O
-	O
If	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
hang	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
'll	O
hang	O
me	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
shall	O
have	O
Fifty	O
Pound	O
for	O
hanging	O
the	O
Captain	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
would	O
have	O
swore	O
away	O
my	O
Life	O
for	O
not	O
taking	O
Care	O
of	O
the	O
Men	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
I	O
swore	O
shift	O
to	O
prevent	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Wade	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
hind	O
Quarter	O
of	O
Veal	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Veal	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Hamper	O
in	O
Leadenhall	B-place
Market	I-place
,	O
and	O
was	O
stopt	O
with	O
it	O
upon	O
his	O
Back	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
when	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Longstaffe	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Mason	O
by	O
Trade	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
live	O
upon	O
Saffron	O
Hill	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Father	O
is	O
a	O
Mason	O
's	O
Labourer	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
him	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
's	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Man	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
is	O
his	O
Wife	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
for	O
his	O
Son	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
Good	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
6	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Dowgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
black	O
Stone	O
Horse	O
value	O
12	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Jenkinson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
entrusted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
sell	O
Horses	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Cornhill	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Haft	O
of	O
a	O
Knife	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Morden	I-pers
;	O
and	O
three	O
Yards	O
of	O
Lace	O
and	O
two	O
Caps	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Stiles	I-pers
Morden	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Temple	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
defrauding	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
How	I-pers
of	O
Six	O
Silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
Elizabeth	O
How	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Shop	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	B-place
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Corbet	O
for	O
six	O
Silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
.	O
I	O
knowing	O
Mr.	O
Corbet	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Man	O
,	O
I	O
deliver	O
'd	O
11	O
Handkerchiefs	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Master	O
might	O
take	O
his	O
Choice	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Harton	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Glasier	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
on	O
one	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Shop	O
as	O
Mrs.	O
How	O
lives	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
mistrusted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
knew	O
him	O
?	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
Whereupon	O
I	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Corbet	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
lives	O
upon	O
College-Hill	O
.	O
Before	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
far	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
another	O
Man	O
,	O
with	O
whom	O
he	O
went	O
thro	O
'	O
Sun-Yard	O
into	O
Broad-street	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
through	O
Newgate	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
Porter	O
to	O
assist	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
stopt	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
deliver	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Bosom	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
thus	O
made	O
his	O
Defence	O
:	O
I	O
met	O
Mr.	O
Corbet	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
his	O
Master	O
had	O
sent	O
him	O
for	O
some	O
Handkerchiefs	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
How	O
's	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
go	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
ow	O
'd	O
a	O
little	O
Money	O
thereabouts	O
:	O
and	O
therefore	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
fetch	O
them	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Things	O
at	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
other	O
Shops	O
,	O
and	O
bring	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
at	O
a	O
House	O
upon	O
Snow-Hill	O
,	O
(	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
forgot	O
the	O
Sign	O
)	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
18	O
d.	O
So	O
I	O
agreed	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
Note	O
of	O
Directions	O
at	O
what	O
Shops	O
to	O
call	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
Goods	O
to	O
ask	O
for	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Corbet	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Harton	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
enquire	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
sent	O
him	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
How	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
Note	O
of	O
Directions	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
says	O
he	O
had	O
from	O
my	O
Servant	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
Note	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
Servant	O
's	O
Writing	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
Servant	O
was	O
gone	O
from	O
me	O
before	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
now	O
indicted	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Ferry	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Magneta	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
persuading	O
John	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
to	O
committ	O
Perjury	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Lothbury	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Books	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
The	O
History	O
of	O
the	O
Pyrates	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
The	O
Principles	O
and	O
Duties	O
of	O
the	O
Christian	O
Religion	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
King	I-pers
Sen.	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
July	O
.	O
Tho.King	O
Sen.	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
I	O
keep	O
two	O
Booksellers	O
Stalls	O
;	O
one	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Token-House-Yard	B-place
in	I-place
Lothbury	I-place
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
in	O
Petty-France	O
.	O
Last	O
Wednesday	O
Night	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Shop	O
in	O
Petty-France	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
me	O
this	O
Book	O
,	O
The	O
Principles	O
and	O
Duties	O
of	O
the	O
Christian	O
Religion	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
Shilling	O
,	O
-	O
't	O
is	O
worth	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
.	O
Soon	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
own	O
Mark	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
by	O
which	O
I	O
concluded	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
stolen	O
from	O
my	O
other	O
Stall	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
Son	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
such	O
a	O
Book	O
.	O
Tho	B-pers
King	I-pers
Jun	O
.	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
The	O
next	O
Day	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
my	O
Father	O
's	O
Stall	O
in	O
Token-House-Yard	O
;	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Description	O
my	O
Father	O
gave	O
me	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
Person	O
that	O
stole	O
the	O
Book	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
's	O
House	O
and	O
watch	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
out	O
The	O
History	O
of	O
the	O
Pyrates	O
look	O
'd	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
Bosom	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
off	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
being	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
laid	O
it	O
down	O
again	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Val	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Howell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Saddle	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joshua	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dalton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Horse-Toppings	O
val	O
.	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Salter	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Little	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Pancras	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Tolfield	I-pers
in	O
an	O
open	O
Field	O
near	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Coat	O
and	O
Wastecoat	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
Wig	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Watch	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Peter	B-pers
Gotier	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Coat	O
and	O
Ten	O
Shillings	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
3d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Jacob	B-pers
Deblet	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
6	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
The	O
Witnesses	O
not	O
being	O
positive	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
robbed	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Fullifull	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coat	O
and	O
Wastecoat	O
val	O
.	O
35	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	O
Fullifull	O
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Ridsly	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Molineux	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Buchanan	I-pers
.	O
Fullifull	O
only	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Brandrith	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Fork	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Arthur	B-pers
Banks	I-pers
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Millican	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sheep	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Tole	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Sanderson	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Clancy	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sheep	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Langham	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
Anne	B-pers
Price	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Housing	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Howell	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
;	O
Wood	O
and	O
Price	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Boots	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoos	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Burbridge	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
June	O
;	O
and	O
Howell	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Champain	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Thorp	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
Guilty	O
:	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gordon	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Swindon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Watch	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Nathanael	B-pers
Wicks	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
June	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
(	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
very	O
bashful	O
Gentleman	O
)	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
acquitted	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
order	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Wicks	O
's	O
Recognizance	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
being	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
follows	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
One	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Bostock	O
.	O
She	O
pleaded	O
her	O
Belly	O
;	O
But	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
being	O
impanell	O
'd	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
her	O
not	O
with	O
quick	O
Child	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
Nine	O
.	O
John	B-pers
May	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Elston	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Tealing	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hog	I-pers
Spinster	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hog	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
G.	O
Hog	O
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
;	O
the	O
last	O
a	O
former	O
Convict	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
Transported	O
,	O
Forty	O
two	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Badger	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Ithell	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
Margery	B-pers
Thackum	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
,	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Henly	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	O
Hall	O
,	O
Martha	B-pers
Mead	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Penington	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Calighan	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Herring	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Herring	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bledall	I-pers
,	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Aberdeen	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Miles	I-pers
;	O
Solomon	B-pers
Southall	I-pers
,	O
David	B-pers
le	I-pers
Count	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Brace	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hancock	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
L'Estrange	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Cartou	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Carron	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	I-pers
Martha	B-pers
Blaithwait	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Wade	I-pers
,	O
Hannah	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Fullifull	I-pers
,	O
Arthur	B-pers
Banks	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Millican	I-pers
,	O
Andrew	B-pers
Sanderson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Clancy	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Housing	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Champain	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
in	O
Gracechurch-Street	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
White-Hart	O
Alehouse	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
BENEFIT	O
of	O
those	O
who	O
are	O
afflicted	O
with	O
the	O
DROPSY	O
.	O
MRs.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Knell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Middle-Street	O
,	O
Cloth-Fair	O
(	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
the	O
Baker	O
and	O
Basket	O
)	O
near	O
West-Smithfield	O
,	O
continues	O
to	O
perform	O
extraordinary	O
Cures	O
in	O
the	O
DROPSY	O
;	O
several	O
of	O
which	O
have	O
been	O
advertised	O
in	O
the	O
News-Papers	O
N	O
B	O
.	O
This	O
excellent	O
Remedy	O
is	O
only	O
to	O
be	O
had	O
at	O
the	O
Place	O
aforesaid	O
;	O
where	O
an	O
Account	O
is	O
given	O
of	O
several	O
remarkable	O
Cures	O
,	O
on	O
both	O
Sexes	O
,	O
Young	O
and	O
Old	O
.	O
This	O
Day	O
is	O
publish	O
'd	O
,	O
No	O
IX	O
for	O
the	O
Month	O
of	O
July	O
;	O
containing	O
the	O
Discovery	O
of	O
NEW	O
SPAIN	O
by	O
CORTEZ	O
his	O
Entry	O
into	O
the	O
Dominions	O
of	O
the	O
Great	O
MONTEZUMA	O
,	O
his	O
founding	O
a	O
colony	O
:	O
Also	O
the	O
famous	O
MAGELLAN	O
's	O
Voyage	O
to	O
discover	O
the	O
Streights	O
of	O
his	O
Name	O
.	O
The	O
General	O
History	O
of	O
the	O
vast	O
Continent	O
and	O
ends	O
of	O
AMERICA	O
,	O
commonly	O
called	O
WEST	O
IN	O
DIES	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
first	O
Discovery	O
thereof	O
:	O
With	O
the	O
best	O
Accounts	O
the	O
People	O
could	O
give	O
of	O
their	O
Antiquities	O
.	O
Collected	O
from	O
the	O
best	O
Relations	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Kings	O
of	O
Spain	O
.	O
By	O
Antonio	B-pers
de	I-pers
Merrer	I-pers
.	O
Historiographer	O
to	O
his	O
Catholick	O
Majesty	O
.	O
Translated	O
into	O
English	O
by	O
Capt	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
contained	O
Monthly	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
illustrated	O
with	O
Cuts	O
as	O
Occasion	O
small	O
offer	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.Batley	O
at	O
the	O
Dove	O
in	O
Pater-Noster	O
Row	O
;	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
T.	O
Cox	O
at	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
A.	O
Dodd	O
at	O
the	O
Peacock	O
without	O
Temple-Bar	O
.	O
W.	O
Lewis	O
in	O
Russel	O
Street	O
,	O
Covent-Garden	O
,	O
J.	O
Jackson	O
in	O
the	O
Pall-Mall	O
near	O
S.	O
James	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
C.	O
King	O
in	O
Westminster-Hall	O
.	O
Pr	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
Where	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
all	O
the	O
former	O
Numbers	O
,	O
price	O
1	O
s.	O
each	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
first	O
Volume	O
complete	O
with	O
Cuts	O
.	O
Also	O
a	O
New	O
Journey	O
thro	O
'	O
GREECE	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Lately	O
publish	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Lives	O
and	O
Amours	O
of	O
the	O
Empresses	O
,	O
Consortis	O
to	O
the	O
first	O
Twelve	O
Caesars	O
of	O
Rome	O
;	O
containing	O
all	O
the	O
Passages	O
of	O
chief	O
Note	O
in	O
Roman	B-pers
History	I-pers
:	O
And	O
particular	O
Characters	O
and	O
Descriptions	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
celebrated	O
Favourites	O
,	O
Courtiers	O
,	O
Poets	O
,	O
Orators	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
those	O
Reigns	O
:	O
Taken	O
from	O
the	O
Ancient	O
Greek	O
and	O
Latin	O
Authors	O
.	O
With	O
Historical	O
and	O
Explanatory	O
Notes	O
,	O
by	O
Monsieur	O
de	O
Servicz	O
.	O
Translated	O
by	O
Geo	O
James	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
Abel	B-pers
Roper	I-pers
;	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
J.	O
Isted	O
at	O
the	O
Golden	O
Ball	O
between	O
S.	O
Dunstan	O
's	O
Church	O
and	O
Chancery-Lane	O
End	O
in	O
Fleetstreet	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Booksellers	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
Westminster	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
will	O
be	O
publish	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
3d	O
Edition	O
of	O
MEMOIRS	O
of	O
the	O
Life	O
and	O
Adventures	O
of	O
Signor	O
ROZELLI	O
,	O
late	O
of	O
the	O
Hague	O
:	O
Giving	O
a	O
particular	O
Account	O
of	O
his	O
Birth	O
,	O
Education	O
,	O
Slavery	O
,	O
Monastick	O
State	O
,	O
Imprisonment	O
in	O
the	O
Inquisition	O
at	O
Rome	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
different	O
Figures	O
he	O
has	O
since	O
made	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
in	O
Italy	O
,	O
as	O
in	O
England	O
France	O
,	O
and	O
Holland	O
.	O
The	O
Whole	O
being	O
a	O
Series	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
diverting	O
History	O
,	O
and	O
surprizing	O
Events	O
,	O
ever	O
yet	O
made	O
Publick	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
A.	O
Roper	O
;	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
J.	O
Isted	O
at	O
the	O
Golden	O
Ball	O
between	O
S.	O
Dunstan	O
's	O
Church	O
and	O
Chancery-Lane	O
End	O
in	O
Fleetstreet	O
.	O
Price	O
5	O
s.	O
Where	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
,	O
The	O
Continuation	O
of	O
the	O
Life	O
and	O
Adventures	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Signor	O
ROZELLI	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Day	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
Price	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Both	O
Volumes	O
adorn	O
'd	O
with	O
curious	O
Copper	O
Cuts	O
.	O
First	O
publish	O
'd	O
,	O
A	O
PRACTICAL	O
TREATISE	O
:	O
Or	O
,	O
Second	O
Thoughts	O
on	O
the	O
Consequences	O
of	O
the	O
VENEREAL	O
DISEASE	O
.	O
In	O
Three	O
Parts	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
I	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Simple	O
Gonotahoea	O
,	O
Gleets	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Weaknesses	O
,	O
whether	O
from	O
Venereal	O
Embraces	O
,	O
Self-Publication	O
.	O
improperly	O
call	O
'd	O
Onanism	O
,	O
or	O
Natural	O
Imbecility	O
.	O
II	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Virulent	O
Gonotahoea	O
,	O
or	O
Clap	O
.	O
III	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Venercal	O
Lues	O
,	O
or	O
Grand	O
Pox	O
.	O
Wherein	O
are	O
plainly	O
shew	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
exact	O
Degrees	O
of	O
Inference	O
;	O
with	O
their	O
Signs	O
,	O
Symptoms	O
,	O
Prognosticks	O
,	O
Cures	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
Cases	O
;	O
their	O
Beginnings	O
,	O
Progress	O
,	O
and	O
fatal	O
Periods	O
,	O
when	O
neglected	O
,	O
or	O
unskillfully	O
managed	O
;	O
and	O
how	O
their	O
absolute	O
Cure	O
,	O
without	O
Violence	O
,	O
or	O
Injury	O
,	O
is	O
completed	O
With	O
proper	O
and	O
effectual	O
Remedies	O
,	O
in	O
their	O
several	O
Stages	O
,	O
prescribed	O
and	O
recommended	O
therein	O
.	O
With	O
some	O
Remarks	O
on	O
that	O
preposterous	O
,	O
Way	O
of	O
Venery	O
,	O
with	O
Machines	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
a	O
plain	O
Discovery	O
of	O
the	O
Dangers	O
(	O
the	O
little	O
expected	O
)	O
which	O
attend	O
that	O
vile	O
Practice	O
.	O
And	O
many	O
other	O
useful	O
Discoveries	O
relating	O
to	O
Infections	O
in	O
both	O
Sexes	O
,	O
not	O
before	O
taken	O
Notice	O
off	O
.	O
The	O
Whole	O
fitted	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
for	O
the	O
Advantage	O
of	O
Patient	O
,	O
as	O
young	O
Practicers	O
.	O
By	O
Joseph	B-pers
Cam	I-pers
,	O
M.D	O
.	O
Printed	O
for	O
the	O
Author	O
;	O
and	O
fond	O
by	O
W	O
Mears	O
without	O
Temple-Bar	O
,	O
G.	O
Strahan	O
against	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
C	O
King	O
in	O
Westminster-Hall	O
,	O
T.	O
Norris	O
on	O
London-bridge	O
,	O
and	O
J.	O
Baker	O
over	O
against	O
Hatton-Garden	O
in	O
Holborn	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
BOOK	O
'S	O
just	O
publish	O
'd	O
,	O
I.	O
ONANIA	O
Examined	O
and	O
Detected	O
;	O
or	O
,	O
the	O
Ignorance	O
,	O
Error	O
Impertinence	O
and	O
Contradication	O
of	O
a	O
Book	O
call	O
'd	O
ONANIA	O
.	O
discover	O
'd	O
and	O
detected	O
;	O
wherein	O
also	O
is	O
consider	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Differences	O
and	O
sundry	O
Degrees	O
of	O
Self	O
Pollution	O
in	O
both	O
Sexes	O
;	O
with	O
Choice	O
of	O
suitable	O
Remedies	O
both	O
for	O
extingnishing	O
excessive	O
Desires	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
for	O
strengthening	O
the	O
Bodies	O
of	O
such	O
as	O
have	O
been	O
hurt	O
by	O
Voluntary	O
or	O
Nocturnal	O
Emissions	O
.	O
Together	O
with	O
some	O
Thoughts	O
on	O
the	O
Use	O
of	O
the	O
Marriage	O
Bed	O
,	O
whether	O
there	O
can	O
be	O
sinful	O
Excesses	O
therein	O
,	O
or	O
it	O
can	O
be	O
defiled	O
without	O
a	O
third	O
Person	O
;	O
with	O
the	O
Opinions	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
Learned	O
and	O
Approved	O
Authors	O
as	O
Divines	O
,	O
Physicians	O
and	O
Surgeons	O
and	O
suitable	O
Observations	O
added	O
by	O
the	O
Author	O
.	O
The	O
whole	O
interspers	O
'd	O
with	O
Variety	O
of	O
Subjects	O
,	O
both	O
serious	O
and	O
jocose	O
.	O
The	O
2d	O
Edition	O
.	O
By	O
Philo-Casticatis	O
;	O
price	O
stitcht	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
II	O
.	O
Authentick	O
Memoirs	O
of	O
the	O
Life	O
and	O
surprizing	O
Adventures	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
.	O
who	O
was	O
executed	O
at	O
Tyburn	O
.	O
November	O
16	O
.	O
1724	O
.	O
The	O
2d	O
Edition	O
.	O
Adorn	O
'd	O
with	O
Variety	O
of	O
Copper	O
Cuts	O
;	O
price	O
bound	O
1	O
s.	O
III	O
.	O
The	O
Order	O
of	O
Causes	O
of	O
God	O
's	O
Foreknowledge	O
,	O
Election	O
,	O
Predestination	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
Man	O
's	O
Salvation	O
and	O
Damnation	O
;	O
as	O
also	O
whether	O
Christ	O
died	O
for	O
all	O
or	O
not	O
for	O
all	O
.	O
By	O
Henry	B-pers
Haggar	I-pers
.	O
The	O
6th	O
Edition	O
;	O
price	O
6	O
d.	O
IV	O
.	O
The	O
Art	O
of	O
Spelling	O
.	O
By	O
J.	O
P.	O
M.	O
A	O
.	O
The	O
9th	O
Edition	O
,	O
with	O
Additions	O
.	O
V.	O
La	O
Plume	O
Volante	O
;	O
of	O
.	O
The	O
Art	O
of	O
Short-Hand	O
improved	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
most	O
swift	O
,	O
regular	O
and	O
easy	O
Method	O
of	O
Short	O
Hand-Writing	O
yet	O
extant	O
;	O
Composed	O
after	O
40	O
Years	O
Practice	O
and	O
Improvement	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Art	O
.	O
By	O
William	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
;	O
price	O
bound	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
VI	O
.	O
An	O
Essay	O
concerning	O
the	O
Infinite	O
Wisdom	O
of	O
God	O
.	O
manifested	O
in	O
the	O
Continuance	O
and	O
Structure	O
of	O
the	O
Skin	O
of	O
Human	O
Bodies	O
;	O
price	O
1	O
s.	O
VII	O
.	O
The	O
Young	B-pers
Man	I-pers
's	O
Guide	O
;	O
being	O
a	O
plain	O
Discovery	O
of	O
the	O
Art	O
of	O
Drawing	O
,	O
Engraving	O
in	O
Copper	O
to	O
the	O
Life	O
and	O
to	O
etch	O
Pictures	O
or	O
other	O
things	O
with	O
Aqua-fortis	O
,	O
price	O
;	O
1	O
s.	O
VIII	O
.	O
The	O
Agreement	O
of	O
the	O
Customs	O
of	O
the	O
Face-Indians	O
,	O
with	O
those	O
of	O
the	O
Jews	O
and	O
other	O
Ancient	O
People	O
;	O
with	O
Cuts	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
are	O
added	O
.	O
Instructions	O
to	O
young	O
Gentlemen	O
that	O
intend	O
to	O
travel	O
;	O
price	O
bound	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
All	O
printed	O
for	O
Jos	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
in	O
Newgate-Street	O
.	O
