TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Jail-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
On	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
,	O
Monday	O
,	O
and	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
15th	O
,	O
16th	O
,	O
18th	O
,	O
and	O
19th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Eleventh	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
GEORGE	B-pers
MERTTINS	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	B-pers
Eyre	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Dormer	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
,	O
Sergeant	O
at	O
Law	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
JURORS	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
The	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Tidman	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
Nathanael	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
Joshua	B-pers
Walfry	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Clifton	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Wackett	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Dryden	B-pers
Leach	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Prater	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Goddard	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wootton	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Gouge	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Gouge	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Worsey	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Brounker	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Wren	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
Hugh	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Daniel	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Best	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
cheapen	O
a	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
one	O
upon	O
his	O
Finger	O
,	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
was	O
stop	O
upon	O
the	O
Cry	O
at	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bow	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Graham	I-pers
a	O
Pocket	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
one	O
Guinea	O
,	O
four	O
Shillings	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Scissars	O
,	O
two	O
Keys	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silk-Gloves	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
,	O
about	O
6	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
met	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
in	O
Cheapside	O
:	O
He	O
thrust	O
his	O
Head	O
under	O
her	O
Coats	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
her	O
Pocket	O
.	O
She	O
presently	O
mist	O
it	O
,	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
stopt	O
him	O
;	O
when	O
others	O
coming	O
to	O
her	O
Assistance	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
.	O
They	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
Restoration	O
if	O
they	O
'd	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Val	O
.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Doncaster	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Gabriel	I-place
Fenchurch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Drugget	O
Cloaths	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Man	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Bedfellow	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
drinking	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
wanting	O
Money	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
find	O
a	O
Way	O
to	O
Supply	O
that	O
Deficiency	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
their	O
Lodging	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Rudge	O
as	O
the	O
Three	O
Balls	O
in	O
Hounsditch	O
for	O
28	O
s.	O
and	O
returning	O
with	O
the	O
Money	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
they	O
spent	O
it	O
all	O
betwixt	O
them	O
before	O
they	O
parted	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Value	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Craft	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Katharine	I-place
Coleman	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hogshead	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Brett	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2	O
d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hobbs	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
)	O
of	O
Aldgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cork-Screw	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
Boxes	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bracey	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
Dec.	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
while	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
busy	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shew-Glass	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
seen	O
by	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
who	O
stopt	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
confess	O
'd	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
another	O
Boy	O
,	O
nick-named	O
Kiddy	B-pers
Madge	I-pers
,	O
had	O
committed	O
other	O
Facts	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
nature	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
-	O
Cummins	O
,	O
not	O
far	O
from	O
the	O
Red	O
Lion	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Mint	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Square	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Baldry	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
)	O
of	O
Alhallows	B-place
Lombard-street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
17	O
Pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
val	O
.	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
three	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Stockings	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Errand-Boy	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
the	O
Goods	O
for	O
2	O
s.	O
to	O
2	O
Scotchman	O
,	O
who	O
he	O
said	O
seduced	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
promis	O
'd	O
him	O
2	O
s.	O
more	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Value	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gandy	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Alban	I-place
Wood-street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Tranter	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Value	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hewlet	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Candy	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Staff	O
a	O
mortal	O
Bruise	O
on	O
the	O
Left	O
Side	O
of	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroners	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
(	O
Son-in-Law	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
)	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
Saturday	O
about	O
Midnight	O
,	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Watchman	O
in	O
Fetter-Lane	O
,	O
they	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
another	O
Watchman	O
)	O
with	O
two	O
Staves	O
and	O
two	O
Lanterns	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
lighted	O
Candle	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
my	O
Father	O
?	O
(	O
says	O
Newman	O
.	O
)	O
Yes	O
,	O
(	O
said	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
he	O
lies	O
dead	O
at	O
Dr.	O
Lad	O
's	O
Door	O
in	O
Castle-Yard	B-place
.	O
Dead	O
!	O
Yes	O
,	O
dead	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
fall	O
.	O
And	O
why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
raise	O
him	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
somebody	O
to	O
his	O
Assistance	O
?	O
D	O
-	O
ye	O
,	O
reply	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
that	O
I	O
kill	O
'd	O
him	O
?	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Staves	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Lanterns	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
then	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
Hands	O
,	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
(	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Steel	O
)	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
Midnight	O
she	O
sent	O
their	O
Boy	O
for	O
a	O
Peck	O
of	O
small-coal	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
the	O
Door	O
a-jar	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
while	O
she	O
heard	O
a	O
hoarse	O
Voice	O
say	O
,	O
If	O
you	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
used	O
you	O
like	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
Watchman	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
use	O
you	O
,	O
like	O
a	O
Watchman	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
go	O
about	O
your	O
Business	O
.	O
The	O
Boy	O
then	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
a	O
Watchman	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wait	I-pers
(	O
a	O
Boy	O
aged	O
13	O
)	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
for	O
the	O
Small-coal	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
past	O
11	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
with	O
a	O
Lantern	O
coming	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Watch-house	O
in	O
Castle-Yard	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
demanded	O
,	O
Who	O
's	O
there	O
?	O
And	O
the	O
other	O
answered	O
,	O
A	O
Friend	O
.	O
Whither	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
?	O
About	O
my	O
Business	O
.	O
D	O
-	O
yes	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
are	O
sawcy	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
send	O
you	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
.	O
Some	O
other	O
Words	O
pass	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
knockt	O
him	O
down	O
at	O
Dr.	O
Lad	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
into	O
his	O
Watch-house	O
again	O
.	O
Eliz	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
(	O
in	O
Magpye-Yard	O
near	O
Castle-Yard	O
)	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
after	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
she	O
heard	O
a	O
Cry	O
of	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
from	O
her	O
Window	O
,	O
saw	O
two	O
Men	O
run	O
by	O
with	O
Staves	O
and	O
Lanterns	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
in	O
a	O
hoarse	O
Voice	O
,	O
Now	O
I	O
have	O
ye	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
smash	O
ye	O
By	O
G	O
-	O
.	O
They	O
pass	O
'd	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
returning	O
,	O
was	O
met	O
by	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
more	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
Did	O
be	O
knock	O
down	O
you	O
,	O
or	O
you	O
him	O
?	O
The	O
hoarse	O
Voice	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
very	O
hoarse	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
through	O
Magpye-Yard	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
two	O
Staves	O
and	O
two	O
Lanterns	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
Lord	O
bless	O
me	O
!	O
how	O
came	O
this	O
Accident	O
?	O
Why	O
,	O
said	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
my	O
Stand	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
be	O
made	O
as	O
Answer	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
stept	O
out	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
a	O
Knock	O
.	O
These	O
Words	O
raised	O
2	O
Suspicion	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
committed	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Hemmit	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
12	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
drunk	O
to	O
his	O
Stand	O
,	O
(	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Bird	O
's	O
Door	O
in	O
Castle-Court	O
)	O
and	O
without	O
any	O
Provocation	O
began	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
quarrelsome	O
,	O
swearing	O
,	O
calling	O
him	O
ill	O
Names	O
,	O
and	O
striking	O
him	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
.	O
Hemmit	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Beat	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
'd	O
make	O
him	O
forfeit	O
Sixpence	O
.	O
(	O
Such	O
a	O
Forfeit	O
being	O
,	O
customary	O
among	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
,	O
if	O
one	O
comes	O
into	O
the	O
other	O
's	O
Beat	O
.	O
)	O
Mr.	O
Bird	O
then	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
threaten	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
charge	O
a	O
Constable	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
send	O
him	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
very	O
free	O
of	O
his	O
ill	O
Language	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bird	O
,	O
and	O
concluding	O
with	O
G	O
-	O
damn	O
it	O
I	O
'll	O
make	O
a	O
Sacrifice	O
of	O
somebody	O
to	O
Night	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
Great	O
Part	O
of	O
this	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Bird	O
himself	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
who	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
Steps	O
of	O
Dr.	O
Lad	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
he	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
spy	O
something	O
White	O
within	O
Dr.	O
Lad	O
's	O
Palisades	O
,	O
and	O
dragging	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Neckcloth	O
;	O
for	O
by	O
comparing	O
it	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
Piece	O
that	O
was	O
then	O
about	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Neck	O
,	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
torne	O
from	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
thrown	O
over	O
the	O
Palisades	O
.	O
Both	O
the	O
Pieces	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
matched	O
exactly	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Lugg	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
into	O
Castle-Yard	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
lying	O
dead	O
on	O
the	O
Stone	O
Steps	O
,	O
his	O
Lantern	O
with	O
a	O
lighted	O
Candle	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Staff	O
standing	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
walking	O
to	O
and	O
fro	O
before	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
who	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
lay	O
there	O
,	O
or	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
his	O
Death	O
;	O
to	O
both	O
which	O
Questions	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
answer	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Negative	O
.	O
He	O
(	O
this	O
Deponent	O
)	O
then	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
that	O
Way	O
again	O
soon	O
after	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Deceased	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Place	O
;	O
but	O
neither	O
his	O
Lantern	O
,	O
Staff	O
,	O
nor	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
were	O
then	O
to	O
be	O
seen	O
there	O
.	O
Other	O
Witnesses	O
confirmed	O
that	O
Particular	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
owning	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
fall	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
abusive	O
quarrelsome	O
Fellow	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Keatly	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
after	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
)	O
he	O
view	O
'd	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
and	O
making	O
an	O
Incision	O
cross	O
wise	O
on	O
the	O
Left	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
Contusion	O
about	O
the	O
Breadth	O
of	O
a	O
Shilling	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
took	O
off	O
the	O
Pericranium	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
no	O
Fracture	O
in	O
the	O
Skull	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
also	O
a	O
deep	O
Bruise	O
in	O
the	O
Left	O
Shoulder	O
but	O
he	O
thought	O
it	O
very	O
unlikely	O
for	O
a	O
Contusion	O
in	O
that	O
Place	O
to	O
prove	O
mortal	O
.	O
As	O
for	O
the	O
Bruise	O
in	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
he	O
thought	O
it	O
might	O
probably	O
be	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
by	O
a	O
Blow	O
with	O
a	O
Staff	O
:	O
But	O
it	O
being	O
demanded	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
possible	O
that	O
such	O
a	O
Bruise	O
might	O
be	O
received	O
by	O
a	O
Fall	O
,	O
he	O
answered	O
,	O
Yes	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
been	O
subject	O
to	O
the	O
Apoplexy	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
often	O
seen	O
him	O
fall	O
into	O
such	O
a	O
Fitt	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Fitt	O
that	O
he	O
dropt	O
down	O
at	O
Dr.	O
Lad	O
's	O
Door	O
.	O
That	O
soon	O
after	O
,	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
coming	O
up	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
light	O
him	O
in	O
at	O
Doors	O
;	O
at	O
which	O
time	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Fellows	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
Holborn	O
,	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Lantern	O
and	O
Staff	O
which	O
stood	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
with'em	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
seeing	O
,	O
ran	O
after'em	O
thro	O
'	O
Magpye-Yard	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
.	O
They	O
finding	O
that	O
he	O
pursu	O
'd	O
'em	O
,	O
threw	O
away	O
the	O
Staff	O
and	O
Lantern	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
off	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
'em	O
up	O
and	O
brought	O
'em	O
back	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
seen	O
by	O
several	O
with	O
2	O
Staves	O
and	O
2	O
Lanterns	O
.	O
Mr.	O
-	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
up	O
Castle-Yard	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
walking	O
about	O
very	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
lying	O
on	O
Dr.	O
Lad	O
's	O
Steps	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
at	O
first	O
thought	O
to	O
be	O
drunk	O
too	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
assured	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
really	O
dead	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
then	O
lighted	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Men	O
coming	O
by	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Lantern	O
and	O
Staff	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pursu	O
'd	O
'em	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
drunk	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
brought	O
the	O
Lantern	O
and	O
Staff	O
back	O
again	O
;	O
at	O
which	O
time	O
some	O
other	O
Watchmen	O
(	O
whose	O
Depositions	O
have	O
already	O
been	O
mentioned	O
)	O
met	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
2	O
Staves	O
and	O
2	O
Lanterns	O
.	O
He	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
believed	O
that	O
these	O
Words	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
smash	O
you	O
by	O
G	O
-	O
were	O
spoken	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Men	O
that	O
took	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Staff	O
and	O
Lantern	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Steel	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Boy	O
Jos	O
.	O
Wait	O
had	O
told	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
but	O
gave	O
his	O
Evidence	O
before	O
the	O
Coroner	O
by	O
the	O
Maid	O
Anne	O
Hall	O
's	O
Persuasions	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
Boy	O
to	O
be	O
much	O
addicted	O
to	O
Lying	O
;	O
for	O
which	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Misdemeanors	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
since	O
turn	O
'd	O
him	O
away	O
.	O
Anne	O
Hall	O
was	O
then	O
called	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
Reason	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
never	O
did	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
least	O
,	O
persuade	O
the	O
Boy	O
to	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
Boy	O
said	O
she	O
persuaded	O
him	O
,	O
merely	O
to	O
escape	O
a	O
severe	O
Whipping	O
,	O
which	O
his	O
Mistress	O
and	O
young	O
Master	O
threatned	O
him	O
with	O
.	O
The	O
Boy	O
was	O
then	O
called	O
up	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
;	O
He	O
said	O
his	O
Mistress	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
strip	O
him	O
stark	O
naked	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Robert	O
steel	O
(	O
his	O
young	O
Master	O
)	O
took	O
the	O
Horse-Whip	O
,	O
and	O
Struck	O
him	O
once	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
threatning	O
not	O
only	O
to	O
whip	O
him	O
then	O
in	O
a	O
terrible	O
Manner	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
to	O
send	O
him	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
except	O
he	O
would	O
confess	O
that	O
the	O
Maid	O
had	O
persuaded	O
him	O
to	O
swear	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
did	O
before	O
the	O
Coroner	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Fear	O
of	O
such	O
Treatment	O
made	O
him	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
they	O
desired	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Rob	B-pers
Steel	I-pers
acknowledged	O
,	O
that	O
knowing	O
the	O
Boy	O
to	O
be	O
addicted	O
to	O
Lying	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
strike	O
him	O
once	O
with	O
a	O
Whip	O
,	O
and	O
threatned	O
him	O
farther	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
confess	O
the	O
Truth	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
all	O
that	O
he	O
desired	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
and	I-pers
Samuel	I-pers
Candy	I-pers
,	O
(	O
Sons	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
)	O
and	O
several	O
others	O
,	O
in	O
Contradiction	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Assertion	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
never	O
known	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
Fitt	O
of	O
the	O
Apoplexy	O
,	O
not	O
was	O
it	O
likely	O
that	O
he	O
tell	O
down	O
being	O
drunk	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
saw	O
him	O
but	O
about	O
an	O
Hour	O
before	O
his	O
Death	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
as	O
sober	O
as	O
a	O
Judge	O
,	O
besides	O
,	O
it	O
could	O
never	O
be	O
thought	O
that	O
an	O
Apoplectick	O
Fitt	O
would	O
fear	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Neckcloth	O
,	O
and	O
throw	O
Part	O
of	O
it	O
over	O
the	O
Palisades	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Walter	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
his	O
Servant	O
some	O
time	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
behaved	O
himself	O
like	O
an	O
honest	O
,	O
harmless	O
,	O
inoffensive	O
Fellow	O
.	O
One	O
or	O
two	O
more	O
spoke	O
in	O
his	O
Behalf	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
,	O
after	O
a	O
long	O
Consideration	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Dumont	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver-Hilted	O
Sword	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Hat	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Baxter	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
Aug.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
Frenchman	O
,	O
and	O
understanding	O
no	O
English	O
,	O
an	O
Interpreter	O
was	O
sworn	O
upon	O
the	O
Tryal	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Baxter	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
living	O
at	O
the	O
French	B-place
Resident	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
Suffolk-street	I-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
)	O
came	O
thither	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
Pass	O
for	O
France	O
.	O
He	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
)	O
going	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
was	O
gone	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Sword	O
and	O
Hat	O
that	O
hung	O
on	O
a	O
Peg	O
below	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
left	O
his	O
own	O
Hat	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
of	O
'em	O
.	O
By	O
making	O
Enquiry	O
,	O
and	O
describing	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
by	O
a	O
Soldier	O
in	O
Southwark	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Sword-Hilt	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
He	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
granted	O
him	O
a	O
Pass	O
to	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Plantations	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Lipsat	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Kelway	I-pers
57	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
29	O
Carolus	O
's	O
,	O
5	O
Jacobug	O
's	O
,	O
3	O
Moidores	O
,	O
6	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Silver	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Buckle	O
set	O
with	O
Stones	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Purses	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robt	O
.	O
Kelway	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
last	O
.	O
Robt	O
.	O
Kelway	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
he	O
left	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
lock	O
'd	O
up	O
safe	O
in	O
the	O
Drawers	O
of	O
his	O
Scrutore	O
,	O
and	O
remaining	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
told	O
that	O
his	O
Servant	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
the	O
Round-House	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Higginson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
lie	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
granted	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
2	O
Snuff	O
Boxes	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
)	O
several	O
Pocket-Pieces	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
which	O
raised	O
a	O
Suspicion	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
honestly	O
gotten	O
.	O
He	O
therefore	O
caused	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
apprehended	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
and	O
Watchman	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
upon	O
searching	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
50	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
30	O
Broad	O
Pieces	O
,	O
3	O
Moidores	O
,	O
2	O
Snuff-Boxes	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Common-Prayer	O
Book	O
.	O
He	O
confes	O
'd	O
before	O
Justice	O
Ellis	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
broke	O
open	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Scrutore	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
thence	O
the	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
His	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Jobson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Porringer	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
2	O
Moidores	O
,	O
2	O
Broad	O
Pieces	O
,	O
6	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Box	O
value	O
8	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Barns	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	O
Barns	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Council	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
opened	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Barns	O
having	O
married	O
a	O
rich	O
Widow	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
had	O
some	O
Acquaintance	O
with	O
her	O
before	O
this	O
last	O
Marriage	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
visit	O
her	O
while	O
her	O
Husband	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
persuaded	O
her	O
to	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
-	O
William	B-pers
Barns	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
out	O
about	O
Noon	O
to	O
receive	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
left	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
last	O
locked	O
in	O
the	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
which	O
stood	O
in	O
his	O
Bed-Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
the	O
Key	O
to	O
Jane	O
his	O
Wife	O
.	O
He	O
returned	O
about	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
understood	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
eloped	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
were	O
fast	O
lock	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Key	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
Window	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
open	O
'em	O
,	O
all	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
When	O
his	O
Wife	O
Jane	O
came	O
home	O
again	O
,	O
she	O
confessed	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Money	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
desired	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
or	O
his	O
Wife	O
might	O
be	O
asked	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
Plate	O
was	O
his	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
,	O
)	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
lent	O
it	O
to	O
Jane	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
before	O
her	O
last	O
Marriage	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Barns	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
that	O
his	O
Wife	O
Jane	O
should	O
be	O
examined	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Cameron	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	B-place
Savoy	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Crew	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
between	O
the	O
2	O
Forefingers	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Length	O
of	O
1	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
Depth	O
of	O
2	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
Stabbing	O
:	O
And	O
a	O
3d	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
the	O
Brother	O
and	O
Widow	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
others	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
kept	O
a	O
Victualling-Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
and	O
enquired	O
for	O
-	O
Foreside	O
,	O
a	O
Soldier	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Wife	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
You	O
have	O
no	O
Occasion	O
to	O
ask	O
that	O
Question	O
,	O
for	O
you	O
know	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
that	O
he	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
Savoy	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
then	O
Shaking	O
his	O
Fist	O
,	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
your	O
Blood	O
,	O
you	O
Bitch	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
be	O
revenged	O
of	O
you	O
for	O
what	O
you	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
the	O
Company	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
either	O
quiet	O
,	O
or	O
go	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
continued	O
very	O
troublesome	O
.	O
A	O
Recruit	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
then	O
drinking	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
stept	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
thrust	O
him	O
up	O
Stairs	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Struggle	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
push	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Recruit	O
,	O
and	O
scratched	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Neck	O
.	O
The	O
Recruit	O
retired	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
seeing	O
him	O
bleed	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Stair	O
foot	O
and	O
called	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Rogue	O
and	O
Villain	O
,	O
for	O
drawing	O
upon	O
a	O
naked	O
Man	O
.	O
You	O
Black-guard	O
Dog	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
come	O
hither	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
serve	O
you	O
the	O
same	O
Sauce	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
stept	O
up	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Stairs	O
towards	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
(	O
there	O
being	O
but	O
7	O
Stairs	O
in	O
all	O
)	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
Top	O
,	O
thrust	O
his	O
Sword	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
stuck	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Hand	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
2	O
Forefingers	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
then	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
returned	O
several	O
times	O
that	O
Night	O
to	O
the	O
Stair	O
Head	O
,	O
calling'em	O
ill	O
Names	O
,	O
flourishing	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
swearing	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
stab	O
every	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
received	O
this	O
Wound	O
about	O
7	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
on	O
Monday	O
Night	O
.	O
They	O
washed	O
it	O
with	O
Geneva	O
;	O
his	O
Hand	O
swell	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
painful	O
.	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
Wednesday	O
and	O
Thursday	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
who	O
dressed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
something	O
to	O
bathe	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Surgeon	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
no	O
more	O
till	O
the	O
Sunday	O
following	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
time	O
he	O
died	O
of	O
a	O
Fever	O
;	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
the	O
Fever	O
and	O
consequently	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
Another	O
Surgeon	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Wound	O
after	O
his	O
Death	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
believe	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
mortal	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Recruit	O
struck	O
him	O
first	O
kickt	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
thrust	O
him	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
the	O
Decreased	O
and	O
others	O
followed	O
with	O
Broomsticks	O
to	O
drive	O
him	O
away	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
draw	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
the	O
Decreased	O
happened	O
to	O
receive	O
that	O
Wound	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
afterwards	O
receiv	O
'd	O
a	O
great	O
Hurt	O
by	O
falling	O
down	O
Stairs	O
with	O
a	O
Barrel	O
of	O
Beer	O
.	O
Several	O
Witnesses	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
days	O
after	O
he	O
received	O
the	O
Wound	O
,	O
going	O
about	O
his	O
Business	O
as	O
usual	O
.	O
That	O
having	O
a	O
Barrel	O
of	O
Beer	O
on	O
his	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Barrel	O
rolled	O
over	O
him	O
:	O
Upon	O
which	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
to	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
O	O
!	O
my	O
Dear	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
gone	O
!	O
That	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
his	O
Death	O
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
that	O
Rogue	O
Cameron	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
And	O
he	O
answered	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
1st	O
and	O
2	O
d	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
on	O
the	O
3	O
d.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Eliz	B-pers
Schooling	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
and	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
Belson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dunn	I-pers
9	O
l.	O
9	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
to	O
go	O
abroad	O
with	O
two	O
Countrymen	O
,	O
and	O
expecting	O
to	O
pay	O
a	O
bill	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
16	O
Guineas	O
into	O
his	O
Purse	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
together	O
to	O
see	O
Westminster	O
Abbey	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Horseshoe	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
about	O
6	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
till	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
.	O
By	O
which	O
time	O
he	O
got	O
tolerably	O
drunk	O
;	O
and	O
parting	O
with	O
his	O
2	O
Friends	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
he	O
presently	O
met	O
with	O
another	O
,	O
but	O
of	O
a	O
different	O
Sex	O
.	O
Great	O
was	O
their	O
Joy	O
at	O
meeting	O
,	O
and	O
away	O
they	O
went	O
,	O
Transported	O
with	O
Pleasure	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Lady	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
in	O
Castle-Yard	B-place
,	O
where	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
3	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
They	O
drank	O
Geneva	O
till	O
they	O
could	O
hardly	O
see	O
one	O
another	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
taking	O
out	O
his	O
Purse	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
but	O
7	O
Guineas	O
left	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
16	O
.	O
But	O
where	O
or	O
how	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
was	O
more	O
than	O
he	O
could	O
tell	O
;	O
for	O
all	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
nothing	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
Gin	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
Belson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Defence	O
of	O
herself	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
2	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
their	O
House	O
with	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
both	O
he	O
and	O
she	O
being	O
so	O
drunk	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
fell	O
down	O
together	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
They	O
got	O
up	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
called	O
her	O
his	O
Dear	O
Mother	O
;	O
she	O
bade	O
him	O
kneel	O
down	O
,	O
ask	O
her	O
Blessing	O
,	O
and	O
kiss	O
her	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
.	O
He	O
obey	O
'd	O
.	O
But	O
hark	O
ye	O
me	O
,	O
Son	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
understand	O
that	O
you	O
lead	O
a	O
very	O
fine	O
Course	O
of	O
Life	O
:	O
You	O
make	O
a	O
common	O
Practice	O
of	O
getting	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
spending	O
all	O
that	O
you	O
have	O
upon	O
naughty	O
Women	O
,	O
while	O
your	O
poor	O
honest	O
Wife	O
and	O
Daughters	O
here	O
,	O
(	O
pointing	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
)	O
have	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
eat	O
these	O
3	O
days	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
good	O
mind	O
to	O
whip	O
you	O
severely	O
.	O
Indeed	O
Mamma	O
,	O
it	O
's	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
.	O
What	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
deny	O
it	O
,	O
Sirrah	O
?	O
Here	O
,	O
fetch	O
me	O
the	O
Rods	O
.	O
Will	O
you	O
do	O
so	O
any	O
more	O
?	O
No	O
,	O
never	O
.	O
Well	O
!	O
get	O
you	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
behave	O
yourself	O
as	O
you	O
ought	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
or	O
i	O
'	O
faith	O
I	O
'll	O
tickle	O
your	O
Toby	O
.	O
His	O
Mother	O
then	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
two	O
staid	O
together	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
his	O
Purse	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
9	O
Guineas	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
his	O
Mother	O
bade	O
him	O
good	O
Night	O
,	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
Proof	O
that	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
had	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Ruth	B-pers
Corket	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Calcot	O
,	O
and	O
Eliz	B-pers
Bridger	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
Sterling	I-pers
a	O
Silver	O
Pepper-Box	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
last	O
.	O
Wm	B-pers
Sterling	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
4	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
on	O
Saturday	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
drinking	O
a	O
Dram	O
at	O
a	O
Chandler	O
's	O
Shop	O
in	O
New-street	O
,	O
Fetter-Lane	O
,	O
where	O
Bridger	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
invited	O
him	O
to	O
her	O
new	O
Lodgings	O
at	O
Corket	B-place
's	I-place
;	I-place
where	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
Seal	O
to	O
cut	O
;	O
for	O
she	O
knew	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
Engraver	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
stand	O
with	O
them	O
all	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
till	O
Sunday	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
.	O
In	O
which	O
time	O
he	O
got	O
drunk	O
and	O
crazy	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
remember	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
together	O
.	O
But	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
he	O
mist	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
back	O
,	O
charged	O
them	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
They	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
except	O
he	O
would	O
pay	O
17	O
s.	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
give	O
'em	O
a	O
Note	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
returned	O
him	O
the	O
Box	O
.	O
Corket	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Sterling	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
Box	O
to	O
her	O
for	O
10	O
s.	O
that	O
he	O
spent	O
in	O
Drams	O
,	O
(	O
with	O
which	O
he	O
treated	O
all	O
Comers	O
)	O
5	O
s.	O
that	O
she	O
lent	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
that	O
Bridger	O
lent	O
him	O
.	O
She	O
called	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
believed	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
industrious	O
Woman	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
lately	O
kept	O
a	O
Cook	O
's	O
Shop	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
now	O
got	O
her	O
Living	O
by	O
letting	O
Lodgings	O
to	O
young	O
Men	O
and	O
Women	O
,	O
washing	O
Linnen	O
,	O
Shaving	O
and	O
Bleeding	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
last	O
Account	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
kept	O
a	O
Dram	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
any	O
of	O
her	O
Patients	O
should	O
faint	O
under	O
the	O
Operation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Crisp	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Alhallows	B-place
,	I-place
Lombard-Street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
dead	O
Goose	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Deal	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Brian	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Iron	O
Bars	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
Jan.	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Pollet	I-pers
,	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
returning	O
from	O
Transportation	O
before	O
the	O
Expiration	O
of	O
7	O
Years	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Arguis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminister	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Beddow	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
last	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Beddow	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Master	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
)	O
keeps	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
.	O
Wm	B-pers
Killiner	I-pers
,	O
Rich	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
were	O
drinking	O
by	O
the	O
Fire-side	O
.	O
She	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
either	O
of	O
'em	O
could	O
give	O
her	O
Change	O
for	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
snatch	O
'd	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
threw	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
a	O
Tobacco	O
Pipe	O
into	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
pretending	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Half	O
Crown	O
that	O
he	O
threw	O
there	O
.	O
They	O
raked	O
all	O
the	O
Fire	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
sifted	O
the	O
Cinders	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
find	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Killiner	O
and	O
Page	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
Maid	O
's	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
Transportation	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Maid	O
desiring	O
him	O
to	O
change	O
the	O
Half-Crown	O
,	O
he	O
,	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
What	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
put	O
an	O
Affront	O
upon	O
me	O
?	O
Do	O
you	O
ask	O
a	O
Journeyman	O
Carpenter	O
to	O
change	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
on	O
a	O
Monday	O
Morning	O
?	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
Rogue	O
,	O
and	O
beat	O
him	O
:	O
For	O
which	O
he	O
arrested	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
in	O
Revenge	O
,	O
indicted	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Harris	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Gregory	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Howard	I-pers
one	O
Guinea	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
Tho	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
a	O
Stranger	O
in	O
London	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
three	O
Men	O
,	O
and	O
enquired	O
the	O
Way	O
to	O
Lothberry	O
:	O
They	O
told	O
him	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
thither	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
shew	O
him	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
bye	O
Alley	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
stopt	O
to	O
play	O
at	O
a	O
Game	O
that	O
they	O
call	O
'd	O
Prick	O
at	O
the	O
Garter	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
)	O
to	O
play	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
them	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
understand	O
it	O
.	O
Phoo	O
!	O
says	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
signifies	O
nothing	O
,	O
I	O
understand	O
it	O
better	O
than	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
'll	O
go	O
your	O
Halves	O
for	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
engage	O
you	O
sha	O
n't	O
lose	O
.	O
He	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
)	O
then	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
which	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
snatch	O
'd	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
hold	O
Stakes	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
then	O
collar	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
that	O
he	O
ow	O
'd	O
him	O
a	O
Shilling	O
;	O
and	O
while	O
they	O
two	O
were	O
quarrelling	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
others	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
by	O
where	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
were	O
at	O
play	O
,	O
they	O
invited	O
him	O
to	O
make	O
24th	O
Man	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Guinea	O
;	O
but	O
having	O
won	O
a	O
Shilling	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
pay	O
him	O
;	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
only	O
refused	O
,	O
but	O
raised	O
a	O
Mob	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Maria	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
and	O
Katharine	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Paul's-Wharf	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
8	O
Sacks	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
18	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
last	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Hussey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
James	B-pers
Hughs	I-pers
8	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Silver	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
last	O
.	O
James	O
Hughs	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
along	O
Shoe-Lame	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
dark	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
catched	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
My	O
Dear	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
where	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
?	O
Wo	O
n't	O
you	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
Pint	O
?	O
You	O
sawcy	O
Bitch	O
,	O
(	O
says	O
he	O
)	O
what	O
should	O
I	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
Pint	O
for	O
?	O
By	O
-	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
have	O
a	O
Kiss	O
then	O
;	O
and	O
throwing	O
one	O
Hand	O
round	O
his	O
Neck	O
,	O
he	O
felt	O
the	O
other	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Rot	O
your	O
Impudence	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
corrupted	O
Toad	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
;	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
to	O
pick	O
my	O
Pocket	O
?	O
He	O
push	O
'd	O
her	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
felt	O
for	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
mist	O
it	O
,	O
stopt	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
Murder	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
passing	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
his	O
Arm	O
round	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
needs	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
together	O
to	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
2	O
s.	O
to	O
occupy	O
her	O
.	O
He	O
would	O
have	O
lain	O
with	O
her	O
all	O
Night	O
;	O
but	O
because	O
she	O
refused	O
,	O
he	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
picking	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Short	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Aldgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
keeps	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
at	O
the	O
Fiery	B-place
Beacon	I-place
in	I-place
Duke's-Place	I-place
,	O
and	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
who	O
had	O
formerly	O
been	O
his	O
Servant	O
)	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
the	O
Maid	O
was	O
gone	O
backward	O
,	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
,	O
without	O
either	O
drinking	O
his	O
Beer	O
or	O
paying	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
sold	O
by	O
two	O
Women	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Field	I-pers
in	O
Southwark	O
for	O
56	O
s.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Kensington	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Silver	O
Chains	O
val	O
4	O
s.	O
8	O
d.	O
one	O
Gold	O
Chain	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
Copper-gilt	O
Chain	O
,	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
Brass-gilt	O
Chains	O
,	O
10	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
nine	O
gilt	O
Brass	O
Hooks	O
,	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Camlet	O
Clock	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jacob	B-pers
Wallis	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
last	O
.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Wallis	I-pers
being	O
dead	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
they	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Proof	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
stolen	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Picken	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Packer	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hornsey	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Charles	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
a	O
Fork	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Scissars	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
Carolus	O
,	O
a	O
Half	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
56	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
Saturday	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
(	O
of	O
East-Barnet	O
)	O
were	O
riding	O
down	O
the	O
hollow	O
Way	O
beyond	O
Highgate	O
(	O
between	O
the	O
Pump	O
and	O
the	O
Brick-Kilns	O
)	O
they	O
were	O
attacked	O
by	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
who	O
bid	O
them	O
stand	O
,	O
made	O
them	O
dismount	O
,	O
searched	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
their	O
Horses	O
loose	O
.	O
They	O
found	O
no	O
Money	O
upon	O
Knight	O
;	O
but	O
Picken	O
took	O
from	O
this	O
Evidence	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
Fork	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Scissars	O
,	O
all	O
in	O
one	O
Sheath	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
keep	O
them	O
for	O
Luck	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
taking	O
some	O
Money	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
left	O
him	O
to	O
Packer	O
,	O
who	O
rifled	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
the	O
whole	O
amounting	O
to	O
between	O
5	O
and	O
6	O
l.	O
Charles	B-pers
Hussey	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
between	O
Twelve	O
and	O
One	O
the	O
time	O
Night	O
,	O
a	O
Watchman	O
called	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Six	O
Cans	O
in	O
Monmouth-Court	O
,	O
Holborn	O
,	O
where	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Men	O
were	O
quarrelling	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
thither	O
,	O
and	O
Picken	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
charge	O
you	O
with	O
that	O
Fellow	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
's	O
a	O
Pick-pocket	O
,	O
pointing	O
to	O
one	O
Henry	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
.	O
Sir	O
,	O
says	O
Hudson	O
,	O
I	O
charge	O
you	O
with	O
those	O
two	O
Rogues	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
)	O
for	O
they	O
are	O
a	O
Couple	O
of	O
Highwaymen	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
taken	O
these	O
two	O
Pistols	O
from	O
them	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
,	O
he	O
searched	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Knife	O
and	O
Fork	O
upon	O
Picken	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Parcels	O
of	O
Money	O
upon	O
both	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Then	O
Picken	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
rented	O
the	O
Tap	O
at	O
the	O
Mermaid	O
at	O
Windsor	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
Town	O
to	O
pay	O
50	O
l.	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Tash	I-pers
;	O
that	O
Packer	O
was	O
his	O
Friend	O
,	O
and	O
only	O
came	O
to	O
bear	O
him	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
brought	O
the	O
Pistols	O
for	O
their	O
own	O
Security	O
.	O
However	O
,	O
he	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Ellis	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
shew	O
the	O
Receipt	O
for	O
the	O
50	O
l.	O
paid	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	O
Tash	O
.	O
Pickers	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket-Book	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Coat	O
that	O
he	O
pluck	O
'd	O
off	O
when	O
he	O
shifted	O
himself	O
at	O
the	O
Round-House	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Packer	O
's	O
Wife	O
had	O
taken	O
that	O
Coat	O
to	O
her	O
Lodgings	O
in	O
Parker's-lane	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
Lodgings	O
in	O
Cross-Court	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
not	O
far	O
distant	O
from	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
A	O
Man	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
search	O
at	O
both	O
Places	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pocket-Book	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Receipt	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
This	O
increasing	O
the	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
the	O
Justice	O
order	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
examin	O
'd	O
apart	O
.	O
They	O
both	O
agreed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
hired	O
the	O
Horses	O
of	O
Mr.	O
French	O
at	O
the	O
Pavior's-Arms	O
by	O
Smithfield-Bars	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Windsor	O
,	O
for	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
set	O
out	O
between	O
3	O
and	O
4	O
,	O
and	O
rode	O
to	O
Brentford	O
.	O
Picken	O
said	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Horses	O
was	O
a	O
Grizzle-grey	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
a	O
Bay	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
growing	O
dark	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
Brantford	O
,	O
they	O
changed	O
their	O
Minds	O
,	O
turn	O
'd	O
their	O
Horses	O
,	O
and	O
rode	O
directly	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
without	O
once	O
alighting	O
,	O
or	O
stopping	O
to	O
drink	O
either	O
at	O
Brentford	O
or	O
any	O
other	O
Place	O
upon	O
the	O
Road	O
.	O
But	O
Packer	O
said	O
that	O
both	O
the	O
Horses	O
were	O
says	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
slope	O
to	O
drink	O
at	O
several	O
Places	O
on	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
Brentford	O
alighted	O
,	O
drank	O
Ale	O
and	O
Brandy	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
committed	O
to	O
New-Prison	O
;	O
and	O
several	O
Countrymen	O
that	O
used	O
Smithfield	O
Market	O
having	O
;	O
been	O
lately	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Knife	O
and	O
Fork	O
that	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
them	O
were	O
left	O
at	O
Joseph	B-pers
Winsmore	I-pers
's	O
(	O
the	O
Lock	O
and	O
Key	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
)	O
to	O
see	O
it	O
any	O
body	O
would	O
own	O
them	O
.	O
There	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Knife	O
was	O
branded	O
in	O
the	O
Handle	O
with	O
C.C	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
sworn	O
by	O
the	O
Owner	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
J.	O
Winsmore	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
New-Prison	O
.	O
They	O
saw	O
Pickner	O
hast	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
what	O
you	O
come	O
about	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
advis	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
myself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Packer	O
.	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
done	O
it	O
last	O
Sunday	O
;	O
but	O
now	O
it	O
's	O
too	O
late	O
.	O
-	O
French	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
hired	O
two	O
Horses	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
one	O
a	O
Grizzled-grey	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
a	O
Bay	O
:	O
At	O
each	O
time	O
they	O
came	O
about	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
told	O
him	O
they	O
went	O
only	O
to	O
the	O
Upper	O
Flask	O
at	O
Hampstead	O
.	O
They	O
commonly	O
return	O
'd	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
,	O
as	O
in	O
particular	O
they	O
did	O
that	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
in	O
then	O
very	O
dirty	O
and	O
splash	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
,	O
only	O
Picken	O
told	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Knife	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
into	O
her	O
House	O
at	O
Cow-Cross	O
one	O
Minute	O
before	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
that	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
:	O
She	O
remember	O
'd	O
the	O
Time	O
exactly	O
,	O
because	O
Puken	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
her	O
Husband	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Clock	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
might	O
tell	O
her	O
Husband	O
at	O
what	O
Time	O
Picken	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
enquire	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
observe	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
dirty	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Abbot	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Abbot	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Brass	O
Shivers	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Wallinger	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
Sept.	O
last	O
.	O
Lewis	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
Transportation	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
two	O
Abbots	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kilkup	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Kilkup	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
90	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Lead	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Parishioners	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Parish	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
unlawfully	O
taking	O
(	O
with	O
Francis	B-pers
Chevers	I-pers
)	O
120	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Lead	O
from	O
Westminster-Abbey	B-place
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
last	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
a	O
Trespass	O
on	O
each	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Twelve	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Chevers	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Misdemeanor	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Loveday	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Carlisle	I-pers
34	O
Yards	O
of	O
Linnen	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
34	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Carlisle	I-pers
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
to	O
cheapen	O
Aprons	O
.	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
perceived	O
by	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
who	O
brought	O
them	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
deposited	O
'em	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Quin	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Frances	B-pers
Dun	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Norman	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
thence	O
75	O
Yards	O
of	O
strip	O
'd	O
Cotton	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
l.	O
6	O
s.	O
8	O
d.	O
220	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cotton	O
Check	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
l.	O
13	O
s.	O
17	O
Yards	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
value	O
35	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
Caps	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Norman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Norman	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
8	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
Dun	O
and	O
Quin	O
came	O
into	O
her	O
Shop	O
at	O
Limehouse	B-place
,	O
and	O
bought	O
a	O
Pack	O
of	O
Cards	O
.	O
They	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Guinea	O
to	O
change	O
,	O
and	O
observing	O
the	O
Woman	O
to	O
look	O
very	O
much	O
about	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
and	O
then	O
to	O
laugh	O
upon	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
She	O
suspected	O
the	O
Guinea	O
was	O
not	O
good	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
unwilling	O
to	O
change	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
Dun	O
tore	O
the	O
Cover	O
off	O
the	O
Cards	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
them	O
untie	O
for	O
Sale	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
So	O
that	O
at	O
last	O
she	O
gave	O
the	O
Change	O
to	O
Dun	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
it	O
over	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
She	O
lighted	O
them	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
shut	O
fast	O
the	O
Hatch	O
and	O
the	O
Door	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
backwards	O
;	O
but	O
soon	O
after	O
,	O
some	O
body	O
knock	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
opened	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
2	O
of	O
her	O
Neighbours	O
with	O
Vaughan	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
her	O
Goods	O
which	O
had	O
just	O
been	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Shop	O
.	O
Jo	B-pers
Norton	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
to	O
drink	O
at	O
a	O
Friend	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
they	O
saw	O
2	O
Men	O
and	O
a	O
Girl	O
whispering	O
together	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
an	O
Alley	O
,	O
opposite	O
to	O
Norman	O
's	O
Shop	O
.	O
Says	O
Hall	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
like	O
the	O
Looks	O
of	O
those	O
Fellows	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
are	O
Bailiffs	O
.	O
Prithee	O
,	O
John	O
,	O
step	O
over	O
and	O
observe	O
'em	O
.	O
It	O
being	O
a	O
Moon-light	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
looked	O
wishful	O
in	O
their	O
Faces	O
;	O
and	O
returning	O
to	O
Hall	O
,	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
looked	O
more	O
like	O
Thieves	O
than	O
Bailiffs	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
they	O
watch	O
'd	O
'em	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
and	O
by	O
they	O
saw	O
Vaughan	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
upon	O
his	O
Shoulder	O
.	O
They	O
stopt	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
Thieves	O
!	O
Rogues	O
!	O
do	O
you	O
design	O
to	O
rob	O
me	O
?	O
They	O
told	O
him	O
they	O
knew	O
who	O
those	O
Goods	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
.	O
Are	O
they	O
yours	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
?	O
No	O
,	O
said	O
they	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
can	O
bring	O
you	O
to	O
the	O
right	O
Owner	O
quickly	O
.	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
be	O
but	O
easy	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
shall	O
go	O
Halves	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
we	O
will	O
have	O
all	O
.	O
All	O
?	O
What	O
wo	O
n't	O
you	O
leave	O
me	O
one	O
Cap	O
?	O
Pray	O
,	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
but	O
a	O
Cap	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
rest	O
betwixt	O
you	O
.	O
They	O
carried	O
him	O
back	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Norman	O
.	O
Quin	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
and	O
Dun	O
were	O
both	O
taken	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
then	O
made	O
their	O
Defence	O
.	O
Vaughan	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
found'em	O
under	O
a	O
bench	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
Norman	O
's	O
.	O
Quin	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
Ipswich	O
when	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
but	O
brought	O
no	O
body	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
A	O
Picklock	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
Evidence	O
at	O
a	O
former	O
Sessions	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
in	O
Sheppard's-Yard	O
in	O
the	O
Little	O
Minories	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Dun	O
was	O
at	O
their	O
House	O
between	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
that	O
Night	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Vaughan	O
and	O
Quin	O
(	O
Brothers	O
by	O
Mother	O
's	O
Side	O
)	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39s	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Christian	B-pers
Christian	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Christian	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Whitechappel	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Muslin	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Fergus	B-pers
Baily	I-pers
and	O
Isabel	B-pers
Fenly	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Silletay	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Whitechappel	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sattin	O
Gown	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
a	O
Cotton	O
Gown	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
2	O
Petticoats	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Scarf	O
,	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Headcloaths	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Percival	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Percival	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
Sept.	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
taken	O
,	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
In	O
her	O
Defence	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Master	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
and	O
Money	O
too	O
,	O
for	O
Favours	O
that	O
he	O
often	O
desired	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
Bed-side	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
to	O
call	O
her	O
up	O
:	O
But	O
for	O
the	O
greater	O
Secrecy	O
,	O
he	O
bade	O
her	O
take	O
a	O
Lodging	O
in	O
some	O
Place	O
where	O
he	O
might	O
conveniently	O
visit	O
her	O
.	O
But	O
she	O
going	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
sending	O
him	O
Word	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
finding	O
her	O
out	O
by	O
chance	O
,	O
prosecuted	O
her	O
in	O
Spight	O
.	O
She	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
make	O
this	O
Defence	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
first	O
apprehended	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
(	O
she	O
said	O
)	O
was	O
only	O
because	O
she	O
was	O
then	O
unwilling	O
to	O
disgrace	O
her	O
Master	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transport	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bed	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
Rug	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Blanket	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Sheet	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
lain	O
there	O
4	O
Nights	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
,	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
Ruth	B-pers
Herringshaw	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Aldgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Sauce	O
Pans	O
and	O
2	O
Copper	O
Cover	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
an	O
Apron	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Farr	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
alias	I-pers
Edith	I-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Hugh	B-pers
Musket	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Burge	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	B-place
Savoy	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
2	O
Sheet	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
Shirt	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
a	O
Smock	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Towel	O
and	O
2	O
Aprons	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	O
Roberts	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
down	O
Stairs	O
about	O
5	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Sash	O
of	O
the	O
Parlour	O
(	O
which	O
he	O
left	O
shut	O
)	O
thrown	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Wastcoat	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
Window	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
farther	O
Search	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Boy	O
aged	O
13	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
a	O
Taylor	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
on	O
an	O
Errand	O
for	O
Silk	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dusk	O
of	O
the	O
Evening	O
.	O
As	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
formerly	O
been	O
his	O
Play-fellow	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
him	O
6d	O
.	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
get	O
into	O
the	O
Parlour	O
.	O
He	O
,	O
the	O
Boy	O
,	O
stept	O
aside	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
throw	O
up	O
the	O
Sash	O
and	O
go	O
in	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
went	O
for	O
the	O
Silk	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
his	O
Return	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Parlour	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
said	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
kill	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
carried	O
the	O
Silk	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Next	O
Night	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
proffered	O
him	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
and	O
a	O
Penknife	O
to	O
cut	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Throat	O
in	O
the	O
Dead	O
of	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
Several	O
Things	O
being	O
lost	O
,	O
this	O
Evidence	O
was	O
suspected	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
Examination	O
,	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
stolen	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tea	O
Spoon	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
his	O
Master	O
turned	O
him	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
afterwards	O
meeting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Lincoln's-lnn-Fields	O
,	O
went	O
and	O
informed	O
his	O
Master	O
of	O
the	O
whole	O
Affair	O
,	O
who	O
thereupon	O
went	O
and	O
apprehended	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Gold	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Golden	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Whitechappel	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
a	O
Smock	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
and	O
other	O
Linnen	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Felony	O
not	O
being	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Dennis	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Braithwaite	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Brock	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Coach	O
Seats	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
s.	O
15	O
Sheep	O
skins	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
30	O
Yards	O
of	O
Linsey-Woolsey	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
affecting	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Susan	B-pers
Cock	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Aldgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Moor	I-pers
16	O
Handkerchiefs	O
value	O
17	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Pearse	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bow	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Weedon	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
Dec.	O
last	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Value	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Susan	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoos	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
cheapen	O
Shoos	O
:	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Pair	O
to	O
look	O
on	O
and	O
she	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
away	O
without	O
paying	O
for	O
them	O
:	O
Which	O
being	O
only	O
a	O
Trespass	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
a	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
away	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Simon	B-pers
Hacket	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Shoreditch	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Shirts	O
,	O
two	O
Aprons	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Clouts	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
a	O
Crowd	O
of	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
another	O
Place	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Charleton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Guineas	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
Aug.	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Son	O
to	O
a	O
Porter	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Crown	O
Office	O
in	O
the	O
Temple	O
;	O
by	O
which	O
Means	O
procuring	O
the	O
Keys	O
of	O
the	O
Doors	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
two	O
others	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
forced	O
open	O
the	O
Desk	O
with	O
a	O
Poker	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
spent	O
at	O
the	O
Blue	O
Ball	O
Alehouse	O
near	O
S.	O
Giles	O
's	O
Pound	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
constantly	O
harbour	O
'd	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Sepulcbre	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Smock	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
three	O
Aprons	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Upton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
Nov.	O
last	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Bull	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Coleman-street	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Smock	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Langford	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
Jan.	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
sufficient	O
Proof	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Martin	B-pers
Eustace	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Boon	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Tho	B-pers
Grace	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Alhallows	B-place
Barkin	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Boat	O
value	O
4	O
l	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Boat	O
was	O
mist	O
from	O
Tower	O
Stairs	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
;	O
and	O
about	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Boat	O
,	O
being	O
pursued	O
by	O
some	O
Sailors	O
for	O
stealing	O
Stanching	O
Irons	O
from	O
the	O
Sloop	O
Glocester	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Boat	O
a-drift	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
take	O
it	O
feloniously	O
,	O
they	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Mercer	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Masters	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Cornhill	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Frock	O
with	O
12	O
Silver	O
Buttons	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Rayner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Aldgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Cup	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Israel	B-pers
Crow	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
Oct.	O
last	O
.	O
Israel	B-pers
Crow	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
who	O
had	O
formerly	O
lodg	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
)	O
came	O
to	O
visit	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
missing	O
.	O
She	O
charged	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
at	O
-	O
Corket	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
Two	O
Golden	O
Balls	O
in	O
Hounsditch	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
Places	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Enfield	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Tottenham	B-place
High-Cross	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
,	O
no	O
person	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
two	O
Coats	O
and	O
Pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	O
Goodwin	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
9	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
John	B-pers
Archer	I-pers
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Field	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
his	O
Back	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
enquired	O
the	O
Way	O
to	O
Walthamstow	O
.	O
They	O
Pass	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
Archer	O
going	O
a	O
little	O
farther	O
,	O
found	O
that	O
Goodwin	O
's	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
:	O
Upon	O
which	O
he	O
turned	O
back	O
,	O
pursued	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Map	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
returning	O
from	O
Transportation	O
,	O
without	O
lawful	O
Cause	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Expiration	O
of	O
seven	O
Years	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
own	O
'd	O
himself	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
it	O
by	O
being	O
press	O
'd	O
on	O
board	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Ship	O
the	O
Greyhound	O
,	O
Capt	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Solgard	I-pers
.	O
Several	O
Sailors	O
appeared	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
said	O
Ship	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
bring	O
none	O
to	O
swear	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
press	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Olivant	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Murder	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Sword	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
in	O
the	O
left	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Belly	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
short	O
Ribs	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Length	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
Depth	O
of	O
10	O
Inches	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languish	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
Major	O
Nortliffe	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
himself	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Olivant	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Lewis	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
dined	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Lewis	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
at	O
Charing-Cross	O
.	O
After	O
Dinner	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
Young	O
Man	O
's	O
Coffee	O
house	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
the	O
Mitre	O
Tavern	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
Parting	O
Glass	O
;	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Olivant	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
an	O
Officer	O
in	O
General	O
Evans	O
's	O
Regiment	O
of	O
Dragoons	O
)	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
for	O
Dorchester	O
.	O
They	O
drank	O
pretty	O
briskly	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
appeared	O
friendly	O
and	O
pleasant	O
.	O
About	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Company	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
only	O
Mr.	O
Olivant	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Lewis	O
and	O
himself	O
,	O
were	O
left	O
together	O
.	O
Soon	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Lewis	O
desired	O
Mr.	O
Olivant	O
to	O
pay	O
him	O
53	O
l.	O
that	O
he	O
ow	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Olivant	O
express	O
'd	O
a	O
Surprize	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
intimate	O
Friend	O
should	O
,	O
without	O
giving	O
him	O
any	O
previous	O
Notice	O
,	O
make	O
such	O
a	O
Demand	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
,	O
when	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
thought	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
such	O
a	O
Sum	O
about	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
possibly	O
have	O
Time	O
to	O
provide	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
either	O
remitt	O
the	O
Sum	O
to	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Regiment	O
,	O
or	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
Note	O
for	O
Value	O
upon	O
a	O
Relation	O
,	O
payable	O
in	O
London	O
.	O
Neither	O
of	O
these	O
Proposals	O
would	O
satisfy	O
the	O
Deceased	O
for	O
he	O
still	O
insisted	O
upon	O
present	O
Payment	O
.	O
He	O
,	O
this	O
Evidence	O
,	O
then	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
himself	O
would	O
discharge	O
the	O
Debt	O
the	O
very	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
if	O
Mr.	O
Olivant	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
Note	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
same	O
Sum	O
at	O
six	O
Months	O
after	O
Date	O
.	O
To	O
this	O
they	O
both	O
acquiesced	O
and	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
good	O
Friends	O
again	O
.	O
And	O
then	O
he	O
,	O
this	O
Evidence	O
,	O
fell	O
asleep	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
suddenly	O
awaked	O
by	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
betwixt	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
.	O
He	O
looked	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
left	O
his	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
gone	O
round	O
the	O
Table	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Olivant	O
,	O
at	O
whom	O
he	O
that	O
instant	O
made	O
a	O
Pass	O
with	O
his	O
drawn	O
Sword	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
other	O
put	O
by	O
with	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
that	O
means	O
received	O
a	O
Wound	O
.	O
He	O
got	O
up	O
to	O
part	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
before	O
he	O
could	O
effect	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
closed	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Lewis	O
under	O
Mr.	O
Olivant	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Olivant	O
's	O
drawn	O
Sword	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
before	O
.	O
Tho	B-pers
Maccarthey	I-pers
the	O
Drawer	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Olivant	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Lewis	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Gentlemen	O
came	O
,	O
they	O
all	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
good	O
Friends	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
spoke	O
a	O
Supper	O
.	O
About	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
Disturbance	O
,	O
ran	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Deceased	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Olivant	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
being	O
undermost	O
.	O
He	O
and	O
the	O
Major	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
who	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
help	O
'd	O
'em	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
ran	O
for	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
At	O
his	O
Return	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
another	O
Room	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
was	O
lying	O
upon	O
a	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Olivant	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
Dear	O
Lewis	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
dying	O
Man	O
;	O
My	O
Life	O
is	O
at	O
Stake	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
to	O
speak	O
what	O
you	O
know	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
your	O
Sword	O
drawn	O
first	O
?	O
The	O
Deceased	O
answered	O
,	O
Ay	O
,	O
Ay	O
,	O
I	O
forgive	O
you	O
freely	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
killed	O
Mr.	O
Olivant	O
.	O
This	O
Evidence	O
farther	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Room	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
Misfortune	O
happened	O
,	O
was	O
very	O
small	O
,	O
and	O
except	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
risen	O
from	O
his	O
Seat	O
,	O
and	O
gone	O
round	O
the	O
Table	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Olivant	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
hardly	O
possible	O
for	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
fallen	O
together	O
in	O
the	O
Place	O
and	O
Manner	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Major	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
followed	O
the	O
last	O
Evidence	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
saw	O
a	O
drawn	O
swords	O
upon	O
the	O
Floor	O
,	O
and	O
raising	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
they	O
convey	O
'd	O
him	O
into	O
another	O
Room	O
,	O
where	O
Mr.	O
Olivant	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
draw	O
first	O
?	O
And	O
the	O
Deceased	O
answered	O
as	O
often	O
,	O
I	O
forgive	O
you	O
.	O
Mr	O
Olivant	O
's	O
Left	O
Hand	O
was	O
bloody	O
.	O
The	O
Sword	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
stained	O
with	O
Blood	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
upon	O
Searching	O
the	O
Wound	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Sword	O
entred	O
the	O
Left	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Belly	O
,	O
pierced	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Diaphragma	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Lungs	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
out	O
under	O
the	O
short	O
Ribs	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
considerable	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Blood	O
extravasated	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
died	O
about	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Wound	O
was	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
Before	O
he	O
died	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Olivant	O
,	O
I	O
forgive	O
you	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bowler	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
he	O
stay	O
'd	O
by	O
him	O
from	O
3	O
o'Clock	O
till	O
he	O
died	O
;	O
betwixt	O
which	O
Times	O
,	O
a	O
certain	O
Gentleman	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
the	O
Deceased	O
(	O
without	O
being	O
asked	O
the	O
Question	O
)	O
said	O
,	O
'T	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Olivant	O
's	O
Fault	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
pay	O
me	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Olivant	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
made	O
no	O
material	O
Variation	O
from	O
the	O
Account	O
that	O
Major	O
Nortliffe	O
had	O
already	O
given	O
,	O
but	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Major	O
was	O
asleep	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
started	O
up	O
from	O
his	O
Seat	O
,	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
came	O
round	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
and	O
push	O
'd	O
at	O
him	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Room	O
being	O
very	O
narrow	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Door	O
opening	O
inwards	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
retreat	O
without	O
manifest	O
Danger	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
which	O
put	O
him	O
under	O
a	O
Necessity	O
of	O
defending	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
Consequence	O
of	O
which	O
proved	O
very	O
unhappy	O
;	O
tho	O
'	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
ignorant	O
when	O
or	O
how	O
the	O
Deceased	O
received	O
the	O
Wound	O
.	O
Dr.	O
Furlong	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
after	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
wounded	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Olivant	O
laid	O
his	O
Hand	O
upon	O
his	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Lewis	O
,	O
Lewis	O
,	O
Was	O
not	O
you	O
the	O
Aggressor	O
?	O
And	O
the	O
Deceased	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
forgive	O
you	O
;	O
't	O
was	O
all	O
fair	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Carter	O
at	O
the	O
Mitre	O
Tavern	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
the	O
Deceased	O
lay	O
wounded	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Olivant	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Company	O
,	O
Take	O
Notice	O
of	O
what	O
he	O
says	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
turning	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
draw	O
first	O
?	O
The	O
Deceased	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
forgive	O
you	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Olivant	O
return	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
's	O
not	O
what	O
I	O
ask	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
Life	O
's	O
at	O
Stake	O
:	O
Did	O
you	O
draw	O
first	O
?	O
To	O
which	O
the	O
Deceased	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
Ay	O
,	O
Ay	O
,	O
I	O
forgive	O
you	O
.	O
Capt	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Hawley	I-pers
and	O
Capt	O
.	O
Newton	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
as	O
he	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
sorry	O
to	O
find	O
him	O
in	O
that	O
Condition	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
it	O
happen	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
It	O
was	O
my	O
own	O
seeking	O
,	O
I	O
freely	O
forgive	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
desire	O
there	O
may	O
be	O
no	O
manner	O
of	O
Prosecution	O
.	O
The	O
Rt	O
.	O
Hon	O
.	O
the	O
Lord	O
Viscount	O
Lonsdale	O
inform	O
'd	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
Mr.	O
Olivant	O
about	O
four	O
Years	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
which	O
time	O
he	O
maintained	O
a	O
fair	O
Character	O
,	O
not	O
being	O
addicted	O
to	O
quarrel	O
,	O
but	O
distinguishing	O
himself	O
by	O
an	O
agreeable	O
Civllity	O
and	O
good	O
Nature	O
.	O
Sir	O
Wilfrid	B-pers
Lawson	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
having	O
known	O
Mr.	O
Olivant	O
three	O
Years	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
constantly	O
found	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
a	O
happy	O
,	O
peaceable	O
Disposition	O
,	O
and	O
far	O
from	O
being	O
quarrelsome	O
.	O
General	O
Evans	O
gave	O
Mr.	O
Olivant	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
an	O
open	O
,	O
peaceable	O
,	O
generous	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
one	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
backward	O
in	O
paying	O
his	O
just	O
Debts	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
very	O
turbulent	O
,	O
and	O
subject	O
to	O
quarrel	O
in	O
his	O
Drink	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
Reason	O
he	O
had	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
his	O
Commission	O
.	O
Col.	O
Lanoe	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Behalf	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Olivant	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
a	O
pleasant	O
,	O
even	O
Temper	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
more	O
the	O
opposite	O
Character	O
,	O
he	O
frequently	O
being	O
(	O
especially	O
when	O
in	O
Drink	O
)	O
very	O
troublesome	O
in	O
the	O
Regiment	O
.	O
Many	O
other	O
Persons	O
of	O
Distinction	O
were	O
ready	O
to	O
appear	O
in	O
Favour	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Olivant	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Court	O
thought	O
it	O
unnecessary	O
.	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
and	O
Francis	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Whitechappel	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
in	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
of	O
Rich	B-pers
Lindsey	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
85	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Lindsey	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
Mason	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Brooks	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Blackbourn	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Thomson	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
black	O
Mare	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Lad	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Bridle	O
and	O
Saddle	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Lawen	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
Tho	B-pers
Higgins	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
having	O
in	O
September	O
last	O
bought	O
a	O
Gelding	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
Trouble	O
about	O
it	O
in	O
November	O
following	O
;	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
standing	O
at	O
an	O
Alehouse-Door	O
with	O
a	O
Mare	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
Brother	O
Dealer	O
,	O
how	O
goes	O
it	O
?	O
Sha	O
n't	O
we	O
drink	O
together	O
?	O
And	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
with	O
all	O
my	O
Heart	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
in	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
Deponent	O
)	O
privily	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Gelding	O
very	O
honestly	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
uneasy	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
the	O
Gelding	O
again	O
and	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
Mare	O
that	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
instead	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Row	I-pers
(	O
at	O
the	O
Two	O
Spies	O
and	O
Grapes	O
in	O
King-street	O
near	O
the	O
Seven	O
Dials	O
)	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
7	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
there	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
hung	O
his	O
Mare	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
:	O
They	O
having	O
some	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
sent	O
for	O
Higgins	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
for	O
Richard	B-pers
Lad	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Owner	O
of	O
the	O
Mare	O
.	O
Richard	O
Lad	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Mare	O
that	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Possession	O
was	O
his	O
Mare	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
turn	O
'd	O
her	O
out	O
to	O
Grass	O
at	O
Barn-Elms	B-place
about	O
6	O
o'Clock	O
the	O
preceding	O
Night	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
try	O
'd	O
last	O
Sessions	O
on	O
three	O
Indicments	O
)	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Dunt	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
120	O
Copper	O
Halfpence	O
in	O
a	O
Bag	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Harriot	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
Dec	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Islington	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Roan	O
Mare	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Humphrey	B-pers
Bodman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
Mare	O
at	O
Barnet	O
for	O
5	O
Guineas	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
apprehended	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
before	O
Justice	O
Smith	O
,	O
he	O
there	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
stoln	O
it	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Nicholson	O
's	O
Ground	O
at	O
Islington	B-place
.	O
H.	O
Bodman	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
Mare	O
to	O
Grass	O
at	O
Mr.Nicholson	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
Mare	O
that	O
was	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
Sale	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Nicholson	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
lately	O
been	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
lost	O
Mr.	O
Bodman	O
's	O
Mare	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
upon	O
what	O
Account	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
stopt	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
thither	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
offer	O
'd	O
the	O
Mare	O
to	O
Sale	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
he	O
take	O
her	O
with	O
a	O
felonious	O
Intent	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
for	O
the	O
Sake	O
of	O
a	O
Ride	O
;	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
Justice	O
prevented	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
rode	O
her	O
back	O
again	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bradley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Margaret	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Riding	O
Hood	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Huckle	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
Jan.	O
last	O
.	O
Marg	O
.	O
Cook	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
along	O
Blackwall	B-place
Causeway	I-place
,	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
took	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Cloak	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Have	O
you	O
got	O
any	O
Money	O
?	O
She	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
Why	O
then	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
your	O
Blood	O
,	O
you	O
Bitch	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
have	O
your	O
Life	O
.	O
She	O
beg	O
'd	O
of	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
murder	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
struck	O
her	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
times	O
with	O
a	O
Stick	O
,	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
her	O
down	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
turn	O
'd	O
up	O
her	O
Petticoats	O
to	O
feel	O
for	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
what	O
he	O
would	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
But	O
finding	O
no	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
beat	O
her	O
again	O
cruelly	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
that	O
he	O
'd	O
do	O
her	O
Business	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
not	O
withstanding	O
her	O
Cries	O
and	O
Entreaties	O
,	O
he	O
drag	O
'd	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
great	O
Road	O
,	O
laid	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Cart-rout	O
,	O
beat	O
her	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
her	O
Cloak	O
.	O
She	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Man	O
coming	O
by	O
,	O
prevented	O
his	O
doing	O
her	O
farther	O
Mischief	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
hearing	O
some	O
Blows	O
given	O
with	O
a	O
Stick	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
crying	O
Murder	O
,	O
he	O
mended	O
his	O
Pace	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
Cloak	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
him	O
swear	O
that	O
he	O
'd	O
have	O
her	O
Blood	O
.	O
He	O
(	O
this	O
Witness	O
)	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
about	O
?	O
But	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
without	O
answering	O
,	O
struck	O
at	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Stick	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
aside	O
out	O
of	O
sight	O
.	O
He	O
(	O
his	O
Deponent	O
)	O
then	O
ran	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Brounker	I-pers
,	O
which	O
was	O
not	O
far	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
what	O
had	O
happen	O
'd	O
.	O
J.	O
Brounker	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
(	O
upon	O
Halls	O
Information	O
)	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
stopt	O
him	O
upon	O
Suspicion	O
.	O
E.	O
Hall	O
and	O
others	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Assistance	O
:	O
They	O
went	O
a	O
little	O
farther	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Way	O
they	O
found	O
her	O
Cloak	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
by	O
it	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Stick	O
and	O
a	O
Glove	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
deny	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Fellow	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Woman	O
had	O
made	O
shift	O
to	O
get	O
to	O
the	O
next	O
house	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
they	O
brought	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Priscilla	B-pers
Bridges	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Katharine	B-pers
Hastings	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
Jan.	O
last	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Val	O
.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Casey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
Shirts	O
val	O
.	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Frock	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
8	O
Napkins	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Rich	B-pers
.	I-pers
Higginson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
Dec.	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Nurse	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
lost	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Robard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Maile	I-pers
,	O
value	O
Three	O
Half-pence	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	B-place
Savoy	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Paterson	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
Seven	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intention	O
to	O
steal	O
.	O
But	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Picton	I-pers
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Moody	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
50	O
Books	O
val	O
.	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Millan	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
reaching	O
Moody	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
full	O
against	O
Picton	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Pinch	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Pinches	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
Scarf	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Fessy	I-pers
;	O
and	O
4	O
Yards	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
Jan.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
unlawfully	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Tickner	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
steal	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
James	B-pers
Tickner	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Pillory	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bowler	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Bowel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Katharine	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
in	O
unlawfully	O
taking	O
from	O
the	O
Tenement	O
of	O
Isabella	B-pers
Lansdown	I-pers
112	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Leaden	O
Pipe	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
last	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bowler	I-pers
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Tibbs	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Whitechappel	B-place
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
,	O
being	O
arm	O
'd	O
with	O
Guns	O
,	O
Swords	O
,	O
and	O
Staves	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
their	O
Faces	O
black	O
'd	O
,	O
or	O
being	O
drest	O
in	O
White	O
,	O
or	O
otherwise	O
disguised	O
,	O
did	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
appear	O
in	O
the	O
High	O
Street	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
great	O
Terror	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Subjects	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Charge	O
not	O
being	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bowler	I-pers
was	O
a	O
3d	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Tibbs	I-pers
a	O
2	O
d	O
time	O
,	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
,	O
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Brooksbank	I-pers
,	O
and	O
take	O
from	O
thence	O
12	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
val	O
.	O
18	O
s.	O
5	O
Quarts	O
of	O
Brandy	O
val	O
.	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
5	O
Bottles	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
14	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
;	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
Goods	O
of	O
H.	O
Brooksbank	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
Eight	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
.	O
Brooksbank	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
arrested	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
more	O
of	O
the	O
New	O
Minters	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
in	O
Whitechappel	O
,	O
about	O
Nine	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
The	O
outer	O
Door	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Sash-Door	O
within	O
was	O
shut	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
forced	O
an	O
Entrance	O
,	O
and	O
Bowler	O
knockt	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
very	O
abusive	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
(	O
but	O
not	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
)	O
had	O
their	O
Faces	O
black	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
Shirts	O
over	O
their	O
other	O
Cloaths	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
were	O
missing	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Goddard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
with	O
Samuel	B-pers
Axtell	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Bollan	I-pers
,	O
did	O
assault	O
Robert	B-pers
Wise	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Crystal	O
Buttons	O
,	O
set	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
last	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Goddard	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Rustead	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
in	O
conspiring	O
to	O
charge	O
Robert	B-pers
Wise	I-pers
with	O
an	O
Intention	O
to	O
committ	O
Sodomy	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Bollan	I-pers
,	O
and	O
by	O
that	O
means	O
extorting	O
from	O
the	O
said	O
Robert	B-pers
Wise	I-pers
a	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
and	O
several	O
Sums	O
of	O
Money	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Wise	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
about	O
Six	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
making	O
Water	O
at	O
Bear-Key	B-place
,	O
a	O
Man	O
(	O
whose	O
Name	O
he	O
has	O
since	O
heard	O
is	O
Bollan	O
)	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
thrust	O
his	O
Hand	O
into	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
when	O
immediately	O
two	O
others	O
,	O
(	O
Goddard	O
and	O
Axtell	O
)	O
started	O
upon	O
them	O
from	O
behind	O
some	O
Hogsheads	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
Now	O
,	O
by	O
G	O
-	O
,	O
we	O
have	O
got	O
him	O
;	O
-	O
A	O
Sodomite	O
!	O
A	O
Sodomite	O
!	O
He	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
surprized	O
at	O
the	O
Charge	O
;	O
which	O
they	O
perceived	O
and	O
swore	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
presently	O
carry	O
him	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
their	O
Oaths	O
that	O
they	O
saw	O
him	O
going	O
to	O
commit	O
the	O
Fact	O
with	O
Bollan	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
Surprize	O
,	O
and	O
assured	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
them	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Crystal	O
Buttons	O
.	O
Goddard	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
swore	O
that	O
they	O
must	O
have	O
something	O
else	O
,	O
or	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
the	O
worse	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
followed	O
him	O
home	O
.	O
They	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
in	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
down	O
again	O
quickly	O
,	O
and	O
bring	O
them	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
carry	O
him	O
to	O
Newgate	O
directly	O
.	O
He	O
promised	O
them	O
to	O
try	O
what	O
he	O
could	O
do	O
.	O
They	O
bade	O
him	O
borrow	O
a	O
Guinea	O
of	O
the	O
Maid	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
it	O
no	O
otherwise	O
.	O
He	O
brought	O
them	O
two	O
York-Building	O
Lottery-Tickets	O
,	O
of	O
30	O
s.	O
value	O
each	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
At	O
two	O
other	O
times	O
they	O
brought	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Rustead	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
extorted	O
15	O
s.	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
waited	O
for	O
his	O
coming	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
Gutter-Lane	O
Rustead	O
clapt	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
now	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
to	O
carry	O
him	O
to	O
Newgate	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
would	O
certainly	O
execute	O
it	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
help	O
them	O
to	O
4	O
l.	O
for	O
Goddard	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
a	O
little	O
Money	O
to	O
fit	O
him	O
out	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
40	O
s.	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
them	O
that	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
never	O
trouble	O
him	O
again	O
:	O
They	O
swore	O
they	O
never	O
would	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
them	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
insisted	O
upon	O
his	O
making	O
it	O
up	O
4	O
l.	O
But	O
still	O
promising	O
,	O
with	O
repeated	O
Imprecations	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
comply	O
'd	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
never	O
come	O
after	O
him	O
any	O
more	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
he	O
gave	O
them	O
the	O
other	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
parted	O
for	O
that	O
time	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
next	O
Night	O
,	O
hearing	O
the	O
Bell	O
ring	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
see	O
who	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
he	O
opened	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
nobody	O
at	O
first	O
;	O
but	O
quickly	O
Rustead	O
stept	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
must	O
needs	O
speak	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
taken	O
him	O
out	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
