TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Jail-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
On	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
13th	O
,	O
14th	O
,	O
and	O
15th	O
Days	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Eleventh	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
GEORGE	B-pers
MERTTINS	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Fortescue	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
Sergeant	O
at	O
Law	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
JURORS	O
were	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
The	O
London	O
Jury	O
James	B-pers
Kelham	I-pers
,	O
Eustace	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Vere	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Best	I-pers
,	O
Oliver	B-pers
Bressington	I-pers
,	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Puller	I-pers
,	O
Edmund	B-pers
Hickman	I-pers
David	B-pers
Tough	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hains	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Dunbar	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cradock	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Purdy	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ryland	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Golding	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Brin	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Wilder	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wisdich	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Proceedings	O
were	O
as	O
follows	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Plant	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Bishopsgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
Ann	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
a	O
Handkerchief	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
two	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
William	O
Brown	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
:	O
I	O
having	O
two	O
Guineas	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
Excise	O
,	O
I	O
ty	O
'd	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
it	O
by	O
my	O
Daughter	O
Ann	O
Brown	O
,	O
a	O
Child	O
about	O
10	O
Years	O
old	O
.	O
She	O
soon	O
came	O
back	O
crying	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
it	O
going	O
through	O
Bishopsgate	B-place
.	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
by	O
others	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
a	O
Sailor	O
's	O
Jacket	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
have	O
such	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
down	O
Hounsditch	O
.	O
A	O
Fellow	O
being	O
afterward	O
,	O
seen	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Jacket	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
distinguishable	O
by	O
three	O
odd	O
Buttons	O
)	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
Examination	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Brother	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
not	O
himself	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
that	O
Jacket	O
on	O
when	O
the	O
Girl	O
lost	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
By	O
his	O
Directions	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Eliz	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Cherry-Tree	O
in	O
Golden-Lane	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
that	O
I	O
ty	O
'd	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
when	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Girl	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
same	O
Handkerchief	O
I	O
found	O
about	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Neck	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
He	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
with	O
it	O
near	O
Bishopsgate	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
immediately	O
ran	O
through	O
Devonshire-Square	O
into	O
Still-Alley	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
untying	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
two	O
Guineas	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
Fellow	O
of	O
an	O
ill	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
long	O
out	O
of	O
New-Prison	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Kingstow	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
:	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
cleaning	O
Shoos	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
near	O
Bishopsgate	O
,	O
about	O
Nine	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pass	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
turn	O
the	O
Lappet	O
of	O
his	O
Jacket	O
aside	O
,	O
thrust	O
a	O
colour	O
'd	O
Handkerchief	O
into	O
his	O
Breeches	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
down	O
Hounsditch	O
;	O
and	O
presently	O
after	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Child	O
Ann	O
Brown	O
crying	O
for	O
the	O
Loss	O
of	O
her	O
Money	O
.	O
Ann	O
Brown	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
lost	O
the	O
Money	O
under	O
Bishopsgate	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
thus	O
made	O
his	O
Defence	O
:	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
,	O
over	O
against	O
the	O
Church	O
,	O
I	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
this	O
Handkerchief	O
lying	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
holding	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
Hand	O
,	O
Who	O
has	O
lost	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
?	O
says	O
I.	O
Whereupon	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
that	O
sells	O
Apples	O
cry	O
'd	O
Halves	O
.	O
But	O
when	O
I	O
open	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
two	O
Guineas	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
'T	O
is	O
all	O
your	O
own	O
,	O
young	O
Man	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
much	O
good	O
may't	O
do	O
you	O
.	O
If	O
the	O
Gentlewoman	O
was	O
here	O
,	O
she	O
'd	O
say	O
the	O
same	O
thing	O
herself	O
.	O
As	O
for	O
my	O
being	O
in	O
New-Prison	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
for	O
no	O
Harm	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
an	O
ill	O
thing	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
:	O
'T	O
was	O
only	O
for	O
Face-making	O
,	O
(	O
that	O
is	O
)	O
getting	O
of	O
Bastard	O
Children	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Large	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
Tho	B-pers
Clements	I-pers
a	O
Handkerchief	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Webster	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Walbrook	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
the	O
Chattels	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Griffis	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
May	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hull	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Harney	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Harvey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Sperry	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Aldgate	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Hilton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
a	O
Wig	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
Hones	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
Looking	O
Glass	O
30	O
s	O
and	O
three	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Human	O
Hair	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Tho	O
.	O
Hilton	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
April	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Hilton	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
:	O
I	O
lie	O
in	O
my	O
Shop	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
about	O
Midnight	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
all	O
fast	O
.	O
About	O
Two	O
,	O
the	O
Watch	O
call	O
'd	O
me	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Bill	O
of	O
my	O
Window	O
was	O
wrenched	O
off	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Shutters	O
taken	O
down	O
,	O
the	O
Sash	O
thrown	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
missing	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
committed	O
to	O
New-Prison	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
another	O
Robbery	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
thither	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
Hones	O
and	O
my	O
Wig	O
upon	O
Ned	O
Harney	O
.	O
My	O
Glass	O
I	O
found	O
at	O
Henry	B-pers
Yarp	I-pers
's	O
in	O
Hounsditch	O
,	O
who	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
Sam	B-pers
Hull	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
then	O
made	O
their	O
Defence	O
.	O
Hull	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Glass	O
he	O
sold	O
to	O
Yarp	O
was	O
left	O
him	O
by	O
his	O
Father	O
.	O
Harney	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Wig	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	O
:	O
And	O
Sperry	O
protested	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
as	O
innocent	O
as	O
the	O
Stones	O
unborn	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hull	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Harney	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Sperry	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Bromley	I-place
,	O
were	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Golding	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Coat	O
val	O
.	O
4.	O
s	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
Stockings	O
,	O
Shoos	O
and	O
Buckles	O
,	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
a	O
Rure	O
,	O
a	O
Pruning-Knife	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Penknife	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Golding	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
:	O
Between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
beyond	O
the	O
Watch-House	O
in	O
Bow	B-place
Road	I-place
,	O
I	O
pass	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
Man	O
which	O
I	O
believe	O
to	O
be	O
Ned	B-pers
Harney	I-pers
:	O
He	O
turn	O
'd	O
back	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
why	O
he	O
did	O
so	O
?	O
He	O
swore	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
stand	O
Some	O
Words	O
pass	O
'd	O
betwixt	O
us	O
,	O
when	O
two	O
more	O
(	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
pretty	O
positive	O
were	O
Sperry	O
and	O
Hull	O
)	O
started	O
up	O
with	O
a	O
G	O
-	O
D	O
-	O
ye	O
,	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
strike	O
the	O
Man	O
for	O
?	O
They	O
drag	O
'd	O
me	O
into	O
a	O
Field	O
,	O
stript	O
me	O
naked	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
give	O
me	O
an	O
old	O
Wastcoat	O
to	O
put	O
on	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
'd	O
hard	O
for	O
my	O
Pocket	O
Book	O
.	O
Tell	O
me	O
where	O
you	O
live	O
,	O
says	O
Hull	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
send	O
:	O
you	O
to-morrow	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
find	O
nothing	O
in	O
it	O
that	O
will	O
be	O
of	O
use	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
lived	O
next	O
to	O
the	O
Five	O
Bells	O
in	O
Bromley	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
not	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
his	O
Word	O
:	O
But	O
however	O
,	O
my	O
Name	O
being	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
found	O
in	O
Wood-street	O
by	O
a	O
Men	O
who	O
was	O
acquainted	O
with	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
being	O
sent	O
to	O
New-Prison	O
on	O
another	O
Occasion	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
thither	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
Breeches	O
upon	O
Sperry	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
them	O
again	O
by	O
the	O
new	O
Strings	O
,	O
a	O
Darn	O
upon	O
the	O
Knee	O
,	O
and	O
1	O
Patch	O
betwixt	O
the	O
Legs	O
.	O
The	O
Pruning	O
Knife	O
I	O
found	O
at	O
Sperry	O
's	O
Lodging	O
.	O
My	O
Penknife	O
he	O
delivered	O
to	O
Sir	O
Isaac	B-pers
Titland	I-pers
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
said	O
,	O
This	O
Knife	O
I	O
took	O
from	O
Golding	O
in	O
these	O
Breeches	O
.	O
Hull	O
and	O
Harney	O
were	O
acquitted	O
;	O
but	O
Sperry	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hull	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Sperry	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Spiller	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
were	O
a	O
3d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Colbin	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
three	O
Wigs	O
value	O
9	O
l.	O
and	O
15	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Human	O
Hair	O
val	O
.	O
21	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Colbin	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Shop	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
Hull	O
's	O
Confession	O
before	O
Sir	O
Francis	B-pers
Forbes	I-pers
was	O
read	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
with	O
Sperry	O
and	O
Harvey	O
,	O
broke	O
open	O
Colbin	O
's	O
Shop	O
in	O
Camomile-street	B-place
,	O
(	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
whether	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
or	O
Day	O
)	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Hair	O
and	O
Wigs	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
sold	O
in	O
Middle-Row	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Sperry	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Aldgate	B-place
,	O
were	O
a	O
4th	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
six	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
val	O
15	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
.	O
James	O
Walker	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
Stockings	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shop	O
at	O
the	O
Hermitage	B-place
;	O
but	O
knew	O
not	O
how	O
,	O
not	O
when	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Johnsy	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
:	O
Sperry	O
had	O
lodg	O
'd	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
:	O
His	O
Wife	O
brought	O
me	O
four	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
get	O
them	O
?	O
says	O
I	O
.	O
-	O
Your	O
Husband	O
leads	O
a	O
loose	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
they	O
are	O
stolen	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
so	O
too	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
'll	O
never	O
leave	O
off	O
till	O
he	O
brings	O
me	O
and	O
himself	O
too	O
to	O
the	O
Gallows	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
'll	O
go	O
and	O
fetch	O
him	O
and	O
his	O
Companion	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
them	O
answer	O
for	O
themselves	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
quickly	O
return	O
'd	O
,	O
with	O
her	O
Husband	O
and	O
Harvey	O
.	O
They	O
asked	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
a	O
Pair	O
for	O
the	O
Stockings	O
.	O
I	O
examin	O
'd	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
by	O
'em	O
;	O
and	O
Harvey	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Sea	O
;	O
but	O
wanting	O
a	O
little	O
ready	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
But	O
afterwards	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
wrenched	O
aside	O
the	O
Shutters	O
of	O
Walker	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
them	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
Hook	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
carry	O
'd	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
:	O
Their	O
Confession	O
was	O
drawn	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
Sperry	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
sign	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
Harvey	O
pull	O
'd	O
him	O
away	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
G	O
-	O
D	O
-	O
ye	O
for	O
a	O
Fool	O
!	O
Are	O
you	O
going	O
to	O
sign	O
your	O
own	O
Dead-Warrant	O
?	O
They	O
were	O
committed	O
to	O
New-Prison	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Keeper	O
there	O
was	O
for	O
having	O
them	O
sent	O
to	O
Newgate	O
;	O
for	O
he	O
thought	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
belong	O
to	O
his	O
Posterity	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
Rawson	B-pers
Paul	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Bride	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Eleven	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Alprice	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transp	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Old-Jewry	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
Ells	O
of	O
Black	O
Mantua	O
Silk	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
30.	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Slater	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Board	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Lothbury	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Vanderplank	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
May	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transp	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Garlick-Hithe	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Silver	O
Mugs	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
7	O
l.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tumbler	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
Nine	O
Spoons	O
val	O
.	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Oliver	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Oliver	O
Mills	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Oliver	O
Mills	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
:	O
I	O
sell	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Home-brew	O
'd	O
Ale	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
up	O
early	O
one	O
Morning	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
brew	O
.	O
Now	O
this	O
Plate	O
of	O
mine	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Box	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
which	O
Box	O
he	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
bodily	O
.	O
I	O
enquired	O
after	O
him	O
of	O
an	O
old	O
Acquaintance	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
a	O
certain	O
Whore	O
in	O
the	O
Mint	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Mint	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
this	O
Whore	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
understood	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
removed	O
to	O
fresh	O
Quarters	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
at	O
the	O
Swan	O
in	O
Leadenhall-Street	O
.	O
He	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
two	O
Mugs	O
and	O
six	O
Spoons	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Hart	O
and	O
Anchor	O
in	O
Barbican	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
.	O
The	O
Tumbler	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
three	O
Spoon	O
he	O
presented	O
to	O
Madam	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Armstrong	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
received	O
the	O
Tumbler	O
and	O
three	O
Spoons	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
..	O
Guilty	O
val	O
.	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Price	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Peirce	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Bishopsgate	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
three	O
Mobs	O
,	O
a	O
Sarsnet-Hood	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Child	O
's	O
Frock	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Benson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
May	O
inst	O
.	O
Jane	O
Benson	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
Mary	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
was	O
my	O
Lodger	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
some	O
Acquaintance	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
now	O
and	O
then	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
it	O
fell	O
out	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
one	O
Day	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
attending	O
the	O
Child	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
cross	O
vixen	O
Thing	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
had	O
befoul	O
'd	O
itself	O
lamentationly	O
:	O
So	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
Mother	O
Benson	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
you	O
look	O
as	O
if	O
you	O
was	O
very	O
weary	O
and	O
sleepy	O
:	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
you	O
go	O
and	O
take	O
a	O
Nap	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
the	O
Child	O
by	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
wash	O
its	O
Things	O
the	O
while	O
.	O
And	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
waked	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
this	O
wicked	O
Jade	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Cloaths	O
were	O
gone	O
too	O
,	O
it	O
put	O
me	O
into	O
a	O
strange	O
Confirmation	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
never	O
respected	O
she	O
would	O
a	O
'	O
served	O
me	O
so	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Witness	O
deposed	O
to	O
this	O
Effect	O
:	O
My	O
Name	O
is	O
Mary	O
Lee	O
;	O
and	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
say	O
it	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
never	O
a	O
Woman	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
that	O
takes	O
more	O
Care	O
for	O
an	O
Honest	O
Livelihood	O
than	O
myself	O
.	O
I	O
turn	O
my	O
Hand	O
to	O
any	O
Thing	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
Penny	O
:	O
Sometimes	O
I	O
sell	O
Things	O
in	O
Leadenhall	O
Market	O
;	O
and	O
sometimes	O
I	O
do	O
an	O
odd	O
Char	O
at	O
one	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
at	O
another	O
.	O
We	O
Market-Women	O
are	O
up	O
early	O
and	O
late	O
,	O
and	O
work	O
hard	O
for	O
what	O
we	O
have	O
.	O
We	O
stand	O
all	O
Weathers	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
thro	O
'	O
thick	O
and	O
thin	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
well	O
known	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
never	O
the	O
Woman	O
that	O
spared	O
my	O
Carcass	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
spend	O
three	O
Farthings	O
now	O
and	O
then	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
nothing	O
but	O
what	O
is	O
my	O
own	O
.	O
I	O
get	O
it	O
honestly	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
care	O
who	O
knows	O
it	O
;	O
for	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
for	O
something	O
to	O
cheer	O
the	O
Spirits	O
between	O
whiles	O
,	O
and	O
keep	O
out	O
the	O
Wet	O
and	O
Cold	O
;	O
alackaday	O
!	O
it	O
would	O
never	O
do	O
:	O
We	O
should	O
never	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
hold	O
it	O
;	O
we	O
should	O
never	O
go	O
thro	O
'	O
stich	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
keep	O
Body	O
and	O
Soul	O
together	O
.	O
But	O
as	O
for	O
this	O
Jenny	O
Johnson	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
coming	O
sometimes	O
for	O
a	O
Quartern	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Shops	O
that	O
I	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
,	O
we	O
now	O
and	O
then	O
had	O
a	O
Dish	O
of	O
Chat	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
became	O
pretty	O
well	O
acquainted	O
;	O
whereof	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Times	O
;	O
and	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Times	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
,	O
she	O
happened	O
to	O
come	O
that	O
Day	O
as	O
my	O
Landlady	O
lost	O
her	O
Things	O
.	O
Now	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
she	O
comes	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
a	O
certain	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
we	O
had	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Quarterns	O
of	O
such	O
simple	O
Stuff	O
as	O
we	O
poor	O
Souls	O
are	O
glad	O
to	O
drink	O
.	O
And	O
from	O
thence	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
another	O
Friend	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
truly	O
she	O
would	O
needs	O
treat	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
right	O
French	O
Brandy	O
;	O
whereof	O
I	O
wondred	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
because	O
we	O
had	O
had	O
but	O
a	O
very	O
indifferent	O
Market	O
that	O
Day	O
.	O
Oh	O
!	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
want	O
for	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
above	O
a	O
Crown	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
another	O
Friend	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
to	O
that	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
by	O
way	O
of	O
Discourse	O
about	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
t'other	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Talking	O
about	O
my	O
Landlady	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
she	O
lost	O
her	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
that	O
;	O
Why	O
,	O
says	O
Jenny	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
as	O
for	O
your	O
Landlady	O
's	O
three	O
Mobs	O
and	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
I	O
sold	O
them	O
all	O
for	O
a	O
Shilling	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
in	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Beatnife	I-pers
,	O
two	O
Spring	O
Sides	O
for	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Wm	O
.	O
Beatnife	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
May	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Mary-le-Bone	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Lewis	B-pers
Robert	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
at	O
the	O
Salutation	O
in	O
Marybone	O
,	O
staid	O
about	O
a	O
Week	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Watch	O
from	O
her	O
Master	O
's	O
Bed	O
,	O
went	O
off	O
at	O
the	O
Back-Door	O
;	O
and	O
next	O
Day	O
offering	O
it	O
to	O
Sale	O
to	O
Lewis	B-pers
Mattaire	I-pers
,	O
she	O
was	O
apprehended	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Master	O
pox	O
'd	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
because	O
his	O
Wife	O
kept	O
him	O
bare	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
to	O
sell	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Val	O
.	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Table-Cloth	O
,	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Faulkner	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Norton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Apron	O
and	O
three	O
Sheets	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Flora	B-pers
Stanburg	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Stew-pan	O
,	O
val	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Garret	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transp	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Hawkshead	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Guilty	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Katharine	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
being	O
Breadths	O
for	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
15.	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Katharine	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Hutton	I-pers
10	O
s.	O
6	O
d	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hutton	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
Meuse	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
Temple	O
to	O
receive	O
a	O
little	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
staid	O
there	O
drinking	O
till	O
One	O
or	O
Two	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
;	O
at	O
which	O
time	O
,	O
being	O
pretty	O
well	O
in	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
I	O
overtook	O
three	O
Soldiers	O
.	O
They	O
jostled	O
me	O
as	O
I	O
pass	O
'd	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
went	O
forward	O
without	O
saying	O
any	O
Thing	O
to	O
them	O
:	O
And	O
soon	O
after	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
Dear	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
Pint	O
?	O
I	O
being	O
willing	O
to	O
shun	O
the	O
Soldiers	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
not	O
far	O
behind	O
me	O
,	O
stept	O
with	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
Crown	B-place
and	I-place
Harp	I-place
Tavern	I-place
,	I-place
the	I-place
Corner	I-place
of	I-place
S.	I-place
Martin's-Lane	I-place
.	O
I	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
;	O
but	O
before	O
we	O
had	O
drunk	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
put	O
my	O
Hand	O
into	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
Half	O
of	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
some	O
Silver	O
.	O
She	O
ran	O
down	O
Stairs	O
a-cross	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
after	O
her	O
:	O
But	O
presently	O
the	O
three	O
Soldiers	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
Assistance	O
.	O
She	O
cry	O
'd	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
Kill	O
the	O
Dog	O
,	O
kill	O
him	O
.	O
So	O
they	O
all	O
drew	O
their	O
Bayonets	O
,	O
and	O
forced	O
me	O
up	O
again	O
the	O
Wall	O
.	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
(	O
says	O
I	O
)	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
so	O
honourable	O
as	O
to	O
kill	O
me	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
the	O
Bottom	O
of	O
S.	O
Martin's-Lane	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
Night	O
was	O
very	O
dark	O
)	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Slap	O
o	O
'	O
the	O
Face	O
given	O
,	O
and	O
somebody	O
say	O
,	O
You	O
have	O
pick	O
'd	O
my	O
Pocket	O
you	O
Bitch	O
of	O
Half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
.	O
Coming	O
nearer	O
,	O
I	O
discovered	O
three	O
Soldiers	O
,	O
with	O
their	O
Bayonets	O
drawn	O
,	O
and	O
pointed	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
forced	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Wall	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Soldiers	O
ran	O
off	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Woman	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
too	O
,	O
ran	O
against	O
a	O
Coach	O
that	O
stood	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Prosecutor	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-House	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
confoundedly	O
drunk	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
She	O
had	O
any	O
more	O
about	O
her	O
than	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
in	O
searching	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
Half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
more	O
Silver	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
thus	O
made	O
her	O
Defence	O
:	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
make	O
me	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Tavern	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
unwilling	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
alone	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
three	O
Pints	O
of	O
Wine	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
me	O
Money	O
to	O
lie	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Gold	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
possible	O
indeed	O
that	O
Half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
might	O
slip	O
in	O
among	O
the	O
Silver	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
none	O
.	O
And	O
because	O
I	O
refused	O
to	O
comply	O
with	O
what	O
he	O
required	O
,	O
be	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
picking	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
was	O
surprized	O
at	O
.	O
However	O
,	O
he	O
paid	O
his	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
went	O
down	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
waited	O
at	O
Door	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
You	O
Bitch	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
my	O
Half	O
Guinea	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Soldiers	O
came	O
up	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
them	O
before	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Marlow	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Murphy	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
25	O
Yards	O
of	O
Dunjar	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Kirk	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	O
Kirk	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
Guilty	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Clemson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Porringer	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Pot	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
3	O
Spoone	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Walter	B-pers
Longford	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Walter	B-pers
Longford	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
following	O
I	O
distributed	O
printed	O
Advertisements	O
to	O
the	O
Goldsmiths	O
,	O
and	O
Pawnbrokers	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
very	O
remarkable	O
,	O
exactly	O
described	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Reward	O
of	O
20	O
s.	O
offer	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
one	O
of	O
these	O
Bills	O
myself	O
to	O
White	O
,	O
a	O
Pawnbroker	O
,	O
in	O
Baldwin	O
's	O
Gardens	O
,	O
who	O
positively	O
denied	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
such	O
Goods	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
;	O
but	O
going	O
thither	O
again	O
with	O
a	O
Search-Warrant	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
,	O
he	O
presently	O
confessed	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
and	O
deliver	O
'd	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
but	O
yet	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
his	O
Servant	O
to	O
demand	O
the	O
Reward	O
promis	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Advertisement	O
.	O
Guilty	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Penington	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
two	O
Yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
(	O
cut	O
out	O
for	O
a	O
Smock	O
)	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Rachel	B-pers
Humes	I-pers
;	O
3	O
Yards	O
and	O
half	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
(	O
cut	O
out	O
for	O
a	O
Shirt	O
)	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Head	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
Jenkinson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
England	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Craftow	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Covent-Garden	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
with	O
Robert	B-pers
Bent	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
1	O
Cock	O
and	O
5	O
Hens	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Kirkland	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Kirkland	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Stall	O
(	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Bow-street	B-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
)	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Poultry	O
,	O
Oranges	O
,	O
Lemons	O
,	O
and	O
Apples	O
,	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Audry	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
England	O
set	O
me	O
to	O
watch	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
whistle	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
came	O
,	O
while	O
they	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
old	O
Man	O
's	O
Apple-Stall	O
;	O
from	O
whence	O
they	O
brought	O
6	O
Fowls	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
Pockets	O
full	O
of	O
Oranges	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Fruit	O
;	O
all	O
which	O
we	O
carried	O
to	O
Tottenham-Court	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
England	O
thus	O
made	O
his	O
Defence	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Slater	O
by	O
Trade	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Rogue	O
Audry	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
my	O
'Prentice	O
:	O
but	O
he	O
stealing	O
a	O
Game-Cock	O
and	O
2	O
Hens	O
,	O
from	O
Justice	O
Ellis	O
,	O
he	O
carried	O
the	O
Cock	O
to	O
fight	O
for	O
5	O
Guineas	O
at	O
the	O
Seven-Dials	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
own	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
apprehended	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
,	O
in	O
Hopes	O
of	O
getting	O
off	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
made	O
himself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
sworn	O
this	O
against	O
me	O
.	O
Most	O
of	O
his	O
Relations	O
have	O
been	O
Rogues	O
and	O
Whores	O
;	O
his	O
Aunt	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
New	O
Prison	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
had	O
3	O
Cousins	O
hang	O
'd	O
at	O
Tyburn	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
he	O
'll	O
go	O
the	O
same	O
Way	O
himself	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
'em	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Cloths	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Nicholson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Guilty	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Thornham	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Caps	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Pinners	O
,	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
3	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Hood	O
,	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Farrow	I-pers
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nolson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Nolson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Islington	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Davison	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
16	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Davison	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Brown	O
Mare	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Davison	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
I	O
being	O
a	O
Taylor	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
done	O
some	O
Work	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
,	O
he	O
recommended	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
Friend	O
of	O
his	O
at	O
Harrow	O
on	O
the	O
Hill	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Place	O
we	O
went	O
together	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
in	O
a	O
Chaise	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
upon	O
his	O
Mare	O
:	O
We	O
return	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
being	O
but	O
an	O
indifferent	O
Horseman	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
drove	O
too	O
fast	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
However	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
jogging	O
after	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
;	O
and	O
about	O
Ten	O
o	O
'	O
Clock	O
came	O
to	O
Holloway	B-place
,	O
where	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
pass	O
'd	O
me	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
'em	O
had	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
Budget	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
like	O
a	O
Carpenter	O
:	O
They	O
saw	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
tired	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
very	O
well	O
get	O
my	O
Mare	O
along	O
the	O
Road	O
;	O
whereupon	O
they	O
turn	O
'd	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
ye	O
,	O
stand	O
and	O
deliver	O
presently	O
,	O
or	O
you	O
're	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
took	O
16	O
s.	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
pulled	O
me	O
off	O
the	O
Mare	O
,	O
and	O
mounted	O
themselves	O
,	O
Tom	O
.	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
Will	O
.	O
behind	O
him	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
Star-light	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
'em	O
pretty	O
plainly	O
,	O
especially	O
Tom	O
.	O
who	O
had	O
a	O
dirty	O
white	O
Wastecoat	O
:	O
They	O
rode	O
towards	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
if	O
I	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
follow	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
walk	O
'd	O
along	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
in	O
my	O
Boots	O
,	O
and	O
enquired	O
of	O
some	O
Waggoners	O
that	O
I	O
met	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
saw	O
such	O
Men	O
upon	O
such	O
a	O
Mare	O
?	O
But	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
at	O
the	O
Queen's-Head	O
at	O
Holloway	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
hear	O
nothing	O
of	O
'em	O
;	O
from	O
thence	O
I	O
made	O
shift	O
to	O
get	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Grimsted	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Angel	O
and	O
Gown	O
in	O
Islington	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
told	O
'em	O
how	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
described	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
the	O
Mare	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
not	O
long	O
after	O
,	O
the	O
Boy	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
saw	O
two	O
Men	O
coming	O
along	O
agreeable	O
to	O
my	O
Description	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
us	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
stopt	O
,	O
hung	O
the	O
Mare	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
Mr.	O
Grimsted	O
have	O
secured	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
unwilling	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
being	O
glad	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
found	O
the	O
Mare	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
rode	O
home	O
,	O
without	O
taking	O
any	O
farther	O
Notice	O
of	O
'em	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
that	O
Tom	O
.	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Men	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
certain	O
that	O
Will	O
.	O
was	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Grimsted	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
Between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
,	O
Davison	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
told	O
the	O
Company	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
described	O
the	O
Persons	O
.	O
Whether	O
he	O
was	O
disordered	O
with	O
the	O
Fright	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
Vexation	O
of	O
being	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
or	O
with	O
walking	O
in	O
his	O
Boots	O
from	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
Mile	O
from	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
or	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
too	O
much	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
but	O
certain	O
it	O
is	O
,	O
that	O
not	O
only	O
I	O
,	O
but	O
all	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
fuddled	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Mare	O
had	O
only	O
thrown	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
ran	O
away	O
But	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
,	O
my	O
Boy	O
comes	O
in	O
and	O
says	O
,	O
Here	O
's	O
two	O
such	O
Men	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
with	O
such	O
a	O
Mare	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
we	O
saw	O
'em	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
of	O
the	O
Boy	O
's	O
Mind	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
answer	O
'd	O
the	O
Description	O
that	O
Davison	O
had	O
given	O
of	O
'em	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
particular	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
white	O
dirty	O
Wastecoat	O
.	O
Davison	O
presently	O
said	O
,	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
Men	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
Mare	O
.	O
But	O
then	O
we	O
thought	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
only	O
a	O
Drunken	O
Frolick	O
,	O
because	O
if	O
these	O
Men	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Mare	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
hardly	O
have	O
stopt	O
at	O
a	O
House	O
so	O
near	O
where	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Davison	O
seeing	O
we	O
gave	O
but	O
little	O
Credit	O
to	O
his	O
Account	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
upon	O
the	O
Mare	O
,	O
and	O
rid	O
homewards	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
never	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
prevent	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
ask	O
'd	O
'em	O
where	O
they	O
got	O
the	O
Mare	O
?	O
They	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
her	O
astray	O
in	O
White	O
Conduit-Feilds	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
carry	O
her	O
to	O
Rolf	O
's	O
Pound	O
:	O
Upon	O
farther	O
Enquiry	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
the	O
direct	O
Road	O
to	O
the	O
Pound	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
round	O
a	O
Byeway	O
,	O
thro	O
'	O
Mr.	O
Sibban	O
's	O
(	O
the	O
Cow-keeper	O
's	O
)	O
Ground	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
times	O
farther	O
about	O
than	O
the	O
right	O
Way	O
.	O
This	O
made	O
me	O
begin	O
to	O
suspect'em	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
thought	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
Reason	O
that	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
Carriers	O
that	O
Davison	O
met	O
on	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
had	O
seen	O
these	O
two	O
Men	O
upon	O
the	O
Mare	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
walk	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
Boots	O
,	O
yet	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
sooner	O
than	O
they	O
that	O
rid	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
.	O
The	O
Deposition	O
of	O
this	O
Witness	O
was	O
corroborated	O
by	O
Basil	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
,	O
Jeremy	B-pers
Eustace	I-pers
,	O
and	O
others	O
.	O
Robin	B-pers
Hughs	I-pers
(	O
the	O
Boy	O
)	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
shutting	O
up	O
the	O
Windows	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
coming	O
along	O
,	O
one	O
upon	O
the	O
Mare	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
walking	O
a	O
foot	O
.	O
It	O
It	O
being	O
the	O
last	O
Day	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
'em	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
a	O
Maying	O
already	O
?	O
And	O
as	O
they	O
came	O
a	O
little	O
nigher	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
and	O
the	O
Beast	O
were	O
agreeable	O
to	O
Davison	O
's	O
Account	O
of	O
'em	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
'em	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
with	O
that	O
Mare	O
?	O
Upon	O
which	O
one	O
'em	O
said	O
,	O
Let	O
's	O
go	O
and	O
see	O
if	O
it	O
's	O
Grimsted	O
's	O
Mare	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
ye	O
what	O
need	O
ye	O
mind	O
what	O
he	O
says	O
?	O
They	O
made	O
a	O
little	O
Stop	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
ran	O
in	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
my	O
Master	O
.	O
Mr.Brown	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Davison	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
Harrow	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
Company	O
all	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
drink	O
nothing	O
that	O
was	O
likely	O
to	O
disorder	O
him	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
benighted	O
in	O
returning	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
but	O
an	O
indifferent	O
Rider	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
him	O
before	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Hollaway	O
But	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
late	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
sober	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nolson	I-pers
thus	O
made	O
a	O
Defence	O
for	O
himself	O
and	O
his	O
Brother	O
:	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
Brother	O
were	O
in	O
Union	O
Court	O
,	O
opposite	O
to	O
S.	O
Andrew	O
's	O
Church	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
at	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
past	O
Ten	O
.	O
From	O
thence	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
my	O
Mother	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
lives	O
at	O
Lower	O
Hollaway	O
;	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
in	O
White-Conduit-Feilds	O
,	O
we	O
saw	O
this	O
Mare	O
saddled	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Bridle	O
thrown	O
over	O
her	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
ty	O
'd	O
to	O
a	O
Stile	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
some	O
Rogues	O
had	O
been	O
robbing	O
thereabouts	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
had	O
left	O
her	O
there	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
says	O
my	O
Brothers	O
,	O
Do	O
n't	O
be	O
afraid	O
,	O
we	O
'll	O
take	O
the	O
Mare	O
to	O
Town	O
;	O
but	O
we	O
wo	O
n't	O
go	O
the	O
Road-way	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
shall	O
be	O
in	O
no	O
Danger	O
of	O
meeting	O
any	O
body	O
.	O
So	O
my	O
Brother	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
walked	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
till	O
we	O
came	O
thro	O
'	O
Sibban	O
's	O
Ground	O
to	O
the	O
Angel	O
and	O
Crown	O
Ale-house	O
.	O
The	O
Boy	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
whose	O
Mare	O
that	O
was	O
?	O
And	O
we	O
said	O
,	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
People	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
'em	O
said	O
to	O
Davison	O
,	O
Is	O
this	O
your	O
Mare	O
?	O
And	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Why	O
then	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
glad	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Whereupon	O
,	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Kemp	O
being	O
there	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
this	O
Fellow	O
,	O
(	O
says	O
Mr.	O
Kemp	O
)	O
he	O
's	O
got	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
pretends	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
to	O
impose	O
upon	O
People	O
's	O
Charity	O
,	O
and	O
get	O
some	O
Money	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Baily	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
New-street	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Scabbard-Maker	O
,	O
and	O
dealt	O
in	O
Sword	O
Blades	O
;	O
that	O
Tom	O
.	O
had	O
been	O
his	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
his	O
Journeyman	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
well	O
all	O
the	O
Time	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
him	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
from	O
my	O
Mother	O
's	O
in	O
Union-Court	O
at	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
past	O
Ten	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
last	O
Day	O
of	O
April	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
then	O
a	O
very	O
bright	O
Moonshine	O
Night	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Green	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
my	O
Door	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Angel	O
and	O
Crown	O
in	O
Union-Court	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
's	O
Girl	O
came	O
to	O
ask	O
me	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Clock	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
wanted	O
just	O
three	O
Minutes	O
of	O
Ten	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
Tom	O
.	O
Nolson	O
and	O
Betty	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
come	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Mother	O
's	O
(	O
Mrs.	O
Witby	O
's	O
)	O
House	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
was	O
afterwards	O
told	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
Saffron-Hill	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
Home	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Witby	I-pers
spoke	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Edge	I-pers
,	O
and	O
her	O
Maid	O
Mary	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Queen's-Head	O
in	O
Holloway	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
between	O
Nine	O
and	O
Ten	O
,	O
or	O
there-abouts	O
,	O
Davison	O
called	O
at	O
their	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
two	O
Men	O
were	O
lately	O
come	O
in	O
there	O
?	O
for	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
of	O
a	O
Mare	O
and	O
two	O
Guineas	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
,	O
in	O
summing	O
up	O
the	O
Evidence	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
observed	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
highly	O
improbable	O
that	O
Davison	O
should	O
tie	O
his	O
Mare	O
to	O
a	O
Stile	O
,	O
and	O
walk	O
in	O
his	O
Boots	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
of	O
Night	O
,	O
so	O
far	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Angel	O
and	O
Crown	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
describe	O
two	O
Men	O
,	O
that	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Evidence	O
given	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
impossible	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
have	O
seen	O
any	O
where	O
that	O
Day	O
,	O
but	O
near	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
;	O
because	O
it	O
was	O
proved	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
ever	O
since	O
the	O
Morning	O
:	O
And	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
that	O
very	O
House	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
Davison	O
.	O
And	O
tho	O
'	O
Davison	O
walked	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Boots	O
,	O
yet	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
a	O
Bye-Way	O
that	O
was	O
further	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
but	O
a	O
Foot-Pace	O
neither	O
,	O
(	O
for	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
walked	O
by	O
the	O
Mare	O
's	O
Side	O
)	O
it	O
is	O
no	O
Wonder	O
that	O
Davison	O
got	O
there	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Sanford	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Peter	B-pers
Goutier	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
14	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Jacob	B-pers
Deblet	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
6	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
3d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
(	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Pancras	I-place
)	O
for	O
assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Tolfield	I-pers
in	O
a	O
Field	O
near	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
a	O
Wig	O
,	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
Wastecoat	O
,	O
Neckcloth	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Goutier	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
Between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
as	O
1	O
and	O
Jacob	B-pers
Deblet	I-pers
were	O
coming	O
from	O
Marybone	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
pass	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Soldier	O
's	O
Coat	O
)	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Little	I-pers
.	O
They	O
turned	O
back	O
upon	O
us	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
clapping	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
my	O
Face	O
,	O
demanded	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
11	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Deblet	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
like	O
manner	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
James	O
Little	O
took	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Tolfield	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
and	O
another	O
were	O
coming	O
over	O
the	O
Field	O
betwixt	O
Kentish	B-place
Town	I-place
and	O
London	O
,	O
James	O
Little	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Soldier	O
's	O
Coat	O
,	O
stept	O
up	O
to	O
us	O
.	O
My	O
Friend	O
was	O
suspicious	O
of	O
their	O
Design	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
G	O
-	O
D	O
-	O
my	O
Blood	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
shoot	O
that	O
Son	O
of	O
a	O
Bitch	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
clapping	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
my	O
face	O
,	O
he	O
bade	O
me	O
deliver	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Little	I-pers
took	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
Wig	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stripp	O
'd	O
me	O
of	O
my	O
Coat	O
,	O
Wastecoat	O
,	O
and	O
Turnover	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
of	O
all	O
three	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Sanford	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Little	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Mary-le-Bone	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Trespass	O
,	O
in	O
assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
and	I-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
his	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intention	O
to	O
rob	O
them	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Milkman	O
,	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
As	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
my	O
Maid	O
,	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
Marybone	O
Fields	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Bear-Garden	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
up	O
;	O
Sanford	O
assaulted	O
my	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
beat	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
Little	O
presenting	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
demanded	O
my	O
Money	O
;	O
which	O
I	O
not	O
giving	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
shot	O
as	O
me	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
small	O
Hurt	O
in	O
my	O
Hand	O
.	O
But	O
however	O
,	O
I	O
began	O
to	O
struggle	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
Sanford	O
left	O
my	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
an	O
Offer	O
to	O
fire	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
Pistol	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
of	O
;	O
which	O
so	O
enraged	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
broke	O
it	O
with	O
beating	O
me	O
about	O
the	O
Head	O
.	O
By	O
this	O
Usage	O
,	O
I	O
received	O
so	O
many	O
Wounds	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
bled	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
two	O
Horses	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
my	O
Maid	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
alarmed	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
;	O
and	O
Sanford	O
perceiving	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
he	O
jumpt	O
over	O
a	O
Bank	O
and	O
got	O
off	O
.	O
I	O
still	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
Little	O
;	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
Struggle	O
he	O
unbuttoned	O
his	O
Coat	O
and	O
Wastecoat	O
,	O
slipt	O
himself	O
out	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
in	O
his	O
Shirt	O
after	O
Sanford	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Coat	O
and	O
Wastecoat	O
that	O
he	O
left	O
in	O
my	O
Hands	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
both	O
very	O
bloody	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
threw	O
'em	O
over	O
my	O
Head	O
to	O
keep	O
off	O
the	O
Cold	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
corroborated	O
by	O
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
Maid	O
.	O
Little	O
going	O
Home	O
that	O
Night	O
to	O
his	O
Father	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
without	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
some	O
Words	O
passed	O
betwixt	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
began	O
to	O
abuse	O
his	O
Father	O
very	O
grosly	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
;	O
where	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Rumour	O
of	O
having	O
lost	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
quickly	O
found	O
out	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
But	O
in	O
regard	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
given	O
Information	O
of	O
several	O
Robberies	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
now	O
try	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
other	O
Facts	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
concerned	O
with	O
Sanford	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Riding-Hood	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
two	O
Smocks	O
and	O
a	O
Shirt	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
7	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Norwood	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Rob	B-pers
Norwood	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Susan	B-pers
Junks	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Holborn	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Guineas	O
and	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Booker	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Joanna	B-pers
Ogden	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
,	O
30	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cotton	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
45.s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	O
Cross	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
Guilty	O
val	O
.	O
10d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Katharine	B-pers
Dorrell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Quilt	O
,	O
a	O
Sheet	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pillowbear	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Trumball	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
val	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Beals	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Finchly	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Sheep	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
24	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ekins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
two	O
Sheep	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bowden	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
thence	O
15	O
Pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
40	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Steed	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
Eleven	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Ashby	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Aldgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Pearl	O
Tassels	O
for	O
a	O
Neckcloth	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
Silver	O
Sockets	O
set	O
with	O
Diamonds	O
val	O
.	O
48	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jacob	B-pers
Pierraro	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Guilty	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Fennel	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
in	O
forging	O
a	O
Certificate	O
or	O
Pass	O
for	O
Joseph	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
to	O
travel	O
the	O
Countries	O
,	O
and	O
beg	O
under	O
the	O
Pretence	O
of	O
being	O
a	O
Ship-wreck	O
'd	O
Sailor	O
going	O
Home	O
to	O
Biddesford	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Pillory	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Month	O
's	O
Imprisonment	O
afterwards	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ferral	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Katharine	B-pers
Gilburn	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
Acquitted	O
Henry	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Keebly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Sepulchre	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
and	O
Smock	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Willoughby	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
Guilty	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Beacham	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Aldgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
44	O
s.	O
6.	O
d.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Clemenson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Clemenson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Matthew	B-pers
Spink	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
51	O
s.	O
and	O
an	O
Earthen	O
Tea-Pot	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Walter	B-pers
Hetherington	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Bolt	O
,	O
six	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
four	O
Silver	O
Forks	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Salt	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Tea	O
Tongs	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charlotte	B-pers
Burrows	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
C.	O
Burrows	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Kelly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
and	O
two	O
Handkerchiefs	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Guilty	O
val	O
.	O
10.	O
d.	O
Transpor	O
.	O
Jophenix	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
12	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Bacon	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Katharine	B-pers
Foulks	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
Guilty	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transp	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Gowns	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Smocks	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Guilty	O
val	O
.	O
10d	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Bruce	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Grisdal	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Wapping	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Ells	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jeffry	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Spurrier	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Wapping	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Blankets	O
,	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Guilty	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Wapping	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Matth.ew	B-pers
Pattison	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
fourteen	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoos	O
val	O
.	O
56	O
s.	O
and	O
three	O
Pair	O
of	O
Boots	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
to	O
the	O
val	O
.	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Sims	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Brow	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Silkwood	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
several	O
Pair	O
of	O
Boots	O
and	O
Shoos	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Matth.ew	B-pers
Pattison	I-pers
,	O
they	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stoln	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Curtains	O
,	O
three	O
Sheets	O
,	O
two	O
Plates	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Pearson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Rowel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Ring	O
,	O
five	O
Shirts	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Alloway	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
,	O
ravishing	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
against	O
her	O
will	O
,	O
carnally	O
knowing	O
Sarah	B-pers
Muns	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Sarah	B-pers
Muns	I-pers
on	O
the	O
River	O
Thames	O
,	O
(	O
it	O
being	O
a	O
Common	O
Highway	O
)	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
9	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Sarah	O
Muns	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Muns	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
On	O
Saturday	O
,	O
Night	O
,	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
a	O
Boat	O
at	O
Hungerford	O
Stairs	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Westminster	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
-	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
-	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
that	O
-	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
-	O
the	O
Waterman	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
carried	O
me	O
upon	O
the	O
Water	O
;	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
,	O
-	O
against	O
my	O
Consent	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
left	O
me	O
floating	O
in	O
the	O
Boat	O
,	O
at	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
Time	O
;	O
but	O
while	O
he	O
staid	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
-	O
rude	O
-	O
and	O
-	O
a	O
-	O
lay	O
with	O
me	O
-	O
once	O
-	O
whether	O
I	O
would	O
or	O
no	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
had	O
the	O
-	O
the	O
car	O
-	O
nal	O
-	O
use	O
of	O
-	O
my	O
Body	O
-	O
without	O
my	O
Con	O
-	O
sent	O
-	O
by	O
-	O
Force	O
-	O
but	O
not	O
-	O
not	O
against	O
my	O
Will	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
comply	O
thro	O
'	O
any	O
Fear	O
-	O
He	O
forced	O
me	O
to	O
it	O
by	O
great	O
Per	O
-	O
Persuasion	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
by	O
any	O
Threats	O
.	O
-	O
And	O
indeed	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
Thing	O
to	O
-	O
to	O
-	O
do	O
with	O
me	O
or	O
no	O
.	O
He	O
might	O
,	O
or	O
might	O
not	O
,	O
-	O
but	O
he	O
never	O
meddled	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
-	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
do	O
me	O
any	O
Harm	O
;	O
for	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
made	O
no	O
Noise	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
-	O
As	O
for	O
the	O
Money	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
:	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
from	O
me	O
-	O
against	O
my	O
Will	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
freely	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
was	O
welcome	O
to	O
any	O
Thing	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
about	O
me	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
young	O
Man	O
(	O
I	O
think	O
his	O
Name	O
is	O
Barnham	O
)	O
found	O
me	O
floating	O
in	O
the	O
Boat	O
about	O
5	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
Surprize	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bowen	I-pers
7	O
Guineas	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Bowen	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
About	O
Ten	O
o	O
'	O
Clock	O
on	O
Monday	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
got	O
confounded	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
riding	O
along	O
Drury-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Russel-street	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
,	O
my	O
Dear	O
?	O
says	O
she	O
;	O
Wo	O
n't	O
you	O
give	O
us	O
a	O
Pint	O
?	O
With	O
all	O
my	O
Heart	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Half-Moon	B-place
Tavern	I-place
.	O
I	O
hung	O
my	O
Horse	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Wine	O
We	O
sat	O
down	O
together	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
my	O
Right	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
on	O
the	O
Left	O
.	O
They	O
began	O
to	O
talk	O
about	O
Country	O
Affairs	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
Essex	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
well	O
acquainted	O
that	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
grew	O
very	O
familiar	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
thrust	O
her	O
Hand	O
into	O
my	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
unbutton	O
'd	O
my	O
Cloaths	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
began	O
to	O
think	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
got	O
into	O
ill	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
felt	O
for	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
charged	O
them	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
However	O
,	O
they	O
gave	O
me	O
good	O
Words	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
not	O
being	O
satisfy	O
'd	O
with	O
that	O
,	O
they	O
quickly	O
came	O
to	O
bad	O
ones	O
.	O
But	O
at	O
last	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
me	O
easy	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
'd	O
help	O
me	O
to	O
my	O
Money	O
again	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
'd	O
pay	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
them	O
the	O
odd	O
Guinea	O
.	O
I	O
offer	O
'd	O
them	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
agreed	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
upon	O
Condition	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
my	O
Money	O
again	O
without	O
telling	O
it	O
over	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
away	O
together	O
to	O
a	O
Gin-Shop	O
in	O
Newtoner's-Lane	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bade	O
me	O
look	O
upon	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
right	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
to	O
tell	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
dash	O
'd	O
it	O
all	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
pick	O
'd	O
it	O
up	O
betwixt	O
'em	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
I	O
should	O
never	O
have	O
any	O
of	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
great	O
Uproar	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Constables	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
Woman	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
secured	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
Search	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
six	O
of	O
the	O
seven	O
Guineas	O
in	O
a	O
Pail	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
thus	O
made	O
her	O
Defence	O
:	O
I	O
accidentally	O
went	O
to	O
light	O
a	O
Candle	O
at	O
the	O
Gin-Shop	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
quarrelling	O
with	O
a	O
Woman	O
.	O
The	O
Woman	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
he	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
being	O
concerned	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Wilde	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Katharine	O
Stetham	O
,	O
50	O
Yards	O
of	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Katharine	B-pers
Stetham	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
whereas	O
50	O
Yards	O
of	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
l.	O
was	O
privately	O
stoln	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Katharine	O
Stetham	O
,	O
by	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
;	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
Jonathan	O
Wilde	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
did	O
feloniously	O
receive	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Katharine	B-pers
Stetham	I-pers
Ten	O
Guineas	O
,	O
on	O
Account	O
and	O
under	O
Colour	O
of	O
helping	O
the	O
said	O
Katharine	O
Stetham	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Lace	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
then	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
time	O
since	O
,	O
discover	O
or	O
apprehend	O
,	O
or	O
cause	O
to	O
be	O
apprehended	O
and	O
brought	O
to	O
Justice	O
,	O
the	O
Persons	O
that	O
committed	O
the	O
said	O
Felony	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
before	O
his	O
Tryal	O
came	O
on	O
,	O
dispersed	O
about	O
the	O
Court	O
a	O
considerable	O
Numbers	O
of	O
printed	O
Lists	O
of	O
the	O
Felons	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
apprehended	O
,	O
which	O
concluded	O
in	O
these	O
Words	O
;	O
In	O
regard	O
therefore	O
of	O
the	O
Numbers	O
above	O
Convicted	O
,	O
some	O
that	O
have	O
yet	O
escaped	O
Justice	O
are	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
the	O
Life	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Jonathan	O
Wilde	O
,	O
This	O
extraordinary	O
Proceeding	O
gave	O
Occasion	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Counsel	O
to	O
observe	O
,	O
That	O
such	O
Practices	O
were	O
unwarrantable	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
suffer	O
'd	O
in	O
any	O
Court	O
of	O
Justice	O
:	O
That	O
this	O
was	O
apparently	O
intended	O
to	O
take	O
off	O
the	O
Credit	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
prepossess	O
and	O
influence	O
the	O
Jury	O
.	O
But	O
as	O
he	O
believed	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
Men	O
of	O
Integrity	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
under	O
no	O
Apprehensions	O
that	O
it	O
would	O
have	O
such	O
an	O
Effect	O
:	O
Nor	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
could	O
he	O
suppose	O
that	O
they	O
would	O
give	O
any	O
other	O
than	O
a	O
conscientious	O
Verdict	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
Evidence	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
the	O
indirect	O
Management	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
far	O
from	O
making	O
his	O
Cause	O
appear	O
favourable	O
.	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
impossible	O
that	O
a	O
Man	O
that	O
has	O
carry	O
'd	O
on	O
a	O
Trade	O
of	O
Felony	O
for	O
so	O
many	O
Years	O
past	O
;	O
a	O
Man	O
that	O
has	O
bred	O
up	O
and	O
erected	O
a	O
Corporation	O
of	O
Felons	O
;	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
whose	O
constant	O
known	O
Practice	O
has	O
been	O
to	O
procure	O
Goods	O
that	O
have	O
been	O
lost	O
in	O
any	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Town	O
;	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
impossible	O
that	O
such	O
a	O
Man	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Power	O
to	O
detect	O
those	O
Felons	O
:	O
And	O
yet	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
good	O
Reason	O
to	O
believe	O
,	O
that	O
(	O
to	O
the	O
great	O
Scandal	O
of	O
publick	O
Justice	O
)	O
he	O
has	O
on	O
the	O
contrary	O
terrify	O
'd	O
many	O
from	O
Reformation	O
,	O
and	O
prevented	O
them	O
from	O
making	O
such	O
Discoveries	O
as	O
might	O
have	O
been	O
of	O
Public	O
Advantage	O
.	O
That	O
if	O
a	O
strict	O
Enquiry	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
after	O
the	O
Motives	O
of	O
his	O
apprehending	O
those	O
Criminals	O
named	O
in	O
his	O
List	O
,	O
we	O
should	O
find	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
private	O
Interest	O
,	O
old	O
Grudges	O
,	O
or	O
fresh	O
Quarrels	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
the	O
least	O
Regard	O
to	O
Justice	O
and	O
his	O
Country	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pray	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
against	O
him	O
might	O
be	O
examin	O
'd	O
apart	O
;	O
which	O
the	O
Court	O
granted	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Kelly	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
In	O
January	O
last	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
Mrs.	O
Johnston	O
,	O
who	O
then	O
lived	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
:	O
Her	O
Husband	O
brought	O
me	O
over	O
from	O
Ireland	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
Account	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
drank	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Holland	O
's	O
Gin	O
together	O
.	O
By	O
and	O
by	O
in	O
comes	O
Mrs.	O
Murphy	O
with	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Brocaded	O
Shoos	O
and	O
Clogs	O
,	O
and	O
makes	O
a	O
Present	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Wilde	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
Company	O
.	O
We	O
drank	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Quarterns	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Murphy	O
got	O
up	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
together	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
which	O
way	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
to	O
my	O
Lodgings	O
at	O
the	O
Seven	O
Dials	O
.	O
I	O
suppose	O
you	O
go	O
Holborn	O
Way	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
.	O
We	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
Yes	O
.	O
Why	O
then	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
tell	O
ye	O
what	O
;	O
-	O
There	O
's	O
an	O
old	O
Blind	O
Bitch	O
that	O
sells	O
fine	O
Flanders	O
Lace	O
just	O
by	O
Holborn-Bridge	O
;	O
her	O
Daughter	O
is	O
as	O
blind	O
as	O
herself	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
ye	O
call	O
there	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
speak	O
with	O
a	O
Box	O
of	O
Lace	O
,	O
(	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
steal	O
a	O
Box	O
)	O
-	O
I	O
'll	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
ye	O
,	O
and	O
shew	O
ye	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
So	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
and	O
Murphy	O
went	O
together	O
,	O
till	O
we	O
came	O
within	O
Sight	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
:	O
He	O
pointed	O
and	O
shew	O
'd	O
us	O
which	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
wait	O
for	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
bring	O
us	O
off	O
,	O
if	O
any	O
Disturbance	O
should	O
happen	O
.	O
Murphy	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
turn	O
'd	O
over	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Lace	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
see	O
none	O
that	O
would	O
please	O
us	O
,	O
not	O
a	O
Piece	O
that	O
was	O
broad	O
enough	O
,	O
and	O
fine	O
enough	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
our	O
Business	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
nice	O
and	O
difficult	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
old	O
Woman	O
stept	O
up	O
Stairs	O
to	O
fetch	O
another	O
Piece	O
:	O
And	O
as	O
People	O
of	O
our	O
Profession	O
are	O
seldom	O
guilty	O
of	O
losing	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
,	O
I	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
this	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
Tin	O
Box	O
of	O
Lace	O
,	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Murphy	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
hid	O
it	O
under	O
her	O
Cloak	O
.	O
The	O
old	O
Woman	O
came	O
down	O
with	O
another	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
shew	O
'd	O
us	O
several	O
Pieces	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
she	O
asked	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
Yard	O
.	O
We	O
offer	O
'd	O
her	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
not	O
being	O
likely	O
to	O
agree	O
about	O
the	O
Price	O
,	O
we	O
came	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
waiting	O
where	O
we	O
left	O
him	O
.	O
We	O
told	O
him	O
what	O
Success	O
we	O
had	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
went	O
back	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
.	O
There	O
we	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Eleven	O
Pieces	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
ask	O
'd	O
us	O
if	O
we	O
would	O
have	O
ready	O
Money	O
,	O
or	O
stay	O
till	O
an	O
Advertisement	O
came	O
out	O
.	O
Stock	O
being	O
pretty	O
low	O
with	O
us	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
we	O
chose	O
the	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
gave	O
us	O
three	O
Guineas	O
and	O
four	O
Broad	O
Pieces	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
for	O
my	O
Share	O
three	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Murphy	O
had	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
afford	O
to	O
give	O
you	O
any	O
more	O
,	O
(	O
says	O
he	O
)	O
;	O
for	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
some	O
Influence	O
over	O
her	O
,	O
by	O
helping	O
her	O
to	O
Goods	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
before	O
,	O
yet	O
I	O
know	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
stingey	O
hard-mouth	O
'd	O
old	O
Bitch	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
sha	O
n't	O
get	O
above	O
Ten	O
Guineas	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Murphy	I-pers
deposed	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
and	O
Katharine	O
Stetham	O
Corroborated	O
that	O
Part	O
of	O
their	O
Depositions	O
which	O
related	O
to	O
their	O
being	O
in	O
her	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Lace	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
was	O
full	O
and	O
positive	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
But	O
here	O
his	O
Counsel	O
(	O
who	O
waited	O
in	O
readiness	O
if	O
any	O
Point	O
of	O
Law	O
should	O
arise	O
)	O
stood	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
beg	O
'd	O
Leave	O
to	O
declare	O
it	O
as	O
their	O
Opinion	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Defendant	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Evidence	O
given	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
and	O
their	O
Reason	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Indictment	O
sets	O
forth	O
,	O
That	O
HE	O
did	O
privately	O
steal	O
this	O
Lace	O
[	O
IN	O
]	O
the	O
Shop	O
;	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
certain	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
enter	O
the	O
Shop	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
might	O
indeed	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
a	O
simple	O
Felony	O
,	O
in	O
being	O
Accessary	O
before	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
or	O
in	O
Receiving	O
the	O
Goods	O
after	O
;	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Capital	O
Offence	O
,	O
except	O
(	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Act	O
)	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
inserted	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
that	O
He	O
did	O
Assist	O
,	O
Here	O
or	O
Command	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
,	O
in	O
summing	O
up	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
observed	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
that	O
in	O
Felonies	O
,	O
Burglaries	O
,	O
and	O
Robberies	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
every	O
Accessary	O
before	O
the	O
Fact	O
is	O
a	O
Principal	O
;	O
he	O
that	O
stands	O
by	O
,	O
or	O
watches	O
at	O
a	O
Distance	O
,	O
being	O
as	O
guilty	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
liable	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Punishment	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
very	O
Man	O
that	O
enters	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
or	O
steals	O
the	O
Money	O
or	O
Goods	O
.	O
But	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
remembered	O
that	O
there	O
had	O
yet	O
been	O
any	O
Precedent	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
like	O
Construction	O
being	O
put	O
upon	O
Indictments	O
of	O
this	O
Nature	O
,	O
it	O
remained	O
as	O
a	O
Matter	O
of	O
Doubt	O
;	O
and	O
therefore	O
,	O
in	O
such	O
Cases	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
most	O
eligible	O
to	O
incline	O
to	O
the	O
Side	O
of	O
Mercy	O
.	O
The	O
2d	O
Indictment	O
against	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Wilde	I-pers
was	O
upon	O
the	O
following	O
Clause	O
in	O
an	O
Act	O
passed	O
in	O
the	O
4th	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
Reign	O
of	O
his	O
present	O
Majesty	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
viz.	O
``	O
And	O
whereas	O
there	O
are	O
several	O
Persons	O
who	O
have	O
secret	O
``	O
Acquaintance	O
with	O
Felons	O
,	O
and	O
who	O
makes	O
it	O
their	O
Business	O
``	O
to	O
help	O
Persons	O
to	O
their	O
stoln	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
that	O
means	O
``	O
gain	O
Money	O
from	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
divided	O
between	O
them	O
and	O
``	O
the	O
Felons	O
,	O
whereby	O
they	O
greatly	O
encourage	O
such	O
Offenders	O
:	O
``	O
Be	O
it	O
Enacted	O
by	O
the	O
Authority	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
That	O
``	O
where	O
ever	O
any	O
Person	O
taken	O
Money	O
or	O
Reward	O
,	O
directly	O
``	O
or	O
indirectly	O
,	O
under	O
Pretence	O
or	O
upon	O
Account	O
of	O
helping	O
``	O
any	O
Person	O
or	O
Persons	O
to	O
any	O
stoln	O
Goods	O
or	O
Chattels	O
,	O
``	O
every	O
such	O
Person	O
so	O
taking	O
Money	O
or	O
Reward	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
``	O
(	O
unless	O
such	O
Person	O
do	O
apprehend	O
,	O
or	O
cause	O
to	O
be	O
apprehended	O
,	O
``	O
such	O
Felon	O
who	O
stole	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
cause	O
such	O
``	O
Felon	O
to	O
be	O
brought	O
to	O
his	O
Tryal	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
``	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
)	O
shall	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
suffer	O
``	O
the	O
Pains	O
and	O
Penalties	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
``	O
Nature	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
committed	O
in	O
stealing	O
such	O
Goods	O
,	O
``	O
and	O
in	O
such	O
and	O
the	O
same	O
Manner	O
as	O
if	O
such	O
Offender	O
had	O
``	O
himself	O
stole	O
such	O
Goods	O
and	O
Chattels	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Manner	O
and	O
``	O
with	O
such	O
Circumstances	O
as	O
the	O
same	O
were	O
stoln	O
.	O
''	O
Katharine	O
Stetham	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
between	O
Three	O
and	O
Four	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
a	O
Man	O
and	O
Woman	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
Shop	O
,	O
under	O
a	O
Pretence	O
of	O
buying	O
some	O
Lace	O
:	O
They	O
were	O
so	O
very	O
difficult	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
below	O
that	O
would	O
please	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
,	O
leaving	O
my	O
Daughter	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
I	O
slept	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
down	O
another	O
Box	O
.	O
We	O
could	O
not	O
agree	O
about	O
the	O
Price	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
together	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
a	O
Tin	O
Box	O
of	O
Lace	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
valu	O
'd	O
at	O
50	O
l.	O
The	O
same	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Jonathan	O
Wilde	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
meeting	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
advertised	O
the	O
Lace	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Reward	O
of	O
15	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Questions	O
ask	O
'd	O
.	O
But	O
hearing	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Jonathan	O
's	O
House	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
met	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
He	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
Description	O
of	O
the	O
Persons	O
that	O
I	O
suspected	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
'd	O
make	O
Enquiry	O
,	O
and	O
bade	O
me	O
call	O
again	O
in	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
so	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
heard	O
something	O
of	O
my	O
Lace	O
,	O
and	O
expected	O
to	O
know	O
more	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
again	O
on	O
that	O
day	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
(	O
I	O
think	O
't	O
was	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
had	O
advertised	O
but	O
15	O
Guineas	O
Reward	O
yet	O
I	O
'd	O
give	O
20	O
or	O
25	O
rathe	O
than	O
not	O
have	O
my	O
Goods	O
.	O
Do	O
n't	O
be	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Hurry	O
,	O
says	O
her	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
but	O
I	O
may	O
help	O
you	O
to	O
it	O
for	O
less	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
can	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
.	O
The	O
Persons	O
that	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
are	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
set	O
them	O
to	O
quarrelling	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
shall	O
get	O
it	O
:	O
the	O
cheaper	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
me	O
word	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
come	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
bring	O
10	O
Guineas	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
help	O
me	O
to	O
my	O
Lace	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
:	O
He	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
call	O
a	O
Porter	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
not	O
knowing	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
one	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
a	O
Person	O
who	O
brought	O
one	O
that	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Ticket-Porter	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
Letter	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
sent	O
him	O
as	O
a	O
Direction	O
where	O
to	O
go	O
for	O
the	O
Lace	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
read	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
deliver	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Porter	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
the	O
Porter	O
Ten	O
Guineas	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
(	O
he	O
said	O
)	O
the	O
Persons	O
that	O
had	O
the	O
Lace	O
would	O
not	O
deliver	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
Porter	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
return	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
me	O
a	O
Box	O
that	O
was	O
seal	O
'd	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
was	O
lost	O
.	O
I	O
open	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
all	O
my	O
Lace	O
but	O
one	O
Piece	O
.	O
Now	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Wilde	O
,	O
(	O
says	O
I	O
)	O
what	O
must	O
you	O
have	O
for	O
your	O
Trouble	O
?	O
Not	O
a	O
Farthing	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
not	O
a	O
Farthing	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
do	O
these	O
things	O
for	O
Worldly	O
Interest	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
for	O
the	O
Good	O
of	O
poor	O
People	O
that	O
have	O
met	O
with	O
Misfortunes	O
.	O
As	O
for	O
the	O
Piece	O
of	O
Lace	O
that	O
is	O
missing	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
for	O
you	O
e'er	O
be	O
long	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
but	O
that	O
I	O
may	O
help	O
you	O
not	O
only	O
to	O
your	O
Money	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
the	O
Thief	O
too	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
can	O
,	O
much	O
good	O
may't	O
do	O
you	O
.	O
And	O
as	O
you	O
're	O
a	O
good	O
Woman	O
and	O
a	O
Widow	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Christian	O
,	O
I	O
desire	O
nothing	O
of	O
you	O
but	O
your	O
Prayers	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
them	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
thankful	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Enemies	O
,	O
and	O
God	O
knows	O
what	O
may	O
be	O
the	O
Consequence	O
of	O
this	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
Convicted	O
a	O
great	O
Number	O
of	O
Criminals	O
;	O
only	O
he	O
desired	O
that	O
Murphy	O
and	O
Kelly	O
might	O
be	O
called	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
granted	O
.	O
Then	O
(	O
this	O
Indictment	O
being	O
laid	O
for	O
helping	O
Kat	O
.	O
Stretham	O
to	O
Goods	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
stole	O
from	O
her	O
by	O
Persons	O
UNKNOWN	O
)	O
he	O
pray	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Murphy	O
might	O
be	O
ask	O
'd	O
who	O
stole	O
the	O
Lace	O
?	O
In	O
expectation	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
unwarily	O
swear	O
,	O
that	O
herself	O
and	O
Kelly	O
were	O
the	O
Persons	O
;	O
(	O
for	O
tho	O
'	O
such	O
Evidence	O
was	O
given	O
in	O
the	O
former	O
Tryal	O
,	O
the	O
Law	O
could	O
take	O
no	O
Notice	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
this	O
,	O
except	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
sworn	O
over	O
again	O
.	O
)	O
But	O
the	O
Court	O
inform	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
Murphy	O
was	O
an	O
Evidence	O
upon	O
Oath	O
,	O
nobody	O
could	O
require	O
her	O
to	O
answer	O
any	O
Questions	O
to	O
accuse	O
herself	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
pray	O
'd	O
the	O
Court	O
would	O
ask	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
stole	O
the	O
Lace	O
?	O
To	O
which	O
she	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
No	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
with	O
those	O
that	O
did	O
steal	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
received	O
it	O
after	O
it	O
was	O
stolen	O
.	O
From	O
hence	O
the	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
beg	O
'd	O
Leave	O
to	O
observe	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
Murphy	O
had	O
sworn	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
they	O
presum	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Act	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
now	O
indicted	O
,	O
was	O
never	O
intended	O
to	O
affect	O
him	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
other	O
Felon	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
such	O
Persons	O
that	O
were	O
not	O
Felons	O
themselves	O
,	O
but	O
hold	O
a	O
Correspondence	O
with	O
Felons	O
.	O
For	O
as	O
there	O
were	O
old	O
Laws	O
in	O
Force	O
for	O
the	O
Punishment	O
of	O
Felons	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
altogether	O
unnecessary	O
that	O
a	O
new	O
Law	O
should	O
be	O
made	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Purpose	O
,	O
-	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
to	O
no	O
Purpose	O
at	O
all	O
-	O
That	O
the	O
very	O
Preamble	O
to	O
that	O
Clause	O
of	O
the	O
Act	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
indicted	O
,	O
intimates	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
plain	O
Distinction	O
,	O
that	O
Felons	O
are	O
not	O
in	O
that	O
Place	O
intended	O
.	O
The	O
Words	O
are	O
thus	O
:	O
``	O
Whereas	O
``	O
there	O
are	O
several	O
Persons	O
who	O
have	O
secret	O
Acquaintance	O
``	O
with	O
Felons	O
and	O
who	O
make	O
it	O
their	O
Business	O
to	O
``	O
help	O
Persons	O
to	O
their	O
Stoln	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
that	O
means	O
``	O
gain	O
Money	O
from	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
divided	O
between	O
THEM	O
``	O
and	O
the	O
FELONS	O
.	O
''	O
-	O
That	O
by	O
a	O
Proviso	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Clause	O
,	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
supposed	O
that	O
felons	O
were	O
there	O
intended	O
,	O
without	O
making	O
Contradictions	O
and	O
Inconsistencies	O
in	O
the	O
Act	O
itself	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Words	O
are	O
,	O
``	O
Unless	O
such	O
Person	O
doth	O
apprehend	O
,	O
``	O
or	O
cause	O
to	O
be	O
apprehended	O
,	O
such	O
Felon	O
who	O
stole	O
``	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
cause	O
such	O
Felon	O
to	O
be	O
brought	O
to	O
a	O
Tryal	O
``	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
''	O
Suppose	O
now	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
but	O
one	O
Person	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Case	O
;	O
can	O
it	O
be	O
thought	O
that	O
ever	O
the	O
Legislature	O
intended	O
that	O
this	O
Person	O
should	O
apprehend	O
himself	O
,	O
bring	O
himself	O
to	O
Tryal	O
,	O
give	O
Evidence	O
against	O
himself	O
,	O
convict	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
hang	O
himself	O
?	O
No	O
,	O
certainly	O
.	O
To	O
this	O
the	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
Crown	O
reply	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
following	O
Effect	O
,	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
no	O
Absurdity	O
or	O
Contradiction	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
that	O
Act	O
was	O
intended	O
to	O
affect	O
Felons	O
,	O
even	O
in	O
a	O
Case	O
where	O
there	O
was	O
but	O
one	O
Felon	O
concern	O
'd	O
:	O
For	O
that	O
a	O
Man	O
's	O
being	O
a	O
Felon	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
any	O
way	O
hinder	O
him	O
from	O
discovering	O
his	O
Accomplices	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
none	O
,	O
but	O
committed	O
the	O
Offence	O
by	O
himself	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
impossible	O
to	O
try	O
him	O
for	O
taking	O
Money	O
upon	O
Account	O
of	O
restoring	O
Goods	O
that	O
were	O
stolen	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
first	O
convicted	O
of	O
stealing	O
those	O
Goods	O
:	O
And	O
this	O
first	O
Conviction	O
would	O
then	O
be	O
sufficient	O
.	O
There	O
would	O
be	O
no	O
Necessity	O
for	O
trying	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
other	O
Offence	O
,	O
for	O
if	O
>	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
make	O
no	O
Alteration	O
in	O
his	O
Punishment	O
:	O
But	O
that	O
this	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
Case	O
of	O
the	O
Prisosoner	O
:	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
evident	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
Accomplices	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
discover	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
farther	O
observ	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Felons	O
were	O
so	O
far	O
from	O
being	O
excepted	O
in	O
that	O
Act	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
principally	O
intended	O
against	O
them	O
;	O
for	O
it	O
particularly	O
mentions	O
,	O
``	O
Those	O
that	O
make	O
it	O
their	O
Business	O
to	O
help	O
People	O
to	O
``	O
stolen	O
Goods	O
.	O
''	O
And	O
it	O
was	O
certain	O
,	O
that	O
such	O
Persons	O
must	O
be	O
Receivers	O
of	O
stolen	O
Goods	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
and	O
such	O
are	O
Felons	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Case	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
within	O
almost	O
every	O
Circumstance	O
of	O
the	O
Act	O
;	O
it	O
being	O
evident	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Person	O
that	O
had	O
secret	O
Acquaintance	O
with	O
Felons	O
,	O
who	O
made	O
it	O
his	O
Business	O
to	O
help	O
People	O
to	O
stolen	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
that	O
means	O
gain	O
'd	O
Money	O
from	O
them	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
divided	O
betwixt	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
Felons	O
,	O
and	O
thereby	O
greatly	O
encouraged	O
such	O
Offenders	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
apprehended	O
them	O
.	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
surprizing	O
Plea	O
for	O
a	O
Man	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
more	O
guilty	O
than	O
you	O
are	O
aware	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
I	O
ought	O
to	O
suffer	O
less	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
thought	O
that	O
the	O
Parliament	O
ever	O
intended	O
by	O
this	O
Act	O
to	O
excuse	O
a	O
Man	O
meerly	O
because	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Felon	O
,	O
and	O
more	O
Criminal	O
than	O
another	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Harpham	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Broom	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
George	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
Hanover-Square	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
High-Treason	O
,	O
in	O
Counterfieting	O
the	O
Current	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Broom	O
being	O
committed	O
but	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
his	O
Arraignment	O
,	O
he	O
pray	O
'd	O
that	O
his	O
Tryal	O
might	O
be	O
deferred	O
till	O
next	O
Sessions	O
;	O
which	O
the	O
Court	O
granted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Fordham	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
Years	O
;	O
he	O
brought	O
a	O
Sett	O
of	O
Coining	O
Implements	O
into	O
my	O
Cellar	O
,	O
in	O
S.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Church-yard	I-place
;	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
Iron	O
Press	O
,	O
two	O
Dyes	O
for	O
Guineas	O
,	O
two	O
for	O
Half-Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
for	O
Moidores	O
,	O
and	O
Pieces	O
that	O
went	O
for	O
six	O
or	O
eight	O
Stivers	O
;	O
a	O
Cutting	O
Tool	O
for	O
making	O
the	O
Blanks	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Edging	O
Tool	O
for	O
grinding	O
the	O
Edges	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
these	O
that	O
are	O
now	O
in	O
the	O
Court	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
especially	O
the	O
Cutting	O
Tool	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Fly	O
of	O
the	O
Press	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
lodge	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
work	O
there	O
now	O
and	O
then	O
;	O
and	O
sometimes	O
I	O
assisted	O
him	O
in	O
coining	O
about	O
twenty	O
Pieces	O
that	O
were	O
counterfeit	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
Half-Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Moidores	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Foreign	O
Peices	O
.	O
He	O
paid	O
me	O
no	O
Rent	O
for	O
my	O
Cellar	O
;	O
but	O
allow	O
'd	O
me	O
Part	O
of	O
this	O
Counterfeit	O
Money	O
,	O
in	O
Proportion	O
to	O
the	O
Quantity	O
that	O
he	O
made	O
.	O
From	O
S.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-yard	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Directions	O
,	O
I	O
removed	O
these	O
Implements	O
into	O
Rosemary-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
's	O
in	O
Benjamin-Street	O
,	O
near	O
Swallow-Street	O
;	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bails	O
's	O
in	O
Wild-Street	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
left	O
'em	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Sea	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
now	O
about	O
two	O
Years	O
ago	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hornby	O
thus	O
deposed	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
Years	O
.	O
I	O
being	O
Clerk	O
of	O
the	O
Works	O
at	O
the	O
Admiralty	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
then	O
a	O
Carpenter	O
,	O
and	O
trading	O
in	O
Timber	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
some	O
Dealings	O
together	O
;	O
but	O
our	O
Correspondence	O
breaking	O
off	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
for	O
six	O
Years	O
together	O
,	O
till	O
about	O
a	O
Year	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
ago	O
.	O
In	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
Statute	O
of	O
Bankrupt	O
was	O
issued	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
chosen	O
Assignee	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
Occasion	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
several	O
times	O
invited	O
me	O
to	O
dine	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Milliscent	O
Russell	O
's	O
in	O
Paradise-Row	O
,	O
by	O
Hanover-Square	O
;	O
so	O
in	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
thither	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
Turkey	O
for	O
Dinner	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
being	O
ready	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
'd	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
'd	O
let	O
me	O
see	O
something	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
his	O
Press	O
:	O
In	O
this	O
Press	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
make	O
Buttons	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
'll	O
shew	O
you	O
a	O
greater	O
Rarity	O
;	O
and	O
with	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
gilt	O
Metal	O
,	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Press	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
came	O
out	O
like	O
a	O
Half-Guinea	O
,	O
except	O
the	O
Milling	O
on	O
the	O
Edge	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
presently	O
did	O
,	O
by	O
running	O
it	O
thro	O
'	O
his	O
Edging	O
Tool	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
that	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
Press	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
same	O
Edging	O
Tool	O
.	O
Milliscent	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
When	O
I	O
first	O
knew	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Fordham	O
in	O
Benjamin-street	O
;	O
from	O
whence	O
,	O
in	O
about	O
four	O
Months	O
,	O
he	O
removed	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
in	O
College-street	O
;	O
from	O
thence	O
into	O
King-street	O
in	O
Golden-Square	O
;	O
and	O
from	O
King-Street	O
to	O
a	O
Plumber	O
's	O
in	O
Jermyn-street	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
lodged	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
He	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
the	O
Use	O
of	O
my	O
Cellar	O
in	O
Paradise-Row	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
damp	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
but	O
of	O
little	O
Service	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
welcome	O
to	O
it	O
without	O
paying	O
any	O
Rent	O
.	O
He	O
brought	O
thither	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
several	O
things	O
in	O
Baskets	O
,	O
two	O
great	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Iron	O
,	O
a	O
Block	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
once	O
work	O
with	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Fordham	O
's	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
then	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
making	O
of	O
buttons	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
Pieces	O
taken	O
out	O
like	O
Money	O
.	O
He	O
put	O
up	O
a	O
Grate	O
in	O
my	O
Cellar	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
sometimes	O
heard	O
Knocking	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
work	O
there	O
;	O
for	O
he	O
always	O
kept	O
the	O
Keys	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
suffer	O
no	O
body	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
.	O
He	O
used	O
to	O
have	O
Sea-Coal	O
and	O
Charcoal	O
brought	O
once	O
in	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Weeks	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
always	O
laid	O
down	O
at	O
the	O
Cellar-Window	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
shovel	O
'd	O
it	O
in	O
himself	O
.	O
He	O
sent	O
me	O
(	O
I	O
believe	O
nine	O
or	O
ten	O
times	O
)	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Yarndner	O
's	O
a	O
Founder	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
blackish	O
Metal	O
to	O
be	O
flatted	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Thickness	O
of	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Notches	O
in	O
this	O
Gage	O
Iron	O
;	O
and	O
sometimes	O
I	O
fetch	O
'd	O
the	O
Pieces	O
back	O
again	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
flatted	O
.	O
These	O
Parcels	O
are	O
very	O
much	O
like	O
them	O
:	O
I	O
believe	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
will	O
fit	O
this	O
Notch	O
;	O
that	O
's	O
the	O
Thickness	O
of	O
a	O
Guinea	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
they	O
fit	O
it	O
exactly	O
.	O
Then	O
here	O
is	O
another	O
Notch	O
of	O
the	O
Thickness	O
of	O
a	O
Half	O
Guinea	O
;	O
another	O
for	O
Half	O
Crowns	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
for	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
;	O
perhaps	O
for	O
Moidores	O
,	O
or	O
some	O
other	O
Outlandish	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
last	O
Parcel	O
I	O
carried	O
to	O
be	O
flatted	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
last	O
Chistmas	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
carried	O
out	O
any	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
after	O
it	O
was	O
flatted	O
.	O
Once	O
or	O
twice	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
I	O
carried	O
some	O
Gold	O
to	O
be	O
flatted	O
.	O
Yardner	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Milliscent	O
Russel	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Broom	I-pers
,	O
had	O
often	O
,	O
within	O
these	O
four	O
Years	O
past	O
,	O
brought	O
him	O
Parcels	O
of	O
Metals	O
to	O
be	O
flatted	O
,	O
20	O
or	O
30	O
lb	O
Weight	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
,	O
which	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Mixture	O
of	O
Brass	O
,	O
Copper	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Metals	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
latterly	O
they	O
had	O
brought	O
some	O
Silver	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Oakly	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
three	O
Years	O
ago	O
he	O
had	O
several	O
times	O
cast	O
a	O
Mixture	O
of	O
Copper	O
,	O
brass	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Metals	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
20	O
or	O
30	O
lb	O
together	O
.	O
The	O
preceding	O
Depositions	O
were	O
confirmed	O
by	O
Quinny	O
,	O
(	O
who	O
served	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
Charcoal	O
)	O
Pierce	O
and	O
Brown	O
,	O
two	O
Smiths	O
;	O
the	O
former	O
mended	O
the	O
Fly	O
of	O
the	O
Press	O
for	O
Fordham	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
made	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Iron	O
Clamp	O
or	O
Collar	O
for	O
the	O
Block	O
,	O
to	O
keep	O
it	O
from	O
splitting	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
Broom	O
the	O
Bricklayer	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
I	O
set	O
up	O
such	O
a	O
Grate	O
as	O
this	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Mrs.	O
Russel	O
's	O
Cellar	O
:	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
by	O
as	O
having	O
so	O
many	O
Bars	O
at	O
the	O
Bottom	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
not	O
usual	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
makes	O
it	O
draw	O
prodigiously	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
such	O
a	O
Grate	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Manner	O
that	O
I	O
fixt	O
it	O
,	O
would	O
burn	O
the	O
Devil	O
and	O
all	O
of	O
Fuel	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
;	O
it	O
must	O
serve	O
me	O
either	O
to	O
roast	O
or	O
boil	O
,	O
bake	O
or	O
stew	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Chandler	O
the	O
Messenger	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
in	O
Mrs.	O
Russell	O
's	O
Cellar	O
,	O
he	O
seized	O
all	O
these	O
Coining	O
Instruments	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
had	O
them	O
ever	O
since	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Custody	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Pinkny	O
,	O
Deputy	O
Warden	O
,	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
This	O
Press	O
,	O
Cutting	O
Tool	O
,	O
Edging	O
Tool	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
Dyes	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
found	O
in	O
Mrs.	O
Russell	O
's	O
Cellar	O
,	O
can	O
serve	O
for	O
no	O
other	O
Use	O
than	O
Coining	O
.	O
I	O
likewise	O
found	O
there	O
,	O
these	O
21	O
false	O
Half	O
Guineas	O
;	O
They	O
are	O
strongly	O
gilt	O
,	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
weigh	O
'd	O
something	O
more	O
than	O
a	O
Guinea	O
.	O
The	O
[	O
O	O
]	O
in	O
[	O
GEORGIUS	O
]	O
leans	O
a	O
little	O
towards	O
the	O
[	O
E	O
]	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
something	O
less	O
than	O
the	O
other	O
Letters	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
exactly	O
the	O
same	O
in	O
this	O
Dye	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Cellar	O
.	O
These	O
Dyes	O
appear	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
lately	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
,	O
for	O
here	O
is	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Gilding	O
now	O
sticking	O
in	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Witnesses	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
.	O
-	O
Knight	O
,	O
a	O
Chair-Maker	O
,	O
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
New	O
Bond	O
street	O
,	O
when	O
Hornby	O
came	O
to	O
us	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
Hurry	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
get	O
an	O
Iron	O
Clamp	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
leave	O
it	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Russell	O
's	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
thus	O
deposed	O
:	O
By	O
Mr.	O
Hornby	O
's	O
Directions	O
,	O
I	O
made	O
the	O
Grate	O
that	O
stands	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
it	O
at	O
Hornby	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
Ax-Yard	O
,	O
Westminster	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
made	O
but	O
one	O
such	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
for	O
a	O
Jeweller	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
indeed	O
seen	O
others	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Nature	O
,	O
that	O
have	O
been	O
made	O
for	O
Silver	O
Smiths	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Trades	O
that	O
have	O
Occasion	O
for	O
fierce	O
Fires	O
to	O
melt	O
Metal	O
.	O
Some	O
others	O
gave	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
often	O
received	O
Money	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
found	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
them	O
any	O
that	O
was	O
bad	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Tesling	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Nabour	I-pers
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
33	O
Guineas	O
from	O
Samuel	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Marsham	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sorrel	O
Mare	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bellers	I-pers
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Blackman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Matth.ew	B-pers
Keaner	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Stow	O
Grate	O
.	O
Guilty	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Newsted	I-pers
,	I-pers
and	I-pers
Mary	I-pers
his	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
of	O
S.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
20	O
lb	O
of	O
Feathers	O
and	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
North	I-pers
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	I-pers
commonly	I-pers
called	I-pers
Blind	I-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
in	O
putting	O
off	O
several	O
Counterfeit	O
Guineas	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
knowing	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
be	O
Counterfeit	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Harpham	O
were	O
drinking	O
together	O
at	O
the	O
Rummer	B-place
Tavern	I-place
,	I-place
Charing-Cross	I-place
.	O
Harpham	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
the	O
Drawer	O
a	O
Guinea	O
to	O
change	O
.	O
He	O
carried	O
it	O
down	O
to	O
his	O
Mistress	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
.	O
She	O
scrupled	O
it	O
for	O
being	O
so	O
thick	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Thomson	O
,	O
Warden	O
of	O
the	O
Mint	O
,	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
behind	O
the	O
Bar	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
