TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
AND	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
:	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
and	O
Monday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
2d	O
,	O
3d	O
,	O
4th	O
,	O
5th	O
,	O
and	O
7th	O
,	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
1726.	O
in	O
the	O
Twelfth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
FORBES	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Denton	O
.	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Hale	I-pers
;	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
,	O
Sergeant	O
at	O
Law	O
;	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
;	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Workman	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Churcher	I-pers
John	B-pers
Fairchild	I-pers
William	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
William	B-pers
Alkin	I-pers
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Taverner	I-pers
George	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
John	B-pers
Siddal	I-pers
Andrew	B-pers
Lister	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Wilmore	I-pers
John	B-pers
Berisford	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Chandler	I-pers
Benjamin	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Rumball	I-pers
Michael	B-pers
Desman	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Coggin	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Young	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Chandler	I-pers
William	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
John	B-pers
Patty	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Dickman	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Brearcliffe	I-pers
John	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Gough	I-pers
,	O
on	O
Feb.	O
11.	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Plowman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Gowns	O
,	O
2	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Dwyer	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
12	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Lodger	O
when	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
confest	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Edginton	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Edgerton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
Samuel	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
,	O
his	O
Hankerchief	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
Jan.	O
25	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Temple	I-pers
and	O
Walter	B-pers
Phenix	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Bishopsgate	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Feather	O
Bed	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
12	O
.	O
John	O
Temple	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
The	O
Witnesses	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
Mrs	O
Hawkins	O
going	O
up	O
Stairs	O
with	O
a	O
lighted	O
Candle	O
,	O
about	O
7	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
she	O
met	O
Temple	O
with	O
her	O
Bed	O
at	O
his	O
Back	O
,	O
Have	O
a	O
Care	O
Mistress	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
Yes	O
you	O
Rogue	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
some	O
Neighbours	O
to	O
her	O
Assistance	O
,	O
she	O
secur	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
Phenix	O
was	O
stopt	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Lake	O
,	O
who	O
saw	O
him	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
House	O
,	O
with	O
2	O
Pillows	O
,	O
a	O
Quilt	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
blanket	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Abraham	B-pers
Gudgeon	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
Boy	O
,	O
)	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Purse	O
,	O
and	O
16	O
d.	O
from	O
Jane	B-pers
Curry	I-pers
,	O
January	O
24	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
standing	O
by	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Church-Yard	I-place
to	O
see	O
a	O
Funeral	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
cut	O
a	O
Hole	O
in	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Money	O
dropt	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ayres	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Velvet	O
Cushion	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
1	O
green	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
blue	O
Squabs	O
,	O
value	O
28	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
February	O
13	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Nesbits	O
Meeting-House	O
,	O
in	O
Hare	B-place
Court	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Aldersgate-street	I-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
about	O
Mid-night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
stopt	O
by	O
the	O
Watchman	O
,	O
with	O
those	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Hamson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
;	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
January	O
13	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Hickenbottom	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
Boy	O
)	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
9	O
s	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
2	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Pristow	I-pers
,	O
20	O
d.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
her	O
Husband	O
Paul	B-pers
Pristow	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
3	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Pristow	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Dark	O
of	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
over	O
London-Bridge	B-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ran	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
past	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
my	O
Pocket	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
14	O
d.	O
and	O
I	O
stopt	O
him	O
immediately	O
with	O
the	O
Money	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
among	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
particular	O
Half-penny	O
which	O
I	O
knew	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
Cut	O
across	O
the	O
Face	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Green	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
About	O
10	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
in	O
a	O
Crowd	O
at	O
Stocks-Market	B-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
2	O
more	O
Boys	O
jostled	O
against	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
felt	O
a	O
Prick	O
upon	O
my	O
Thigh	O
,	O
like	O
the	O
Prick	O
of	O
a	O
sharp	O
Knife	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
lookt	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Hand	O
at	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
I	O
catch	O
'd	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
got	O
away	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
My	O
Pocket	O
was	O
cut	O
,	O
and	O
9	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
each	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Aurelia	B-pers
Wilmot	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Shirts	O
,	O
2	O
Smocks	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Holman	I-pers
,	O
October	O
30	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
and	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Cane	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
he	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Tea	O
Kettle	O
,	O
a	O
Coffee	O
Pot	O
,	O
a	O
Saucepan	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Pound	O
of	O
Candles	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
;	O
and	O
she	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stoln	O
,	O
January	O
17	O
.	O
Glover	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
Cane	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Trueboy	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
10	O
Pound	O
of	O
Iron	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Halsey	I-pers
,	O
Feb	O
,	O
7	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Buckingham	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Shirts	O
,	O
and	O
1	O
Smock	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bedell	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Morris	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Evan	I-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Mug	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Oliver	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
House	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Martha	B-pers
Drew	I-pers
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Drew	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Curtains	O
.	O
5	O
Tea	O
Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
Sheet	O
,	O
2	O
Dishes	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Looking	O
Glass	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
.	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Snellham	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
some	O
Plate	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Beddal	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Osborn	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Pot	O
and	O
Box	O
Iron	O
,	O
and	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Simmons	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
(	O
who	O
was	O
transported	O
for	O
another	O
Felony	O
)	O
did	O
assault	O
Mary	B-pers
Batten	I-pers
in	O
an	O
open	O
Place	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
12s	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
Hankerchief	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
,	O
Ravishing	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
her	O
Will	O
,	O
carnally	O
knowing	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	O
Batten	O
,	O
Spinster	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
1724	O
.	O
Mary	O
Batten	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
Last	O
Christmas	O
was	O
Twelve	O
Month	O
,	O
about	O
4	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
Shop-Mate	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
who	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
;	O
but	O
is	O
since	O
dead	O
.	O
She	O
and	O
I	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
wind	O
Silk	O
together	O
.	O
And	O
there	O
I	O
staid	O
till	O
one	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
;	O
not	O
that	O
I	O
use	O
to	O
keep	O
ill	O
Hours	O
;	O
for	O
it	O
is	O
very	O
well	O
known	O
that	O
I	O
take	O
an	O
honest	O
Care	O
for	O
a	O
Livelyhood	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
Holiday	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
were	O
willing	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
little	O
Merry	O
together	O
.	O
-	O
So	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
going	O
along	O
Windford-street	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
way	O
home	O
,	O
there	O
came	O
3	O
Men	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Jackson	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
Black	O
Lyon	O
Ale-house	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Names	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
others	O
,	O
were	O
Ward	O
and	O
Borce	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
's	O
a	O
jolly	O
Girl	O
she	O
shall	O
be	O
my	O
Wife	O
No	O
,	O
says	O
another	O
,	O
She	O
shall	O
be	O
mine	O
.	O
But	O
indeed	O
says	O
the	O
third	O
,	O
she	O
shall	O
be	O
mine	O
,	O
-	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
drove	O
me	O
along	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Spittle-fields-Market	B-place
,	O
and	O
there	O
they	O
threw	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
held	O
me	O
while	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
-	O
Laud	O
bless	O
me	O
,	O
-	O
what	O
shall	O
I	O
say	O
now	O
,	O
-	O
must	O
I	O
speak	O
plain	O
,	O
-	O
plain	O
English	O
?	O
-	O
and	O
before	O
all	O
these	O
Gentlemen	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
vow	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
a-sham	O
'd	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
dont	O
know	O
how	O
to	O
speak	O
such	O
a	O
Word	O
,	O
-	O
but	O
if	O
I	O
must	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
,	O
-	O
they	O
held	O
me	O
while	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ravish	O
'd	O
me	O
:	O
and	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
and	O
struggled	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
all	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
to	O
hinder	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
signified	O
nothing	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
there	O
came	O
a	O
Watchman	O
with	O
his	O
Lanthorn	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Face	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
bid	O
the	O
Watchman	O
go	O
about	O
his	O
Business	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
'd	O
satisfy	O
him	O
another	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
the	O
Watchman	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Two	O
serv	O
'd	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Manner	O
as	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
.	O
They	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
French	O
Disease	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
my	O
Gown	O
and	O
Handkerchief	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
Upon	O
Enquiry	O
in	O
Spittle	O
fields-Market	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
others	O
.	O
They	O
own	O
'd	O
they	O
had	O
lain	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
They	O
beg	O
'd	O
she	O
'd	O
give	O
them	O
no	O
Trouble	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
from	O
Time	O
to	O
Time	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
'd	O
come	O
and	O
make	O
her	O
amends	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
her	O
6	O
Shillings	O
a	O
piece	O
to	O
buy	O
her	O
a	O
new	O
Gown	O
,	O
but	O
were	O
never	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
their	O
Promise	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
born	O
and	O
bred	O
a	O
Butcher	O
in	O
Spittle-fields-Market	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
absconded	O
upon	O
this	O
Account	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Trotman	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
my	O
Daughters	O
Husband	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
's	O
as	O
honest	O
a	O
Fellow	O
as	O
ever	O
liv	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Occasion	O
to	O
ravish	O
any	O
Body	O
,	O
for	O
my	O
Daughter	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
say	O
it	O
,	O
is	O
as	O
likely	O
a	O
Woman	O
as	O
any	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
.	O
Other	O
Witnesses	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
sober	O
,	O
industrious	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Priscilla	B-pers
Waller	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sauce	O
Pan	O
,	O
a	O
Porringer	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Hays	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Holbourn	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Raworth	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
January	O
29	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
24	O
Pound	O
of	O
Beef	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jeremy	B-pers
Harford	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Moreton	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
Boy	O
,	O
)	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Godfrey	I-pers
,	I-pers
from	I-pers
the	I-pers
Person	I-pers
of	I-pers
Mary	I-pers
his	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Mary	O
his	O
Wife	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
as	O
Mrs.	O
Godfrey	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
her	O
own	O
Door	O
(	O
the	O
Prince	B-place
's	I-place
Head	I-place
in	I-place
Tyburn-Road	I-place
)	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
when	O
Sells	O
and	O
Mattocks	O
were	O
going	O
by	O
to	O
be	O
executed	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
stood	O
close	O
before	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
his	O
Hand	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
cut	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
she	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
look	O
downwards	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Bowell	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Keeble	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hillington	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
Randall	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
3	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Anniseed	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Moody	I-pers
,	O
February	O
15	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Lindsey	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
4	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
an	O
Iron	O
Pot	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
several	O
Persons	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
(	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Cooms	I-pers
)	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Seals	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Warrener	I-pers
,	O
January	O
the	O
18th	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Warrener	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
In	O
Lincolz	O
's	O
Inn	O
Fields	O
about	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
one	O
John	O
Cooms	O
,	O
pray	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
change	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
laid	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
,	O
they	O
follow	O
'd	O
me	O
thro	O
'	O
Russel	O
street	O
,	O
into	O
Charles-street	B-place
,	O
and	O
there	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
playly	O
at	O
Prick	O
Belt	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
won	O
15	O
Pence	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
since	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
the	O
half	O
Crown	O
chang	O
'd	O
,	O
they	O
'd	O
play	O
who	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
all	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
'd	O
hold	O
Stakes	O
;	O
I	O
agreed	O
,	O
it	O
rain	O
'd	O
very	O
hard	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
Body	O
out	O
ourselves	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
play	O
,	O
a	O
Boy	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
time	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Cooms	O
catch	O
'd	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
Arms	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
me	O
while	O
the	O
Boy	O
pull	O
'd	O
the	O
Watch	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
.	O
Cooms	O
made	O
off	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
knockt	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
down	O
,	O
he	O
presently	O
got	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
into	O
the	O
Bear	O
Inn	O
,	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
easie	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
'd	O
procure	O
me	O
the	O
Watch	O
again	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
sent	O
a	O
Porter	O
to	O
Turnbull-street	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Porter	O
return	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Watch	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
had	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
I	O
'd	O
be	O
favourable	O
he	O
'd	O
help	O
me	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
pull	O
'd	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Beasly	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Ladle	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Taster	O
,	O
4	O
Moidores	O
,	O
8	O
Broad-pieces	O
,	O
and	O
29	O
l.	O
14	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
The	O
Witnesses	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
keeps	O
a	O
Distillers	O
Shop	O
,	O
the	O
Black	B-place
Boy	I-place
and	I-place
Still	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Clare-Market	I-place
;	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
besides	O
the	O
Plate	O
and	O
Money	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Bills	O
,	O
and	O
Notes	O
of	O
Hand	O
,	O
for	O
upwards	O
of	O
350	O
l.	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
Among	O
these	O
was	O
a	O
promissory	O
Note	O
from	O
Mr.	O
James	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Tonson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
therefore	O
sent	O
Word	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
of	O
his	O
House	O
being	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
that	O
if	O
such	O
a	O
Note	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
secure	O
the	O
Bearer	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
who	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
Little-Britain	B-place
,	O
was	O
observ	O
'd	O
to	O
live	O
very	O
irregularly	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
to	O
appear	O
in	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
different	O
Suits	O
in	O
one	O
Day	O
,	O
without	O
having	O
any	O
visible	O
Means	O
of	O
maintaining	O
himself	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Manner	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
took	O
particular	O
Notice	O
of	O
his	O
coming	O
home	O
drunk	O
,	O
about	O
7	O
a	O
Clock	O
that	O
Morning	O
the	O
Burglary	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
And	O
some	O
other	O
Circumstances	O
concurring	O
to	O
raise	O
a	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
the	O
stoln	O
Plate	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
necessary	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
an	O
Iron	O
Bar	O
in	O
his	O
Chamber	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
broken	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Cellar	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
drinking	O
in	O
a	O
Coffee-House	O
near	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
,	O
till	O
Mid-night	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
two	O
Hours	O
before	O
the	O
Burglary	O
;	O
for	O
betwixt	O
2	O
and	O
3	O
a	O
Clock	O
that	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Drawer	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
Lincoln's-Inn-Fields	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
thus	O
made	O
his	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
Coffee-House	O
in	O
Clare-street	O
about	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
I	O
crost	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
betwixt	O
Mr.Cross	O
's	O
Ware-House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Fishmongers	O
;	O
I	O
stumbled	O
over	O
something	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
just	O
under	O
a	O
Lamp	O
,	O
I	O
lookt	O
about	O
and	O
saw	O
lying	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
Plate	O
that	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
my	O
Vault	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Piece	O
of	O
Iron	O
that	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
my	O
Chamber	O
.	O
From	O
whence	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Drury-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
pickt	O
up	O
a	O
Blackamoor	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
her	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Night-House	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
Wife	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Byrom	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
36	O
Bottles	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Beaven	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
10	O
.	O
Acquit	O
.	O
Bridget	B-pers
Farrel	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ambrose	I-pers
,	O
February	O
2	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Wigs	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Will	B-pers
.	I-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
14	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Judith	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
January	O
20	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Plowright	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
Yard	O
of	O
Dunjar	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Sheltram	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
25	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Leg	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Salt	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Berwick	I-pers
,	O
November	O
17	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Raven	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Wastecoat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pocket-book	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Moor	I-pers
,	O
December	O
23	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Alice	B-pers
Hibball	I-pers
,	O
was	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Plate	O
,	O
February	O
16	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Millington	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Witchell	I-pers
,	O
by	O
striking	O
,	O
fracturing	O
,	O
and	O
mortally	O
bruising	O
his	O
left	O
Leg	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Ancle	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
February	O
;	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languisht	O
till	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Month	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquest	O
for	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
whole	O
Evidence	O
,	O
the	O
Fact	O
appeared	O
thus	O
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
drinking	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Hoop	B-place
and	I-place
Griffin	I-place
Tavern	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Thames-street	I-place
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
Bricklayer	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
his	O
Name	O
was	O
not	O
Sam	O
.	O
Millington	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
Yes	O
.	O
Why	O
then	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
Scrub	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
-	O
A	O
Scrub	O
?	O
For	O
what	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
'll	O
tell	O
you	O
for	O
what	O
.	O
Do	O
n't	O
ye	O
remember	O
that	O
about	O
12	O
Years	O
ago	O
,	O
I	O
fought	O
with	O
your	O
Friend	O
Bond	O
,	O
a	O
Carpenter	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Castle	O
in	O
Angel-street	O
in	O
St	O
:	O
Martin	O
's	O
-	O
Well	O
and	O
what	O
then	O
?	O
-	O
And	O
do	O
n't	O
ye	O
remember	O
that	O
you	O
parted	O
us	O
by	O
taking	O
me	O
off	O
.	O
-	O
Suppose	O
I	O
did	O
?	O
-	O
Why	O
then	O
,	O
I	O
say	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
Scrub	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Scoundrel	O
for	O
your	O
Pains	O
,	O
for	O
if	O
you	O
had	O
let	O
us	O
alone	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
beat	O
him	O
.	O
-	O
You	O
'	O
a	O
'	O
beat	O
him	O
!	O
No	O
,	O
that	O
's	O
a	O
great	O
Mistake	O
of	O
yours	O
!	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
beat	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
instead	O
of	O
calling	O
me	O
Scrub	O
,	O
you	O
ought	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
Bottle	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
Mistake	O
of	O
mine	O
!	O
Why	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
beat	O
him	O
or	O
you	O
either	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
of	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
can	O
still	O
,	O
for	O
all	O
I	O
am	O
grown	O
so	O
fat	O
.	O
I	O
'll	O
fight	O
you	O
for	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
here	O
it	O
is	O
.	O
-	O
You	O
're	O
not	O
in	O
earnest	O
sure	O
?	O
-	O
By	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
sha	O
n't	O
believe	O
it	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
see	O
you	O
pull	O
off	O
your	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
.	O
-	O
Why	O
then	O
there	O
's	O
my	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
's	O
my	O
Wig	O
.	O
Now	O
cover	O
the	O
Guinea	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
taking	O
off	O
his	O
own	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
,	O
answer	O
'd	O
no	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
fight	O
it	O
shall	O
be	O
for	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
a	O
Bottle	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
had	O
rather	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
Bottle	O
and	O
let	O
it	O
alone	O
.	O
But	O
since	O
you	O
will	O
needs	O
sight	O
,	O
there	O
's	O
the	O
first	O
Blow	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
so	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
in	O
a	O
jocular	O
Manner	O
gave	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
a	O
gentle	O
Tap	O
or	O
Stroke	O
upon	O
the	O
Cheek	O
.	O
D	O
-	O
ye	O
for	O
a	O
Cowardly	O
Dog	O
.	O
(	O
says	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
)	O
do	O
n't	O
stroke	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
strike	O
as	O
hard	O
as	O
you	O
can	O
.	O
I	O
wont	O
take	O
the	O
Law	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
,	O
as	O
Mr.	O
Burleigh	O
made	O
Oath	O
the	O
first	O
Blow	O
was	O
given	O
by	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
who	O
struck	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
Stomach	O
,	O
and	O
tore	O
his	O
Shirt	O
;	O
but	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
believe	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
struck	O
first	O
.	O
However	O
they	O
both	O
fell	O
to	O
fighting	O
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
strike	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
knockt	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
down	O
three	O
Times	O
.	O
He	O
rose	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
his	O
third	O
Rising	O
,	O
somebody	O
pusht	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
shutting	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
his	O
Heel	O
was	O
catch	O
'd	O
betwixt	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Door-case	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
hastily	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
get	O
up	O
,	O
gave	O
his	O
Leg	O
such	O
a	O
Wrench	O
as	O
dislocated	O
his	O
Ancle	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Whadcock	I-pers
the	O
Surgeon	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
Being	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
to	O
set	O
the	O
broken	O
Leg	O
of	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Tibia	O
(	O
or	O
great	O
Bone	O
of	O
his	O
Leg	O
)	O
forced	O
quite	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Skin	O
,	O
and	O
hung	O
over	O
his	O
Shoe	O
.	O
He	O
being	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
ill	O
Habit	O
of	O
Body	O
,	O
his	O
Leg	O
presently	O
morrify	O
'd	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
after	O
advising	O
with	O
other	O
Surgeons	O
,	O
I	O
cut	O
it	O
off	O
.	O
He	O
fell	O
into	O
a	O
Fever	O
and	O
dy	O
'd	O
delirious	O
.	O
The	O
Widow	O
of	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
his	O
Death	O
,	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
Sam	O
.	O
Millington	O
was	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
my	O
Death	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
ow	O
'd	O
me	O
a	O
Spite	O
these	O
Twelve	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
he	O
has	O
paid	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
brought	O
in	O
their	O
Verdict	O
,	O
Accidental	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Oneby	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Gower	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
by	O
maliciously	O
giving	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
drawn	O
Sword	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
left	O
Part	O
of	O
his	O
Belly	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Navel	O
,	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
of	O
the	O
Breadth	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
ten	O
Inches	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languisht	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
.	O
and	O
then	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
February	O
about	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Blunt	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
self	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Castle-Tavern	B-place
in	I-place
Drury-lane	I-place
;	O
where	O
,	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Rich	O
came	O
to	O
us	O
.	O
About	O
the	O
fourth	O
or	O
fifth	O
Bottle	O
,	O
Box	O
and	O
Dice	O
were	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
Dice	O
laid	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
I	O
dont	O
know	O
by	O
whom	O
.	O
The	O
Box	O
and	O
Bottle	O
went	O
round	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
tho	O
'	O
we	O
plaid	O
so	O
low	O
,	O
as	O
not	O
to	O
set	O
above	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
yet	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
great	O
Inclination	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
especially	O
to	O
set	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
therefore	O
after	O
a	O
trifling	O
Loss	O
,	O
I	O
declined	O
the	O
Play	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
exprest	O
a	O
Disgust	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
should	O
follow	O
my	O
own	O
Inclination	O
,	O
without	O
regarding	O
whether	O
or	O
no	O
it	O
was	O
agreeable	O
to	O
his	O
Humour	O
.	O
They	O
continued	O
playing	O
:	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
lost	O
30	O
Shillings	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Rich	O
said	O
,	O
Who	O
will	O
set	O
me	O
Three	O
half	O
Crowns	O
?	O
Upon	O
which	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
took	O
something	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
but	O
conceal	O
'd	O
it	O
with	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
set	O
you	O
3	O
Pieces	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
taking	O
his	O
Hand	O
away	O
we	O
saw	O
3	O
Half-pence	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
not	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
much	O
affronted	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
impertinent	O
to	O
set	O
3	O
Half-pence	O
,	O
or	O
Words	O
to	O
that	O
Effect	O
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
meant	O
by	O
impertinent	O
.	O
You	O
're	O
an	O
impertinent	O
Puppy	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Man	O
that	O
calls	O
me	O
Puppy	O
,	O
is	O
a	O
Rascal	O
or	O
a	O
Scoundrel	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
which	O
,	O
He	O
had	O
hardly	O
spoke	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
snatch	O
'd	O
up	O
a	O
Bottle	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
Violence	O
threw	O
it	O
at	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
which	O
beat	O
some	O
Powder	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Wig	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
him	O
no	O
hurt	O
.	O
He	O
in	O
return	O
Tost	O
a	O
Glass	O
(	O
or	O
a	O
Candlestick	O
)	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
which	O
,	O
for	O
both	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
reach	O
him	O
.	O
They	O
both	O
rose	O
up	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
their	O
Swords	O
;	O
which	O
hung	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
being	O
quickest	O
got	O
his	O
Sword	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
drew	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
still	O
in	O
a	O
Posture	O
of	O
Defence	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
good	O
Distance	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
advancing	O
,	O
and	O
drawing	O
his	O
Sword	O
to	O
meet	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Rich	O
stept	O
in	O
between	O
,	O
and	O
prevented	O
him	O
,	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
then	O
threw	O
away	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
all	O
sat	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
for	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
:	O
When	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
offering	O
his	O
Hand	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
said	O
to	O
this	O
Effect	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
had	O
hot	O
Words	O
.	O
Major	O
,	O
you	O
was	O
the	O
Aggressor	O
:	O
But	O
let	O
us	O
be	O
reconcil	O
'd	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
answer	O
'd	O
to	O
this	O
Effect	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
ye	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
have	O
your	O
Blood	O
;	O
and	O
turning	O
to	O
me	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Hawkins	O
,	O
You	O
was	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
this	O
.	O
Why	O
then	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
have	O
any	O
Thing	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
your	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
see	O
you	O
out	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
another	O
Chap	O
first	O
.	O
In	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
near	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
Company	O
broke	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
Street	O
Door	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
rain	O
;	O
I	O
waited	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
seeing	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Company	O
come	O
down	O
,	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
wounded	O
,	O
and	O
leaning	O
on	O
a	O
Chair	O
in	O
a	O
languishing	O
Condition	O
.	O
He	O
dy	O
'd	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
intimately	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
dont	O
believe	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
sweeter	O
Temper	O
'd	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Rich	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
,	O
among	O
whom	O
were	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
went	O
together	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
New	O
Tragedy	O
of	O
Hecuba	O
.	O
We	O
sat	O
together	O
in	O
the	O
Pit	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
good	O
Friends	O
all	O
the	O
Time	O
of	O
the	O
Play	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
over	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
for	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
them	O
again	O
at	O
the	O
Castle	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
Box	O
and	O
Dice	O
,	O
which	O
not	O
being	O
to	O
be	O
had	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Pepper	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Dice	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
but	O
knew	O
not	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
laid	O
down	O
3	O
half	O
Crowns	O
.	O
The	O
Major	O
set	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
threw	O
.	O
Seven	O
was	O
the	O
Main	O
,	O
and	O
Six	O
the	O
Chance	O
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
put	O
down	O
3	O
half	O
Pence	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Here	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
set	O
ye	O
3	O
Pieces	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
the	O
Brass	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
an	O
impertinent	O
Puppy	O
:	O
Says	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
to	O
this	O
effect	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
afraid	O
of	O
ye	O
;	O
he	O
that	O
calls	O
me	O
Impertinent	O
is	O
a	O
Rascal	O
At	O
these	O
Words	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
threw	O
a	O
Bottle	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
brusht	O
his	O
Wig	O
as	O
it	O
past	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
in	O
return	O
tost	O
a	O
Glass	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
both	O
took	O
their	O
Swords	O
;	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
drew	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
ready	O
to	O
defend	O
himself	O
;	O
but	O
made	O
no	O
Offer	O
to	O
push	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Table	O
and	O
Chair	O
betwixt	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
coming	O
forward	O
to	O
engage	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
stept	O
between	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
Longe	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
thro	O
'	O
my	O
Body	O
;	O
which	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
unarm	O
'd	O
would	O
be	O
Wilful	O
Murder	O
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
then	O
threw	O
away	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
sat	O
down	O
again	O
;	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
forward	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Come	O
,	O
Major	O
,	O
let	O
us	O
be	O
reconcil	O
'd	O
:	O
We	O
have	O
had	O
Words	O
in	O
heat	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
ought	O
to	O
be	O
forgiven	O
and	O
forgot	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
passionately	O
answer	O
'd	O
.	O
to	O
this	O
effect	O
G	O
-	O
D	O
-	O
ye	O
you	O
lie	O
-	O
I	O
'll	O
have	O
your	O
Blood	O
by	O
G	O
-	O
a	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
all	O
got	O
up	O
to	O
go	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
hung	O
his	O
great	O
Coat	O
upon	O
his	O
Shoulders	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
button	O
'd	O
it	O
in	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
places	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hawkins	O
went	O
out	O
first	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Blunt	O
next	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
hardly	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
.	O
Hark	O
ye	O
,	O
young	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
something	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
ye	O
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
went	O
back	O
,	O
they	O
both	O
re-enter	O
'd	O
the	O
Room	O
;	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
immediately	O
shut	O
last	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Clashing	O
of	O
Swords	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
stamp	O
upon	O
the	O
Floor	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
made	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
heavy	O
Man	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Blunt	O
stept	O
back	O
,	O
we	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
get	O
in	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
immediately	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
by	O
the	O
Drawers	O
Assistance	O
,	O
we	O
got	O
in	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Blunt	O
first	O
and	O
I	O
close	O
behind	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
then	O
next	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
standing	O
with	O
his	O
Sword	O
drawn	O
in	O
his	O
Right	O
Hand	O
the	O
Point	O
of	O
it	O
toward	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
held	O
by	O
the	O
shoulder	O
with	O
his	O
Left	O
Hand	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
had	O
then	O
no	O
Sword	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
soon	O
afterwards	O
found	O
it	O
close	O
to	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
behind	O
the	O
Foldings	O
of	O
the	O
Table	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
greasy	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
Inches	O
from	O
the	O
Point	O
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
clos	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
manner	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
rather	O
fell	O
towards	O
him	O
thro	O
'	O
Weakness	O
,	O
than	O
otherwise	O
;	O
which	O
makes	O
me	O
think	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
given	O
him	O
before	O
we	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
We	O
put	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
I	O
receiv	O
'd	O
a	O
little	O
Prick	O
with	O
(	O
as	O
I	O
suppose	O
)	O
the	O
Major	O
's	O
Sword	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
accidentally	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
part	O
them	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Blunt	O
receiv	O
'd	O
a	O
dangerous	O
Wound	O
in	O
the	O
Belly	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
ignorant	O
by	O
what	O
Means	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
he	O
had	O
kill	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
only	O
frighted	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
suppose	O
I	O
had	O
kill	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
do	O
in	O
such	O
Affairs	O
;	O
for	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
kill	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
Night	O
(	O
while	O
the	O
Quarrel	O
was	O
fresh	O
)	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
Law	O
on	O
my	O
Side	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
on	O
his	O
Death	O
Bed	O
if	O
he	O
receiv	O
'd	O
the	O
Wound	O
fairly	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
faintly	O
.	O
I	O
-	O
think	O
-	O
I	O
-	O
did	O
-	O
but	O
-	O
I	O
dont	O
know	O
-	O
what	O
might	O
have	O
happened	O
-	O
if	O
you	O
-	O
had	O
not	O
-	O
come	O
in	O
-	O
The	O
former	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
preceeding	O
Depositions	O
,	O
being	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
Michael	B-pers
Blunt	I-pers
,	O
he	O
thus	O
went	O
on	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
throwing	O
of	O
the	O
Bottle	O
,	O
I	O
being	O
apprehensive	O
that	O
their	O
Quarrel	O
would	O
break	O
out	O
again	O
next	O
Day	O
;	O
I	O
invited	O
the	O
Company	O
to	O
dine	O
together	O
,	O
in	O
hopes	O
to	O
bring	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
Reconciliation	O
,	O
and	O
thereby	O
prevent	O
farther	O
Mischief	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
answer	O
'd	O
my	O
Offer	O
,	O
with	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
ye	O
all	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
dine	O
with	O
none	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
back	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
no	O
sooner	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
shut	O
violently	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Clashing	O
of	O
Swords	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
got	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
had	O
any	O
Sword	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
sinking	O
forwards	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
going	O
to	O
a	O
assist	O
him	O
,	O
receiv	O
'd	O
a	O
Wound	O
in	O
my	O
Belly	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
was	O
mortal	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
how	O
,	O
or	O
by	O
whom	O
it	O
was	O
given	O
:	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
not	O
by	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
no	O
Sword	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
not	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Condition	O
to	O
wound	O
me	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Shaw	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
languishing	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
,	O
his	O
Guts	O
appear	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
Wound	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
mortifying	O
by	O
being	O
expos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Air	O
.	O
I	O
drest	O
him	O
and	O
sent	O
him	O
home	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
second	O
Rupture	O
of	O
his	O
Intestines	O
.	O
He	O
dyed	O
soon	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Wound	O
was	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
thus	O
made	O
his	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
Dice	O
and	O
Pepper	O
Box	O
were	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
by	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
flung	O
a	O
Main	O
and	O
past	O
it	O
about	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hawkins	O
refus	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
thought	O
there	O
was	O
as	O
good	O
Fellowship	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
play	O
,	O
as	O
in	O
altogether	O
drinking	O
:	O
At	O
last	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
set	O
3	O
half	O
Pence	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
impertinent	O
.	O
He	O
call	O
'd	O
me	O
Rascal	O
.	O
You	O
impertinent	O
Puppy	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
ye	O
mean	O
by	O
that	O
;	O
and	O
taking	O
up	O
a	O
Flask	O
I	O
threw	O
it	O
towards	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
threw	O
a	O
Glass	O
at	O
any	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
in	O
so	O
doing	O
he	O
acted	O
very	O
basely	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
sat	O
down	O
again	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Company	O
was	O
going	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
on	O
my	O
great	O
Coat	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
think	O
did	O
not	O
look	O
as	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
any	O
Thought	O
of	O
fighting	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
and	O
I	O
being	O
the	O
two	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
be	O
no	O
sooner	O
saw	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Company	O
gone	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
slung	O
the	O
Door	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
drew	O
upon	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
oblig	O
'd	O
to	O
draw	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
parrying	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
receiv	O
'd	O
3	O
Wounds	O
,	O
one	O
on	O
my	O
Knee	O
,	O
another	O
across	O
my	O
Finger	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
third	O
on	O
my	O
Buttock	O
;	O
which	O
last	O
I	O
receiv	O
'd	O
when	O
I	O
clos	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
then	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
stab	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
by	O
him	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Blunt	O
receiv	O
'd	O
his	O
Wound	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
part	O
us	O
.	O
The	O
Drawer	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
enter	O
'd	O
the	O
Room	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
both	O
with	O
their	O
Swords	O
in	O
their	O
Hands	O
,	O
pointing	O
towards	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
closed	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
so	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
rather	O
falling	O
than	O
pushing	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
with	O
his	O
Left	O
Hand	O
,	O
for	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
we	O
parted	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
so	O
weak	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
stand	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
stab	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
behind	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
for	O
God	O
Sake	O
what	O
are	O
ye	O
doing	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Burdet	O
,	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Day	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Gardiner	O
,	O
in	O
Dean-street	O
,	O
near	O
Red-Lyon-Square	O
;	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
conceal	O
'd	O
himself	O
.	O
He	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
dress	O
his	O
Wounds	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
three	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
now	O
says	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Inch	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Gardner	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
.	O
Some	O
Points	O
of	O
Law	O
arising	O
from	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
gave	O
in	O
a	O
Special	O
Verdict	O
:	O
which	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
determin	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Judges	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Gates	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Vulcan	I-pers
,	O
being	O
attainted	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
by	O
not	O
surrendring	O
himself	O
within	O
40	O
Days	O
after	O
the	O
Publication	O
of	O
an	O
Order	O
of	O
Council	O
requiring	O
him	O
so	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
say	O
why	O
Judgment	O
of	O
Death	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
past	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
answered	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Name	O
was	O
William	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
,	O
and	O
not	O
Gates	O
.	O
He	O
stood	O
convicted	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
on	O
a	O
Clause	O
in	O
an	O
Act	O
of	O
the	O
9th	O
year	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
commonly	O
called	O
The	O
Black	O
Act	O
,	O
which	O
provides	O
,	O
That	O
if	O
Information	O
is	O
given	O
upon	O
Oath	O
,	O
before	O
two	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
of	O
any	O
Person	O
who	O
has	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Offences	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Act	O
:	O
And	O
if	O
that	O
Information	O
is	O
certify	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Secretary	O
of	O
State	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
him	O
laid	O
before	O
the	O
King	O
in	O
Council	O
;	O
and	O
thereupon	O
an	O
Order	O
of	O
Council	O
is	O
issued	O
out	O
,	O
requiring	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
surrender	O
himself	O
within	O
40	O
Days	O
after	O
the	O
Date	O
thereof	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
on	O
two	O
Market	O
Days	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
two	O
Market	O
Towns	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Offence	O
is	O
committed	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Order	O
is	O
openly	O
read	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
affixed	O
in	O
a	O
publick	O
Place	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Markets	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
publish	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
London	O
Gazette	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
thereupon	O
the	O
Person	O
so	O
requir	O
'd	O
to	O
surrender	O
,	O
does	O
not	O
surrender	O
himself	O
within	O
the	O
limited	O
Time	O
,	O
he	O
shall	O
stand	O
convicted	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
try	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Offences	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
The	O
Information	O
,	O
the	O
Certificate	O
,	O
the	O
Order	O
of	O
Council	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
proper	O
Publication	O
in	O
July	O
last	O
were	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Henry	B-pers
Best	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Humphry	B-pers
Buckle	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
very	O
Man	O
,	O
against	O
whom	O
they	O
made	O
the	O
Information	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
now	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Men	O
that	O
enter	O
'd	O
Enfield	B-place
Chace	I-place
,	O
kill	O
'd	O
two	O
Deer	O
,	O
and	O
shot	O
at	O
these	O
Deponents	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
knew	O
him	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Will	O
Gates	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
usually	O
call	O
'd	O
Vulcan	O
.	O
Tho	B-pers
Archer	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
Newgate	O
.	O
One	O
Day	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
shave	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
for	O
his	O
Name	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
News	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
he	O
always	O
carry	O
'd	O
Pistols	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
intended	O
to	O
leave	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
a	O
News	O
Paper	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
William	O
Gates	O
,	O
alias	O
Vulcan	O
,	O
was	O
requir	O
'd	O
to	O
surrender	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
Person	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Josiah	B-pers
Charleton	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
laced	O
cloth	O
Housing	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
Horse	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Snuffers	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
s	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Robert	B-pers
Lord	I-pers
Bingly	I-pers
,	O
December	O
the	O
10th	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Silver	O
Medals	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Pound	O
of	O
Brass	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
noble	O
Henry	B-pers
Duke	I-pers
of	I-pers
Kent	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
Decem	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Burleigh	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sold	O
me	O
some	O
burnt	O
Lace	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
Snuffers	O
;	O
I	O
melted	O
'em	O
both	O
down	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
remember	O
the	O
Snuffers	O
had	O
the	O
same	O
Coat	O
of	O
Arms	O
,	O
as	O
this	O
Silver	O
has	O
which	O
is	O
my	O
Lord	O
Bingly	O
's	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Footman	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
accidentally	O
broke	O
the	O
Snuffers	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
his	O
Place	O
was	O
worth	O
,	O
if	O
his	O
Lord	O
should	O
know	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
a	O
new	O
Pair	O
with	O
his	O
own	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
had	O
these	O
old	O
ones	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
As	O
for	O
the	O
Lace	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
off	O
an	O
old	O
Horse	O
Furniture	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Lord	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
-	O
The	O
Goods	O
being	O
mist	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
examin	O
'd	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
he	O
confest	O
he	O
stole	O
'em	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
39	O
s.	O
On	O
the	O
second	O
Indictment	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Paris	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
about	O
9	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
after	O
the	O
Fire	O
at	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Kent	O
's	O
in	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Square	I-place
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
my	O
Lady	O
Dutchess	O
's	O
Closet	O
;	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
him	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
and	O
searcht	O
him	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
this	O
Silver	O
bottom	O
of	O
a	O
Sconce	O
,	O
these	O
2	O
Medals	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Brass	O
,	O
which	O
came	O
off	O
her	O
Graces	O
Escritore	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cesar	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Black	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
7	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
Headcloths	O
,	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
Smocks	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
Jan	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Napper	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
we	O
found	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Robinson	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
New-Bond-street	B-place
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Plate	O
and	O
Linnen	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
again	O
the	O
same	O
Morning	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Bed	O
,	O
in	O
Silver-Court	B-place
.	O
which	O
is	O
not	O
far	O
from	O
our	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Watchman	O
and	O
Constable	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Bed	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Plunket	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Warren	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Bowman	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
144	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Christopher	O
Bowman	O
,	O
Sept.	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
10	O
Fustian	O
Frocks	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
February	O
the	O
12th	O
,	O
of	O
both	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Baily	I-pers
and	O
Martha	B-pers
Suple	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Hambleton	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
10	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
.	O
52	O
Plates	O
,	O
2	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
3	O
Cloaks	O
,	O
a	O
great	O
quantity	O
of	O
Linnen	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
.	O
Feb.	O
4	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
Timeindicted	O
.	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Katherine	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
9	O
Dishes	O
,	O
12	O
Plates	O
,	O
a	O
Cloak	O
,	O
a	O
Kettle	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
February	O
12	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
Francis	O
Baily	O
and	O
another	O
came	O
to	O
drink	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
they	O
walked	O
into	O
the	O
Garden	O
,	O
and	O
lookt	O
about	O
'em	O
here	O
and	O
there	O
and	O
every	O
where	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
me	O
take	O
notice	O
of	O
'em	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
about	O
9	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
all	O
the	O
Doors	O
fast	O
;	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
House	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Goods	O
gone	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
-	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Garden	O
Wall	O
was	O
broke	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Ladder	O
left	O
standing	O
against	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Door	O
of	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Room	O
were	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Chissel	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
Window	O
.	O
Katherine	B-pers
Bury	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
,	O
our	O
Land	O
lord	O
Matthew	B-pers
Wildman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
his	O
Comrade	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
is	O
now	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
About	O
2	O
a	O
Clock	O
that	O
Morning	O
,	O
as	O
this	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
they	O
brought	O
Home	O
a	O
great	O
parcel	O
of	O
Pewter	O
and	O
Linnen	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
while	O
they	O
staid	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
to	O
receive	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Martha	O
Suple	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
carry	O
'd	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Linnen	O
to	O
be	O
washt	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
was	O
apprehended	O
.	O
Katherine	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Baily	O
and	O
Wildman	O
came	O
to	O
drink	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
in	O
Knightsbridge	B-place
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
about	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
at	O
12	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
2	O
the	O
Watch	O
call	O
'd	O
me	O
up	O
,	O
my	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Goods	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Morning	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
crying	O
,	O
a	O
Woman	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
askt	O
me	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Thieves	O
says	O
she	O
?	O
No	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
2	O
Men	O
that	O
were	O
here	O
last	O
Night	O
,	O
because	O
they	O
talkt	O
a	O
little	O
oddly	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
said	O
as	O
how	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
Loss	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
as	O
how	O
they	O
'd	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
some	O
way	O
or	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
carried	O
Pistols	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
what	O
sort	O
of	O
Men	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
subscrib	O
'd	O
'em	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
whereof	O
she	O
said	O
.	O
She	O
believ	O
'd	O
she	O
knew	O
'em	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
she	O
directed	O
me	O
to	O
Wildmans	O
House	O
in	O
Westminster	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
'em	O
a	O
drinking	O
of	O
Punch	O
;	O
as	O
for	O
Wildman	O
he	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Constable	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Baily	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
Pewter	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
scratch	O
'd	O
my	O
Name	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
again	O
by	O
the	O
Man	O
's	O
Name	O
that	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
,	O
for	O
here	O
it	O
is	O
,	O
-	O
here	O
's	O
T.	O
for	O
Thomas	O
,	O
and	O
W.	O
for	O
Wigmore	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
Martha	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
:	O
But	O
found	O
Francis	O
Baily	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Bray	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Wise	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
stealing	O
2	O
Knives	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
February	O
16	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Suits	O
of	O
Headcloths	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Coppard	I-pers
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Hannah	B-pers
Armstrong	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Strawbridge	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
2	O
l	O
15	O
s.	O
Jan.	O
3d	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
got	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
Home	O
to	O
my	O
Wife	O
,	O
about	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
by	O
each	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
Gin	O
Shop	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
kept	O
by	O
Patrick	B-pers
Macclan	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Crown-Court	B-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
my	O
Money	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
lost	O
any	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
safe	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
staid	O
about	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
a	O
Sleep	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
waked	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
to	O
Bed	O
about	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
thought	O
of	O
my	O
Money	O
all	O
this	O
while	O
till	O
I	O
waked	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
my	O
Wife	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
searched	O
my	O
Pockets	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
find	O
but	O
a	O
penny	O
in	O
them	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Christian	B-pers
Wildsmith	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Flood	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Katherine	B-pers
Nelthrop	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Peticoat	O
,	O
a	O
Cloak	O
,	O
2	O
Hoods	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Cloths	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Everet	I-pers
,	O
January	O
3	O
Wildsmith	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Nelthrop	O
found	O
guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
Katherine	O
Nelthrop	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Riding	O
hood	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
19	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Brigs	I-pers
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Miles	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Napkins	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
Pound	O
of	O
Candles	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Cornelius	I-pers
,	O
December	O
28	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jeremy	B-pers
Fitzpatrick	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cask	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Emerton	I-pers
,	O
January	O
3	O
John	O
Emerton	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
January	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Smith	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
half	O
an	O
Anchor	O
of	O
Brandy	O
for	O
a	O
Customer	O
of	O
his	O
.	O
We	O
agreed	O
upon	O
a	O
Price	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
pay	O
ready	O
Money	O
if	O
his	O
Friend	O
lik	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
if	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
please	O
,	O
the	O
Porter	O
should	O
bring	O
it	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
should	O
pay	O
the	O
Porterage	O
.	O
I	O
accordingly	O
sent	O
my	O
Porter	O
with	O
the	O
Cask	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
strict	O
Orders	O
not	O
to	O
deliver	O
it	O
without	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Porter	O
came	O
back	O
with	O
a	O
Cask	O
,	O
but	O
instead	O
of	O
Brandy	O
it	O
was	O
fill	O
'd	O
with	O
Water	O
.	O
The	O
Porter	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
put	O
the	O
Cask	O
of	O
Prandy	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
Pag	O
.	O
and	O
was	O
carry	O
it	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
Pressoner	O
William	B-pers
Smit	I-pers
to	O
the	O
Anchor	O
Ale-house	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
saffy	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
ass	O
we	O
was	O
coming	O
together	O
,	O
honest	O
Porter	O
says	O
he	O
.	O
If	O
my	O
Friend	O
was	O
like	O
the	O
Brandy	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
kive	O
you	O
the	O
Money	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
put	O
if	O
he	O
to	O
n't	O
,	O
you	O
was	O
take	O
it	O
pack	O
again	O
-	O
Tiss	O
ferry	O
well	O
Sir	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
pitcht	O
my	O
Purden	O
upon	O
the	O
Taple	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
other	O
Pressoner	O
Fitzpatrick	O
,	O
a	O
sitting	O
upon	O
a	O
Pench	O
py	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
plue	O
Apron	O
on	O
,	O
Come	O
Honesty	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
sit	O
town	O
while	O
you	O
stand	O
and	O
call	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
Peer	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
tid	O
.	O
And	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
trinking	O
,	O
Smith	O
was	O
take	O
the	O
Cask	O
of	O
Prandy	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Pag	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
Corner	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
behind	O
a	O
Ped	O
or	O
a	O
Screen	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
traw	O
same	O
in	O
a	O
Class	O
,	O
and	O
pring	O
it	O
to	O
Fitzpatrick	O
.	O
Here	O
Lantlort	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
see	O
how	O
you	O
was	O
like	O
this	O
Prandy	O
.	O
So	O
when	O
Fitzpatrick	O
was	O
trink	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Fait	O
now	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
like	O
it	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
she	O
Prandy	O
that	O
you	O
prought	O
me	O
pefore	O
was	O
after	O
pang	O
potter	O
as	O
this	O
.	O
Inteet	O
.	O
says	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
ferry	O
sorry	O
you	O
was	O
not	O
like	O
the	O
Prandy	O
;	O
put	O
since	O
it	O
is	O
so	O
,	O
the	O
Porter	O
must	O
cen	O
carry	O
it	O
pack	O
again	O
.	O
And	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Ped	O
Side	O
,	O
and	O
pring	O
out	O
my	O
Pag	O
with	O
a	O
Cask	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
take	O
it	O
upon	O
my	O
Pack	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
it	O
home	O
;	O
put	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
open	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Piffel	O
a	O
pit	O
of	O
Prandy	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
full	O
of	O
Water	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Fitzpatrick	O
are	O
both	O
Lodgers	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
January	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
an	O
empty	O
half	O
Anchor	O
into	O
my	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
carry	O
'd	O
it	O
away	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
both	O
him	O
and	O
Smith	O
filling	O
the	O
same	O
Cask	O
with	O
Water	O
.	O
Fitzpatrick	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
Smith	O
had	O
accidentally	O
spilt	O
some	O
Brandy	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
filling	O
the	O
Cask	O
with	O
Water	O
again	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
how	O
much	O
was	O
lost	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
had	O
fill	O
'd	O
it	O
they	O
carried	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
whether	O
or	O
no	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Anchor	O
Ale-house	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
-	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
brought	O
this	O
Cask	O
of	O
Water	O
to	O
our	O
House	O
(	O
Mr.	O
Dockrell	O
's	O
at	O
tho	O
Anchor	O
in	O
the	O
Savoy	O
)	O
and	O
there	O
they	O
blackt	O
it	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
look	O
old	O
.	O
Smith	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
Fitzpatrick	O
put	O
on	O
a	O
blue	O
Apron	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
wear	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
suppose	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
pass	O
for	O
the	O
Landlord	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
sitting	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
when	O
Smith	O
return	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Porter	O
,	O
who	O
pitch	O
'd	O
his	O
Bag	O
with	O
a	O
Cask	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Table	O
;	O
Smith	O
took	O
the	O
Cask	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
it	O
behind	O
the	O
Screen	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
Porter	O
was	O
drinking	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
put	O
a	O
Cask	O
into	O
the	O
Porters	O
Bag	O
,	O
and	O
send	O
him	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
Porter	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
Smith	O
and	O
Fitzpatrick	O
carry	O
'd	O
out	O
another	O
Cask	O
between	O
them	O
.	O
Smith	O
thus	O
made	O
his	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
fair	O
Agreement	O
for	O
the	O
Brandy	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
the	O
Distiller	O
has	O
been	O
cheated	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
by	O
the	O
Porter	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
Fitzpatrick	O
is	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
myself	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Fitzpatrick	O
made	O
his	O
Defence	O
.	O
Arra	O
fait	O
if	O
I	O
dont	O
make	O
my	O
Innoshence	O
appear	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
be	O
after	O
forfeiting	O
both	O
my	O
Head	O
and	O
Ears	O
to	O
thish	O
honourable	O
Court	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
Plaush	O
consherning	O
the	O
Cashk	O
of	O
Water	O
.	O
Why	O
fait	O
now	O
,	O
Smith	O
only	O
took	O
down	O
an	O
empty	O
Cashk	O
of	O
Water	O
that	O
lay	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
to	O
shee	O
whether	O
or	O
no	O
it	O
wash	O
leaky	O
;	O
and	O
ash	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
be	O
shav	O
'd	O
that	O
ish	O
all	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
.	O
And	O
ash	O
for	O
my	O
wearing	O
a	O
blue	O
Apron	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
pleash	O
to	O
be	O
after	O
ashking	O
any	O
Body	O
that	O
knowsh	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
will	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
I	O
kept	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
twelve	O
Yearsh	O
ago	O
,	O
but	O
meeting	O
with	O
Mishfortunes	O
,	O
I	O
wash	O
forsh	O
'd	O
to	O
leave	O
it	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
turn	O
Merchant	O
,	O
and	O
sho	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
Room	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairsh	O
.	O
and	O
should	O
Brandy	O
;	O
and	O
therefore	O
I	O
hope	O
thish	O
honourable	O
Court	O
will	O
be	O
after	O
taking	O
it	O
into	O
Conshideration	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
Wife	O
and	O
four	O
shmall	O
Families	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lyon	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Edgworth	I-pers
Bess	I-pers
,	O
(	O
Relict	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
memorable	O
Jack	B-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
)	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Bury	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
6	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Tongs	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Strainer	O
,	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Bury	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
My	O
Husband	O
is	O
a	O
Hog-Butcher	O
,	O
and	O
our	O
House	O
is	O
in	O
Clerkenwell	B-place
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
Morning	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
very	O
early	O
to	O
Market	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
Window	O
open	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
left	O
fast	O
shut	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
indeed	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
pane	O
of	O
Glass	O
broke	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
presently	O
mist	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
suspected	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
workt	O
at	O
the	O
Trade	O
for	O
my	O
Husband	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
been	O
gone	O
away	O
about	O
2	O
Weeks	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
heard	O
he	O
kept	O
Company	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
here	O
he	O
is	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
Handkerchief	O
upon	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Seymour	I-pers
,	O
who	O
says	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
White-Cross-street	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
perswaded	O
me	O
to	O
rob	O
my	O
Masters	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
'd	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Way	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
was	O
drunk	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
togegether	O
.	O
Twas	O
between	O
4	O
and	O
5	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Cart	O
standing	O
under	O
my	O
Mistresses	O
Window	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Cart	O
and	O
taking	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Casement	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
that	O
it	O
only	O
stood	O
a	O
jar	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
got	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Seymour	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
This	O
Handkerchief	O
I	O
had	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
sell	O
a	O
Dram	O
of	O
Gin	O
now	O
and	O
then	O
,	O
in	O
Peter	O
's	O
lane	O
,	O
behind	O
Hicks's-Hall	O
.	O
About	O
5	O
a	O
Clock	O
that	O
Morning	O
as	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Bury	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Smith	O
knockt	O
me	O
up	O
.	O
She	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Dram	O
,	O
and	O
pulling	O
out	O
half	O
a	O
Dozen	O
Tea	O
Spoons	O
,	O
she	O
kist	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
These	O
were	O
left	O
me	O
by	O
my	O
Dear	O
,	O
John	O
Sheppard	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
just	O
fetcht	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
Pawn	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
that	O
Smith	O
pickt	O
her	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
these	O
Spoons	O
to	O
lye	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
truly	O
she	O
thought	O
she	O
might	O
as	O
well	O
earn	O
them	O
that	O
Way	O
herself	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
let	O
another	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Hannah	B-pers
Penny	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Sheets	O
,	O
a	O
Smock	O
,	O
a	O
Box-Iron	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Love	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Swift	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
with	O
Robert	B-pers
Cable	I-pers
,	O
in	O
an	O
open	O
Place	O
near	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
did	O
assault	O
Mary	B-pers
Cassel	I-pers
,	O
put	O
her	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
from	O
her	O
4	O
Table	O
Cloths	O
,	O
8	O
Napkins	O
,	O
2	O
Smocks	O
,	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Audley	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
10	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Hickenbotham	I-pers
,	O
in	O
an	O
open	O
Place	O
near	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
2	O
Smocks	O
,	O
2	O
Napkins	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Frances	B-pers
Parnell	I-pers
.	O
Widow	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Cassel	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
Between	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
my	O
Master	O
John	O
Hickenbotham	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
Islington	B-place
Causey	I-place
,	O
each	O
of	O
us	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
of	O
Cloths	O
:	O
Four	O
Men	O
met	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
past	O
'em	O
,	O
they	O
stood	O
talking	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
,	O
keep	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Wall	O
Child	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
ye	O
fall	O
in	O
the	O
Ditch	O
;	O
but	O
another	O
,	O
holding	O
out	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
cry	O
'd	O
stand	O
and	O
deliver	O
,	O
or	O
G	O
-	O
D	O
-	O
your	O
Bloods	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
shoot	O
ye	O
both	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
our	O
Bundle	O
away	O
.	O
and	O
I	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
run	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
Swore	O
we	O
were	O
both	O
dead	O
if	O
we	O
stir	O
'd	O
an	O
Inch	O
before	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Lamp	O
about	O
6	O
Yards	O
off	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Light	O
of	O
which	O
,	O
I	O
plainly	O
saw	O
the	O
Face	O
of	O
Swift	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
positive	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
John	O
Hickenbotham	O
depos	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
Coming	O
from	O
Islington	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
Jack	B-pers
Barton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Bob	B-pers
Cable	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
'em	O
what	O
they	O
did	O
there	O
so	O
late	O
,	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
waited	O
for	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
knowing	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Bailiffs	O
follower	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
were	O
only	O
setting	O
somebody	O
for	O
an	O
Arrest	O
.	O
John	O
Barton	O
appaear	O
'd	O
to	O
give	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
an	O
Indictment	O
found	O
against	O
him	O
for	O
Burglary	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
allowed	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Witness	O
.	O
Simpson	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Swift	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
indictment	O
Death	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Isabel	B-pers
Hughs	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Stone	O
of	O
Powder	O
'd	O
Beef	O
,	O
a	O
Stone	O
of	O
Pork	O
,	O
and	O
15	O
Pound	O
of	O
Candles	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
French	I-pers
,	O
Jan	B-pers
21	I-pers
.	O
Hughs	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Howard	O
Guilty	O
.	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Isabel	B-pers
Hughs	I-pers
,	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Hickman	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
29	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Birch	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
porridge	O
Pot	O
,	O
a	O
Sauce-pan	O
and	O
a	O
Stew-pan	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
19	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Cater	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
35	O
s.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Will	O
Pew	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Pew	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
by	O
myself	O
,	O
to	O
drink	O
at	O
the	O
Bull	B-place
and	I-place
Butcher	I-place
in	I-place
Long-lane	I-place
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
she	O
was	O
one	O
that	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
she	O
came	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
drink	O
to	O
her	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
yes	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
,	O
she	O
thrust	O
her	O
Hand	O
into	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
thrust	O
it	O
into	O
her	O
Bosom	O
,	O
I	O
catch	O
'd	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
to	O
the	O
Woman	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
search	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
only	O
6	O
Shillings	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
her	O
Shoe	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
pickt	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
her	O
into	O
that	O
Ale-House	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
of	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
tho	O
'd	O
they	O
search	O
'd	O
her	O
from	O
top	O
to	O
bottom	O
,	O
they	O
could	O
find	O
nothing	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
her	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
she	O
thought	O
it	O
very	O
hard	O
that	O
the	O
Court	O
did	O
not	O
Order	O
the	O
Constable	O
to	O
return	O
her	O
the	O
Six	O
Shillings	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Bishopsgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
30	O
Pound	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
2	O
Cannisters	O
of	O
Snuff	O
,	O
20	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Quarter	O
Broad	O
Pieces	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
and	I-pers
,	I-pers
Edward	I-pers
Thorowgood	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
10	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Servant	O
.	O
and	O
at	O
Several	O
Times	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Till	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Hungate	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Stationers	O
Prentice	O
in	O
Southwark	O
,	O
used	O
to	O
embezzle	O
and	O
barter	O
their	O
Masters	O
Goods	O
with	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
Hungates	O
Master	O
sent	O
him	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Bury	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Saucepan	O
,	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
and	O
Flower-box	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edw	B-pers
Emery	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Pot	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Cannon	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
14	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Watton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Salver	O
,	O
3	O
Silver	O
Salts	O
,	O
3	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Porringer	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bland	I-pers
,	O
Jan	O
20	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
Milton	B-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
Gravesend	I-place
,	O
where	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
publish	O
'd	O
Advertisements	O
of	O
'em	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
Means	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
in	O
London	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
some	O
frivolous	O
Excuses	O
of	O
his	O
finding	O
'em	O
in	O
a	O
Dunghil	O
.	O
Several	O
Persons	O
of	O
Good	O
Repute	O
appear	O
'd	O
in	O
Favour	O
of	O
his	O
Character	O
,	O
from	O
whom	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
heretofore	O
lived	O
in	O
good	O
Credit	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Partner	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Barton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Askew	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
2	O
Gold	O
Chains	O
.	O
5	O
Gold	O
Necklaces	O
,	O
17	O
Snuff	O
Boxes	O
,	O
72	O
Tea	O
Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
Aug.	O
1	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Askew	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Goldsmiths	O
Shop	O
in	O
Barbican	B-place
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
August	O
about	O
12	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
my	O
Kinswoman	O
to	O
fasten	O
the	O
Doors	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
did	O
.	O
-	O
But	O
she	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
-	O
The	O
Watch	O
rais	O
'd	O
me	O
about	O
3	O
.	O
My	O
Shop	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Goods	O
gone	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Marjoram	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
committed	O
this	O
Fact	O
about	O
peep	O
of	O
Day	O
.	O
We	O
cut	O
a	O
whole	O
in	O
the	O
Window	O
.	O
Shutter	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
unpin	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
took	O
it	O
down	O
and	O
rifled	O
the	O
Shop	O
.	O
We	O
carry	O
'd	O
the	O
Place	O
into	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
hid	O
it	O
'till	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
fetch	O
'd	O
it	O
away	O
and	O
divided	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
John	O
Barton	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
50	O
Pieces	O
of	O
printed	O
Linnen	O
,	O
10	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Turky	O
Cotton	O
,	O
and	O
10	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Dutch	O
Holland	O
,	O
Sept.	O
23	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Walter	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
about	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
fasten	O
'd	O
his	O
Doors	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Watch	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
up	O
about	O
3	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
found	O
that	O
his	O
Shop	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
above	O
200	O
l.	O
William	B-pers
Marjoram	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
Sackful	O
of	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
'em	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
White	O
Horse-Alley	O
in	O
Chick-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
sold	O
my	O
Part	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
for	O
4	O
l.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Barton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Higgs	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
thence	O
100	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
l	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	O
Higgs	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
Time	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Higgs	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
made	O
fast	O
her	O
Shop	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
call	O
'd	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
Watch	O
about	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
Window-Shutters	O
was	O
cut	O
:	O
2	O
of	O
'em	O
taken	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
lost	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Marjoram	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
About	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
in	O
Chancery-Lane	B-place
,	O
and	O
stole	O
a	O
great	O
parcel	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
Milliners	O
Goods	O
We	O
bored	O
Holes	O
in	O
the	O
Shutter	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
cut	O
one	O
Hole	O
into	O
another	O
,	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
the	O
Pin	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
down	O
the	O
Shutter	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
in	O
and	O
fill	O
'd	O
a	O
great	O
Sack	O
,	O
and	O
handed	O
it	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
We	O
sold	O
'em	O
at	O
a	O
Lump	O
for	O
3	O
l.	O
to	O
Nell	B-pers
Gaton	I-pers
.	O
Who	O
then	O
lived	O
in	O
Newtoners-Lane	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
the	O
Marshalsea	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
had	O
surrendered	O
my	O
self	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
fir	O
'd	O
a	O
Pistol	O
at	O
me	O
hard	O
by	O
Goldsmiths-Hall	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Bullet	O
went	O
over	O
my	O
Head	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
,	O
and	O
-	O
Smith	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
Marjoram	O
in	O
New	O
Prison	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
us	O
that	O
he	O
believed	O
we	O
might	O
find	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
Black-Mary's-Hole	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
that	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
Path	O
betwixt	O
Black-Mary's-Hole	O
and	O
the	O
Spaw	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
out	O
2	O
Pistols	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
'd	O
fire	O
at	O
us	O
.	O
You	O
must	O
be	O
quick	O
then	O
says	O
smith	O
,	O
for	O
if	O
you	O
dont	O
fire	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
he	O
shot	O
first	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
wounded	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Thigh	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Morrel	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Horse-cloth	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Spurs	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
Dec.31	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Newmarsh	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
Hester	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
her	O
Husband	O
Thomas	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
28	O
.	O
Hester	O
Shaw	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
Night	O
last	O
,	O
betwixt	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
over	O
London-Bridge	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
stop	O
of	O
Coaches	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
Crowd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
jostled	O
against	O
me	O
several	O
Times	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
very	O
close	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Wax	O
Work	O
last	O
Southwark	B-place
Fair	I-place
,	O
and	O
there	O
a	O
Friend	O
of	O
mine	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
this	O
Bird	O
along	O
with	O
Betty	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
what	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
Fellow	O
he	O
was	O
.	O
I	O
remembered	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
clapt	O
my	O
Hand	O
upon	O
my	O
Pocket	O
for	O
fear	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
cut	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
cautious	O
to	O
late	O
,	O
for	O
my	O
Pocket	O
was	O
cut	O
and	O
my	O
Money	O
gone	O
,	O
Birds	O
Hand	O
was	O
then	O
at	O
my	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
Newmarsh	O
stood	O
close	O
too	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
slipt	O
between	O
the	O
Coaches	O
and	O
got	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
heard	O
that	O
the	O
most	O
likely	O
Place	O
to	O
find	O
'em	O
at	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
scandalous	O
House	O
,	O
a	O
Harbour	O
for	O
Rogues	O
in	O
Bird-Cage-Alley	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Mint	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
the	O
Bell	O
and	O
7	O
Stars	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
Bell	O
and	O
Garter	O
,	O
I	O
forgot	O
which	O
,	O
but	O
't	O
is	O
kept	O
by	O
-	O
Fitzgerald	O
,	O
and	O
Irishman	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
Assistance	O
,	O
went	O
thither	O
and	O
found	O
'em	O
both	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Ells	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Headcloths	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
44	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Paul	B-pers
Ambrose	I-pers
Shute	I-pers
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Blanket	O
,	O
a	O
Childs	O
Frock	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Cap	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Paul	B-pers
Ambrose	I-pers
Shuts	I-pers
Jan.	O
30	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
.	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Rossiter	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
31	O
Yards	O
of	O
Woollen	O
Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
Pound	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Crips	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
4	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
76	O
Yards	O
of	O
Woollen	O
Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
Weatley	I-pers
.	O
Feb.	O
6	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
third	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
28	O
Yards	O
of	O
Woolen	O
Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
l	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
10	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
West	O
Country	O
Waggons	O
,	O
betwixt	O
Turnham	B-place
Green	I-place
,	O
and	O
Kensington	B-place
.	O
Some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
advertis	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
apprehended	O
upon	O
his	O
bringing	O
them	O
to	O
Pawn	O
,	O
they	O
both	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Dolly	I-pers
Prior	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Ellwood	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Babel	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
Boys	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
3	O
Brass	O
Molds	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
Blankets	O
Pillows	O
,	O
Bolsters	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
of	O
Oliver	B-pers
Slowcock	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williford	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
Girl	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
knowing	O
'em	O
to	O
be	O
stoln	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
Boys	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Burcher	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Iron	O
work	O
from	O
3	O
Ploughs	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Franklin	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
23	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Hardy	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
43	O
Plains	O
,	O
3	O
Saws	O
,	O
and	O
10	O
Chissels	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
Feb.	O
17	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Carpenter	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sheet	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Blanket	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
his	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
8	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Pendergrass	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
for	O
conspiring	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dursly	I-pers
(	O
since	O
dead	O
)	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Irwin	I-pers
,	O
to	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
steal	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
in	O
Danger	O
the	O
Life	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bramston	I-pers
,	O
and	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
persuade	O
Robert	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
to	O
be	O
an	O
Accomplice	O
thereto	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Ridgely	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
100	O
Weight	O
of	O
Nails	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Iron	O
Gouge	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Hancock	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
very	O
good	O
Credit	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
the	O
Gougeamong	O
other	O
old	O
Iron	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
valued	O
at	O
but	O
a	O
Penny	O
,	O
nothing	O
was	O
said	O
against	O
him	O
about	O
the	O
Nails	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Andrew	I-pers
Poupie	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Pearl	O
Necklaces	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Human	O
Hair	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Carpenter	I-pers
.	O
Feb.	O
3	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Christian	B-pers
Campbel	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Toms	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Smock	O
,	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Moses	B-pers
Fidoe	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
27	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
22	O
s.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Hester	B-pers
Primer	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
13	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Neck	O
and	O
Breast	O
of	O
Mutton	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Whitcomb	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Slider	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Shirts	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Laced	O
Head	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Shelton	I-pers
,	O
Jan	O
25	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Mollineux	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Holloway	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Sugar	O
Loaf	O
.	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Grimes	I-pers
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Wise	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Pestel	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Sheets	O
,	O
8	O
Smocks	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Linnen	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
.	O
Wise	O
and	O
Pestel	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Grimes	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jeremy	B-pers
Ayres	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
Ling	O
,	O
and	O
7	O
Cod	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Lillet	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Haddock	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Rochford	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Wilcox	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Efflet	I-pers
,	O
near	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecution	O
appear	O
'd	O
so	O
villainous	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Jury	O
had	O
Acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
the	O
Court	O
granted	O
him	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
his	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
committed	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
(	O
Corporal	O
Wilcox	O
)	O
to	O
Newgate	O
for	O
Perjury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Carpenter	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cock	O
and	O
two	O
Hens	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Henly	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susan	B-pers
Street	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
4	O
.	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Frederick	B-pers
Bush	I-pers
;	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gibbons	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stoln	O
,	O
February	O
19	O
Gibbons	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Street	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Caps	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Duncan	I-pers
,	O
February	O
7.	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stoln	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ray	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Vanhorn	I-pers
,	O
February	O
10	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Vanhorn	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
merry	O
Making	O
till	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
my	O
way	O
home	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
at	O
a	O
Night-Cellar	O
at	O
Charing	B-place
Cross	I-place
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
I	O
drank	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
drunk	O
and	O
fell	O
a	O
sleep	O
.	O
My	O
Landlord	O
awaked	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
mist	O
my	O
Watch	O
.	O
but	O
Newman	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Ray	O
being	O
examin	O
'd	O
,	O
confest	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
Newman	O
creep	O
under	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
Watch	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
(	O
the	O
Landlord	O
of	O
the	O
Night-Cellar	O
)	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
enquiry	O
after	O
Newman	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
3	O
Days	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
confest	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
given	O
it	O
to	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Box	I-pers
to	O
pawn	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
-	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
's	O
and	O
there	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Newman	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
won	O
the	O
Watch	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
at	O
Cards	O
.	O
But	O
that	O
Excuse	O
appeared	O
frivolous	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
several	O
,	O
who	O
saw	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
Silver	O
and	O
Gold	O
about	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Watch	O
.	O
Ray	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Newman	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Allibourn	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Earl	I-pers
of	I-pers
Cornwall	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Kingdom	O
of	O
Scotland	B-place
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Earl	O
,	O
February	O
24	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
enter	O
'd	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
then	O
quite	O
Night	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
order	O
'd	O
to	O
remain	O
till	O
next	O
Sessions	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
then	O
try	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
Trespass	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Newbury	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Gilbert	B-pers
Leeds	I-pers
,	O
February	O
13	O
.	O
Acquit	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Kennet	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Dimock	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Iron	O
Grate	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Botler	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Margaret	I-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Griffith	B-pers
Loyd	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Katherine	I-pers
Dennis	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Revel	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Suits	O
of	O
Apparel	O
,	O
32	O
pieces	O
of	O
Silks	O
and	O
Stuffs	O
,	O
3	O
pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Stockings	O
,	O
a	O
Tea	O
Kettle	O
,	O
a	O
Coffee	O
Pot	O
,	O
a	O
large	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Linnen	O
.	O
Bedding	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
5	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
.	O
Feb.	O
19	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
Mary	O
Philips	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
left	O
at	O
home	O
with	O
only	O
a	O
Child	O
.	O
She	O
bundled	O
up	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
and	O
Revel	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
found	O
upon	O
.	O
Philips	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
,	O
and	O
Revel	O
acquitted	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
order	O
'd	O
to	O
remain	O
till	O
next	O
Sessions	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
then	O
try	O
'd	O
for	O
feloniously	O
receiving	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Brotherton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Plates	O
.	O
2	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Brass	O
Pot	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Beddal	I-pers
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
King	I-pers
Cabbage	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Coach	O
Seats	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Bridget	B-pers
Buckley	I-pers
,	O
February	O
12	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
alias	I-pers
Jacob	I-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
20	O
pound	O
of	O
Pork	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Will	B-pers
.	I-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Katherine	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Blankets	O
,	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Brass	O
Pot	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Pew	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Workman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
several	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
pieces	O
of	O
Leather	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
and	I-pers
others	I-pers
and	O
others	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Southwell	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
8	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Piedmont	O
Silk	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
and	I-pers
Peter	I-pers
Chevalier	I-pers
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Fawks	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Fork	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Razors	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Roe	I-pers
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Sanders	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
2	O
Loins	O
,	O
1	O
Leg	O
,	O
and	O
1	O
Shoulder	O
of	O
Mutton	O
,	O
and	O
1	O
Leg	O
of	O
Beef	O
,	O
the	O
whole	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Tovey	I-pers
.	O
Acquit	O
.	O
Mossam	B-pers
Wye	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
20	O
Yards	O
of	O
Irish	O
Cloth	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
Yards	O
of	O
Check	O
Holland	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Prat	I-pers
,	O
February	O
14	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Kates	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Skates	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
240	O
pair	O
of	O
Buckles	O
,	O
144	O
Ink	O
Pots	O
,	O
72	O
Dozen	O
Buttons	O
,	O
12	O
Snuff-Boxes	O
,	O
120	O
Cork	O
Screws	O
,	O
540	O
Forks	O
,	O
360	O
Knives	O
,	O
6	O
Cases	O
of	O
Instruments	O
,	O
168	O
Pair	O
of	O
Spurs	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Person	O
unknown	O
.	O
Disney	B-pers
Todd	I-pers
(	O
a	O
Woman	O
)	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
harbouring	O
,	O
comforting	O
,	O
and	O
maintaining	O
the	O
said	O
Skates	O
,	O
after	O
she	O
knew	O
he	O
committed	O
the	O
said	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
for	O
receiving	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stoln	O
.	O
and	O
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Vie	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Levy	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stoln	O
.	O
The	O
Witnesses	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
Skates	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Jarrat	I-pers
about	O
7	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Cart	O
in	O
Holbourn	B-place
,	O
and	O
carried	O
'em	O
to	O
Disney	O
Todd	O
's	O
Room	O
in	O
Chick-lane	B-place
,	O
she	O
entertained	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
4	O
Dozen	O
of	O
the	O
Knives	O
to	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Farmers	O
in	O
Chick-lane	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
sold	O
'em	O
for	O
4	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
she	O
met	O
with	O
Frank	O
le	O
Vie	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
who	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
'd	O
buy	O
all	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
Skates	O
and	O
Jarrat	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
by	O
Appointment	O
met	O
him	O
late	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Sheep	O
Pens	O
in	O
Smithfield	B-place
.	O
They	O
brought	O
with	O
them	O
their	O
Laps	O
full	O
of	O
hard	O
Ware	O
paper	O
'd	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
weighted	O
'em	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
their	O
Price	O
for	O
the	O
Lump	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
12	O
l.	O
value	O
,	O
they	O
asked	O
10	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
he	O
bid	O
'em	O
6	O
s	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
consented	O
to	O
give	O
'em	O
9	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
upon	O
Condition	O
that	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
hard	O
Bargain	O
,	O
they	O
should	O
bring	O
him	O
ano	O
ther	O
odd	O
Parcel	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
they	O
agreed	O
,	O
he	O
paid	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
being	O
Men	O
of	O
Honour	O
and	O
scorning	O
to	O
be	O
worse	O
than	O
their	O
Word	O
,	O
stept	O
Home	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
,	O
21	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Knives	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
amends	O
.	O
As	O
for	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
stoln	O
from	O
'em	O
by	O
Mother	O
Todd	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
'em	O
all	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Fenwick	I-pers
,	O
by	O
beating	O
,	O
bruising	O
,	O
and	O
throwing	O
of	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
on	O
Nov.	O
25	O
.	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coronors	O
Inquest	O
for	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
being	O
drunk	O
at	O
the	O
Baptist	O
Head-Tavern	O
,	O
in	O
White-Cross	O
Street	O
;	O
he	O
begun	O
a	O
quarrel	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
and	O
they	O
fought	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
beat	O
him	O
,	O
notwithstanding	O
which	O
he	O
challeng	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
fight	O
