TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
For	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
AND	O
ON	O
The	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
31st	O
,	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
1st	O
,	O
2d	O
,	O
and	O
3d	O
,	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
1726.	O
in	O
the	O
Twelfth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
FORBES	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
,	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
,	O
Serjeant	O
at	O
Law	O
;	O
and	O
other	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
aforesaid	O
;	O
together	O
with	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bather	I-pers
John	B-pers
Cheshire	I-pers
John	B-pers
Stiff	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
John	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Hughs	I-pers
John	B-pers
Liddal	I-pers
Jasper	B-pers
Bridges	I-pers
John	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
Ambrose	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
James	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
Edmund	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Chandler	I-pers
George	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Coggin	I-pers
John	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
William	B-pers
Wyat	I-pers
John	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
William	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
Jacob	B-pers
Broughton	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Young	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Redshaw	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Blick	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Bleak	I-pers
,	I-pers
and	I-pers
Barbara	I-pers
his	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Barbara	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Feather	O
Bed	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Moor	I-pers
,	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Witness	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
had	O
Lodged	O
about	O
3	O
Quarters	O
of	O
a	O
Year	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
mist	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
suspected	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
Examin	O
'd	O
,	O
they	O
Confest	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
carried	O
them	O
out	O
to	O
pawn	O
.	O
The	O
Man	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
but	O
the	O
Woman	O
being	O
under	O
the	O
Power	O
and	O
Direction	O
of	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Accquitted	O
her	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Velvet	O
Palls	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
l.	O
a	O
Velvet	O
Coverlet	O
,	O
36	O
Pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
75	O
Yards	O
of	O
Crape	O
,	O
12	O
Yards	O
of	O
Alamode	O
Silk	O
,	O
12	O
Pounds	O
of	O
Wax	O
Lights	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Salver	O
,	O
a	O
Night	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Peruque	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Say	I-pers
,	O
August	O
4	O
last	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Say	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
Servant	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
not	O
coming	O
as	O
usual	O
to	O
shut	O
the	O
Shop	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
not	O
to	O
open	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
it	O
made	O
me	O
Suspicious	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
he	O
that	O
had	O
rob	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
,	O
I	O
spread	O
a	O
large	O
number	O
of	O
Advertisements	O
,	O
wherein	O
I	O
describ	O
'd	O
his	O
Person	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
he	O
was	O
Apprehended	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Forestreet	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
Having	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Advertisements	O
to	O
disperse	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Red	O
Cross	O
Street	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Park	O
Southwark	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
appearing	O
like	O
an	O
Undertakers	O
Servant	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
him	O
a	O
proper	O
Person	O
to	O
deliver	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Bills	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
one	O
accordingly	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
observing	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
very	O
much	O
answer	O
'd	O
the	O
Description	O
of	O
the	O
Person	O
I	O
wanted	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Opinion	O
was	O
strengthen	O
'd	O
,	O
by	O
seeing	O
him	O
have	O
a	O
Silver	O
Salver	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
great	O
fancy	O
Friend	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
are	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
looking	O
for	O
,	O
-	O
how	O
came	O
you	O
by	O
that	O
Salver	O
.	O
He	O
made	O
but	O
a	O
shuffling	O
Answer	O
,	O
which	O
heightning	O
my	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
I	O
search	O
'd	O
him	O
farther	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
several	O
Pair	O
of	O
Black	O
Silk	O
Gloves	O
,	O
3	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
l.	O
which	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
part	O
of	O
what	O
was	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Say	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
Frances	B-pers
alias	I-pers
Mary	I-pers
Blacket	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Whittle	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
August	O
6	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Whittle	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
Between	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Moon	O
shining	O
very	O
clearly	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
Black-Horse-Yard	B-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
White	I-place
Chappel-Bars	I-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
2	O
Men	O
seiz	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
Swore	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
deliver	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
;	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
see	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
,	O
and	O
thrust	O
her	O
Hand	O
into	O
my	O
Breeches	O
,	O
took	O
out	O
my	O
Watch	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Men	O
Swore	O
they	O
'd	O
kill	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
there	O
till	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
gone	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
About	O
7	O
the	O
same	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
leave	O
the	O
Watch	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
pawn	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
knowledge	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
(	O
for	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
Goods	O
to	O
me	O
before	O
,	O
)	O
and	O
thinking	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
honestly	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
in	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
about	O
2	O
hours	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
describ	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
might	O
probably	O
find	O
her	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Half	O
Moon	O
Ale	O
House	O
in	O
Petticoat	O
Lane	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
New-Prison	O
,	O
she	O
confest	O
that	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Hands	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Walnut-Tree-Yard	O
in	O
Bishops-gate-Street	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
there	O
accordingly	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Allison	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Black	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ginger	I-pers
,	O
August	O
16	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ginger	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
Horse	O
from	O
Northall	B-place
Common	I-place
,	O
and	O
coming	O
to	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
offering	O
him	O
to	O
Sale	O
,	O
I	O
cheapen	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
8	O
l.	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
enquir	O
'd	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
his	O
Brother	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Blankets	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Benjamen	B-pers
Beddow	I-pers
,	O
July	O
18	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Christian	B-pers
Tool	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Mackenzie	I-pers
,	O
August	O
8	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Prentice	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bay	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Street	I-pers
,	O
August	O
10	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Grey	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Hanson	I-pers
,	O
August	O
10	O
.	O
The	O
Witnesses	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
Two	O
or	O
Three	O
Days	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Hanson	O
lost	O
his	O
Horse	O
from	O
Chelmsford	B-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
to	O
buy	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
times	O
bade	O
Money	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
he	O
agreed	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Hanson	O
for	O
the	O
Price	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
15	O
Guineas	O
,	O
but	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
ride	O
a	O
little	O
turn	O
with	O
the	O
Horse	O
to	O
try	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Hanson	O
granting	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Shilling	O
earnest	O
,	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
liked	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
immediately	O
pay	O
him	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
mounting	O
,	O
he	O
rode	O
directly	O
(	O
in	O
about	O
two	O
Hours	O
time	O
)	O
to	O
the	O
Bull	O
Inn	O
in	O
White	O
Chappel	O
,	O
where	O
Mr.	O
Street	O
the	O
other	O
Prosecutor	O
dwelt	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
been	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
times	O
about	O
buying	O
Mr	O
.	O
Streets	O
Bay	O
Gelding	O
,	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
that	O
Gelding	O
was	O
yet	O
Sold	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
answer	O
'd	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
Sold	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
at	O
Finsbury	B-place
Stables	I-place
.	O
He	O
rid	O
to	O
the	O
Cross	O
Keys	O
in	O
Grace-Church-Street	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
put	O
up	O
the	O
Grey	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
went	O
to	O
Finsbury	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
agreed	O
to	O
pay	O
him	O
14	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
for	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Shilling	O
earnest	O
,	O
but	O
geting	O
on	O
the	O
Horses	O
back	O
to	O
try	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
rode	O
quite	O
away	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
before	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutors	O
both	O
got	O
their	O
Horses	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Horses	O
,	O
and	O
intended	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
short	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
keep	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
.	O
He	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
added	O
that	O
about	O
3	O
Years	O
ago	O
,	O
his	O
Father	O
left	O
him	O
600	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
Brew-house	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
Sold	O
,	O
not	O
being	O
capable	O
to	O
manage	O
it	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
since	O
dealt	O
in	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
and	O
Brandy	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Wilcox	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
10	O
Pound	O
of	O
Beef	O
,	O
2	O
Pound	O
of	O
Cheese	O
,	O
and	O
10	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Bread	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
August	O
22	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Rimes	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
value	O
35	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Burkett	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
May	O
30	O
.	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Magdalen	B-pers
Quesnel	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Salt	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
July	O
21	O
.	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Cundell	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Richard	B-pers
Clevely	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
Field	O
near	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
15	O
s.	O
July	O
25	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Clevely	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
About	O
4	O
a	O
Clock	O
on	O
Monday	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
drink	O
at	O
the	O
New	O
Spaw	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
kept	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Sanderson	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
others	O
were	O
playing	O
at	O
Skettles	O
,	O
I	O
made	O
one	O
among	O
them	O
,	O
we	O
afterwards	O
went	O
to	O
Cards	O
.	O
Cundell	O
lost	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
no	O
Money	O
left	O
,	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
pay	O
4	O
d.	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
in	O
pretence	O
of	O
returning	O
the	O
Civility	O
,	O
would	O
needs	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
me	O
over	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
then	O
about	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
Turner	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
the	O
same	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
bear	O
us	O
company	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
near	O
Lambs	B-place
Conduit	I-place
,	O
they	O
took	O
notice	O
of	O
some	O
Candles	O
that	O
appear	O
'd	O
at	O
a	O
distance	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
for	O
laying	O
a	O
Wager	O
about	O
what	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Town	O
those	O
Lights	O
were	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
'd	O
lay	O
no	O
Wagers	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
Turner	O
catch	O
'd	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
D	O
-	O
ye	O
but	O
you	O
shall	O
,	O
-	O
Nay	O
Gentlemen	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
If	O
I	O
must	O
buy	O
the	O
Hare	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
took	O
away	O
my	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
's	O
so	O
Drunk	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
wont	O
remember	O
what	O
's	O
become	O
of	O
his	O
Money	O
.	O
-	O
You	O
're	O
Mistaken	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
both	O
;	O
if	O
you	O
'll	O
give	O
me	O
my	O
Money	O
again	O
,	O
all	O
shall	O
be	O
well	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
ye	O
do	O
n't	O
,	O
Look	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Spaw	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
enquir	O
'd	O
after	O
them	O
.	O
There	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
somebody	O
that	O
knew	O
Cundell	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
taken	O
that	O
Day	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
that	O
when	O
Cundell	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
he	O
discover	O
'd	O
Turner	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
an	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Sanderson	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Evening	O
before	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
rob	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Drunk	O
and	O
very	O
abusive	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
forced	O
him	O
to	O
lay	O
the	O
Wagers	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
got	O
his	O
Money	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Place	O
where	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
was	O
near	O
some	O
Houses	O
in	O
Lambs	O
Conduit	O
Fields	O
,	O
where	O
a	O
Watch	O
was	O
kept	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
call	O
out	O
.	O
And	O
said	O
farther	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
but	O
by	O
their	O
Cloaths	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Deal	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
7	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
value	O
39	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Applebury	I-pers
,	O
March	O
31	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Childbed	O
Linnen	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
July	O
28	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Simonds	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Weeden	I-pers
,	O
July	O
19	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Heppard	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Shirts	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Hankerchiefs	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Grimes	I-pers
,	O
August	O
17	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Haddocks	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Sieves	O
of	O
Cherries	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
June	O
11	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Conner	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
60	O
pound	O
of	O
Solder	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
St.	I-pers
John	I-pers
late	O
Viscount	O
Bolingbroke	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Gilbert	B-pers
Tempest	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tea	O
Pot	O
,	O
a	O
Mugg	O
,	O
a	O
Canister	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Emery	B-pers
Tempest	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Careless	I-pers
,	O
July	O
14	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Cartwright	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
25	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Chauvin	I-pers
,	O
3	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
79	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Chauvin	I-pers
Jun	O
.	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Chavin	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
Servant	O
,	O
he	O
lighted	O
me	O
to	O
Bed	O
about	O
a	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
suppose	O
came	O
afterwards	O
into	O
my	O
Room	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
asleep	O
,	O
for	O
when	O
I	O
waked	O
I	O
mist	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
Till	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Breeches	O
;	O
-	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
mist	O
79	O
l.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Till	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Parger	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Abergavenny	O
in	O
Wales	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
leave	O
this	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
Hands	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
granted	O
;	O
He	O
courted	O
a	O
young	O
Woman	O
soon	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
his	O
discourse	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
Pater-noster	B-place
Row	I-place
,	O
was	O
his	O
Brother	O
.	O
She	O
sent	O
thither	O
privately	O
to	O
enquire	O
of	O
the	O
truth	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
that	O
means	O
he	O
was	O
discover	O
'd	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Spurling	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
7	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Strong	I-pers
,	O
July	O
29	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Barret	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Frazier	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
20	O
Yards	O
of	O
Straw	O
Ground	O
Brocaded	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Moone	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
,	O
in	O
their	O
Shop	O
,	O
June	O
1	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
appear	O
'd	O
thus	O
.	O
The	O
Silk	O
was	O
lost	O
from	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Messieurs	O
Moore	O
and	O
Stone	O
,	O
the	O
Queens	B-place
Head	I-place
and	I-place
Anchor	I-place
on	I-place
Ludgate-hill	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
Not	O
long	O
after	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
Mercers	O
Shop	O
,	O
the	O
backside	O
of	O
St.	O
Clements	O
,	O
to	O
cheapen	O
some	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Silk	O
was	O
missing	O
.	O
These	O
Women	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
their	O
Profession	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
often	O
at	O
Several	O
Shops	O
in	O
that	O
Neighbourhood	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
pretty	O
well	O
known	O
.	O
He	O
acquainted	O
several	O
Shopkeepers	O
thereabouts	O
with	O
his	O
loss	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
long	O
before	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Woman	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
making	O
another	O
Tour	O
;	O
He	O
gave	O
the	O
Mercer	O
notice	O
,	O
who	O
traced	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
-	O
Johnson	O
a	O
Victualler	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Thistle	O
and	O
Crown	O
,	O
in	O
Denmark	O
Court	O
.	O
Where	O
he	O
searched	O
for	O
his	O
Goods	O
to	O
no	O
purpose	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Brocaded	O
Silk	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
made	O
into	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
Lin	O
'd	O
with	O
a	O
Pink	O
colour	O
'd	O
Mantua	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Gown	O
to	O
be	O
hers	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
Maker	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
George	O
Ale-house	O
by	O
Stocks	O
Market	O
,	O
(	O
a	O
House	O
frequented	O
by	O
Weavers	O
,	O
)	O
but	O
her	O
Husband	O
being	O
a	O
Journey-man	O
Shooe-maker	O
,	O
he	O
thought	O
such	O
a	O
Gown	O
was	O
too	O
fine	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
threatned	O
to	O
burn	O
it	O
,	O
to	O
prevent	O
which	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
persuaded	O
Johnson	O
to	O
let	O
it	O
lye	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
.	O
Several	O
Mercers	O
were	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
they	O
knew	O
the	O
Silk	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Moone	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
that	O
number	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Brocade	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
thus	O
made	O
her	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
Holland	O
Trader	O
for	O
Several	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
a	O
large	O
Acquaintance	O
,	O
Moll	O
Burton	O
,	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Wilds	I-pers
Maid	O
,	O
)	O
brought	O
me	O
this	O
Brocade	O
to	O
sell	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
shew	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
some	O
,	O
who	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
the	O
Figure	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
accident	O
a	O
Mug	O
of	O
Drink	O
was	O
Spilt	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
damaged	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
thrown	O
upon	O
my	O
Hands	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
pawn	O
my	O
Goods	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Ravenscroft	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Fenton	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Holloway	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Hafield	I-pers
,	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
that	O
Brocade	O
,	O
till	O
it	O
was	O
shewn	O
me	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Moone	O
,	O
at	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
in	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
her	O
self	O
spoke	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
(	O
i.e	O
.	O
Stole	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
Jane	O
Holmes	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
40	O
Yards	O
of	O
Pink	O
Colour	O
'd	O
Mantua	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Matth.ew	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
,	O
May	O
1	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Herbert	O
,	O
I	O
remember	O
the	O
missing	O
of	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Pink	O
Mantua	O
,	O
and	O
believe	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
Lining	O
to	O
the	O
Brocade	O
is	O
a	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
was	O
we	O
make	O
our	O
own	O
Goods	O
;	O
We	O
make	O
them	O
,	O
as	O
this	O
is	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
broader	O
than	O
usual	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Barton	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Lodging	O
in	O
Black	O
Fryers	O
,	O
between	O
3	O
and	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
something	O
very	O
good	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.Herbert	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
I	O
cheapen	O
'd	O
some	O
Straw	O
colour	O
'd	O
Mantua	O
for	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
they	O
asked	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
d.	O
a	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
offer	O
'd	O
them	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
In	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Pink	O
Mantua	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
away	O
undiscover	O
'd	O
.	O
We	O
measur	O
'd	O
it	O
at	O
her	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
there	O
was	O
42	O
Yards	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
equally	O
divided	O
.	O
She	O
bade	O
me	O
3	O
s.	O
for	O
my	O
half	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
more	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
'd	O
line	O
her	O
Gown	O
with	O
part	O
of	O
her	O
own	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
this	O
Lining	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
afterwards	O
sold	O
my	O
half	O
to	O
Ann	O
Green	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Katherine	B-pers
Fitzpatrick	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Green	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Boswell	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
19	O
Yards	O
of	O
Green	O
Damask	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Gifford	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Ravenell	I-pers
,	O
in	O
their	O
Shop	O
,	O
July	O
29	O
.	O
1724	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Gifford	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
Damask	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Drawer	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
the	O
Golden	B-place
Lamb	I-place
on	I-place
Ludgate-hill	I-place
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
me	O
out	O
.	O
-	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Giffords	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
red	O
Damask	O
.	O
While	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Men	O
were	O
shewing	O
us	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
went	O
backwards	O
to	O
fetch	O
more	O
Pieces	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
open	O
a	O
Drawer	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
drawn	O
from	O
under	O
the	O
Counter	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Green	O
Damask	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
her	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
pinn	O
'd	O
up	O
.	O
-	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
she	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Theodosia	O
Kirk	O
to	O
pawn	O
.	O
Theodosia	B-pers
Kirk	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Green	O
Damask	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
her	O
Cousin	O
Madam	O
Cately	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
the	O
Widow	O
of	O
a	O
Mercer	O
that	O
broke	O
.	O
I	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Martin	O
in	O
Black	O
Fryers	O
,	O
who	O
lent	O
me	O
6	O
Guineas	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
at	O
3	O
d.	O
in	O
the	O
Pound	O
for	O
a	O
Month	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Silk	O
of	O
Moll	O
.	O
Burton	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
Katherine	O
Fitzpatrick	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
.	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
10	O
Yards	O
of	O
Green	O
Sat	O
tin	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Moone	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
,	O
in	O
their	O
Shop	O
,	O
February	O
10	O
.	O
1724-5	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Stone	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
Two	O
Women	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
Black	O
and	O
White	O
Three	O
Quarter	O
Mantua	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
they	O
came	O
from	O
Reading	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
knowing	O
several	O
in	O
that	O
Town	O
,	O
it	O
occasion	O
'd	O
a	O
pretty	O
deal	O
of	O
Discourse	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
we	O
were	O
talking	O
,	O
my	O
Prentice	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Green	O
Sattin	O
in	O
a	O
Wrapper	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
sent	O
him	O
for	O
,	O
to	O
my	O
Lady	O
Withringtons	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
it	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
.	O
-	O
When	O
the	O
Women	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
put	O
the	O
Sattin	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
laid	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Counter	O
;	O
-	O
We	O
search	O
'd	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
find	O
nothing	O
but	O
the	O
Wrapper	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Shop	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
some	O
Ash	O
colour	O
'd	O
Silk	O
;	O
We	O
had	O
some	O
talk	O
about	O
Reading	O
.	O
The	O
Boy	O
brought	O
in	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Green	O
Sattin	O
in	O
a	O
Wrapper	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Counter	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Wrapper	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
it	O
off	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
lived	O
in	O
Fleet-lane	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
often	O
saw	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Boy	O
,	O
come	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
the	O
Boy	O
would	O
know	O
me	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
intend	O
to	O
change	O
my	O
Lodging	O
.	O
-	O
She	O
carried	O
the	O
Silk	O
to	O
Kirk	O
,	O
who	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
Martins	O
Wife	O
for	O
40	O
s.	O
The	O
Apprentice	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
brought	O
home	O
the	O
Green	O
Sattin	O
in	O
a	O
Wrapper	O
;	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
while	O
2	O
Women	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
.	O
-	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
mist	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
Horse	O
in	O
Fleet-Lane	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Lawson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Katherine	B-pers
Fitzpatrick	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
50	O
Yards	O
of	O
Green	O
Mantua	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hutt	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
May	O
15	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Hutt	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
an	O
Upholster	O
's	O
Shop	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Pauls	I-place
Church-Yard	I-place
.	O
Two	O
Women	O
in	O
Riding	O
Hoods	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
Blankets	O
.	O
-	O
Mary	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
follow	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
being	O
very	O
like	O
a	O
Neighbours	O
Neice	O
,	O
I	O
mistook	O
her	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
had	O
no	O
Suspicion	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
the	O
Blankets	O
were	O
for	O
her	O
Aunt	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
yes	O
.	O
A	O
Piece	O
of	O
Green	O
Mantua	O
had	O
been	O
brought	O
home	O
that	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
in	O
haste	O
to	O
use	O
about	O
10	O
Yards	O
of	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
Bed	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Weaver	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
it	O
measured	O
,	O
I	O
cut	O
off	O
what	O
I	O
wanted	O
,	O
but	O
left	O
a	O
narrow	O
Edge	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Ticket	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
-	O
and	O
then	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
mist	O
it	O
soon	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
2	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
which	O
in	O
our	O
way	O
of	O
Speaking	O
signifies	O
to	O
go	O
a	O
Shoplifting	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
drest	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
they	O
intended	O
to	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
would	O
wait	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
Brandy	O
Shop	O
in	O
St.	O
Pauls	O
Church-Yard	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
,	O
I	O
drest	O
my	O
self	O
and	O
follow	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Brandy	O
Shop	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
them	O
;	O
The	O
Gentlewoman	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
said	O
something	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
my	O
Aunt	O
.	O
Fitzpatrick	O
took	O
the	O
Silk	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
her	O
Hood	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
long	O
Edging	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
cut	O
in	O
little	O
Escallops	O
,	O
that	O
had	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
betray	O
'd	O
us	O
.	O
She	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Yard	O
,	O
but	O
Sarah	O
Turner	O
was	O
angry	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
have	O
got	O
4	O
s.	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Moone	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
When	O
Turner	O
was	O
first	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
advis	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
make	O
herself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
then	O
be	O
persuaded	O
.	O
She	O
afterwards	O
escaped	O
from	O
the	O
Officer	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
again	O
in	O
the	O
Gate-house	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
re-taken	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
cry	O
'd	O
and	O
confest	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
this	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
beg	O
'd	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
get	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
transported	O
,	O
and	O
wish	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
my	O
Advice	O
,	O
but	O
then	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
late	O
,	O
for	O
upon	O
his	O
Majesties	O
Promise	O
of	O
Pardon	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Reward	O
of	O
50	O
l.	O
publish	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Gazette	O
,	O
Mary	O
Burton	O
had	O
voluntarily	O
surrendred	O
herself	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Katherine	B-pers
Fitzpatrick	I-pers
,	O
was	O
a	O
4th	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
63	O
Yards	O
of	O
Modena	O
,	O
and	O
Pink	O
Italian	O
Mantua	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joshua	B-pers
Feary	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
February	O
20	O
.	O
1724-5	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Lowfield	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
that	O
the	O
Silk	O
was	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Fearys	O
Shop	O
,	O
the	O
Wheatsheaf	B-place
and	I-place
Star	I-place
on	I-place
Ludgate-hill	I-place
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
I	O
agreed	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
we	O
pitch	O
'd	O
upon	O
Mr.	O
Fearys	O
Shop	O
,	O
Fitzpatrick	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
went	O
in	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
Ash	O
colour	O
'd	O
Mantua	O
;	O
Turner	O
came	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
wanted	O
Silk	O
for	O
an	O
Apron	O
.	O
The	O
Man	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
back	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
,	O
Fitzpatrick	O
lifted	O
up	O
the	O
Counter	O
Lid	O
,	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Silk	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
Apron	O
;	O
We	O
divided	O
it	O
equally	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
21	O
Yards	O
a	O
piece	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Moone	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
Turner	O
Confest	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
Burton	O
and	O
Fitzpatrick	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
Stole	O
that	O
Silk	O
.	O
Mr.Justice	O
Vaughan	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
Several	O
of	O
the	O
Shoplifters	O
were	O
brought	O
before	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
examin	O
'd	O
.	O
Holms	O
would	O
fain	O
have	O
been	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
named	O
I	O
believe	O
near	O
40	O
Robberies	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
having	O
been	O
transported	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
admit	O
her	O
.	O
Then	O
Turner	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
become	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
confest	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
committed	O
several	O
Felonies	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
Fitzpatrick	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
ever	O
been	O
in	O
Newgate	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
one	O
Night	O
indeed	O
a	O
walking	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
with	O
a	O
Girl	O
(	O
Molly	B-pers
Grainge	I-pers
)	O
and	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
pick	O
'd	O
us	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
us	O
to	O
the	O
Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
hang	O
'd	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
Mary	O
Burton	O
came	O
in	O
a	O
voluntary	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Information	O
that	O
she	O
then	O
gave	O
me	O
,	O
agrees	O
in	O
every	O
particular	O
with	O
what	O
she	O
now	O
swears	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
Theodosia	B-pers
Kirk	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
commonly	O
talk	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
,	O
that	O
Turner	O
had	O
hang	O
'd	O
Molly	B-pers
Grainge	I-pers
(	O
who	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
Water-lane	O
)	O
by	O
perswading	O
her	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
herself	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
concerned	O
.	O
Fitzpatrick	O
call	O
'd	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
sold	O
Geneva	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
kept	O
a	O
Cook	O
's	O
Shop	O
in	O
Fore-street	O
.	O
And	O
being	O
cross	O
'd	O
question	O
'd	O
,	O
they	O
acknowledge	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
long	O
had	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
Shoplifter	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Holms	I-pers
,	O
a	O
3d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Hester	B-pers
Dobbins	I-pers
,	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
January	O
7	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Reedman	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
Three	O
Women	O
(	O
Mary	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
)	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
Mistresses	O
Shop	O
(	O
the	O
Indian	B-place
Queen	I-place
in	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
)	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
wanted	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Satin	O
.	O
My	O
Mistress	O
had	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
the	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
Ale	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
call	O
'd	O
away	O
,	O
she	O
sat	O
it	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
Side	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
says	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Women	O
,	O
Tis	O
very	O
cold	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
went	O
and	O
sat	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
the	O
Cup	O
was	O
mist	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Shop	O
,	O
Holms	O
and	O
I	O
lookt	O
upon	O
some	O
Sattin	O
,	O
but	O
Robinson	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Fire	O
Side	O
,	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
threw	O
the	O
Ale	O
into	O
the	O
Ashes	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
her	O
Lap	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
Sattin	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
to	O
prevent	O
the	O
Man	O
from	O
casting	O
his	O
Eye	O
towards	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
he	O
should	O
miss	O
the	O
Cup	O
.	O
-	O
Robinson	O
went	O
out	O
first	O
,	O
Holms	O
stole	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Sattin	O
,	O
and	O
follow	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
last	O
.	O
Robinson	O
's	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
she	O
acknowledged	O
the	O
stealing	O
of	O
the	O
Cup	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
Hannah	B-pers
Briton	I-pers
for	O
4	O
s.	O
an	O
Ounce	O
.	O
Guilty	O
each	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Jane	O
Holms	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
4th	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	O
Robinson	O
,	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
80	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cherry	O
colour	O
'd	O
Mantua	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bourn	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Harper	I-pers
,	O
in	O
their	O
Shop	O
,	O
December	O
24	O
.	O
And	O
Hannah	B-pers
Briton	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stoln	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Bourn	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
three	O
.	O
Women	O
came	O
to	O
their	O
Shop	O
,	O
the	O
Crown	B-place
and	I-place
Anchor	I-place
the	I-place
Corner	I-place
of	I-place
York-street	I-place
,	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
mist	O
soon	O
after	O
they	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
Holms	O
and	O
Robinson	O
and	O
myself	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
,	O
under	O
Pretence	O
of	O
buying	O
a	O
Riding-hood	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
Reality	O
to	O
steal	O
any	O
Thing	O
that	O
we	O
could	O
.	O
A	O
piece	O
of	O
Persian	O
lay	O
under	O
some	O
Riding-hoods	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
Holms	O
took	O
it	O
;	O
we	O
all	O
got	O
off	O
safe	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
agreed	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
Silk	O
to	O
Hannah	B-pers
Briton	I-pers
's	O
who	O
then	O
kept	O
the	O
Bull-Head	O
Ale-House	O
,	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Newtoners-Lane	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
accordingly	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
we	O
had	O
spoke	O
with	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Silk	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
well	O
acquainted	O
with	O
our	O
Profession	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
that	O
by	O
saying	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
spoke	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
we	O
meant	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
stole	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
measur	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
us	O
a	O
Shilling	O
a	O
Yard	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bourn	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Briton	I-pers
sent	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
me	O
5	O
Guineas	O
not	O
to	O
prosecute	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
'd	O
make	O
me	O
farther	O
Satisfaction	O
when	O
she	O
got	O
out	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
was	O
worth	O
a	O
Thousand	O
Pound	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Briton	O
:	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Ambler	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
l.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mayhew	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Low	I-pers
,	O
August	O
20	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Hamsted	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Bell	O
a	O
Fishmonger	O
,	O
in	O
Old	B-place
Fish-street	I-place
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
a	O
Saturday	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
George	B-pers
Mademan	I-pers
to	O
look	O
after	O
the	O
Shop	O
.	O
Before	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
a	O
Man	O
to	O
,	O
whom	O
I	O
ow	O
'd	O
a	O
Shilling	O
for	O
doing	O
some	O
Work	O
,	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
pay	O
him	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
I	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Money	O
Drawer	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
out	O
a	O
Bag	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
two	O
Bank	O
Notes	O
for	O
50	O
l.	O
and	O
above	O
10	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
I	O
paid	O
him	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
Bag	O
up	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Ticket	O
Porter	O
,	O
and	O
plying	O
thereabouts	O
,	O
was	O
then	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Mony	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
my	O
Return	O
,	O
asked	O
if	O
any	O
Body	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
no	O
.	O
I	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Drawer	O
,	O
and	O
mist	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
for	O
the	O
two	O
Notes	O
they	O
were	O
put	O
into	O
another	O
Till	O
,	O
and	O
Mademan	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Mademan	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
away	O
to	O
go	O
of	O
an	O
Errand	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
my	O
Wife	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
.	O
Margery	B-pers
Mademan	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
When	O
my	O
Husband	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
began	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
Flourishes	O
,	O
and	O
play	O
his	O
Tricks	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
the	O
Money	O
Drawer	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
take	O
any	O
Thing	O
away	O
.	O
Why	O
ar'n't	O
you	O
an	O
Impudent	O
Boldface	O
now	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
pray	O
what	O
Business	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
meddle	O
with	O
the	O
Drawer	O
,	O
Why	O
ye	O
old	O
Bitch	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
what	O
's	O
that	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
meddle	O
with	O
what	O
I	O
please	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
began	O
to	O
pull	O
and	O
haul	O
,	O
and	O
touzle	O
me	O
about	O
at	O
such	O
a	O
Rate	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
'd	O
'	O
a	O
blest	O
your	O
self	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
fain	O
'	O
a	O
'	O
had	O
me	O
'	O
a	O
'	O
gone	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
to	O
lye	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
short	O
he	O
grew	O
so	O
rude	O
and	O
obstropolus	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
forc	O
'd	O
to	O
run	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
I	O
had	O
certainly	O
been	O
ravisht	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
sad	O
thing	O
in	O
my	O
old	O
Age	O
,	O
for	O
alackaday	O
I	O
have	O
liv	O
'd	O
these	O
Threescore	O
and	O
Fourteen	O
Years	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
never	O
ravish	O
'd	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
what	O
became	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Laurance	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
About	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
teizing	O
the	O
old	O
Beggar	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
Thieving	O
Dog	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Business	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
thus	O
made	O
his	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
for	O
the	O
old	O
Beggar	O
Woman	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
minded	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
little	O
Fun	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
say	O
,	O
That	O
if	O
you	O
take	O
an	O
old	O
Woman	O
and	O
bite	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Ear	O
,	O
she	O
'll	O
serve	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
a	O
young	O
Girl	O
.	O
Some	O
Witnesses	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
farther	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
Mademan	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
were	O
first	O
charged	O
with	O
this	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
lately	O
been	O
sent	O
to	O
Bridewel	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Candlestick	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Susan	B-pers
Dennis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Strainer	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Leather	O
Pocket	O
Case	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
July	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
,	O
Modesty	O
not	O
suffering	O
him	O
to	O
appear	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Isabel	B-pers
Lucky	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
Lucky	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
Alexander	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
,	O
16	O
Ounces	O
humane	O
Hair	O
,	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pocket	O
Book	O
,	O
August	O
11	O
,	O
and	O
Jones	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stoln	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
got	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
to	O
Cats	O
Hole	O
in	O
St.	O
Catherines	O
.	O
In	O
my	O
Wastecoat	O
Pocket	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
Hair	O
in	O
a	O
Bladder	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pocket	O
Book	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
Pocket	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
coming	O
under	O
Aldgate	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Isabel	O
Lucky	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Tap	O
upon	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
a	O
little	O
farther	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
she	O
walked	O
sometimes	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
behind	O
,	O
till	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
Goodman's-Yard	B-place
,	O
and	O
there	O
she	O
turned	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
Porch	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
after	O
her	O
.	O
Well	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
what	O
will	O
you	O
give	O
me	O
now	O
.	O
Why	O
indeed	O
my	O
Dear	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
no	O
Money	O
at	O
present	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
you	O
'll	O
oblige	O
me	O
so	O
and	O
so	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
make	O
ye	O
Amends	O
the	O
next	O
Time	O
I	O
see	O
ye	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
live	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
Way	O
off	O
.	O
Truly	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
do	O
nothing	O
without	O
ready	O
Money	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
afford	O
to	O
trust	O
.	O
-	O
Indeed	O
my	O
Dear	O
you	O
must	O
for	O
this	O
once	O
.	O
-	O
Will	O
you	O
be	O
as	O
good	O
as	O
your	O
Word	O
then	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
indeed	O
I	O
will	O
Child	O
.	O
-	O
Well	O
then	O
if	O
I	O
must	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
laid	O
her	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
afraid	O
of	O
daubing	O
her	O
Cloths	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
as	O
dirty	O
a	O
Pickle	O
as	O
she	O
is	O
in	O
now	O
.	O
But	O
however	O
as	O
foul	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
deny	O
but	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
commit	O
that	O
filthy	O
Sin	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
in	O
the	O
Heat	O
of	O
Action	O
,	O
she	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
The	O
Watch	O
,	O
the	O
Watch	O
is	O
a	O
coming	O
,	O
get	O
away	O
and	O
shift	O
for	O
your	O
self	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
got	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
turn	O
'd	O
my	O
Back	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
up	O
my	O
Breeches	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Watch	O
not	O
coming	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Porch	O
and	O
felt	O
for	O
her	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
felt	O
in	O
my	O
Pockets	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
all	O
was	O
lost	O
.	O
Well	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
to	O
my	O
self	O
,	O
The	O
Bitch	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
taken	O
away	O
every	O
Thing	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
about	O
me	O
;	O
my	O
very	O
Hair	O
and	O
Bladder	O
and	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
undone	O
Man	O
!	O
So	O
having	O
no	O
body	O
to	O
make	O
my	O
Apology	O
to	O
,	O
I	O
e'en	O
walk	O
'd	O
home	O
in	O
that	O
Condition	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
the	O
Things	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Porch	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hardy	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Barber	O
in	O
White	O
Chappel	O
,	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Sarah	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
offer	O
'd	O
me	O
some	O
of	O
this	O
Hair	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
I	O
examin	O
'd	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
Isabel	B-pers
Lucky	I-pers
,	O
who	O
waited	O
hard	O
by	O
.	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
,	O
Pocket	O
Book	O
upon	O
Jones	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
search	O
being	O
made	O
after	O
Lucky	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
at	O
Billingsgate	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Gravesend	O
Tilt	O
Boat	O
,	O
just	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
going	O
off	O
.	O
Lucky	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Goodman	O
's	O
Yard	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dark	O
,	O
She	O
Kick	O
'd	O
something	O
soft	O
before	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
Hair	O
.	O
Jones	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
that	O
meeting	O
Lucky	O
,	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
Hair	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
telling	O
her	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Hair	O
from	O
a	O
Sailor	O
of	O
her	O
Acquaintance	O
.	O
Lucky	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
Jones	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Sadler	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
42	O
Napkins	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cornwall	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
August	O
20	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Ridley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeaner	O
for	O
receiving	O
2	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
stoln	O
by	O
Persons	O
,	O
unknown	O
,	O
she	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stoln	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hatchet	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
by	O
cutting	O
his	O
Throat	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
dyed	O
,	O
August	O
3	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
about	O
9	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
Lane	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
sitting	O
upon	O
a	O
Bench	O
very	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
-	O
What	O
would	O
you	O
have	O
good	O
Woman	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
?	O
-	O
Give	O
me	O
a	O
little	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
tell	O
you	O
a	O
Secret	O
.	O
-	O
What	O
Secret	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
Why	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
Do	O
n't	O
ye	O
know	O
that	O
a	O
Man	O
was	O
murder	O
'd	O
two	O
Nights	O
ago	O
,	O
Yes	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
Well	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
held	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
while	O
his	O
Throat	O
was	O
cut	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
coming	O
by	O
,	O
bid	O
her	O
have	O
a	O
care	O
what	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
might	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
answer	O
'd	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
value	O
that	O
,	O
she	O
wanted	O
a	O
Nights	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
Hopes	O
to	O
get	O
one	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
an	O
other	O
Place	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
kill	O
'd	O
.	O
Several	O
Witnesses	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
quite	O
beside	O
her	O
Senses	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
say	O
any	O
Thing	O
when	O
she	O
got	O
drunk	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Head	O
had	O
been	O
so	O
disorder	O
'd	O
by	O
some	O
unlucky	O
Blows	O
that	O
she	O
receiv	O
'd	O
from	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
who	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
beat	O
her	O
unmercifully	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Halfpennyworth	O
of	O
Geneva	O
would	O
make	O
her	O
speak	O
all	O
the	O
Extravagancies	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
in	O
Bedlam	O
.	O
A	O
Watchman	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Man	O
was	O
found	O
Murder	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
August	O
about	O
Midnight	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
on	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
from	O
10	O
a	O
Clock	O
till	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lay	O
on	O
a	O
Bulk	O
near	O
his	O
Stand	O
,	O
with	O
Guinea	O
Pigs	O
in	O
a	O
Basket	O
.	O
Other	O
Witnesses	O
spoke	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
Peticoat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
August	O
8	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Stanford	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Fender	O
,	O
a	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
a	O
Bible	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
.	O
August	O
18	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Cocker	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Cowen	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Niles	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Wise	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
Cocker	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Peticoat	O
.	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Mings	I-pers
,	O
July	O
2	O
.	O
and	O
Niles	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stoln	O
.	O
Cocker	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
Niles	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Sherman	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
Timothy	B-pers
Sherman	I-pers
,	O
Vintner	O
,	O
of	O
Covent-Garden	B-place
;	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Mark	B-pers
Shovat	I-pers
,	O
by	O
mixing	O
a	O
great	O
Quantity	O
of	O
white	O
Arsnick	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
deadly	O
Poison	O
,	O
with	O
Milk	O
and	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
sending	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
drank	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
thereby	O
Poisoned	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
variously	O
Sick	O
and	O
Distemper	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
languish	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
24th	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Month	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Disney	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
visit	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
lying	O
upon	O
his	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
complaining	O
of	O
a	O
Cold	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
by	O
crossing	O
the	O
Water	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Return	O
from	O
Dr.	O
Lloyd	O
's	O
Feast	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
Pain	O
in	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
Limbs	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
since	O
been	O
taken	O
with	O
a	O
Purging	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Times	O
a	O
Day	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
partly	O
remov	O
'd	O
his	O
Pains	O
.	O
I	O
advis	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
Rhubarh	O
to	O
take	O
off	O
the	O
Purging	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
Monday	O
following	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
them	O
pretty	O
easy	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
Purging	O
gone	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
again	O
about	O
10	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
if	O
he	O
might	O
venture	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Knights-Bridge	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
I	O
advis	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
stay	O
a	O
little	O
longer	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
breathing	O
Sweat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
declining	O
Feaver	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
thought	O
would	O
prove	O
intermiring	O
.	O
I	O
administred	O
a	O
proper	O
Draught	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
easier	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
being	O
Tuesday	O
;	O
but	O
about	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
his	O
Feaver	O
return	O
'd	O
,	O
which	O
left	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
breathing	O
Sweat	O
as	O
before	O
.	O
About	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
his	O
Servant	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Vial	O
of	O
Liquid	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Godfrey	O
,	O
the	O
Chymist	O
,	O
with	O
Orders	O
to	O
take	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
Pint	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
much	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Emulsion	O
made	O
with	O
Orange-Flower	O
Water	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
Servant	O
that	O
if	O
Mr.	O
Godfrey	O
sent	O
it	O
,	O
his	O
Master	O
might	O
take	O
it	O
safely	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
visit	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
understood	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
thrice	O
of	O
that	O
Emulsion	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
Pint	O
each	O
Time	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
very	O
faint	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
above	O
40Sou	O
the	O
preceeding	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
extreamly	O
grip	O
'd	O
and	O
crampt	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Ambrose	B-pers
Godfrey	I-pers
to	O
know	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Godfrey	O
appear	O
'd	O
very	O
much	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
assur	O
'd	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
sent	O
any	O
Thing	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
Rhubarb	O
,	O
Diascordium	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Cordial	O
I	O
Draught	O
,	O
he	O
sometimes	O
grew	O
worse	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
mended	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
Sunday	O
following	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
voided	O
Blood	O
,	O
and	O
dyed	O
on	O
the	O
succeeding	O
Wednesday	O
Morning	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
open	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
discover	O
no	O
Symptom	O
of	O
Poison	O
in	O
his	O
Stomach	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
indeed	O
a	O
little	O
enflamed	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
what	O
commonly	O
happens	O
from	O
a	O
violent	O
Dysentery	O
or	O
Diarrhaea	O
.	O
The	O
Guts	O
were	O
lined	O
with	O
Blood	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
observe	O
an	O
Excoriation	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Blood	O
taken	O
out	O
;	O
But	O
However	O
that	O
Emulsion	O
,	O
might	O
possibly	O
be	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
,	O
for	O
though	O
I	O
am	O
satisfied	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
Poisonous	O
put	O
into	O
it	O
,	O
yet	O
there	O
might	O
be	O
something	O
which	O
might	O
throw	O
him	O
into	O
that	O
violent	O
Laxity	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Belcher	O
the	O
Apothecary	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Stomach	O
of	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
no	O
Inflamation	O
till	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Duodenum	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
enflam	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
great	O
Guts	O
were	O
fill	O
'd	O
with	O
Blood	O
and	O
Excrement	O
,	O
and	O
bylous	O
Juices	O
,	O
as	O
is	O
usual	O
in	O
Dysentries	O
which	O
ensue	O
Diarrheas	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
not	O
the	O
least	O
Sympton	O
of	O
Poison	O
,	O
and	O
verily	O
believe	O
that	O
he	O
dy	O
'd	O
a	O
natural	O
Death	O
;	O
I	O
tasted	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Emulsion	O
that	O
was	O
left	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
grown	O
a	O
little	O
Acid	O
with	O
keeping	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
discover	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
thing	O
Poisonous	O
,	O
or	O
Hurtful	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Cooling	O
Innocent	O
Draught	O
,	O
made	O
of	O
Almonds	O
,	O
Barly-water	O
,	O
Orange	O
Flower-water	O
,	O
Sugar	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
harmless	O
Ingredients	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
advis	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
make	O
some	O
tryal	O
of	O
its	O
Effect	O
,	O
upon	O
a	O
Puppy	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
Kitling	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
enough	O
left	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
Experiment	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
think	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
the	O
Deceaseds	O
Death	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Godfrey	O
the	O
Chymist	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
sending	O
that	O
Emulsion	O
to	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
try	O
'd	O
several	O
Chymical	O
Experiments	O
upon	O
what	O
was	O
left	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
least	O
Poisonous	O
,	O
Purgative	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
way	O
Hurtfull	O
.	O
Dr.	O
Hollings	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
the	O
Potion	O
was	O
not	O
Poisonous	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
a	O
natural	O
violent	O
Looseness	O
,	O
that	O
put	O
an	O
End	O
to	O
the	O
Life	O
of	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Smith	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Bedford	O
Coffee-House	O
,	O
on	O
Monday	O
Evening	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
an	O
elderly	O
Gentlewoman	O
and	O
a	O
Girl	O
,	O
came	O
thither	O
.	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Attack	O
made	O
into	O
Punch	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
,	O
they	O
desir	O
'd	O
something	O
Cool	O
,	O
I	O
brought	O
her	O
a	O
Drink	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
call	O
Oziat	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
drank	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
liked	O
it	O
so	O
well	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
a	O
Pint	O
away	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
she	O
paid	O
a	O
Shilling	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Jarret	I-pers
the	O
Prisoners	O
Cook	O
maid	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
Night	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
my	O
Mistress	O
call	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Mary	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
trust	O
no	O
body	O
but	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
last	O
Night	O
at	O
the	O
Bedford	O
Coffee	O
house	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
drank	O
some	O
pleasant	O
Cool	O
Liquor	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
brought	O
this	O
Pint	O
home	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Shovat	O
at	O
next	O
Door	O
.	O
is	O
ill	O
of	O
a	O
Feaver	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
will	O
do	O
him	O
good	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
I	O
'd	O
have	O
you	O
carry	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
-	O
hold	O
the	O
Bottle	O
by	O
the	O
Neck	O
,	O
that	O
your	O
Hands	O
may	O
heat	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
little	O
as	O
possible	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
when	O
bethinking	O
my	O
self	O
,	O
Pray	O
Madam	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
should	O
ask	O
who	O
sent	O
it	O
,	O
what	O
shall	O
I	O
say	O
-	O
Why	O
tell	O
them	O
says	O
my	O
Mistress	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
brought	O
it	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Godfrey	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Shovat	O
must	O
drink	O
half	O
a	O
Pint	O
to	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
Mr.	O
Godfrey	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
House	O
very	O
angry	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
who	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
carried	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
his	O
Name	O
,	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Shovat	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
(	O
as	O
my	O
Mistress	O
had	O
Instructed	O
me	O
;	O
)	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
Black	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
whom	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
several	O
times	O
is	O
Mr.	O
Shovats	O
Company	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Godfrey	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
Pasion	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
was	O
enough	O
to	O
ruin	O
his	O
Credit	O
,	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Shovat	O
was	O
dangerously	O
ill	O
after	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
threatn	O
'd	O
me	O
hard	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
me	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
me	O
discover	O
who	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
black	O
was	O
,	O
my	O
Master	O
Bail	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
grew	O
worse	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sadly	O
frighten	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Mistress	O
appear	O
'd	O
very	O
much	O
concern	O
'd	O
,	O
who	O
would	O
have	O
thought	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
that	O
that	O
Innocent	O
Emulsion	O
,	O
should	O
have	O
done	O
the	O
poor	O
Gentleman	O
any	O
hurt	O
.	O
But	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
be	O
afraid	O
,	O
you	O
can	O
come	O
to	O
no	O
harm	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
beg	O
of	O
you	O
,	O
not	O
to	O
tell	O
who	O
you	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
,	O
for	O
if	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
known	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
ruin	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
's	O
what	O
my	O
Neighbours	O
want	O
.	O
Now	O
I	O
knew	O
as	O
how	O
that	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
had	O
been	O
saying	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
my	O
Master	O
had	O
been	O
Jealous	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Shovat	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
thought	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
told	O
that	O
my	O
Mistress	O
had	O
sent	O
him	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
it	O
might	O
make	O
them	O
talk	O
but	O
the	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
bring	O
her	O
into	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
trouble	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
still	O
stood	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
black	O
gave	O
the	O
Bottle	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Shovat	O
dy	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
it	O
all	O
came	O
out	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
that	O
there	O
had	O
ever	O
been	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
,	O
or	O
Malice	O
between	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
mistress	O
,	O
he	O
frequented	O
our	O
House	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
Day	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
ill.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hanford	I-pers
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
Servant	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
maid	O
brought	O
the	O
Emulsion	O
,	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
it	O
came	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Godfrey	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
order	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
it	O
carry	O
'd	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
Master	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
being	O
in	O
haste	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
before	O
my	O
Mistress	O
came	O
down	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Shovat	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
Married	O
to	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
about	O
10	O
Months	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
down	O
to	O
receive	O
this	O
Emulsion	O
,	O
which	O
my	O
Man	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
was	O
left	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Sherman	O
's	O
Cook	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
given	O
her	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
tall	O
Man	O
in	O
black	O
,	O
who	O
order	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
it	O
came	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Godfrey	O
;	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
if	O
Mr.	O
Godfrey	O
knew	O
Mr.	O
Shovat	O
had	O
a	O
Feavor	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
yes	O
,	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
strong	O
Waters	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
an	O
innocent	O
Cool	O
thing	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
might	O
taste	O
if	O
I	O
pleas	O
'd	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
had	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
my	O
Husband	O
,	O
who	O
being	O
willing	O
to	O
have	O
Mr.	O
Disneys	O
Opinion	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
-	O
Mr.	O
Disney	O
sent	O
word	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
it	O
was	O
innocent	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
it	O
came	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Godfrey	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
venture	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
set	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
Bed-side	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
three	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
my	O
Spouse	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
it	O
-	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
very	O
ill	O
about	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
violent	O
purging	O
,	O
the	O
Gripes	O
,	O
Cramps	O
,	O
and	O
Fainting	O
Fits	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
continued	O
till	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
voided	O
several	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Blood	O
,	O
and	O
dy	O
'd	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
Morning	O
following	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
thus	O
made	O
her	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
acknowledge	O
that	O
I	O
sent	O
that	O
Liquor	O
to	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
drank	O
of	O
it	O
my	O
self	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
very	O
harmeless	O
,	O
Cooling	O
,	O
and	O
Pleasant	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
might	O
do	O
good	O
,	O
or	O
at	O
least	O
no	O
hurt	O
to	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
illness	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
I	O
bore	O
a	O
respect	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
a	O
Customer	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
very	O
Civil	O
Gentleman	O
.	O
His	O
free	O
and	O
familiar	O
Carriage	O
,	O
had	O
indeed	O
created	O
some	O
uneasiness	O
in	O
my	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
a	O
few	O
spitefull	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
had	O
taken	O
occasion	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
liberal	O
of	O
their	O
Censures	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
I	O
was	O
Cautious	O
,	O
in	O
sending	O
him	O
that	O
small	O
present	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Shaw	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
Body	O
,	O
the	O
Day	O
after	O
his	O
Death	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
not	O
the	O
least	O
Symptom	O
of	O
Poison	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
thing	O
but	O
what	O
is	O
common	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
natural	O
Effect	O
of	O
Diarrhea	O
and	O
Dysentries	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
many	O
in	O
the	O
like	O
Case	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
drank	O
half	O
a	O
mouthfull	O
of	O
the	O
Emulsion	O
that	O
was	O
left	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
did	O
me	O
no	O
hurt	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
drank	O
it	O
all	O
if	O
desir	O
'd	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
frequently	O
drank	O
the	O
same	O
sort	O
at	O
the	O
Coffee-house	O
,	O
and	O
can	O
depend	O
upon	O
my	O
taste	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
mixt	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
Half	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
small	O
Beer	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
other	O
cool	O
Liquid	O
,	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
like	O
distemper	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Vevers	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Wyersdell	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
19	O
s.	O
August	O
24	O
.	O
Benjamen	O
Wyersdale	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
,	O
my	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Kinswoman	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
at	O
my	O
Lord	O
Castlemains	O
Gardens	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
returning	O
home	O
in	O
a	O
Hackney	O
Coach	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
bright	O
Moon	O
light	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
Nine	O
o'Clock	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
upon	O
Cambridge-Heath	B-place
,	O
(	O
between	O
Bethnal	O
Green	O
and	O
Hackney	O
Road	O
.	O
)	O
and	O
there	O
a	O
Man	O
upon	O
a	O
black	O
Horse	O
(	O
or	O
Mare	O
)	O
rode	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Coachman	O
,	O
and	O
holding	O
out	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
cry	O
'd	O
Stand	O
!	O
G	O
-	O
D	O
-	O
ye	O
Stand	O
!	O
or	O
I	O
'll	O
Shoot	O
ye	O
through	O
the	O
Head	O
.	O
My	O
Wife	O
sat	O
facing	O
the	O
Horses	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
.	O
The	O
Man	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
Claping	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
my	O
Breast	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
ye	O
deliver	O
.	O
I	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
Civil	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
my	O
Money	O
.	O
Come	O
,	O
Come	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
D	O
-	O
ye	O
says	O
he	O
deliver	O
immediately	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
about	O
a	O
11	O
s.	O
and	O
some	O
Halfpence	O
.	O
G	O
-	O
D	O
-	O
ye	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
wheres	O
your	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
your	O
Watch	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
,	O
Why	O
then	O
by	O
G	O
-	O
I	O
'll	O
kill	O
ye	O
says	O
he	O
.	O
I	O
assure	O
ye	O
Sir	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
given	O
you	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
would	O
not	O
use	O
me	O
ill.	O
-	O
My	O
Wife	O
then	O
gave	O
me	O
6	O
or	O
8	O
s.	O
more	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
still	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
ye	O
whereas	O
your	O
Gold	O
!	O
your	O
Gold	O
!	O
I	O
must	O
have	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
again	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
about	O
Cock	O
'd	O
his	O
Pistol	O
,	O
clapt	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
Breast	O
,	O
Swore	O
he	O
'd	O
Shoot	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
pull	O
'd	O
the	O
Triger	O
.	O
The	O
Flint	O
struck	O
Fire	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
priming	O
was	O
blown	O
away	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
off	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
let	O
the	O
Coach	O
pass	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
quickly	O
came	O
up	O
again	O
and	O
searched	O
my	O
Fob	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
round	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
fallen	O
in	O
a	O
Ditch	O
,	O
but	O
recovering	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
rode	O
off	O
towards	O
Bednall	O
Green	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
drove	O
homeward	O
,	O
Shoreditch	O
way	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
Swear	O
positively	O
,	O
though	O
I	O
did	O
think	O
then	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
such	O
a	O
Face	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
remember	O
where	O
-	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
talking	O
of	O
my	O
loss	O
,	O
and	O
described	O
the	O
Man	O
:	O
and	O
Horse	O
as	O
exactly	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
people	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Bricklayer	O
,	O
and	O
liv	O
'd	O
not	O
far	O
from	O
the	O
Black	O
Day	O
,	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
,	O
and	O
keeps	O
his	O
Mare	O
in	O
a	O
Stable	O
near	O
my	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
since	O
seen	O
that	O
Mare	O
,	O
and	O
believe	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Wyersdale	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
that	O
rob	O
'd	O
my	O
Husband	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
knowledge	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
Husband	O
so	O
that	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
-	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
both	O
by	O
his	O
voice	O
and	O
Face	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
so	O
certain	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
very	O
Man	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
never	O
more	O
fully	O
satisfied	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
remember	O
when	O
my	O
Husband	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Watch	O
not	O
Ring	O
's	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
know	O
him	O
,	O
What	O
!	O
Such	O
a	O
Man	O
as	O
you	O
,	O
go	O
abroad	O
without	O
Watch	O
or	O
Rings	O
?	O
William	B-pers
Stout	I-pers
the	O
Coachman	O
.	O
Confirm	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Wyersdells	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
thus	O
added	O
.	O
The	O
Man	O
was	O
tall	O
and	O
thin	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
dark	O
brown	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
light	O
Wig	O
.	O
He	O
rode	O
upon	O
a	O
black	O
Beast	O
with	O
a	O
white	O
Bridle	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
exactly	O
observe	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
because	O
his	O
Back	O
was	O
mostly	O
towards	O
me	O
-	O
On	O
the	O
Friday	O
following	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Mare	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
do	O
really	O
believe	O
that	O
the	O
Mare	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
quite	O
so	O
certain	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
However	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
talk	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Mare	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Stable	O
,	O
that	O
Evening	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
Committed	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
boy	O
had	O
taken	O
her	O
out	O
to	O
Water	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wyersdale	O
again	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
boy	O
was	O
Examin	O
'd	O
about	O
the	O
Mare	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
rode	O
her	O
to	O
Bartholomew	O
Fair	O
,	O
and	O
return	O
'd	O
about	O
7	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
Most	O
of	O
this	O
Deposition	O
was	O
corroberuted	O
by	O
George	B-pers
English	I-pers
,	O
who	O
sat	O
upon	O
the	O
Coach-box	O
with	O
this	O
Witness	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
another	O
Place	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
who	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Pitman	O
din	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
they	O
went	O
together	O
through	O
Swan	O
Fields	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
some	O
work	O
to	O
do	O
.	O
There	O
he	O
found	O
his	O
Boy	O
,	O
and	O
(	O
it	O
being	O
Bartholomew	O
Day	O
)	O
gave	O
him	O
half	O
a	O
Holiday	O
,	O
and	O
order	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
ride	O
his	O
Mare	O
out	O
to	O
water	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
.	O
-	O
From	O
thence	O
they	O
two	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Barnets	O
at	O
Jeremy	O
's	O
Ferry	O
,	O
she	O
owing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
some	O
Money	O
for	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
him	O
5	O
Guineas	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Receipt	O
which	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
They	O
staid	O
drinking	O
there	O
till	O
after	O
7	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
.	O
and	O
then	O
came	O
away	O
together	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
overtaken	O
near	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
of	O
Mutton	O
,	O
by	O
Mr	O
Herbert	O
a	O
Bricklayer	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Salmon	O
and	O
Ball	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
then	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
past	O
8	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
not	O
sat	O
long	O
before	O
a	O
Hackney	O
Coach	O
came	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Coachman	O
told	O
somebody	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Coach	O
had	O
been	O
rob	O
'd	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
Highwayman	O
upon	O
Cambridge	O
heath	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
)	O
about	O
9	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
they	O
all	O
three	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
where	O
Mr.	O
Herbert	O
left	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
Pitman	O
kept	O
him	O
Company	O
till	O
a	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
upon	O
any	O
Horse	O
or	O
Mare	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
The	O
Coachman	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Salmon	O
and	O
Ball	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
somebody	O
that	O
the	O
Coach	O
had	O
been	O
rob	O
'd	O
upon	O
Cambridge-heath	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Boy	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
between	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
he	O
rode	O
the	O
Mare	O
out	O
to	O
water	O
upon	O
Cambridge	O
heath	O
and	O
return	O
'd	O
at	O
7	O
or	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
lockt	O
the	O
Mare	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Stable	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
she	O
was	O
out	O
no	O
more	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pyner	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Frances	B-pers
Baylion	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
August	O
4	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hood	O
,	O
Napkins	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Neckcloth	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Powler	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Markham	I-pers
.	O
July	O
11	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Anthony	B-pers
Newel	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Nevitt	I-pers
,	O
by	O
aiding	O
and	O
abetting	O
William	B-pers
Leneve	I-pers
(	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
)	O
who	O
had	O
bear	O
and	O
bruis	O
'd	O
the	O
said	O
Nevit	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languish	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
14	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
It	O
thus	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
Leuneve	O
had	O
Arrested	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
who	O
making	O
some	O
resistance	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
beat	O
him	O
violently	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
(	O
who	O
were	O
likewise	O
Bailiff	O
s	O
)	O
to	O
his	O
aid	O
.	O
They	O
at	O
last	O
carry	O
'd	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
dismal	O
bloody	O
condition	O
,	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Cross	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
Southwark	B-place
,	O
at	O
whose	O
Suit	O
he	O
was	O
Arrested	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
Debt	O
which	O
originally	O
was	O
no	O
more	O
then	O
two	O
Pence	O
half-penny	O
,	O
but	O
now	O
with	O
the	O
Charges	O
,	O
amounted	O
to	O
24	O
Shillings	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
discharged	O
by	O
a	O
Friend	O
of	O
his	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
he	O
complain	O
'd	O
to	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
that	O
Leneve	O
had	O
bruis	O
'd	O
and	O
lick	O
'd	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
privy	O
Parts	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
never	O
be	O
his	O
own	O
Man	O
again	O
.	O
A	O
Feaver	O
succeeded	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
dy	O
'd	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
.	O
The	O
searchers	O
that	O
view	O
'd	O
his	O
Body	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
bruised	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Blood	O
worked	O
out	O
at	O
his	O
Nose	O
and	O
Mouth	O
in	O
an	O
unusual	O
Manner	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Privities	O
were	O
swell	O
'd	O
as	O
big	O
as	O
their	O
3	O
Fists	O
,	O
and	O
turn	O
'd	O
as	O
black	O
as	O
a	O
Hat	O
.	O
Mr	O
Thomson	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
Deceas'ds	O
Body	O
4	O
Days	O
after	O
his	O
Death	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
bloated	O
and	O
all	O
over	O
black	O
and	O
blue	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Grissel	O
of	O
his	O
Nose	O
broke	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
perceive	O
any	O
violent	O
means	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Jeremy	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Ates	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Gossip	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Jessup	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Ravishing	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
her	O
Will	O
,	O
carnally	O
knowing	O
Mary	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Haddon	I-pers
,	O
August	O
11	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
2d	O
,	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
Assaulting	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
Ravish	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	B-pers
Haddon	I-pers
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Haddon	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
About	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
from	O
my	O
Lodgings	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
Swallow-Street	O
to	O
Totenham	B-place
Court	I-place
Fair	I-place
,	O
with	O
my	O
Mistress	O
and	O
her	O
Children	O
;	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
to	O
hear	O
a	O
blind	O
Fidler	O
play	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
up	O
comes	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
both	O
Coachmen	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
'd	O
have	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
at	O
last	O
agreed	O
to	O
.	O
Then	O
Jessup	O
got	O
upon	O
the	O
Coach-Box	O
,	O
and	O
Yates	O
put	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
in	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
Windows	O
.	O
Jessup	O
drove	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
sadly	O
frighted	O
,	O
but	O
knew	O
not	O
how	O
to	O
help	O
my	O
self	O
,	O
for	O
Yates	O
turn	O
'd	O
up	O
my	O
Peticoats	O
,	O
and	O
lean	O
'd	O
his	O
Breast	O
so	O
hard	O
against	O
my	O
Mouth	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
cry	O
out	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
Legs	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
about	O
his	O
Middle	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
main	O
Force	O
lay	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
carnal	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
my	O
Body	O
,	O
without	O
my	O
Consent	O
.	O
And	O
so	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Condition	O
,	O
that	O
what	O
with	O
the	O
Fright	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
with	O
having	O
my	O
Mouth	O
stopt	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
with	O
striving	O
and	O
strugling	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
quite	O
spent	O
,	O
and	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Senses	O
,	O
and	O
ready	O
to	O
die	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
recover	O
my	O
self	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Jessup	O
,	O
was	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Coach	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
ravish	O
'd	O
me	O
as	O
the	O
other	O
had	O
done	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
,	O
when	O
all	O
was	O
over	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
Breath	O
enough	O
to	O
cry	O
out	O
Murder	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
into	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
Road	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
used	O
me	O
so	O
barbarously	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
forc	O
'd	O
to	O
call	O
at	O
a	O
House	O
by	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
home	O
till	O
near	O
11	O
a	O
Clock	O
.	O
My	O
Husband	O
saw	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
out	O
of	O
Order	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
Company	O
I	O
had	O
kept	O
till	O
that	O
time	O
of	O
Night	O
.	O
I	O
not	O
telling	O
him	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
he	O
began	O
to	O
rave	O
and	O
curse	O
like	O
a	O
Madman	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
that	O
he	O
'd	O
never	O
lie	O
with	O
me	O
again	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
satisfy	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
besides	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
given	O
me	O
the	O
Clap	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Delavot	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Midwife	O
;	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
Mary	O
Hadden	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
force	O
used	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
by	O
her	O
Husband	O
or	O
any	O
other	O
Person	O
,	O
is	O
more	O
than	O
I	O
can	O
tell	O
.	O
Other	O
Witnesses	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Mary	O
Hadden	O
had	O
told	O
them	O
how	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
serv	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
very	O
ill	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Yates	O
thus	O
made	O
his	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutors	O
Wife	O
was	O
my	O
old	O
Acquaintance	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
Lain	O
with	O
her	O
many	O
and	O
many	O
a	O
good	O
Time	O
.	O
-	O
About	O
7	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
and	O
Jessup	O
were	O
talking	O
,	O
we	O
saw	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Fair	O
standing	O
with	O
another	O
Man	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
ye	O
Molly	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
d	O
'ye	O
do	O
Jerry	O
says	O
she	O
.	O
Now	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
out	O
of	O
Business	O
,	O
the	O
Coach	O
belonged	O
to	O
Jessup	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
several	O
Turns	O
from	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
Pound	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
drink	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
agreed	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
Molly	O
left	O
the	O
other	O
Man	O
and	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
Alehouse	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
except	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
with	O
her	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
And	O
she	O
was	O
well	O
enough	O
pleas	O
'd	O
with	O
what	O
past	O
,	O
for	O
if	O
any	O
thing	O
had	O
troubled	O
her	O
she	O
might	O
have	O
made	O
Noise	O
enough	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
People	O
enow	O
in	O
the	O
Road	O
agoing	O
from	O
the	O
Fair	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
lain	O
with	O
her	O
a	O
whole	O
Week	O
together	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
King's-Arms	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
lane	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
got	O
upon	O
the	O
Loose	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
cost	O
me	O
7	O
half	O
Crowns	O
in	O
Expences	O
.	O
-	O
We	O
have	O
bedded	O
together	O
twenty	O
and	O
twenty	O
Times	O
in	O
a	O
Hayloft	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Longfield	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
Year	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
ago	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
Yates	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Haddon	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Kings	O
Head	O
in	O
New	O
Bond	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
Mothers	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
bring	O
none	O
of	O
his	O
Whores	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
in	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
bitter	O
cold	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
bethought	O
my	O
self	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
into	O
our	O
Hayloft	O
.	O
He	O
and	O
she	O
lay	O
at	O
one	O
end	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
at	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
bid	O
him	O
lye	O
close	O
and	O
keep	O
her	O
warm	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
for	O
all	O
that	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
pleas	O
'd	O
his	O
Fancy	O
,	O
he	O
fell	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
crept	O
softly	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
she	O
was	O
willing	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
keep	O
her	O
warm	O
too	O
,	O
for	O
in	O
short	O
I	O
did	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
her	O
before	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
and	O
her	O
about	O
a	O
Year	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
do	O
with	O
him	O
as	O
before	O
,	O
for	O
now	O
she	O
was	O
married	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
half	O
a	O
Year	O
ago	O
,	O
Yates	O
and	O
she	O
lay	O
together	O
in	O
his	O
Hayloft	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Teeling	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Monday	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
apprehended	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Hadden	I-pers
was	O
sitting	O
upon	O
a	O
Bench	O
in	O
Piccadlly	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
.	O
-	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
Yates	O
did	O
what	O
he	O
pleas	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
should	O
never	O
have	O
concern	O
'd	O
herself	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
sent	O
another	O
Man	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Nugent	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
Yates	O
put	O
Mary	B-pers
Hadden	I-pers
into	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
go	O
in	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
seem	O
'd	O
very	O
well	O
pleas	O
'd	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Jessup	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
meddle	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
as	O
he	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
one	O
Door	O
,	O
she	O
got	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
them	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Roushey	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Linnen	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
April	O
15	O
.	O
and	O
Judith	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stoln	O
.	O
July	O
26	O
.	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Aldridge	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Samuel	I-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
returning	O
from	O
Transportation	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Expiration	O
of	O
7	O
Years	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
transported	O
in	O
August	O
27.	O
in	O
the	O
10th	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
20	O
lb	O
of	O
Iron	O
,	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
.	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
a	O
Watchman	O
at	O
the	O
7	O
Dials	O
,	O
where	O
quarreling	O
with	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
she	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
returning	O
from	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Hoff	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Ounce	O
of	O
human	O
Hair	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Horse	O
Hair	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Maurice	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
.	O
August	O
18	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Floyd	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
an	O
empty	O
House	O
belonging	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Lead	O
from	O
the	O
Freehold	O
,	O
August	O
1	O
,	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Long	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
old	O
Shoes	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Blind	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
knowingly	O
putting	O
off	O
a	O
counterfeit	O
Guinea	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bradford	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Smathers	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Joseph	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
him	O
of	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
a	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
40	O
s.	O
August	O
1	O
Joseph	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
About	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
Barbican	O
I	O
knew	O
'em	O
to	O
be	O
loose	O
Fellows	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
Design	O
upon	O
me	O
.	O
For	O
I	O
had	O
put'em	O
in	O
the	O
Crown-Office	O
,	O
and	O
sworn	O
the	O
Peace	O
against	O
them	O
for	O
threatening	O
my	O
Death	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
sworn	O
Treason	O
against	O
me	O
for	O
cursing	O
the	O
King	O
;	O
and	O
therefore	O
being	O
afraid	O
they	O
would	O
do	O
me	O
a	O
Mischief	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Bell-Inn	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
People	O
there	O
was	O
,	O
2	O
Rogues	O
laid	O
in	O
wait	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
staid	O
about	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Ostler	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Old	B-place
Street	I-place
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
might	O
go	O
back	O
then	O
for	O
I	O
believ	O
'd	O
I	O
was	O
pretty	O
safe	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
gone	O
far	O
before	O
they	O
set	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
took	O
away	O
my	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
40	O
s.	O
Then	O
they	O
put	O
a	O
Rope	O
about	O
my	O
Neck	O
,	O
and	O
haul	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
Bridge	O
,	O
that	O
parts	O
Cripplegate	O
Parish	O
and	O
Shoreditch	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
they	O
try	O
'd	O
the	O
Rope	O
to	O
the	O
Rail	O
of	O
the	O
Bridge	O
,	O
and	O
turn	O
'd	O
me	O
over	O
towards	O
the	O
Ditch	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
me	O
hanging	O
there	O
by	O
my	O
self	O
But	O
how	O
long	O
I	O
hung	O
,	O
or	O
who	O
cut	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
or	O
whether	O
I	O
was	O
cut	O
down	O
or	O
no	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
self	O
lying	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
the	O
Rope	O
about	O
my	O
Neck	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
deplorable	O
Condition	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bacchus	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
Between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Man	O
making	O
lamentable	O
Moan	O
by	O
the	O
Bridge	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
Moonlight	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
lying	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
with	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
Cord	O
(	O
I	O
think	O
its	O
a	O
Garter	O
)	O
about	O
his	O
Neck	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
piece	O
about	O
the	O
Rail	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
two	O
Men	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
hang	O
'd	O
him	O
afterwards	O
,	O
but	O
who	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
unhang	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
was	O
more	O
than	O
he	O
could	O
inform	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
Ostler	O
at	O
the	O
Bell	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
said	O
2	O
Men	O
,	O
that	O
had	O
swore	O
Treason	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
dog	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
Gun	O
loaded	O
with	O
small	O
Shot	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
-	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Old-street	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
safe	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
could	O
go	O
the	O
back	O
Ways	O
,	O
and	O
miss	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
of	O
good	O
Credit	O
,	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
another	O
Place	O
when	O
this	O
pretended	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Barns	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Barns	I-pers
and	O
their	O
Servants	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Smathers	O
(	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
Weaver	O
,	O
and	O
lodges	O
at	O
their	O
House	O
in	O
Holloway	O
street	O
,	O
Shoredich	O
,	O
)	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
Room	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
Isaac	O
Spring	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Birch	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Bradford	O
was	O
drinking	O
at	O
Birch	O
's	O
House	O
(	O
the	O
Clothworkers	O
Arms	O
,	O
in	O
Red-Lyon	O
street	O
,	O
White	O
Chappel	O
)	O
from	O
7	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
till	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
past	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
They	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
Men	O
of	O
good	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
order	O
'd	O
Harrison	O
to	O
be	O
committed	O
to	O
Newgate	O
for	O
Perjury	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Bather	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Tun	O
of	O
Rags	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
l.	O
and	O
25	O
Pound	O
of	O
Leather	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Corfield	I-pers
,	O
July	O
14	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Surjabell	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Peticoat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Bodice	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
July	O
1	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dalton	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Doulton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeaner	O
,	O
in	O
Assaulting	O
Joseph	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
commit	O
Sodomy	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
then	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
About	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
sleep	O
upon	O
a	O
Bench	O
in	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
park	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
waked	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
walked	O
together	O
.	O
He	O
squeez	O
'd	O
my	O
Hand	O
hug	O
'd	O
me	O
in	O
his	O
Arms	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
me	O
his	O
dear	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
drink	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
guest	O
at	O
what	O
he	O
wanted	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
Friends	O
House	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
Crown	B-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Strand	I-place
)	O
opposite	O
York-house	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Drawer	O
aside	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
Sodomite	O
,	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
shew	O
us	O
a	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
bring	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
stand	O
privately	O
,	O
and	O
watch	O
my	O
Gentlemans	O
motions	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Drawer	O
did	O
accordingly	O
.	O
This	O
Evidence	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
others	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
related	O
the	O
indecent	O
and	O
filthy	O
behaviour	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elias	B-pers
Northcott	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Norgate	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
black	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stubblefield	I-pers
,	O
August	O
8	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2nd	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
brown	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
August	O
8	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
3d	O
,	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
bay	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Witherly	I-pers
,	O
August	O
9	O
.	O
Mr	O
Jenkins	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
black	O
Gelding	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
Aldersgate	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stublefield	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
that	O
Gelding	O
was	O
his	O
Mothers	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
lost	O
from	O
Waltham	B-place
Abby	I-place
.	O
Thomas	O
Green	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
brown	O
Gelding	O
from	O
Waltham	B-place
Abby	I-place
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Possession	O
of	O
Mr	O
.	O
Staples	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Staples	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
bought	O
that	O
Horse	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wetherwell	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
bay	O
Gelding	O
from	O
Waltham	B-place
Abby	I-place
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
at	O
Mr	O
.	O
Whites	O
Stables	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
John	O
Street	O
.	O
And	O
John	B-pers
Sibley	I-pers
(	O
Mr	O
.	O
Whites	O
Man	O
)	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
that	O
Gelding	O
was	O
brought	O
thither	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
thus	O
made	O
his	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
Horses	O
of	O
another	O
Man	O
to	O
Sell	O
for	O
him	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
they	O
made	O
such	O
a	O
noise	O
and	O
an	O
uproar	O
about	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Man	O
heard	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
never	O
meet	O
with	O
him	O
since	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Boswell	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
him	O
of	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
July	O
14	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
merry	O
making	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
coming	O
a	O
long	O
Bolton	B-place
Street	I-place
in	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
between	O
1	O
and	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
clap	O
'd	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
Pot	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Alehouse	O
open	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
I	O
would	O
,	O
-	O
he	O
follow	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
took	O
my	O
Hat	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
strike	O
up	O
my	O
heels	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
meant	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
or	O
Bayonet	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
which	O
,	O
and	O
Swore	O
he	O
'd	O
stick	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
after	O
me	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
-	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
another	O
Fact	O
3	O
Weeks	O
after	O
.	O
A	O
Watchman	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ask	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
for	O
a	O
Pet	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
follow	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
a	O
Moon	O
light	O
Morning	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Beaven	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Biffen	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bed	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Grates	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
How	I-pers
,	O
July	O
16	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Akers	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Ayres	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
July	O
17	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Coats	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hepworth	I-pers
,	O
August	O
6	O
Guilty	O
4s	O
.	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Gordon	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Curtains	O
,	O
and	O
1	O
Sheet	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Parr	I-pers
,	O
July	O
18	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Ellmore	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
in	O
attempting	O
to	O
Commit	O
Sodomy	O
,	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Curry	I-pers
,	O
aged	O
18	O
,	O
April	O
15	O
,	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
Curry	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
Newgate	O
for	O
the	O
like	O
Crime	O
,	O
The	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
12.	O
George	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
Frances	B-pers
Blacket	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Allison	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Cartwright	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
,	O
Katherine	B-pers
Fitzpatrick	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
Elias	B-pers
Northcott	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Boswell	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Aldridge	I-pers
.	O
Martin	O
,	O
Holms	O
,	O
Fitzpatrick	O
and	O
Turner	O
pleaded	O
their	O
Bellies	O
.	O
A	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
being	O
impannell	O
'd	O
found	O
that	O
neither	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
with	O
quick	O
Child	O
.	O
Whipt	O
5.	O
Phillip	B-pers
Conner	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Barber	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Surjabell	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
.	O
Transportation	O
15.	O
William	B-pers
Blick	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
Christian	B-pers
Yool	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Simonds	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
,	O
Gilbert	B-pers
Tempest	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Deal	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Spurling	I-pers
,	O
Hannnah	B-pers
Briton	I-pers
,	O
Isabel	B-pers
Lucky	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Cocker	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pyner	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Akers	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Coats	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dolton	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
Baker	O
)	O
to	O
stand	O
upon	O
the	O
Pillory	O
at	O
Charing-Cross	O
,	O
pay	O
a	O
Fine	O
of	O
20	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
suffer	O
6	O
Months	O
imprisonment	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Floyd	I-pers
to	O
pay	O
a	O
Fine	O
of	O
5	O
Marks	O
,	O
suffer	O
6	O
Months	O
imprisonment	O
,	O
and	O
find	O
Security	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
for	O
3	O
Years	O
afterwards	O
.	O
