TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
For	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
AND	O
ON	O
And	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
and	O
Thursday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
17th	O
and	O
18th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
1727	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Thirteenth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
EYLES	I-pers
,	O
Bart	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Fortescue	O
,	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
,	O
Serjeant	O
at	O
Law	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
.	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
aforesaid	O
:	O
Together	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Gerrard	B-pers
Hatley	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Killingworth	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Mealing	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Say	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Northover	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Purse	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Greenoway	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Staygold	I-pers
,	O
Bryan	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Leach	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Craddock	I-pers
,	O
Allin	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Wildair	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Shakespear	I-pers
,	O
Arthur	B-pers
Rawlinson	I-pers
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
Bryan	B-pers
Payne	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bridgeman	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Wallbrook	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Padlock	O
,	O
Value	O
2	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Niel	I-pers
and	I-pers
Comp	I-pers
and	O
Comp	O
.	O
-	O
Savil	O
a	O
Watchman	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Person	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
took	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
having	O
taken	O
the	O
Padlock	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Warehouse-Door	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Person	O
getting	O
away	O
,	O
he	O
,	O
with	O
another	O
Watchman	O
searched	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
8	O
picklock	O
Keys	O
in	O
his	O
Coat	O
Pocket	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Padlock	O
he	O
dropt	O
in	O
the	O
Channel	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
afterwards	O
found	O
.	O
This	O
Evidence	O
was	O
corroborated	O
by	O
the	O
Deposition	O
of	O
Ball	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
Watchman	O
;	O
who	O
assisted	O
in	O
taking	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
The	O
picklock	O
Keys	O
and	O
the	O
Padlock	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
appearing	O
by	O
several	O
plain	O
Circumstances	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Padlock	O
with	O
a	O
design	O
to	O
rob	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
single	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pound	O
of	O
Thread	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
12	O
Yards	O
of	O
Gartering	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Amos	I-pers
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Hickerton	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Wats	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Shop	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
about	O
Business	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
the	O
Goods	O
was	O
missing	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
pursued	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
Search	O
found	O
the	O
Gartering	O
in	O
his	O
Right	O
Coat	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Spicer	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
at	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Thread	O
in	O
his	O
Left	O
Coat	O
Pocket	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
thereupon	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchre	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Thomas	B-pers
Raynton	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
;	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
and	O
Chain	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
Steal	O
Seal	O
and	O
Tobacco-Box	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
coming	O
through	O
Chick-Lane	B-place
at	O
the	O
Time	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
violent	O
Manner	O
jostled	O
him	O
against	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
whilst	O
he	O
defended	O
himself	O
against	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
put	O
her	O
Hand	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
Tobacco	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
fumbled	O
about	O
his	O
Fob	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
believe	O
she	O
then	O
took	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
felt	O
it	O
gone	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
called	O
out	O
for	O
Help	O
and	O
secur	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
plain	O
to	O
the	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
Richard	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Humphreys	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
Black	O
)	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
another	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
apprehended	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
not	O
positively	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
alledged	O
that	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
was	O
not	O
worth	O
the	O
Money	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
(	O
being	O
a	O
good	O
Christan	O
)	O
begg	O
'd	O
the	O
Court	O
would	O
consider	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
but	O
an	O
Infidel	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
proving	O
the	O
Form	O
of	O
Baptism	O
had	O
been	O
administred	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
this	O
Artifice	O
was	O
but	O
of	O
little	O
Effect	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Winch	I-pers
and	O
Tho	B-pers
Modesty	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Kensington	B-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Cocks	O
and	O
5	O
Hens	O
,	O
Value	O
12	O
d.	O
each	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Kerby	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Twynam	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
coming	O
up	O
to	O
Town	O
with	O
his	O
Waggon	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
fell	O
into	O
Discourse	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
pretending	O
to	O
be	O
lame	O
,	O
would	O
fain	O
have	O
persuaded	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
ride	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
being	O
heavy	O
loaded	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
liking	O
their	O
Looks	O
,	O
would	O
not	O
suffer	O
it	O
;	O
nevertheless	O
they	O
still	O
kept	O
pace	O
with	O
the	O
Waggon	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
Side	O
of	O
Kensington	O
,	O
they	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Waggon	O
and	O
spoiled	O
several	O
New	O
Cheeses	O
,	O
afterwards	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
Fowls	O
in	O
this	O
Deponent	O
's	O
Sight	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
being	O
armed	O
with	O
3	O
Swords	O
,	O
a	O
Bayonet	O
and	O
Musket	O
,	O
he	O
thought	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
hazardous	O
to	O
resist	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
let	O
them	O
go	O
without	O
opposition	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
afterwards	O
took	O
them	O
at	O
Kensington	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
plain	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
single	O
Felony	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Linnen	O
Aprons	O
,	O
2	O
Pillowbiers	O
and	O
2	O
Towels	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
30	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Guischard	I-pers
and	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Beroe	I-pers
.	O
Margaret	O
Guischard	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
caught	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
the	O
Stairs	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
her	O
Apron	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
gave	O
so	O
slender	O
an	O
Account	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Rook	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Chiswick	B-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
(	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
set	O
a	O
curious	O
Blood	O
Stone	O
)	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
15	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Madam	B-pers
Lutridge	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
missing	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
order	O
'd	O
a	O
strict	O
Search	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
after	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
length	O
heard	O
it	O
was	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
pawn	O
'd	O
to	O
one	O
Mr	O
Granger	O
,	O
who	O
stopt	O
the	O
Box	O
and	O
secur	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Granger	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
one	O
Katharine	B-pers
Chainey	I-pers
brought	O
the	O
Box	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
not	O
believing	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
own	O
,	O
demanded	O
to	O
know	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
satisfied	O
with	O
her	O
Answer	O
,	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
stop	O
it	O
till	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
right	O
Owner	O
.	O
(	O
This	O
destroys	O
the	O
Notion	O
of	O
some	O
People	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
impossible	O
for	O
a	O
Pawnbroker	O
to	O
be	O
honest	O
.	O
)	O
Katharine	B-pers
Chainey	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
Box	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
a	O
young	O
Gentlewoman	O
had	O
occasion	O
for	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
a	O
Half	O
to	O
pay	O
her	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
borrow	O
the	O
Money	O
on	O
that	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Deponent	O
not	O
suspecting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
have	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
went	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Granger	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
her	O
coming	O
back	O
and	O
telling	O
how	O
it	O
was	O
stopt	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
at	O
first	O
she	O
would	O
sooner	O
lose	O
it	O
than	O
go	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
afterwards	O
she	O
rose	O
in	O
a	O
Passion	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
fetch	O
it	O
with	O
a	O
Ceceraro	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Granger	O
's	O
with	O
this	O
Deponent	O
,	O
and	O
telling	O
a	O
Story	O
contrary	O
to	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
told	O
before	O
,	O
this	O
Deponent	O
very	O
honestly	O
detected	O
her	O
.	O
After	O
Madam	O
Lutridge	O
came	O
and	O
owned	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
begg	O
'd	O
she	O
might	O
not	O
be	O
sent	O
to	O
Newgate	O
;	O
upon	O
her	O
Trial	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
Box	O
in	O
the	O
Coach-House	O
:	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Price	I-pers
and	O
others	O
,	O
that	O
by	O
the	O
Orders	O
of	O
Madam	O
Lutridge	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
searched	O
the	O
Coach	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
)	O
searching	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
this	O
Excuse	O
was	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
as	O
frivolous	O
.	O
She	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
her	O
Character	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Court	O
indulged	O
so	O
far	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
a	O
Hearing	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Luke	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
4	O
Velvet	O
Patterns	O
,	O
embroidered	O
with	O
Silver	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
with	O
a	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Silk	O
Girdles	O
,	O
Laces	O
and	O
Topnots	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Thoroughgood	I-pers
;	O
and	O
Katherine	B-pers
Luke	I-pers
,	O
(	O
her	O
Mother	O
)	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Mary	O
Luke	O
,	O
had	O
for	O
some	O
Time	O
been	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
missing	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
he	O
suspected	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
searching	O
her	O
Mother	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
:	O
This	O
was	O
confirmed	O
by	O
the	O
Constable	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
they	O
was	O
found	O
under	O
Lock	O
and	O
Key	O
in	O
the	O
Mother	O
's	O
Cellar	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
being	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
Katharine	O
Luke	O
,	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
Daughter	O
,	O
Mary	O
Luke	O
,	O
at	O
several	O
Times	O
bring	O
Mr.	O
Thoroughgood	O
's	O
Goods	O
,	O
not	O
only	O
those	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
but	O
Coals	O
,	O
Candles	O
,	O
Beef	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
which	O
being	O
evidently	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchre	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
into	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Langford	I-pers
,	O
with	O
a	O
Design	O
to	O
steal	O
and	O
bear	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Richard	O
Langford	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
his	O
Body	O
half	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
and	O
half	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
broke	O
a	O
Hole	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
Shutter	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
creeping	O
in	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Portman	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
suspicious	O
Person	O
:	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
Richard	B-pers
Langford	I-pers
's	O
House	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
and	O
attempted	O
to	O
be	O
robb	O
'd	O
several	O
Times	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
Night	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
:	O
sate	O
up	O
on	O
purpose	O
to	O
watch	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
seen	O
to	O
lurk	O
about	O
the	O
House	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
he	O
committed	O
this	O
Burglary	O
:	O
The	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
plain	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
2	O
Quilts	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
2	O
Looking-Glasses	O
,	O
1	O
Pewter	O
Dish	O
,	O
a	O
Copper	O
Sauce-pan	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Smoothing-Iron	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bearcroft	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
she	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
took	O
her	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
;	O
at	O
which	O
Time	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
telling	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
to	O
one	O
Clark	O
for	O
19	O
Shillings	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
brought	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
him	O
at	O
several	O
Times	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
taken	O
upon	O
them	O
in	O
all	O
19	O
Shillings	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
evidently	O
proved	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchre	I-place
's	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
30	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
he	O
confes	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
took	O
20	O
Shillings	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
in	O
costing	O
up	O
:	O
But	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
plain	O
to	O
the	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Draper	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	O
Money	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Design	O
to	O
steal	O
and	O
bear	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Money	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Watchman	O
,	O
coming	O
home	O
before	O
his	O
usual	O
Time	O
,	O
heard	O
his	O
wife	O
cry	O
out	O
Murder	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
making	O
what	O
haste	O
he	O
could	O
he	O
got	O
within	O
Doors	O
just	O
as	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
secur	O
'd	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Kimplin	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
bolted	O
the	O
Door	O
at	O
Night	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
by	O
Violence	O
wrenched	O
off	O
the	O
Staple	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
heard	O
Murder	O
cried	O
out	O
just	O
before	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
being	O
a	O
next	O
Door	O
Neighbour	O
ran	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
secured	O
.	O
Another	O
Neighbour	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
waked	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Sleep	O
with	O
the	O
Noise	O
of	O
Murder	O
,	O
Murder	O
;	O
and	O
thereupon	O
getting	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
at	O
first	O
made	O
some	O
opposition	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
Deponent	O
being	O
the	O
stronger	O
Man	O
,	O
got	O
him	O
down	O
and	O
beat	O
him	O
heartily	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
instead	O
of	O
making	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
shewed	O
such	O
distracted	O
Gestures	O
as	O
made	O
it	O
evidently	O
appear	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
his	O
right	O
Senses	O
;	O
to	O
prove	O
which	O
several	O
Persons	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
such	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
his	O
Behaviour	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
first	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
during	O
the	O
Time	O
of	O
his	O
Confinement	O
,	O
as	O
left	O
it	O
undisputable	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Non	O
compos	O
mentis	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
they	O
brought	O
in	O
their	O
Verdict	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Lunatick	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Soams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
the	O
Lord	B-pers
Newbury	I-pers
,	O
(	O
now	O
Earl	B-pers
of	I-pers
Cholmondley	I-pers
)	O
a	O
wooden	O
Buroe	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
5	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Silver	O
handle	O
Knives	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
1722	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Wemersley	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
finding	O
his	O
Lordship	O
's	O
Goods	O
missing	O
,	O
he	O
shut	O
up	O
all	O
the	O
Doors	O
,	O
and	O
commanded	O
all	O
the	O
Servants	O
to	O
appear	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
detect	O
the	O
Villany	O
,	O
but	O
Soams	O
not	O
being	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
great	O
Reason	O
to	O
believe	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
aforesaid	O
;	O
after	O
this	O
a	O
Woman	O
came	O
and	O
enquir	O
'd	O
for	O
Soams	O
,	O
which	O
Woman	O
his	O
Lordship	O
's	O
Servants	O
seized	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
telling	O
them	O
where	O
Soams	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
Lodging	O
,	O
they	O
immediately	O
went	O
thither	O
,	O
and	O
searching	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Budore	O
,	O
the	O
Locks	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Things	O
which	O
was	O
therein	O
taken	O
out	O
;	O
a	O
particular	O
Inventory	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
taken	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
lost	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
there	O
were	O
Jewels	O
,	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
of	O
great	O
Value	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Coats	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
Woman	O
came	O
and	O
enquir	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
Servants	O
of	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
Chandler	O
's	O
Shop	O
in	O
Berwick-street	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Budore	O
;	O
he	O
likewise	O
confirmed	O
the	O
other	O
Particulars	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
deposed	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Wamersley	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
3	O
Quarters	O
of	O
a	O
Year	O
,	O
and	O
during	O
that	O
Time	O
behaved	O
himself	O
very	O
orderly	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Deakons	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Hunt	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
in	O
the	O
Budore	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
came	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
Several	O
other	O
Evidences	O
appear	O
'd	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
since	O
the	O
Time	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
my	O
Lord	O
Cholmondley	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
kept	O
a	O
Barber	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
removing	O
from	O
one	O
Place	O
to	O
another	O
he	O
had	O
gone	O
by	O
several	O
Names	O
:	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Will	B-pers
Beddoe	I-pers
and	O
Will	B-pers
Boseley	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Casks	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
containing	O
27	O
Gallons	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Ewin	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
going	O
to	O
a	O
Dinner	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Adamson	O
's	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Casks	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
knowing	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Adamson	O
took	O
Beer	O
of	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
occasion	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
particular	O
Enquiry	O
after	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
,	O
that	O
though	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
the	O
Beer	O
and	O
paid	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
Brewhouse	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Hughes	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
clandestine	O
Manner	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Adamson	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Customer	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hughes	O
for	O
Strong	O
Beer	O
,	O
he	O
order	O
'd	O
his	O
Servants	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
to	O
bring	O
him	O
some	O
Small	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
3	O
Casks	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
about	O
6	O
Weeks	O
;	O
which	O
Beer	O
it	O
appeared	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
without	O
the	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Hughes	O
,	O
or	O
his	O
Clerk	O
Mr.	O
Ewin	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
accused	O
each	O
other	O
of	O
the	O
Crime	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Beddoe	O
:	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Boseley	O
:	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Cornelius	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Movements	O
of	O
two	O
Watches	O
,	O
(	O
of	O
Brass	O
)	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Wrench	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
hired	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
for	O
a	O
Year	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
converted	O
his	O
Brass	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
Use	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wrench	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
some	O
Time	O
before	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
lost	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
her	O
Husband	O
's	O
Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
suspecting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
foul	O
Practices	O
,	O
they	O
searched	O
him	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
mended	O
,	O
contrary	O
to	O
her	O
Husband	O
's	O
Knowledge	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Movements	O
of	O
the	O
Watches	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
a	O
Practice	O
or	O
taking	O
his	O
Master	O
s	O
Brass	O
in	O
a	O
clandestine	O
Manner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
His	O
Master	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
for	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
leave	O
to	O
work	O
for	O
himself	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Master	O
could	O
not	O
positively	O
deny	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Whole	O
,	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wade	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Boucher	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bartholomew	I-place
's	I-place
;	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
9	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cambrick	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
Instant	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wharton	I-pers
;	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Boucher	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
as	O
accessary	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stoln	O
:	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
Stealing	O
15	O
pair	O
of	O
Womens	O
Stockings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mr	B-pers
Theed	I-pers
;	O
and	O
John	O
Boucher	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
first	O
Indictment	O
Mr.	O
John	O
Wharton	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
and	O
pretended	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Cambrick	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
not	O
agreeing	O
about	O
the	O
Price	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
soon	O
after	O
which	O
he	O
mist	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
this	O
Elizabeth	O
Wade	O
,	O
charg	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
though	O
he	O
searched	O
her	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
them	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Wardly	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
drinking	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
(	O
at	O
the	O
Cock	O
and	O
Bottle	O
Alehouse	O
near	O
the	O
Cloysters	O
,	O
Smithfield	O
)	O
and	O
he	O
not	O
liking	O
their	O
Looks	O
,	O
said	O
to	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
they	O
been	O
here	O
?	O
They	O
are	O
but	O
just	O
now	O
come	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
,	O
my	O
Dear	O
.	O
Soon	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
being	O
gone	O
)	O
this	O
Deponent	O
heard	O
that	O
his	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Wharton	O
,	O
had	O
taken	O
Elizabeth	O
Wade	O
on	O
suspicion	O
of	O
robbing	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
searched	O
,	O
(	O
but	O
being	O
modest	O
,	O
he	O
turned	O
his	O
Face	O
away	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
pulled	O
her	O
peticoats	O
and	O
Stays	O
off	O
;	O
at	O
which	O
Time	O
he	O
told	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Man	O
with	O
her	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
a	O
Bundle	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
:	O
Upon	O
this	O
Notice	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
John	B-pers
Boucher	I-pers
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Theed	O
appeared	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Stockings	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
knew	O
by	O
the	O
Mark	O
.	O
Both	O
Indictments	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
:	O
John	O
Boucher	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
Transportation	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	O
Wade	O
,	O
alias	O
Boucher	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
She	O
pleaded	O
her	O
Belly	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
was	O
impanell	O
'd	O
but	O
they	O
brought	O
in	O
their	O
Verdict	O
that	O
the	O
was	O
not	O
Quick	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
pretended	O
.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Tattershall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
,	O
and	O
another	O
Peruke	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Carey	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
to	O
be	O
shaved	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
afterwards	O
missing	O
the	O
Perukes	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
;	O
at	O
which	O
Time	O
he	O
confest	O
his	O
taking	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Norwood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
York	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
under	O
the	O
pretence	O
of	O
buying	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Buckles	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
shuffling	O
and	O
chastering	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
gone	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
missing	O
the	O
Buckles	O
,	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
by	O
Threatning	O
and	O
Promises	O
he	O
pulled	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
This	O
Evidence	O
was	O
corroborated	O
by	O
the	O
Oath	O
of	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Carn	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pulled	O
out	O
the	O
Buckles	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Mead	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
's	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
to	O
Yards	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Dimitty	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ashwell	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
reposing	O
too	O
much	O
Confidence	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
alone	O
;	O
at	O
which	O
Time	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
in	O
writing	O
several	O
Letters	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
Colley	I-pers
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
extort	O
Money	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
or	O
otherwise	O
to	O
swear	O
he	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
Sodomitical	O
Practices	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Splawfoot	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Strange	I-pers
and	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Haslop	I-pers
;	O
which	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Andrew	B-pers
Moodey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.Sepulchre	B-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Cheshire	O
Cheeses	O
,	O
and	O
8	O
pound	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
John	B-pers
'Leake	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
gave	O
Orders	O
to	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
all	O
Night-walkers	O
that	O
should	O
come	O
in	O
their	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
such	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
at	O
an	O
unseasonable	O
Time	O
of	O
Night	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Cheeses	O
and	O
Sugar	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
cou	O
'd	O
not	O
give	O
a	O
good	O
Account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Raven	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Cornish	I-pers
,	O
two	O
Watchmen	O
,	O
severally	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
he	O
told	O
them	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
he	O
Sugar	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
keeping	O
a	O
Chandler	O
's	O
Shop	O
had	O
bought	O
the	O
Cheeses	O
for	O
Sale	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Cheesemonger	O
in	O
Southwark	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
making	O
Enquiry	O
,	O
could	O
find	O
no	O
such	O
Person	O
as	O
he	O
directed	O
them	O
to	O
;	O
not	O
withstanding	O
he	O
had	O
several	O
appeared	O
in	O
his	O
Behalf	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
sober	O
honest	O
,	O
industrious	O
Person	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
considered	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Drury	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
some	O
Table-cloaths	O
and	O
other	O
Linnen	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
30	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Coaley	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
pawn	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Hester	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
up	O
on	O
this	O
carrying	O
her	O
before	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
she	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
which	O
Confession	O
being	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pewter	O
Chamber-pot	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
;	O
which	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
on	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Prickloe	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
10	O
pound	O
of	O
unwrought	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
his	O
Partner	O
Mr.	O
Gale	O
,	O
was	O
interested	O
with	O
Silk	O
,	O
which	O
Silk	O
being	O
embezzl	O
'd	O
;	O
they	O
searched	O
his	O
Trunk	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Silk	O
there	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
the	O
prisoner	O
could	O
not	O
account	O
for	O
:	O
Upon	O
this	O
,	O
taking	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
he	O
confest	O
he	O
had	O
followed	O
that	O
vile	O
practice	O
for	O
some	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
sold	O
several	O
parcels	O
of	O
Silk	O
to	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Read	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Whitegate-Alley	O
,	O
who	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
and	O
encouraged	O
him	O
and	O
his	O
Fellow	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
Villany	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
single	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Littleton	B-pers
Pew	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bennet	I-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Wharf	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
potlid	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
2	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Causeway	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
going	O
to	O
move	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
employ	O
'd	O
the	O
prisoner	O
as	O
a	O
Porter	O
,	O
to	O
carry	O
some	O
of	O
her	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
missing	O
several	O
Things	O
,	O
she	O
made	O
strict	O
Enquiry	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Keebit	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
heard	O
him	O
own	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Brandy	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Lambridge	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
;	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
a	O
Barge	O
with	O
the	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
Deponent	O
seized	O
him	O
on	O
suspicion	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
then	O
confes	O
'd	O
he	O
stole	O
it	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Varney	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
first	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
him	O
own	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
to	O
make	O
Satisfaction	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Bickerton	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
married	O
her	O
Servant	O
Maid	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
her	O
Knowledge	O
had	O
behaved	O
him	O
self	O
very	O
honestly	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
came	O
to	O
this	O
Deponent	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
she	O
would	O
appear	O
in	O
his	O
Behalf	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Hands	O
of	O
a	O
litigious	O
Woman	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
neither	O
Justice	O
nor	O
Mercy	O
:	O
Upon	O
which	O
Mrs.	O
Bickerton	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
enquiry	O
into	O
the	O
Circumstance	O
;	O
at	O
which	O
Time	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
prisoner	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
twenty	O
pounds	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
prosecute	O
,	O
afterwards	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
to	O
ten	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
was	O
interrupted	O
in	O
making	O
the	O
Bargain	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
coming	O
in	O
of	O
a	O
Lawyer	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
she	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
by	O
talking	O
with	O
this	O
Deponent	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
was	O
too	O
cunning	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Humphreys	I-pers
,	O
David	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Morgan	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
severally	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
had	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
some	O
Years	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
careful	O
,	O
industrious	O
,	O
honest	O
Man	O
:	O
But	O
as	O
a	O
Character	O
can	O
not	O
overthrow	O
plain	O
Evidence	O
of	O
Guilt	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
with	O
a	O
Napkin	O
,	O
a	O
Clout	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
lac	O
'd	O
Pinners	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
which	O
appearing	O
plain	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Stuff-Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
two	O
Linnen	O
Aprons	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Brass	O
Saucepan	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Newcart	I-pers
:	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
,	O
her	O
Recognizance	O
was	O
estreated	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
100	O
Yards	O
of	O
Linnen	O
Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
26	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Murrah	I-pers
.	O
Priscilla	B-pers
Young	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
with	O
the	O
Cloth	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
suspecting	O
by	O
his	O
running	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
honestly	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
cried	O
,	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
dropt	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
soon	O
after	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samuel	B-pers
Clements	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Gemmins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
another	O
Person	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Samuel	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Airis	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
near	O
Shadwell	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
design	O
to	O
rob	O
them	O
.	O
Samuel	O
Smith	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
a	O
Lane	O
near	O
Cannon-street	B-place
,	I-place
Ratcliff	I-place
Highway	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
April	O
about	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
2nd	O
another	O
Person	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
us	O
and	O
knockt	O
me	O
down	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
my	O
Brother	O
Airis	O
knockt	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
immediately	O
fell	O
all	O
together	O
by	O
the	O
Ears	O
,	O
and	O
fought	O
a	O
Battle-Royal	O
,	O
till	O
they	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
have	O
enough	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
giving	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
a	O
kick	O
on	O
the	O
Arse	O
at	O
parting	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
turned	O
about	O
and	O
fired	O
a	O
Pistol	O
at	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
wounded	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Finger	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
positively	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
fired	O
the	O
Pistol	O
,	O
but	O
running	O
after	O
them	O
I	O
took	O
Clements	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Brother	O
took	O
Gemmins	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
ran	O
away	O
:	O
But	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
willing	O
such	O
Villains	O
should	O
escape	O
,	O
put	O
my	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Hands	O
of	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
pursued	O
him	O
that	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
over	O
a	O
Bank	O
into	O
a	O
Field	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
seize	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
fired	O
a	O
Pistol	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
other	O
had	O
done	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
got	O
away	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Airis	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
corroborated	O
by	O
Oath	O
of	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
in	O
whose	O
Hands	O
Samuel	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
had	O
left	O
Clements	O
when	O
he	O
pursued	O
him	O
that	O
got	O
away	O
:	O
This	O
Gentleman	O
searching	O
Clements	O
,	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
a	O
Pistol	O
loaded	O
,	O
an	O
Auger	O
,	O
with	O
Flint	O
,	O
Steel	O
,	O
Tinder-Box	O
and	O
Matches	O
.	O
Clements	O
being	O
asked	O
for	O
what	O
End	O
and	O
Purpose	O
he	O
carried	O
a	O
loaded	O
Pistol	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
answered	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
the	O
Bailiffs	O
,	O
though	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
he	O
pretended	O
it	O
was	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
being	O
carried	O
away	O
by	O
a	O
Press	O
Gang	O
,	O
the	O
Knife	O
he	O
pretended	O
he	O
bought	O
for	O
the	O
Cook	O
of	O
the	O
Ship	O
he	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
,	O
though	O
it	O
look	O
'd	O
more	O
fit	O
for	O
a	O
Cut-throat	O
;	O
this	O
Knife	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
new	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
wore	O
with	O
use	O
,	O
as	O
evidently	O
shew	O
'd	O
this	O
Excuse	O
was	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Piece	O
with	O
the	O
former	O
.	O
Gemmins	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
likewise	O
very	O
innocent	O
:	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
otherwise	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
they	O
was	O
both	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Aberall	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
2	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Berrie	I-pers
,	O
(	O
Servant	O
to	O
a	O
Laundress	O
)	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
pulling	O
out	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
Mr.	O
Widdrington	O
Darby	O
's	O
Linnen	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
the	O
Particulars	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Darby	O
's	O
Murder	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
a	O
relation	O
of	O
the	O
unhappy	O
Accident	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
insinuated	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
as	O
though	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
no	O
Crime	O
for	O
her	O
to	O
give	O
Mr.	O
Darby	O
's	O
Servant	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
of	O
those	O
Shirts	O
,	O
or	O
otherwise	O
to	O
embezzle	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
being	O
of	O
a	O
better	O
Principle	O
,	O
gave	O
no	O
heed	O
to	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
though	O
he	O
urg	O
'd	O
it	O
with	O
much	O
Importunity	O
;	O
finding	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
prevail	O
with	O
her	O
this	O
way	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
little	O
Small	O
Beer	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
whilst	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
draw	O
it	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
probability	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
two	O
Shirts	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Next	O
Day	O
Mary	B-pers
Berrie	I-pers
missing	O
the	O
Shirts	O
,	O
she	O
asked	O
her	O
Mistress	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
,	O
if	O
she	O
knew	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
telling	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Reason	O
of	O
suspect	O
Madam	O
Williams	O
's	O
Footman	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Bcoth	O
,	O
impatient	O
to	O
be	O
satisfied	O
,	O
sent	O
to	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
who	O
was	O
acquainted	O
in	O
the	O
Family	O
,	O
to	O
enquire	O
if	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
any	O
such	O
Shirts	O
as	O
was	O
lost	O
;	O
which	O
Gentleman	O
upon	O
strict	O
Search	O
detected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Booth	O
went	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
comparing	O
the	O
other	O
Shirts	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Darby	O
's	O
,	O
to	O
those	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
stole	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Cloth	O
,	O
Make	O
,	O
Size	O
and	O
Mark	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
Consequence	O
the	O
Shirts	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
stood	O
indicted	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
several	O
to	O
appear	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
an	O
extraordinary	O
Character	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
positively	O
deny	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
At	O
the	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
the	O
Court	O
was	O
so	O
merciful	O
as	O
to	O
order	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
only	O
have	O
some	O
private	O
Correction	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Read	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
buying	O
and	O
receiving	O
10	O
pound	O
of	O
unwrought	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
wickedly	O
inveigled	O
him	O
and	O
his	O
Fellow	O
Apprentice	O
to	O
steal	O
and	O
bring	O
away	O
what	O
Silk	O
they	O
could	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
their	O
Master	O
Mr.	O
Gale	O
,	O
carrying	O
them	O
to	O
Alehouses	O
,	O
and	O
treating	O
them	O
till	O
he	O
had	O
brought	O
them	O
over	O
to	O
commit	O
this	O
heinous	O
Crime	O
against	O
their	O
Master	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
evident	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Philip	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
and	O
Christopher	B-pers
Rawlins	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Mr.	O
Matth.ew	B-pers
Duburg	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
25	O
Guineas	O
,	O
1	O
half	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
six	O
Moidores	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
12	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Duburg	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
over	O
Lincoln's-Inn-Fields	B-place
,	O
and	O
three	O
persons	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
slung	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
they	O
tied	O
both	O
my	O
Hands	O
and	O
Legs	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
that	O
seemed	O
like	O
a	O
Butcher	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
white	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
had	O
a	O
Knife	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
offered	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
noise	O
he	O
would	O
cut	O
my	O
Throat	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
positively	O
say	O
the	O
prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
are	O
the	O
persons	O
who	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
was	O
taken	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
here	O
are	O
Witnesses	O
who	O
are	O
come	O
to	O
give	O
Evidence	O
against	O
them	O
.	O
One	O
Smallman	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Watchman	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
heard	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
call	O
out	O
for	O
help	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
went	O
and	O
untied	O
him	O
;	O
afterwards	O
he	O
with	O
another	O
found	O
the	O
prisoners	O
at	O
a	O
Brandy	O
Shop	O
of	O
bad	O
Character	O
in	O
Middle-Row	O
,	O
Holborn	O
,	O
and	O
apprehended	O
them	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
sober	O
Dram	O
among	O
the	O
honest	O
people	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
saw	O
Philip	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
drinking	O
in	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
thus	O
expressing	O
himself	O
,	O
The	O
first	O
Person	O
I	O
meet	O
shall	O
stand	O
or	O
die	O
,	O
or	O
deliver	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
is	O
now	O
dark	O
Nights	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
resolved	O
to	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
that	O
Advantage	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
must	O
and	O
will	O
have	O
Money	O
against	O
Whitsuntide	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Lebell	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
saw	O
Christopher	B-pers
Rawlins	I-pers
2	O
or	O
3	O
Days	O
after	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
drinking	O
at	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Owsley	O
's	O
in	O
Marybone	O
Fields	O
,	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
some	O
others	O
,	O
boasting	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
lately	O
concerned	O
in	O
a	O
Robbery	O
where	O
the	O
Booty	O
was	O
13	O
Guineas	O
,	O
7	O
Moidores	O
and	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
only	O
tied	O
his	O
Hands	O
and	O
Feet	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
left	O
him	O
.	O
This	O
Deponent	O
did	O
not	O
willingly	O
appear	O
against	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
telling	O
Mrs.	O
Owsley	O
of	O
the	O
Adventure	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
was	O
let	O
into	O
as	O
a	O
Secret	O
,	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
that	O
heard	O
her	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
her	O
bring	O
out	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
was	O
industrious	O
persons	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
live	O
by	O
such	O
practices	O
,	O
the	O
Employment	O
of	O
one	O
being	O
to	O
carry	O
a	O
Link	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
to	O
drive	O
a	O
Wheelbarrow	O
with	O
Apples	O
and	O
Pears	O
,	O
Dice	O
and	O
Oranges	O
:	O
But	O
though	O
it	O
appeared	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
that	O
they	O
was	O
scandalous	O
persons	O
and	O
us	O
'd	O
lewd	O
Houses	O
,	O
yet	O
this	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
proved	O
on	O
them	O
they	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Silver	O
Tea	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
laced	O
Caps	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
Shillings	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Armyshall	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Fact	O
plainly	O
appearing	O
upon	O
her	O
by	O
her	O
own	O
Confession	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jenkings	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
dozen	O
of	O
Silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
24	O
Shillings	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Doctor	O
Wright	O
,	O
(	O
a	O
merry	O
Translator	O
)	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
pursuing	O
him	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
dropt	O
them	O
just	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
this	O
Deponent	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Birchfield	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Hester	B-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
21	O
Sheep	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
8	O
Sheep	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
of	O
Higham-Ferries	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Wats	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
in	O
Hester	O
Parish	O
,	O
saying	O
they	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
them	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Sheep	O
mentioned	O
was	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
his	O
Master	O
Mr.	O
Richards	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
the	O
Shepherd	O
who	O
kept	O
them	O
,	O
could	O
positively	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
Mark	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
was	O
stole	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Pastures	O
near	O
Higham	B-place
Ferries	I-place
.	O
John	B-pers
Datum	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Shepherd	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Saunders	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
eight	O
Sheep	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
second	O
Indictment	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
did	O
belong	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
likewise	O
stole	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Pastures	O
near	O
Higham	O
Ferries	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
with	O
those	O
belonging	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Richards	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Stubbins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
some	O
Money	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Wyman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
;	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
coming	O
through	O
Gunston	B-place
Square	I-place
in	I-place
White-Chapel	I-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
and	O
cut	O
a	O
hole	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
being	O
seized	O
,	O
he	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Martha	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Yard	O
of	O
Cambrick	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Grazeth	I-pers
,	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Bernard	B-pers
Kentye	I-pers
Massip	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
and	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
Shirt	O
,	O
Stock	O
and	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
34	O
Shillings	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
May	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Crispin	B-pers
Tomlinson	I-pers
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
an	O
Italian	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
understanding	O
English	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
(	O
by	O
the	O
Mouth	O
of	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
Court	O
)	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
the	O
Privilege	O
which	O
is	O
granted	O
by	O
the	O
merciful	O
Laws	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
in	O
such	O
Cases	O
,	O
i.	O
e.	O
When	O
a	O
Foreigner	O
not	O
having	O
the	O
Advantage	O
of	O
our	O
Speech	O
,	O
stands	O
upon	O
his	O
delivery	O
before	O
any	O
Court	O
of	O
Judicature	O
,	O
he	O
may	O
have	O
the	O
Liberty	O
of	O
a	O
Jury	O
chosen	O
for	O
that	O
purpose	O
,	O
consisting	O
of	O
six	O
English	O
Men	O
and	O
six	O
Foreigners	O
,	O
which	O
Request	O
was	O
granted	O
him	O
,	O
their	O
Names	O
were	O
as	O
follows	O
:	O
Thomas	B-pers
Craddock	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Senneccan	I-pers
,	O
Allin	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Philleoan	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Wildiare	I-pers
,	O
David	B-pers
Payne	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Shakespear	I-pers
,	O
Solomon	B-pers
Bevine	I-pers
,	O
Arthur	B-pers
Rawlinson	I-pers
,	O
Stephen	B-pers
Gondaun	I-pers
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
Noeah	B-pers
Myah	I-pers
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Debumar	I-pers
was	O
sworn	O
Interpreter	O
between	O
the	O
Court	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Tomlinson	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
losing	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
Suspicion	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
carrying	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Waistcoat	O
and	O
Shirt	O
being	O
then	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Marple	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
Round	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
a	O
Trap	O
Door	O
at	O
the	O
Top	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
it	O
appeared	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
so	O
great	O
a	O
Stranger	O
to	O
our	O
Language	O
as	O
he	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
;	O
but	O
its	O
possible	O
he	O
might	O
flatter	O
himself	O
with	O
hopes	O
,	O
that	O
by	O
such	O
dilatory	O
Proceedings	O
he	O
might	O
tire	O
out	O
the	O
Patience	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
discharged	O
,	O
to	O
prevent	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Trouble	O
which	O
must	O
necessarily	O
be	O
the	O
Consequence	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
arraigned	O
and	O
convicted	O
in	O
such	O
Manner	O
as	O
the	O
Law	O
directs	O
on	O
these	O
Occasions	O
:	O
But	O
though	O
he	O
found	O
more	O
Mercy	O
than	O
he	O
could	O
have	O
expected	O
,	O
yet	O
as	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
altogether	O
to	O
escape	O
from	O
Justice	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
marrying	O
a	O
second	O
Wife	O
,	O
his	O
former	O
being	O
still	O
alive	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
Sessions	O
being	O
ended	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
follows	O
:	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
2.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wade	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
.	O
To	O
be	O
whipt	O
4.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Boseley	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Averall	I-pers
and	O
Bernard	B-pers
Kenty	I-pers
Massip	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
2.	O
Henry	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Penelope	B-pers
Chatterson	I-pers
.	O
Transportation	O
27.	O
John	B-pers
Willson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Splawfoot	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Eirchill	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
Littleton	O
Pew	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Winch	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Modesty	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Rook	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Luke	I-pers
,	O
Catharine	B-pers
Luke	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Soams	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Beddoe	I-pers
,	O
Jacob	B-pers
Tattershall	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Norwood	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Mead	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Drury	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Prickloe	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Read	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jenkings	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Brickford	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Stubbins	I-pers
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Clements	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
Jemmins	I-pers
,	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
assaulting	O
Samuel	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
&	O
c.	O
were	O
sentenced	O
to	O
three	O
Years	O
Imprisonment	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
give	O
Security	O
for	O
their	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
for	O
4	O
Years	O
more	O
after	O
they	O
are	O
discharged	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
Fin	I-pers
'd	I-pers
10	O
l.	O
ADVERTISEMENT	O
.	O
Books	O
printed	O
for	O
Edward	B-pers
Symon	I-pers
,	O
against	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
.	O
Connection	O
of	O
the	O
History	O
of	O
the	O
Old	O
and	O
New	O
Testament	O
,	O
with	O
that	O
of	O
the	O
Jews	O
and	O
Neighbouring	O
Nations	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Declension	O
of	O
the	O
Kingdoms	O
of	O
Israel	O
and	O
Judah	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Time	O
of	O
Christ	O
.	O
By	O
Humphry	O
Prideaux	B-pers
,	I-pers
D.	I-pers
D	I-pers
.	I-pers
Dean	O
of	O
Norwich	O
,	O
2	O
Vols	O
.	O
Folio	O
,	O
with	O
Cutts	O
and	O
Maps	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
The	O
Dealers	O
in	O
Stocks	O
Assistant	O
;	O
or	O
a	O
Calculation	O
of	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
any	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Stock	O
,	O
from	O
1000	O
l.	O
to	O
1	O
l.	O
at	O
the	O
Rate	O
of	O
the	O
16th	O
Part	O
of	O
a	O
Pound	O
per	O
Cent	O
.	O
to	O
200	O
l.	O
per	O
cent	O
.	O
for	O
the	O
Ease	O
of	O
the	O
Proprietors	O
of	O
the	O
several	O
Transferable	O
Stocks	O
,	O
in	O
Buying	O
,	O
Selling	O
,	O
and	O
Casting	O
up	O
Dividends	O
.	O
By	O
G.	O
Clerks	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
South-Sea	O
House	O
.	O
Price	O
2s	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
Physical	O
Dictionary	O
,	O
wherein	O
the	O
Terms	O
of	O
Anatomy	O
,	O
the	O
Names	O
and	O
Causes	O
of	O
Diseases	O
,	O
Chirurgical	O
Instruments	O
,	O
their	O
Use	O
,	O
are	O
accurately	O
described	O
.	O
As	O
also	O
the	O
Names	O
and	O
Virtues	O
of	O
Medicinal	O
Plants	O
,	O
Minerals	O
,	O
Stones	O
,	O
Gums	O
,	O
Salts	O
,	O
Barths	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Method	O
of	O
chusing	O
the	O
best	O
Drugs	O
:	O
The	O
Terms	O
of	O
Chymistry	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
Apothecary	O
's	O
Art	O
:	O
The	O
various	O
Forms	O
of	O
Medicines	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Ways	O
of	O
compounding	O
them	O
.	O
By	O
Stephen	B-pers
Blancard	I-pers
,	O
M.	O
D.	O
Professor	O
of	O
Physick	O
at	O
Middleburg	O
in	O
Zealand	O
.	O
The	O
Seventh	O
Edition	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Addition	O
of	O
many	O
Thousand	O
Terms	O
of	O
Art	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
Explantion	O
(	O
from	O
the	O
last	O
and	O
best	O
Edition	O
of	O
Castellus	O
's	O
Lexicon	O
Medicum	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Authors	O
)	O
more	O
than	O
in	O
any	O
former	O
Impression	O
;	O
also	O
a	O
Catalogue	O
of	O
the	O
Characters	O
us	O
'd	O
in	O
Physick	O
,	O
both	O
in	O
Latin	O
and	O
English	O
,	O
curiously	O
Engrav	O
'd	O
on	O
Copper	O
.	O
Tables	O
of	O
Interest	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Rate	O
of	O
3	O
&	O
4	O
and	O
half	O
5	O
,	O
6	O
,	O
7	O
,	O
and	O
8	O
per	O
cent	O
.	O
from	O
One	O
Thousand	O
Pounds	O
to	O
,	O
one	O
Shilling	O
for	O
one	O
Day	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Exactly	O
computed	O
to	O
the	O
Thousandth	O
Part	O
of	O
a	O
Penny	O
.	O
Also	O
Tables	O
of	O
Compound	O
Interest	O
.	O
By	O
,	O
The	O
Lydal	O
,	O
Accomptant	O
to	O
the	O
Commissioners	O
of	O
Excise	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
E.	O
Symon	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
;	O
and	O
Sold	O
by	O
J.	O
Roberts	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Oxford-Arms	O
in	O
Warwick-Lane	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
Four	O
Pence	O
.	O
)	O
