TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
At	O
the	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
And	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTRY	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
,	O
Monday	O
,	O
and	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
1st	O
,	O
2d	O
,	O
3d	O
,	O
4th	O
,	O
6th	O
,	O
and	O
7th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
1728	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
First	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Price	O
Six	O
Pence	O
.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
EDWARD	B-pers
BECHER	I-pers
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Raymond	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Hale	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Price	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	B-pers
Baron	I-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Serjeant	O
Law	O
;	O
and	O
other	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
aforesaid	O
:	O
Together	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wintworth	I-pers
,	O
Oliver	B-pers
Gorstelow	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Perkins	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Boheme	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Cose	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Warden	I-pers
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Hassell	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Mellton	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Thorlton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Waite	I-pers
,	O
Hugh	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Northridge	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Whiteband	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wooten	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Beck	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Underwood	I-pers
,	O
Paul	B-pers
Hussey	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Burdone	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Painter	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Collson	I-pers
,	O
Alexander	B-pers
Dicks	I-pers
.	O
The	O
following	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Facts	O
not	O
Material	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Guilty	O
as	O
follows	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bride	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
8	O
Guineas	O
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
some	O
Silver	O
and	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Allice	B-pers
Tunnell	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
George	B-pers
Scabrook	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Gibbons	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
Several	O
Bruises	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
and	O
Body	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
the	O
Aforesaid	O
Murder	O
;	O
to	O
both	O
which	O
Indictments	O
he	O
pleaded	O
,	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
drinking	O
together	O
in	O
St.	B-place
John's-street	I-place
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
with	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Difference	O
arising	O
between	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
She	O
smote	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Face	O
and	O
flung	O
the	O
Drink	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
resenting	O
,	O
he	O
beat	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
thinking	O
he	O
us	O
'd	O
her	O
too	O
cruelly	O
,	O
told	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
Shame	O
for	O
a	O
Man	O
to	O
beat	O
a	O
Woman	O
:	O
Upon	O
which	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
took	O
Occasion	O
to	O
Quarrel	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
challenged	O
him	O
to	O
fight	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
notwithstanding	O
this	O
Deponent	O
and	O
others	O
would	O
have	O
dissuaded	O
him	O
from	O
fighting	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
obstinate	O
,	O
and	O
continued	O
to	O
provoke	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
till	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
and	O
fought	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
returning	O
the	O
Blow	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
fell	O
,	O
getting	O
up	O
he	O
stagger	O
'd	O
.	O
fell	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
died	O
immediately	O
.	O
This	O
Relation	O
being	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Depositions	O
of	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Fuller	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Kensington	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Bryan	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
several	O
Wounds	O
and	O
Bruises	O
with	O
his	O
Hands	O
and	O
Feet	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Wounds	O
and	O
Bruises	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
;	O
to	O
both	O
which	O
Indictments	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
heard	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Quarrel	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
the	O
Interposition	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Master	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
then	O
prevented	O
from	O
fighting	O
,	O
though	O
they	O
fought	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
when	O
after	O
several	O
Falls	O
on	O
either	O
side	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
enough	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
then	O
they	O
parted	O
,	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
which	O
he	O
died	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
persuaded	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
not	O
to	O
fight	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
others	O
used	O
the	O
like	O
Intreaties	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
prevailed	O
with	O
,	O
that	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
fought	O
as	O
before	O
,	O
they	O
shook	O
Hands	O
,	O
both	O
affirming	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
angry	O
with	O
each	O
other	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
then	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
went	O
with	O
this	O
Deponent	O
to	O
a	O
publick	O
House	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
sick	O
,	O
drank	O
a	O
little	O
Rum	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
died	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Bristow	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Leavenstone	I-pers
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
like	O
Effect	O
,	O
both	O
agreeing	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
the	O
Encounter	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Banks	O
,	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
carefully	O
view	O
'd	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
no	O
external	O
Bruises	O
,	O
and	O
opening	O
it	O
,	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Cavity	O
of	O
his	O
Belly	O
2	O
Gallons	O
of	O
extravacated	O
Blood	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Vessels	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
;	O
but	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
by	O
a	O
Fall	O
,	O
Strain	O
,	O
or	O
violent	O
Wrench	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Whole	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
Joseph	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bennet	I-place
's	I-place
Gracechurch-street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Joyns	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
buying	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
shewing	O
him	O
several	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
slung	O
down	O
a	O
Bath-metal	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
stead	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
running	O
with	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
call	O
d	O
out	O
,	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
soon	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Ring	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
brought	O
back	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
on	O
his	O
Knees	O
,	O
and	O
begg	O
'd	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
Time	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
would	O
be	O
merciful	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
pulling	O
the	O
Ring	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Mouth	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
Time	O
he	O
had	O
ever	O
done	O
such	O
a	O
Thing	O
,	O
and	O
begg	O
'd	O
they	O
would	O
be	O
merciful	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
young	O
Woman	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Ring	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Bath-metal	O
one	O
to	O
match	O
the	O
Size	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
through	O
Mistake	O
he	O
left	O
the	O
Bath-metal	O
one	O
upon	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Gold	O
one	O
:	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
he	O
ran	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
continuing	O
to	O
run	O
when	O
pursued	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
confessing	O
it	O
being	O
attested	O
both	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
Constable	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Septon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Islington	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Henry	B-pers
Bunn	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
value	O
3l	O
.	O
2	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Foreign	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
s.	O
and	O
8	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bunn	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
about	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
on	O
Saturday	O
last	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
near	O
Cambray	B-place
House	I-place
,	O
he	O
was	O
set	O
upon	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
two	O
other	O
Persons	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
his	O
Watch	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
certain	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
so	O
dark	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
plain	O
View	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Cockin	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Sister	O
had	O
lodg	O
'd	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
for	O
some	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
this	O
Deponent	O
to	O
lend	O
him	O
two	O
Guineas	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
that	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
he	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
quarrell	O
'd	O
with	O
his	O
Sister	O
;	O
insomuch	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
Stairs	O
and	O
told	O
this	O
Deponent	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
did	O
believe	O
her	O
Brother	O
was	O
upon	O
some	O
desperate	O
Design	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
loaded	O
Pistol	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
shoot	O
the	O
first	O
Man	O
who	O
came	O
to	O
apprehend	O
him	O
;	O
she	O
therefore	O
begg	O
'd	O
of	O
this	O
Deponent	O
to	O
get	O
Constable	O
and	O
secure	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
feared	O
he	O
would	O
either	O
shoot	O
her	O
or	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
taking	O
her	O
Advice	O
they	O
secured	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
then	O
believing	O
that	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
not	O
honestly	O
come	O
by	O
,	O
look	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
Maker	O
's	O
Name	O
on	O
the	O
Dial-Plate	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
out	O
the	O
Maker	O
,	O
who	O
found	O
out	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
same	O
Watch	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Cockin	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Sister	O
coming	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
saying	O
they	O
believ	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
either	O
a	O
Highway-man	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
Street-Robber	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
secured	O
him	O
;	O
at	O
which	O
Time	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Pistol	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Round	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
was	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Pockets	O
a	O
Thimble	O
and	O
a	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
from	O
a	O
Milk-woman	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
from	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
on	O
Black-Heath	O
:	O
At	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
his	O
robbing	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Laurence	B-pers
Clinsmith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
's	I-place
Hanover-Square	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
9	O
China	O
Dishes	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Porringer	O
,	O
4	O
Silver	O
Forks	O
,	O
2	O
Silver	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
2	O
Silver	O
Hasted	O
Knives	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
valuable	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Bernard	B-pers
,	I-pers
Count	I-pers
Welderen	I-pers
,	O
the	O
young	O
Countess	B-pers
Welderen	I-pers
,	O
and	O
other	O
Persons	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Owen	B-pers
Golegar	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Van-a-peer	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
were	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Bernard	O
Count	O
Welderen	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
had	O
made	O
Confession	O
before	O
Justice	O
Blagney	O
,	O
of	O
his	O
taking	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Bernard	O
Count	O
Welderen	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Manner	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
desposed	O
of	O
them	O
:	O
The	O
Confession	O
being	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
Substance	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
,	O
Lawrence	O
Clinsmith	O
,	O
had	O
taken	O
divers	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Bernard	O
Count	O
Welderen	O
,	O
in	O
particular	O
2	O
Silver	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
carried	O
to	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
20	O
s.	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
making	O
much	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
stole	O
at	O
another	O
Time	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Bernard	O
Count	O
Welderen	O
,	O
9	O
China	O
Dishes	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
presenting	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
in	O
Gratuity	O
she	O
obliged	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Night	O
's	O
Lodging	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
afterwards	O
took	O
a	O
Silver	O
Porringer	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Count	O
Weldern	O
's	O
Brother	O
;	O
that	O
with	O
a	O
Poker	O
he	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
break	O
into	O
some	O
Rooms	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
designed	O
to	O
steal	O
and	O
bear	O
away	O
such	O
Things	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
find	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
Silver	O
Hasted	O
Knife	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
stolen	O
several	O
Things	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
which	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
Servants	O
of	O
Count	O
Welderen	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
by	O
the	O
Advice	O
of	O
a	O
Black-Shoe-Boy	O
,	O
had	O
stole	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
four	O
Silver	O
Forks	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
and	O
Spoon	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Boy	O
,	O
had	O
with	O
a	O
Hatcher	O
,	O
cut	O
off	O
the	O
Coat	O
of	O
Arms	O
which	O
were	O
on	O
the	O
Forks	O
and	O
Spoon	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Clinsmith	I-pers
,	O
had	O
put	O
off	O
his	O
own	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
on	O
those	O
of	O
the	O
Black-Shoe-Boy	O
;	O
in	O
which	O
Dress	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Silver	O
Smith	O
(	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
)	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
said	O
Plate	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Montgomery	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
him	O
four	O
Silver	O
Forks	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
to	O
Sale	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
this	O
Deponent	O
stopping	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Count	O
Welderen	O
's	O
Boy	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Master	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Dutch-land	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
this	O
Deponent	O
's	O
sending	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
stole	O
he	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
his	O
Master	O
Bernard	O
,	O
Count	O
Welderen	O
.	O
Walter	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
the	O
Officer	O
who	O
was	O
charg	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
persuaded	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Spoons	O
to	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
Holland	O
:	O
He	O
further	O
told	O
this	O
Deponent	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Dutch	O
Embassador	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
stolen	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Excellency	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
own	O
Confession	O
being	O
sign	O
'd	O
with	O
his	O
own	O
Hand	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
plain	O
Proofs	O
against	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
and	O
Owen	B-pers
Golegar	I-pers
,	O
as	O
Accessories	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Edmington	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Grey	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Crew	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
Horse	O
from	O
Grass	O
about	O
Christmas	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
afterwards	O
stealing	O
a	O
Horse	O
something	O
like	O
his	O
,	O
he	O
fell	O
in	O
Discount	O
with	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
rode	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
New-Prison	O
,	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
a	O
Prisoner	O
who	O
could	O
very	O
likely	O
give	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Trouble	O
about	O
a	O
Horse	O
;	O
accordingly	O
that	O
Person	O
whose	O
Name	O
in	O
George	B-pers
Cann	I-pers
,	O
informed	O
him	O
,	O
That	O
Ben	O
Johnson	O
could	O
help	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Ben	O
Johnson	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
his	O
Directions	O
found	O
the	O
Horse	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Lane	O
,	O
of	O
Whitechapel	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Lane	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Gelding	O
of	O
Ben	O
Johnson	O
,	O
in	O
Exchange	O
for	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
Ben	O
Johnson	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
give	O
an	O
Account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Le	I-place
Bone	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
9	O
Silver	O
Watches	O
and	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Morran	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Morran	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
And	O
John	B-pers
Perkins	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
as	O
Accessory	O
,	O
he	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Morran	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
hearing	O
of	O
Thomas	O
Neaves	O
being	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
other	O
Facts	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
informed	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Richard	O
Nichols	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Watches	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shop	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
directed	O
Mr.	O
Morran	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
where	O
he	O
might	O
find	O
3	O
of	O
the	O
Watches	O
in	O
pawn	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
found	O
accordingly	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Watches	O
being	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
he	O
found	O
by	O
the	O
Directions	O
of	O
Thomas	O
Neaves	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bridle	O
swore	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
Father	O
's	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
Mr	O
Morran	O
to	O
be	O
mended	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Taylor	O
produced	O
another	O
of	O
the	O
Watches	O
,	O
which	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
Mr.	O
Morran	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
pawn	O
'd	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Taylor	O
on	O
the	O
very	O
Day	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
stolen	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Morran	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Neaves	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
he	O
,	O
with	O
four	O
others	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Show-Glass	O
with	O
the	O
Watches	O
in	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Body	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
they	O
agreed	O
to	O
steal	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
observing	O
a	O
Barber	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
Side	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
were	O
afraid	O
of	O
being	O
detected	O
;	O
but	O
to	O
avoid	O
that	O
,	O
Nichols	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
went	O
over	O
to	O
the	O
Barber	O
,	O
and	O
under	O
the	O
Pretence	O
of	O
wanting	O
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
he	O
placed	O
,	O
himself	O
so	O
as	O
the	O
Barber	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
them	O
take	O
away	O
the	O
Show-Glass	O
:	O
That	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
,	O
Nichols	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
this	O
is	O
Rum	O
enough	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
Perkins	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
White	O
Horse	O
Alley	O
in	O
Chick-lane	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Night	O
Perkins	O
sent	O
his	O
Wife	O
out	O
with	O
3	O
of	O
the	O
Watches	O
,	O
and	O
pawned	O
two	O
others	O
himself	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Silver	O
Watches	O
that	O
remained	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
for	O
which	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
sold	O
,	O
was	O
equally	O
divided	O
amongst	O
them	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
he	O
,	O
this	O
Deponent	O
Neaves	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
carried	O
to	O
Shrewsbury	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
8	O
l.	O
Robert	B-pers
Alboni	I-pers
the	O
Barber	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Nichols	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
buying	O
a	O
Wig	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
put	O
one	O
on	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
at	O
himself	O
in	O
the	O
Glass	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
call	O
for	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Cook	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
pawn	O
'd	O
a	O
Watch	O
for	O
Perkins	O
,	O
at	O
one	O
Wilson	O
's	O
on	O
Saffron-Hill	O
,	O
which	O
Watch	O
being	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
it	O
was	O
owned	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
Persons	O
appeared	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Bellinger	I-pers
,	O
and	O
George	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Brother	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
their	O
Company	O
on	O
Friday	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
from	O
8	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
till	O
Nine	O
at	O
Night	O
;	O
but	O
their	O
Evidence	O
not	O
having	O
that	O
Weight	O
to	O
overpoise	O
the	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Nichols	O
on	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
several	O
plain	O
and	O
undeniable	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
And	O
Perkins	O
guilty	O
as	O
Accessory	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Twickenham	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
five	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
set	O
with	O
Diamonds	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
l.	O
9	O
Serjeants	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
14	O
s.	O
2	O
Guineas	O
,	O
a	O
Broad	O
Piece	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Things	O
of	O
Value	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
,	O
Serjeant	O
at	O
Law	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
Raby	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Chambers	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
miss	O
'd	O
he	O
advertised	O
them	O
in	O
Mist	O
's	O
Journal	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Day	O
the	O
Advertisement	O
was	O
published	O
,	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Higgins	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Rings	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
which	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
Mr	O
.	O
Chambers	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
Raby	O
's	O
:	O
Her	O
Confession	O
was	O
likewise	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
sign	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
own	O
Hand	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
being	O
entertained	O
as	O
a	O
Charr-woman	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
Raby	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
whilst	O
a	O
Servant	O
Maid	O
was	O
sick	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
moved	O
with	O
them	O
from	O
Twickenham	O
.	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Higgins	I-pers
,	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
:	O
The	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Jenkyns	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bennet	I-place
's	I-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Wharf	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
4	O
Guineas	O
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Bath-metal	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Anthony	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
March	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
Bell-Inn	O
in	O
Friday-street	O
,	O
and	O
enquiring	O
the	O
Way	O
for	O
Birchin-Lane	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
.	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
at	O
the	O
Expence	O
of	O
a	O
Coach	O
she	O
would	O
bear	O
him	O
Company	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
agreeing	O
to	O
,	O
they	O
got	O
into	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
whose	O
Directions	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
were	O
set	O
down	O
at	O
a	O
Tavern	B-place
near	I-place
Doctors	I-place
Commons	I-place
,	O
where	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Tavern	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Box	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
Ring	O
;	O
and	O
getting	O
her	O
secured	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Ray	O
the	O
Constable	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
search	O
'd	O
her	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Modesty	O
would	O
permit	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
finding	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
charg	O
'd	O
Jane	B-pers
Jewell	I-pers
to	O
search	O
her	O
further	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Jewell	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
stript	O
she	O
felt	O
the	O
Box	O
in	O
a	O
Place	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
mention	O
'd	O
with	O
Modesty	O
;	O
and	O
calling	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
with	O
shaking	O
and	O
disturbing	O
her	O
the	O
Box	O
fell	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Mayo	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
opened	O
in	O
the	O
Presence	O
of	O
the	O
Constable	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
the	O
Ring	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
for	O
Favours	O
receiv	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
if	O
Lewdness	O
would	O
extenuate	O
her	O
Crimes	O
,	O
she	O
seem	O
'd	O
pleased	O
at	O
the	O
Repetition	O
of	O
her	O
Beastality	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Prince	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
,	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Hoar	I-pers
,	O
about	O
four	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
(	O
the	O
said	O
Edward	O
Hoar	O
being	O
therein	O
)	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
a	O
Satten	O
Gown	O
,	O
2	O
Linnen	O
Gowns	O
,	O
a	O
lac	O
'd	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
a	O
black	O
Silk	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
Callamanco	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
l.	O
Edward	O
Hoar	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Sash	O
at	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
himself	O
had	O
nail	O
'd	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
fast	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
coming	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
found	O
it	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
with	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Part	O
bundled	O
up	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
carry	O
off	O
;	O
that	O
upon	O
his	O
being	O
apprehended	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
begg	O
'd	O
Pardon	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hoar	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
confirming	O
the	O
Deposition	O
of	O
her	O
Husband	O
Edward	B-pers
Hoar	I-pers
,	O
in	O
every	O
particular	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Tipping	I-pers
and	O
Daniel	B-pers
Moor	I-pers
severally	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
being	O
Journeymen	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
their	O
Landlady	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hoar	I-pers
cry	O
out	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
with	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
others	O
Bundled	O
up	O
to	O
carry	O
away	O
;	O
they	O
likewise	O
heard	O
him	O
confess	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
beg	O
Pardon	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
not	O
having	O
the	O
least	O
Excuse	O
to	O
make	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Hether	B-pers
Landale	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Alhallows	B-place
Barkin	I-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
the	I-place
Tower	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
.	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
24	O
th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
(	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
)	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cummings	I-pers
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
(	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
)	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Yateman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
1726-7	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
first	O
Indictment	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cummings	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
her	O
House	O
with	O
another	O
Person	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
d	O
for	O
a	O
Tankard	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
Pen	O
and	O
Ink	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
have	O
great	O
Business	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
sent	O
for	O
Meat	O
to	O
a	O
Cook	O
's	O
Shop	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
liking	O
it	O
when	O
it	O
came	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
Person	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
fetch	O
some	O
Veal	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
himself	O
hastily	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
Deponent	O
fearing	O
that	O
her	O
Tankard	O
was	O
not	O
safe	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
not	O
being	O
paid	O
,	O
she	O
stopp	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Jasper	B-pers
Bensh	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
Daughter	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
being	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
another	O
Person	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
convey	O
'd	O
away	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
intrusted	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
Person	O
being	O
gone	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
force	O
his	O
way	O
out	O
likewise	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
2d	O
Indictment	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Yateman	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
March	O
was	O
Twelvemonth	O
,	O
and	O
seemed	O
positive	O
in	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
away	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
Daughter	O
,	O
who	O
like	O
wise	O
seem	O
'd	O
positive	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
Person	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
calling	O
Mr.	O
Allen	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Ewell	O
,	O
they	O
severally	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
for	O
2	O
Years	O
past	O
a	O
close	O
confin	O
'd	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
till	O
discharg	O
'd	O
by	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
most	O
gracious	O
Pardon	O
last	O
Sessions	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
infinuated	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
been	O
let	O
out	O
to	O
commit	O
Robberies	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
go	O
back	O
again	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Allen	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Ewell	O
gaining	O
more	O
Credit	O
than	O
that	O
vulgur	O
Insinuation	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
appearing	O
incongruous	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
should	O
run	O
the	O
Risque	O
of	O
forfeiting	O
their	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
laying	O
all	O
that	O
is	O
valuable	O
at	O
Stake	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Mercy	O
of	O
a	O
Villain	O
,	O
who	O
would	O
,	O
no	O
Doubt	O
,	O
embrace	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
of	O
Running	O
away	O
,	O
sooner	O
than	O
return	O
to	O
meet	O
Justice	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
the	O
Hazzard	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
by	O
standing	O
a	O
Trial	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
last	O
Indictment	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hendron	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Pendergrass	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
upon	O
a	O
Statute	O
of	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
Harry	O
the	O
VIIth	O
,	O
for	O
aiding	O
and	O
abetting	O
Richard	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
in	O
forcibly	O
and	O
unlawfully	O
marrying	O
and	O
defiling	O
Sibble	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
;	O
against	O
her	O
Will	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Sibble	O
Morris	O
being	O
a	O
Maiden	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
an	O
Estate	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Holliday	I-pers
,	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Morris	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Mrs.	O
Hendron	O
asked	O
her	O
to	O
bring	O
her	O
young	O
Mistress	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
in	O
Feb.	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
upon	O
her	O
Intercession	O
they	O
went	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
prevail	O
'd	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Pendergrass	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
saw	O
Richard	O
Russel	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
extraordinary	O
happened	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
;	O
however	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Henderon	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
them	O
have	O
a	O
good	O
Opinion	O
of	O
Russel	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
rich	O
Merchant	O
in	O
the	O
City	O
,	O
that	O
dealt	O
in	O
Oyls	O
,	O
Silks	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Value	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
,	O
she	O
prevail	O
'd	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
come	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
towards	O
Hendron	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
they	O
met	O
one	O
Peggy	O
Johnson	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Kitty	B-pers
Pendergrass	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Daughter	O
of	O
Pendergrass	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
them	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Hendron	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
but	O
wanted	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
they	O
would	O
come	O
to	O
her	O
at	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
New	B-place
Round	I-place
Court	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Strand	I-place
.	O
Mrs.	O
Morris	O
was	O
against	O
going	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
and	O
the	O
Maid	O
were	O
both	O
pull	O
'd	O
along	O
by	O
Peggy	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
and	O
Kitty	O
Pendergrass	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Murphew	O
in	O
Round	O
Court	O
;	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Hendron	O
,	O
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Pendergrass	I-pers
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
obliged	O
them	O
to	O
come	O
in	O
,	O
pulling	O
Miss	O
Morris	O
through	O
a	O
long	O
dark	O
Entry	O
into	O
a	O
Room	O
where	O
the	O
Windows	O
were	O
shut	O
up	O
with	O
Shutters	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
Candles	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Company	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Morris	O
being	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
at	O
this	O
,	O
would	O
have	O
turned	O
back	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
hindred	O
by	O
Hendron	O
who	O
lock	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
upon	O
her	O
and	O
the	O
Maid	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
their	O
saying	O
they	O
would	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
would	O
signify	O
nothing	O
,	O
for	O
no	O
Body	O
could	O
hear	O
them	O
.	O
Immediately	O
Russel	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Morris	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
to	O
tell	O
her	O
Christian	O
Name	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
refused	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
surprize	O
and	O
Fright	O
;	O
that	O
a	O
Person	O
in	O
the	O
Habit	O
and	O
Appearance	O
of	O
a	O
Clergyman	O
being	O
there	O
,	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
when	O
Hendron	O
and	O
a	O
Person	O
who	O
officiated	O
as	O
Clerk	O
,	O
forcibly	O
held	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
ready	O
to	O
faint	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Person	O
began	O
the	O
Ceremony	O
,	O
but	O
Mrs.	O
Morris	O
did	O
not	O
answer	O
to	O
the	O
Questions	O
put	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
only	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
married	O
:	O
However	O
,	O
he	O
proceeded	O
in	O
the	O
Ceremony	O
,	O
and	O
Hendron	O
and	O
Pendergrass	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
answer	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
there	O
to	O
be	O
married	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
only	O
Faint-hearted	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
all	O
this	O
Time	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
utmost	O
Confusion	O
,	O
and	O
even	O
lost	O
the	O
Power	O
of	O
Speech	O
and	O
Strength	O
to	O
support	O
herself	O
under	O
such	O
Usage	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
Mock-Marriage	O
,	O
Hendron	O
and	O
others	O
dragg	O
'd	O
her	O
up	O
Stairs	O
to	O
a	O
Bed-Chamber	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
also	O
shut	O
up	O
with	O
Shutters	O
,	O
and	O
Kitty	O
Pendergrass	O
and	O
Peggy	O
Johnson	O
,	O
pulled	O
off	O
her	O
Cloaths	O
by	O
Force	O
,	O
Hendron	O
holding	O
her	O
Hands	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Rigy	O
was	O
there	O
present	O
while	O
all	O
this	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
forc	O
'd	O
her	O
into	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Hendron	O
held	O
her	O
down	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
commanded	O
this	O
Deponent	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
she	O
complained	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Shame	O
they	O
should	O
use	O
her	O
Mistress	O
so	O
;	O
that	O
upon	O
the	O
Stairs	O
she	O
met	O
Russel	O
undress	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
his	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
Hendron	O
lock	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
leaving	O
them	O
together	O
;	O
after	O
this	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
others	O
for	O
about	O
Half	O
an	O
Hour	O
were	O
very	O
merry	O
,	O
till	O
Mrs.	O
Morris	O
and	O
Russell	O
came	O
down	O
Stairs	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
Mrs.	O
Morris	O
to	O
have	O
eat	O
some	O
Supper	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
refused	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
go	O
home	O
that	O
Russell	O
went	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
being	O
cross-examined	O
as	O
to	O
Margaret	O
Pendergrass	O
,	O
this	O
Deponent	O
said	O
,	O
She	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Hendron	O
,	O
when	O
Mrs.	O
Morris	O
was	O
drag	O
'd	O
through	O
the	O
Entry	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
where	O
the	O
pretended	O
Marriage	O
was	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
told	O
Mrs.	O
Morris	O
she	O
must	O
be	O
married	O
to	O
Russell	O
;	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
to	O
her	O
Advantage	O
that	O
she	O
consented	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
commended	O
what	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
up	O
Stairs	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
while	O
her	O
Daughter	O
Kitty	O
Pendergrass	O
assisted	O
in	O
forcing	O
off	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Morris	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
unlock	O
'd	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
in	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
staid	O
there	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
the	O
Supper	O
was	O
.	O
This	O
Deponent	O
,	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
the	O
Measure	O
of	O
her	O
Mistress	O
Finger	O
,	O
in	O
Order	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
Ring	O
made	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
Measure	O
she	O
brought	O
to	O
Hendron	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
the	O
Measure	O
of	O
her	O
Mistress	O
's	O
Finger	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
some	O
Proof	O
of	O
her	O
bringing	O
some	O
Measure	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Hendron	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
she	O
brought	O
a	O
Measure	O
to	O
Hendron	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Measure	O
of	O
her	O
Mistress	O
's	O
Finger	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
without	O
her	O
Mistress	O
's	O
Knowledge	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
having	O
once	O
mention	O
'd	O
such	O
a	O
Thing	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
suffer	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
Hendron	O
by	O
her	O
Insinuations	O
having	O
made	O
her	O
believe	O
that	O
her	O
Mistress	O
's	O
Marriage	O
would	O
be	O
much	O
to	O
her	O
Advantage	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
betray	O
'd	O
to	O
that	O
Indiscretion	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
Wheeler	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
at	O
the	O
Marriage	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
he	O
appear	O
when	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Violencies	O
were	O
acted	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
at	O
Supper	O
with	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Company	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Sibble	O
Morris	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
Particulars	O
of	O
her	O
Maid	O
's	O
Deposition	O
,	O
with	O
regard	O
to	O
the	O
forcible	O
Marriage	O
,	O
and	O
forcing	O
her	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
that	O
Hendron	O
was	O
the	O
chief	O
Actor	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
held	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Time	O
of	O
the	O
Ceremony	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
answer	O
to	O
the	O
Matrimonial	O
Responses	O
,	O
was	O
dragg	O
'd	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Bed-Chamber	O
,	O
forced	O
into	O
Bed	O
against	O
her	O
Will	O
and	O
Consent	O
,	O
that	O
Richard	O
Russell	O
had	O
Carnal	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
her	O
Body	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
the	O
foul	O
Distemper	O
,	O
making	O
an	O
Advantage	O
of	O
her	O
Surprize	O
and	O
Weakness	O
,	O
and	O
tho	O
'	O
she	O
resisted	O
to	O
the	O
utmost	O
of	O
her	O
Strength	O
,	O
he	O
held	O
her	O
down	O
in	O
Bed	O
and	O
overcame	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
stopt	O
her	O
Mouth	O
,	O
that	O
Pendergrass	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
Marriage	O
,	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
forcing	O
off	O
her	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
assisted	O
and	O
persuaded	O
to	O
the	O
Marriage	O
,	O
and	O
consented	O
to	O
all	O
that	O
was	O
acted	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
remember	O
that	O
Wheeler	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
or	O
at	O
the	O
Marriage	O
,	O
or	O
in	O
the	O
Bed-Chamber	O
,	O
or	O
was	O
privy	O
to	O
any	O
Violence	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Allen	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
officiated	O
as	O
Clerk	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
provided	O
the	O
Parson	O
by	O
the	O
Persuasion	O
and	O
Importunity	O
of	O
Wheeler	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
him	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
Times	O
before	O
he	O
would	O
consent	O
to	O
have	O
any	O
Thing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
Wheeler	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
marry	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
to	O
a	O
Servant	O
Maid	O
,	O
with	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
fallen	O
in	O
love	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
that	O
End	O
he	O
appointed	O
to	O
meet	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
Parson	O
(	O
whose	O
Name	O
is	O
Evans	O
,	O
a	O
Parson	O
at	O
the	O
Fleet	O
)	O
at	O
the	O
seven	O
Stars	O
in	O
Cross-street	O
,	O
Long-Acre	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
met	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Murphew	O
in	O
New	O
.	O
Round	O
Court	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
where	O
this	O
Deponent	O
said	O
,	O
Russell	O
and	O
his	O
Accomplices	O
were	O
met	O
together	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
perform	O
the	O
Ceremony	O
Mrs.	O
Morris	O
trembled	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
perceive	O
that	O
she	O
gave	O
her	O
Consent	O
,	O
but	O
on	O
the	O
contrary	O
refused	O
it	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
told	O
the	O
Parson	O
he	O
might	O
shut	O
up	O
his	O
Books	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
like	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Wedding	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Company	O
saying	O
,	O
she	O
answered	O
to	O
the	O
Questions	O
put	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Parson	O
went	O
through	O
the	O
Form	O
of	O
Matrimony	O
,	O
that	O
Pendergrass	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
affirmed	O
she	O
spoke	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
married	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
only	O
Faint-hearted	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
this	O
Deponent	O
said	O
,	O
for	O
his	O
own	O
Part	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
her	O
say	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
married	O
,	O
yet	O
the	O
Parson	O
went	O
on	O
with	O
the	O
Ceremony	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
the	O
Ceremony	O
was	O
concluded	O
they	O
left	O
them	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Daniel	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Wheeler	O
,	O
the	O
Parson	O
and	O
Clerk	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
at	O
the	O
7	O
Stars	O
in	O
Cross-street	O
,	O
Long-Acre	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
some	O
Passages	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
there	O
was	O
something	O
going	O
forward	O
which	O
was	O
not	O
fair	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
soon	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
Margaret	O
Pendergrass	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
and	O
enquired	O
for	O
such	O
People	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
his	O
saying	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
she	O
stamp	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
Foot	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
rather	O
have	O
given	O
five	O
Pounds	O
than	O
be	O
disappointed	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Morris	O
(	O
the	O
Father	O
of	O
the	O
injur	O
'd	O
Gentlewoman	O
)	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
an	O
Estate	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
at	O
present	O
20	O
Pounds	O
per	O
Annum	O
clear	O
to	O
her	O
(	O
and	O
would	O
be	O
more	O
)	O
in	O
Southampton-street	O
,	O
Covent-Garden	O
,	O
which	O
Estate	O
was	O
left	O
her	O
by	O
a	O
deceas	O
'd	O
Uncle	O
;	O
he	O
farther	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
this	O
pretended	O
Marriage	O
being	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
following	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
pretending	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Friend	O
to	O
Russel	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
acquainted	O
him	O
of	O
his	O
Daughter	O
's	O
Marriage	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
Gentleman	O
afrerwards	O
appear	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
depos	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
by	O
Margaret	O
Pendergrass	O
,	O
as	O
Russells	O
Friend	O
)	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
at	O
this	O
,	O
went	O
immediately	O
to	O
his	O
Daughter	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
answered	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
vilely	O
impos	O
'd	O
on	O
and	O
barbarously	O
used	O
under	O
the	O
Pretence	O
of	O
a	O
Marriage	O
,	O
but	O
for	O
Fear	O
and	O
Shame	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
acquainted	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
(	O
she	O
being	O
a	O
young	O
Girl	O
between	O
16	O
and	O
17	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
.	O
)	O
That	O
Russell	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
any	O
Conversation	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
since	O
he	O
is	O
absconded	O
.	O
Mary	O
Hendron	O
,	O
and	O
Margaret	O
Pendergrass	O
,	O
were	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
And	O
as	O
Wheeler	O
was	O
employed	O
by	O
Margaret	O
Pendergrass	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
Parson	O
,	O
and	O
might	O
be	O
imposed	O
on	O
by	O
her	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
privy	O
to	O
any	O
Force	O
at	O
the	O
Marriage	O
or	O
otherwise	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Frost	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Mary	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Silk	O
and	O
Cotton	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
But	O
notwithstanding	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
postively	O
to	O
his	O
Person	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Circumstances	O
concurring	O
therewith	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
good	O
Fortune	O
to	O
escape	O
,	O
several	O
appearing	O
to	O
his	O
Character	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
;	O
But	O
at	O
the	O
Conclusion	O
of	O
the	O
Sessions	O
they	O
desired	O
he	O
might	O
not	O
be	O
discharged	O
out	O
of	O
Custody	O
till	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
Security	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Joyns	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
one	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
Moidore	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Gathie	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
pick	O
'd	O
him	O
up	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
a	O
Brandy	O
Shop	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Dram	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
another	O
Dram	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
Gratuity	O
she	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
her	O
Lodgings	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Dram	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
confes	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
yet	O
he	O
remembered	O
his	O
Mistress	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
's	O
,	O
in	O
White	O
Horss	O
Alley	O
,	O
Chick-Lane	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Books	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Reason	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Yellop	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Velvet	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Moses	B-pers
Kendale	I-pers
and	O
other	O
Persons	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
plain	O
upon	O
Yellop	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s	O
but	O
Elizabeth	O
Waters	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Bishopsgate-street	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
16	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Oats	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Long	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
Coachman	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Horses	O
he	O
drove	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
only	O
taken	O
a	O
larger	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Oats	O
than	O
his	O
Master	O
allow	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
out	O
of	O
respect	O
to	O
his	O
Horses	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
respect	O
of	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
himself	O
under	O
this	O
Prosecution	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Court	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
severely	O
reprimanded	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchre	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
d.	O
and	O
some	O
money	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
Necessary	O
House	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
is	O
an	O
open	O
Court	O
for	O
the	O
Use	O
of	O
the	O
several	O
Houses	O
there	O
)	O
with	O
a	O
Candle	O
and	O
Candlestick	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
four	O
Women	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
violently	O
hustled	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Candlestick	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
that	O
House	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
Money	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
it	O
:	O
However	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
she	O
and	O
one	O
Margaret	B-pers
Noon	I-pers
took	O
away	O
the	O
Candelestick	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
9	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
This	O
Mary	O
Fowler	O
,	O
has	O
for	O
some	O
Time	O
kept	O
a	O
notorious	O
Bawdy	O
House	O
in	O
White	O
Horse	O
Alley	O
,	O
Chick-Lane	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
Place	O
unthinking	O
simple	O
Sots	O
have	O
been	O
frequently	O
ensnared	O
,	O
gull	O
'd	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
Strumpets	O
have	O
been	O
brought	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
to	O
Justice	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Mother	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
fair	O
Way	O
for	O
a	O
long	O
Voyage	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
hoped	O
the	O
Crew	O
will	O
be	O
dispersed	O
into	O
other	O
Quarters	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Drew	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
cutting	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Dun	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
which	O
appearing	O
plain	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
several	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Goods	O
from	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Apron	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Steward	B-pers
Bass	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
William	B-pers
Russell	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Holden	I-pers
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Crouch	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Martha	B-pers
Hyde	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Broadcloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
forty	O
Shillings	O
,	O
a	O
Looking-Glass	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
and	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Dalton	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
the	O
three	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
overtaking	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
about	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
in	O
Fleetstreet	O
,	O
they	O
agreed	O
to	O
snatch	O
the	O
Bundle	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
having	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
they	O
followed	O
her	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
Lincoln's-Inn-Fields	B-place
,	O
where	O
Crouch	O
knock	O
'd	O
her	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
Russell	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Bundle	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
opened	O
the	O
Bundle	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
Found	O
in	O
it	O
several	O
Aprons	O
,	O
a	O
Womans	O
Mourning	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
Black	O
Hoods	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
Bundle	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Looking-Glass	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
being	O
bound	O
up	O
well	O
,	O
it	O
fell	O
out	O
and	O
broke	O
to	O
Pieces	O
:	O
He	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
sold	O
the	O
Bundle	O
altogether	O
,	O
to	O
one	O
Susan	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Buyer	O
of	O
stolen	O
Goods	O
,	O
for	O
24	O
s.	O
(	O
which	O
in	O
their	O
Language	O
is	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
Lock	O
)	O
and	O
to	O
their	O
great	O
mortification	O
they	O
heard	O
afterwards	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
forty	O
Shillings	O
in	O
money	O
wrapt	O
up	O
in	O
Rag	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
contain	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Bundle	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hide	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
in	O
Lincoln's-Inn-Fields	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
aforsaid	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
bundle	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictmemt	O
.	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
Russell	O
and	O
Crouch	O
at	O
a	O
Brandy	O
Shop	O
soon	O
after	O
this	O
happen	O
'd	O
,	O
when	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
arising	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
Russell	O
said	O
to	O
Crouch	O
,	O
If	O
you	O
meddle	O
with	O
Nichols	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
cut	O
the	O
Coat	O
off	O
your	O
Back	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
Woman	O
's	O
Coat	O
which	O
I	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
in	O
Lincoln's-Inn-Fields	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
as	O
much	O
Right	O
to	O
it	O
as	O
you	O
.	O
He	O
further	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
to	O
his	O
certain	O
Knowledge	O
,	O
Crouch	O
pawn	O
'd	O
an	O
old	O
Coat	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
Alteration	O
of	O
this	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Coat	O
had	O
a	O
picked	O
Cape	O
of	O
Cloth	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Velvet	O
Cape	O
set	O
on	O
instead	O
thereof	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Willis	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
Russell	O
,	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
his	O
taking	O
these	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
sold	O
for	O
about	O
22	O
s.	O
And	O
Dalton	O
further	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
Russell	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
value	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
he	O
should	O
die	O
among	O
such	O
Brave	O
Fellows	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
all	O
three	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bride	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Richard	B-pers
Corbet	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Silver	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
2	O
Silver	O
Watches	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Buckles	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Corbet	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
broke	O
open	O
several	O
Locks	O
to	O
come	O
at	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Tomlin	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sign	O
his	O
Confession	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Corbet	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Drawers	O
to	O
come	O
at	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Hews	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
likewise	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Corbet	O
,	O
he	O
lock	O
'd	O
the	O
Doors	O
over	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
and	O
locked	O
it	O
safe	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
the	O
Doors	O
were	O
found	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
gone	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
plain	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Parr	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Bishopsgate-street	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Adam	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
left	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
in	O
Custody	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
no	O
sooner	O
gone	O
but	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
missing	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
York	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Tankard	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
and	O
Woman	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
gave	O
them	O
6	O
l.	O
7	O
s.	O
that	O
they	O
call	O
'd	O
each	O
other	O
Mother	O
and	O
Son	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
Lettice	B-pers
Benson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
her	O
Mother	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
an	O
old	O
Gentlewoman	O
had	O
left	O
his	O
Wife	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
not	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
Mr	O
York	O
for	O
6	O
l.	O
7	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
paid	O
her	O
some	O
Money	O
which	O
he	O
owed	O
her	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
likewise	O
confirmed	O
by	O
Sarah	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Tankard	O
being	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
Mr.	O
York	O
depes	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
which	O
was	O
sold	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
which	O
was	O
stolen	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
nothing	O
being	O
plainer	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
12	O
Moidores	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Jacob	B-pers
Hawthorn	I-pers
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Hawthorn	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
about	O
Ten	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
consenting	O
too	O
,	O
she	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	B-place
George	I-place
near	I-place
White-Fryers	I-place
Dock	I-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
going	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
him	O
call	O
for	O
a	O
Winchester	O
,	O
(	O
or	O
Quart	O
)	O
that	O
presently	O
there	O
came	O
up	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Women	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
then	O
lock	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
Key	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
falling	O
upon	O
him	O
without	O
any	O
Provocation	O
,	O
she	O
beat	O
out	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Teeth	O
,	O
and	O
loosened	O
another	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
it	O
has	O
hung	O
by	O
Geometry	O
ever	O
since	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
slung	O
him	O
down	O
and	O
fell	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
cut	O
his	O
Throat	O
if	O
he	O
resisted	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
then	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Sum	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
,	O
she	O
flung	O
her	O
Petticoats	O
over	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
almost	O
smothered	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
down	O
'd	O
upon	O
his	O
Knees	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
If	O
you	O
love	O
a	O
Man	O
let	O
me	O
alone	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
give	O
you	O
Half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
a-piece	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
offered	O
any	O
Violence	O
to	O
him	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
the	O
Constable	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
finding	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Bed	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
positive	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
some	O
Time	O
afterwards	O
asking	O
her	O
who	O
were	O
her	O
Confederates	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
King	I-pers
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
first	O
apprehended	O
her	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
Room	O
,	O
A	O
Knife	O
lay	O
upon	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
which	O
Knife	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
which	O
she	O
offered	O
to	O
cut	O
his	O
Throat	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
then	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
she	O
chang	O
'd	O
a	O
Guinea	O
.	O
Obediah	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
was	O
the	O
Watchman	O
who	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
find	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
Candlestick	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
and	O
hid	O
it	O
under	O
the	O
Bench	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
not	O
be	O
mistaken	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
found	O
a	O
Candlestick	O
under	O
the	O
Bench	O
accordingly	O
.	O
At	O
which	O
Words	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
And	O
ought	O
not	O
the	O
old	O
Rogue	O
to	O
be	O
Prosecuted	O
for	O
stealing	O
my	O
Candlestick	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dykes	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
heard	O
her	O
confess	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
the	O
Constable	O
.	O
She	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
but	O
the	O
common	O
Excuses	O
of	O
the	O
Women	O
of	O
the	O
Town	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hornby	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Gregory	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Ward	I-place
of	I-place
Castle	I-place
Barnard	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Edward	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
and	O
two	O
Guineas	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Ellis	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
2	O
of	O
the	O
Men	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Church-Yard	I-place
,	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
caught	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Throat	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
tripp	O
'd	O
up	O
his	O
Heels	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
beat	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
took	O
away	O
his	O
Money	O
and	O
Watch	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
hearing	O
of	O
Neaves	O
being	O
taken	O
,	O
went	O
and	O
enquired	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
told	O
by	O
Neaves	O
himself	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
,	O
with	O
John	O
Hornby	O
,	O
and	O
Brown	O
,	O
alias	O
Benson	O
,	O
were	O
the	O
Persons	O
which	O
robb	O
'd	O
and	O
abus	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
gave	O
this	O
Deponent	O
an	O
exact	O
Description	O
of	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
repeated	O
the	O
Particulars	O
which	O
happened	O
when	O
they	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Neaves	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Brown	O
,	O
alias	O
Benson	O
,	O
assaulted	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Watch	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
Hornby	O
would	O
have	O
taken	O
his	O
Ring	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
it	O
off	O
his	O
Finger	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
sold	O
the	O
Watch	O
to	O
one	O
Madam	O
Toy	O
,	O
who	O
used	O
to	O
buy	O
their	O
stolen	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
entertain	O
them	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
;	O
that	O
two	O
Days	O
after	O
this	O
Fact	O
,	O
Benson	O
and	O
Hornby	O
went	O
to	O
Norwich	O
.	O
Madam	O
Toy	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
received	O
a	O
Watch	O
of	O
Neaves	O
as	O
a	O
Pledge	O
for	O
Money	O
,	O
Drink	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
remember	O
that	O
Hornby	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
ever	O
seen	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Robertson	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
heard	O
Madam	O
Toy	O
say	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
this	O
Trial	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
knew	O
Hornby	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lodg	O
'd	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
by	O
another	O
Name	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Graves	I-pers
being	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
Hornby	O
's	O
Reputation	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
He	O
had	O
heard	O
an	O
ill	O
Character	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Gamester	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
Neaves	O
,	O
but	O
for	O
the	O
Life	O
he	O
had	O
led	O
this	O
last	O
Half	O
Year	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
Account	O
,	O
nor	O
could	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
call	O
'd	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
say	O
any	O
Thing	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
Course	O
of	O
Life	O
for	O
the	O
last	O
Half	O
Year	O
.	O
He	O
being	O
a	O
Joyner	O
,	O
was	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
followed	O
his	O
Business	O
this	O
last	O
Half	O
Year	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
he	O
had	O
maintained	O
himself	O
.	O
He	O
brought	O
two	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
,	O
the	O
one	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
set	O
up	O
three	O
Shelves	O
,	O
and	O
drove	O
a	O
Staple	O
into	O
a	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Nail	O
into	O
a	O
Lock	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
talk	O
'd	O
about	O
setting	O
up	O
a	O
Bedstead	O
for	O
her	O
in	O
that	O
Time	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Upon	O
his	O
pleading	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Innocence	O
,	O
Neaves	O
desired	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
asked	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
some	O
Time	O
since	O
committed	O
to	O
Tuttle-fields	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
what	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
confidently	O
denied	O
his	O
ever	O
being	O
there	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
his	O
own	O
Father	O
being	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
give	O
him	O
any	O
Character	O
that	O
was	O
to	O
his	O
Advantage	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Whole	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Burden	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
5	O
Broad-Pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
2	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Two-Pence	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
(	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
)	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Bonner	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutrix	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
her	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
missing	O
the	O
Money	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Box	O
,	O
which	O
stood	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
about	O
that	O
Time	O
,	O
buying	O
herself	O
new	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
laying	O
out	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Money	O
in	O
unnecessary	O
Pride	O
,	O
she	O
charging	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
her	O
Money	O
,	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
Father	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Goodin	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Stowell	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Nellson	I-pers
,	O
Mrs.	O
Goodin	O
,	O
and	O
Stephen	B-pers
Woodbridge	I-pers
,	O
all	O
severally	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
her	O
taking	O
the	O
Money	O
without	O
the	O
Knowledge	O
and	O
Consent	O
of	O
her	O
Mistress	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Beadle	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bow	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Shillings	O
and	O
Six-pence	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutrix	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
it	O
being	O
St.	O
David	O
's	O
Day	O
,	O
she	O
stood	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Welch	O
Folks	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
Church	O
,	O
when	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Archer	I-pers
came	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
nothing	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
she	O
searching	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Petticoat	O
and	O
Pocket	O
both	O
cut	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Money	O
gone	O
.	O
Nicholas	O
Archer	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Hand	O
at	O
her	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
held	O
with	O
one	O
Hand	O
in	O
a	O
designing	O
Posture	O
and	O
that	O
then	O
this	O
Deponent	O
saw	O
a	O
naked	O
Knife	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
they	O
caused	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
apprehended	O
,	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
any	O
Money	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
same	O
Knife	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
before	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
which	O
plainly	O
proved	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
cut	O
the	O
Pocket	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
might	O
convey	O
that	O
Money	O
away	O
to	O
an	O
Accomplice	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Susanna	B-pers
Vine	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Bag	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
a	O
Seal	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
French	O
Crown	O
,	O
four	O
Guineas	O
,	O
5	O
Half	O
Guineas	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Steel	O
Buckles	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Silver	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Dean	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Country	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
to	O
Town	O
about	O
Business	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
walked	O
about	O
in	O
his	O
Boots	O
all	O
Day	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
tir	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
towards	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
about	O
9	O
or	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
pass	O
'd	O
through	O
a	O
Street	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
under	O
a	O
Lamp	O
(	O
where	O
he	O
could	O
plainly	O
see	O
her	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
discover	O
her	O
Person	O
)	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Pot	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
You	O
shall	O
do	O
what	O
you	O
will	O
with	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
Pot	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
not	O
willing	O
to	O
have	O
any	O
Thing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
turned	O
away	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
still	O
keeping	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
feel	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
which	O
he	O
refusing	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
stoop	O
'd	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
may	O
go	O
now	O
and	O
be	O
Damn	O
'd	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
running	O
away	O
,	O
he	O
felt	O
in	O
his	O
Pockets	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Money	O
;	O
but	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
got	O
a	O
Watchman	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
her	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
her	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
yet	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
his	O
Surprize	O
was	O
so	O
great	O
at	O
the	O
Loss	O
of	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
Dream	O
of	O
nothing	O
else	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
saw	O
her	O
as	O
plainly	O
in	O
his	O
Sleep	O
by	O
Imagination	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
saw	O
her	O
under	O
the	O
lamp	O
in	O
Reality	O
:	O
However	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
her	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
some	O
Trouble	O
caused	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
apprehended	O
:	O
Susanna	B-pers
Church	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodged	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Night	O
after	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
offer	O
'd	O
her	O
a	O
French	O
Crown	O
to	O
change	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
telling	O
her	O
it	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
for	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
a	O
Half	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
changing	O
it	O
,	O
paid	O
this	O
Deponent	O
four	O
Shillings	O
she	O
owed	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Night	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
happening	O
between	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
her	O
Sister	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Philip	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
this	O
Deponent	O
turn	O
'd	O
'em	O
all	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
then	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
she	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
Country	O
Man	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
herself	O
had	O
the	O
Money	O
taken	O
from	O
her	O
at	O
Church	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
Man	O
who	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
what	O
he	O
pleased	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
hang	O
20	O
before	O
she	O
would	O
hang	O
herself	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
plain	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
having	O
bought	O
new	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
consum	O
'd	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Money	O
in	O
that	O
little	O
Interval	O
of	O
Time	O
from	O
the	O
Country	O
Man	O
's	O
being	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
to	O
her	O
being	O
taken	O
up	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Rawlins	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Thomas	I-pers
Rawlins	I-pers
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Ashley	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Ashby	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Rowden	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Hulks	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Mr.	O
Francis	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
2	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
Moidore	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
coming	O
home	O
in	O
a	O
Hackney	O
Coach	O
,	O
between	O
Watling-street	B-place
and	I-place
St.	I-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
School	I-place
in	I-place
St.	I-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Church-Yard	I-place
,	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Coachman	O
commanded	O
to	O
stop	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
a	O
Man	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
a	O
Pistol	O
into	O
it	O
,	O
demanded	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
four	O
others	O
came	O
and	O
presented	O
Pistols	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
saying	O
they	O
had	O
no	O
Time	O
to	O
lose	O
,	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
into	O
his	O
Fob	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
his	O
Watch	O
and	O
Money	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
produced	O
the	O
Watch	O
in	O
Court	O
and	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Dalton	I-pers
,	O
which	O
Watch	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Dalton	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
(	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
the	O
Admonitions	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
to	O
keep	O
up	O
to	O
Truth	O
,	O
and	O
notwithstanding	O
the	O
Indulgence	O
he	O
had	O
met	O
with	O
,	O
as	O
being	O
admitted	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
careful	O
how	O
he	O
swore	O
in	O
a	O
Matter	O
of	O
such	O
Consequence	O
)	O
That	O
he	O
,	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Person	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
attacked	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
himself	O
went	O
first	O
up	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Rowden	O
took	O
the	O
Watch	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
a	O
Guinea	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
and	O
Rawlins	O
kept	O
secret	O
from	O
the	O
others	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Watch	O
they	O
pawned	O
for	O
two	O
Guineas	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
inform	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
Custody	O
,	O
who	O
setch	O
'd	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
pawn	O
by	O
his	O
Directions	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
being	O
in	O
search	O
of	O
Disorderly	O
Houses	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
Dalton	O
,	O
against	O
whom	O
he	O
having	O
Information	O
,	O
he	O
seized	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
made	O
an	O
Ingenious	O
Confession	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
be	O
admitted	O
as	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
be	O
of	O
great	O
Service	O
to	O
the	O
Public	O
,	O
and	O
naming	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
with	O
them	O
robb	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
,	O
and	O
shew	O
'd	O
them	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
Rawlins	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
had	O
the	O
Fellow	O
,	O
and	O
directing	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Chick-Lane	O
,	O
he	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
Brother	O
Robert	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
,	O
who	O
confirm	O
'd	O
his	O
Evidence	O
,	O
went	O
and	O
seized	O
Rawlins	O
and	O
Rowden	O
,	O
Sword	O
in	O
Hand	O
,	O
Ashley	O
made	O
no	O
Resistance	O
,	O
but	O
got	O
under	O
the	O
Bed	O
;	O
with	O
them	O
they	O
found	O
a	O
Pistol	O
the	O
exact	O
Fellow	O
to	O
that	O
which	O
Dalton	O
gave	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
drawing	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
a	O
Slug	O
therein	O
,	O
which	O
exactly	O
corresponded	O
with	O
the	O
Slug	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
Dalton	O
's	O
Pistol	O
;	O
for	O
great	O
Williams	O
they	O
had	O
but	O
very	O
little	O
Excuse	O
,	O
only	O
pretended	O
not	O
to	O
have	O
any	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
Dalton	O
:	O
But	O
he	O
produced	O
one	O
Wyatt	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
were	O
very	O
well	O
acquainted	O
,	O
and	O
frequently	O
met	O
and	O
lodged	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
all	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Mr.	O
Downs	O
near	B-place
Snow-Hill	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
last	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Purse	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
Ten	O
Guineas	O
and	O
14	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
they	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
)	O
and	O
a	O
Bunch	O
of	O
Keys	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
near	O
Snow-Hill	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
about	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
fearing	O
he	O
might	O
fall	O
amongst	O
Thieves	O
,	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
immediately	O
attacked	O
by	O
several	O
Men	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
his	O
Money	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
taking	O
it	O
they	O
let	O
it	O
fall	O
into	O
the	O
Mud	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
first	O
who	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
had	O
a	O
drawn	O
Sword	O
and	O
a	O
Pistol	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
swore	O
if	O
he	O
spoke	O
a	O
Word	O
they	O
would	O
shoot	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
a	O
Link-Boy	O
with	O
him	O
they	O
put	O
out	O
the	O
Link	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
stood	O
on	O
his	O
Right	O
Side	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
at	O
his	O
Left	O
,	O
with	O
Pistols	O
,	O
whilst	O
a	O
Third	O
pick	O
'd	O
out	O
his	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
though	O
a	O
Watchman	O
came	O
by	O
in	O
the	O
Interim	O
they	O
never	O
fled	O
,	O
nor	O
dare	O
he	O
call	O
out	O
whilst	O
they	O
stood	O
in	O
that	O
Posture	O
:	O
After	O
this	O
they	O
drove	O
him	O
down	O
Fleet-Ditch	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Dalton	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
attack	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
and	O
Place	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
fight	O
a	O
Duel	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
match	O
him	O
at	O
Sword	O
he	O
could	O
at	O
Pistol	O
,	O
and	O
drawing	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
he	O
obliged	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
drop	O
the	O
Point	O
of	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
otherwise	O
he	O
threatned	O
to	O
shoot	O
him	O
:	O
Rawlins	O
and	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
held	O
the	O
Pistols	O
at	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
Rowdens	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
but	O
filling	O
down	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
only	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
Shilling	O
and	O
a	O
Bunch	O
of	O
Keys	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
flung	O
into	O
Fleet-Ditch	O
;	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
remembring	O
the	O
Circumstances	O
as	O
Dalton	O
related	O
them	O
,	O
confirmed	O
his	O
Evidence	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Rawlins	I-pers
was	O
again	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cane	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
3	O
Seals	O
,	O
and	O
8	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
about	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Coach	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
in	O
Castle-Yard	B-place
,	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
by	O
two	O
Persons	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
putting	O
a	O
Pistol	O
into	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
took	O
his	O
Watch	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Watch	O
being	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
by	O
Mr	O
Willis	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
Dalton	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
Dalton	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
Coach	O
they	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
for	O
Bellamy	O
being	O
taken	O
from	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
resolved	O
to	O
leave	O
Haul	O
Cly	O
,	O
snatching	O
of	O
Pockets	O
)	O
and	O
rob	O
Coaches	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Rawlins	O
and	O
he	O
hustled	O
for	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
Rawlins	O
won	O
it	O
;	O
afterwards	O
Rawlins	O
and	O
he	O
not	O
agreeing	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
put	O
in	O
the	O
Hands	O
of	O
Wyat	O
.	O
Wyat	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Rawlins	O
and	O
Dalton	O
differed	O
about	O
the	O
Watch	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
put	O
in	O
his	O
Wife	O
's	O
Hands	O
,	O
this	O
Watch	O
Mr.	O
Willis	O
found	O
at	O
Wyat	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
a	O
Pepper-Mill	O
over	O
the	O
Chimney-Piece	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Information	O
of	O
Dalton	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cobbs	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
2	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Beans	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Bushel	O
of	O
Barley	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
defective	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cobbs	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Tottenham	B-place
,	O
was	O
again	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bay	O
Gelding	O
,	O
Price	O
5	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ayliff	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
Horse	O
being	O
lost	O
from	O
Grass	O
about	O
Christmas	O
last	O
,	O
he	O
advertis	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
Intelligence	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
White-Hart	O
at	O
Tottenham	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
he	O
had	O
stolen	O
from	O
Grass	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
made	O
himself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Horse	O
from	O
Grass	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Horse	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
very	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cobbs	I-pers
,	O
was	O
a	O
3d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
George	B-pers
Risley	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
last	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
9	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Risley	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
at	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
between	O
Hammersmith	B-place
and	I-place
Chiswick	I-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Robert	O
Ward	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
Cobbs	O
bid	O
him	O
Stand	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
not	O
readily	O
obeying	O
,	O
he	O
cut	O
him	O
over	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
then	O
Ward	O
took	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
between	O
them	O
they	O
took	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
asking	O
for	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
them	O
he	O
left	O
it	O
at	O
a	O
Place	O
where	O
he	O
drank	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
then	O
mounted	O
their	O
Horses	O
,	O
and	O
rode	O
away	O
:	O
He	O
further	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
talking	O
familiarly	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
Cobbs	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
Cobbs	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
Ward	O
had	O
cheated	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
but	O
one	O
Shilling	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
,	O
with	O
John	O
Cobbs	O
,	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
and	O
Place	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
and	O
confirmed	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Particulars	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Benson	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Boyston	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Gale	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Kiddy	I-pers
George	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Crowder	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
James	B-pers
Colvert	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Colvert	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
near	B-place
the	I-place
Dog-House	I-place
Bar	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
April	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
Pistol	O
go	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
a	O
Man	O
appear	O
'd	O
on	O
each	O
Side	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
deliver	O
:	O
Accordingly	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
his	O
Watch	O
and	O
Money	O
:	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
saw	O
but	O
three	O
Persons	O
himself	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Coachman	O
told	O
him	O
there	O
were	O
four	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Neaves	I-pers
made	O
himself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
;	O
and	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
attack	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
and	O
Place	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
(	O
by	O
the	O
same	O
Token	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
that	O
very	O
Night	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
French	O
Person	O
at	O
Hogsdon	O
)	O
that	O
Crowder	O
stopp	O
'd	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
his	O
Place	O
,	O
but	O
shot	O
at	O
the	O
Coachman	O
before	O
he	O
bid	O
him	O
Stand	O
,	O
that	O
Benson	O
and	O
Gale	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Coach-Doors	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
the	O
Prosesecutor	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Person	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
24	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
describing	O
the	O
Postures	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
stood	O
in	O
:	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
shared	O
the	O
Money	O
amongst	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
Gale	O
Half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
for	O
his	O
Share	O
in	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
which	O
Watch	O
Benson	O
pawn	O
'd	O
next	O
Day	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bradford	O
,	O
for	O
Two	O
Guineas	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bradford	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
Benson	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
Watch	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
2	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Watch	O
being	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
he	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
which	O
Benson	O
pawn	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
Time	O
it	O
had	O
a	O
black	O
String	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Colvert	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
Watch	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
black	O
String	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Hillditch	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
by	O
the	O
Information	O
of	O
Madam	O
Toy	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
altogether	O
,	O
they	O
Lodging	O
all	O
in	O
one	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
they	O
were	O
provided	O
with	O
Pistols	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
Time	O
,	O
Neaves	O
being	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
a	O
full	O
Discovery	O
.	O
Several	O
Witnesses	O
appear	O
'd	O
in	O
Behalf	O
of	O
Crowder	O
and	O
Gale	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
:	O
but	O
as	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
the	O
Reputation	O
of	O
Persons	O
have	O
but	O
little	O
Effect	O
,	O
where	O
Facts	O
are	O
plainly	O
and	O
positively	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
all	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Mansel	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
together	O
with	O
Edward	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Crowder	I-pers
,	O
did	O
assault	O
Marmaduke	B-pers
Hendery	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
a	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Spectacles	O
and	O
an	O
Almanack	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Toon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
with	O
George	B-pers
Gale	I-pers
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Benson	I-pers
,	O
did	O
assault	O
James	B-pers
Flemming	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
fifty	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Guineas	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Flemming	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
coming	O
from	O
a	O
Tavern	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
attack	O
'd	O
by	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
Men	O
,	O
who	O
bid	O
him	O
deliver	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
holding	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
shoot	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
feeling	O
in	O
his	O
Pockets	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
perceive	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
their	O
demanding	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
them	O
two	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
off	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Neaves	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
going	O
down	O
Crispin-street	B-place
,	I-place
Spittle-fields	I-place
,	O
resolved	O
to	O
stop	O
the	O
first	O
single	O
Man	O
they	O
met	O
,	O
and	O
meeting	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
his	O
Watch	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
pawned	O
the	O
Watch	O
to	O
one	O
Madam	O
Toy	O
,	O
who	O
,	O
he	O
says	O
,	O
keeps	O
an	O
ill	O
House	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
the	O
Water	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
had	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
a	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
for	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
Brown	O
and	O
Crowder	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
shared	O
that	O
amongst	O
us	O
,	O
for	O
when	O
we	O
have	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
we	O
cheat	O
one	O
another	O
;	O
the	O
Watch	O
being	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
his	O
knowing	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
Neaves	O
,	O
but	O
Neaves	O
affirmed	O
that	O
they	O
have	O
been	O
acquainted	O
together	O
ever	O
since	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
returned	O
from	O
Transportation	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
5	O
Months	O
since	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
wilful	O
and	O
corrupt	O
Perjury	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
done	O
in	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
charg	O
'd	O
before	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Worthington	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Wilful	O
and	O
corrupt	O
Perjury	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
appearing	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Gun	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
wilful	O
and	O
corrupt	O
Perjury	O
,	O
in	O
swearing	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
some	O
Time	O
since	O
,	O
by	O
Samuel	B-pers
Vevers	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Vevers	O
then	O
clearing	O
himself	O
by	O
the	O
Testimony	O
of	O
several	O
indisputable	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
and	O
proving	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
,	O
that	O
Robert	O
Gun	O
was	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
ill	O
Fame	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
were	O
pleased	O
to	O
grant	O
him	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
his	O
Indictment	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
Robert	B-pers
Gun	I-pers
absconded	O
;	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Vevers	O
willing	O
to	O
vindicate	O
his	O
Character	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
so	O
aspers	O
'd	O
,	O
pursued	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
at	O
Bristol	O
,	O
and	O
bringing	O
him	O
to	O
Town	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
Newgate	O
.	O
Being	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
in	O
a	O
miserable	O
Condition	O
,	O
dejected	O
and	O
confus	O
'd	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Vevers	O
(	O
upon	O
his	O
asking	O
Pardon	O
,	O
confessing	O
his	O
Crime	O
,	O
and	O
giving	O
Security	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
towards	O
him	O
)	O
generously	O
dropp	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
had	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
in	O
Court	O
to	O
prove	O
him	O
perjur	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Affidavits	O
made	O
by	O
two	O
Persons	O
,	O
who	O
heard	O
this	O
Robert	O
Gun	O
confess	O
,	O
That	O
since	O
his	O
prosecuting	O
Mr.	O
Vevers	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
stript	O
off	O
his	O
own	O
Cloaths	O
himself	O
,	O
flung	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
Ditch	O
,	O
and	O
wounded	O
himself	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
designing	O
to	O
swear	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Vevers	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Court	O
taking	O
Notice	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
suffering	O
by	O
Sickness	O
,	O
Want	O
and	O
Imprisonment	O
,	O
had	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
lowest	O
Degree	O
of	O
Misery	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
believed	O
Vevers	O
had	O
suffered	O
wrongfully	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Character	O
,	O
was	O
vindicated	O
by	O
Gun	O
's	O
Confession	O
,	O
Vevers	O
did	O
not	O
bring	O
him	O
upon	O
his	O
Trial	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Lewin	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Archer	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Pearson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Foreign	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Silk	O
Purse	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Beggars	O
Opera	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Passage	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
New	B-place
Playhouse	I-place
,	O
she	O
had	O
her	O
Pocket	O
pick	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
being	O
behind	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
seeming	O
to	O
be	O
of	O
the	O
Prosession	O
of	O
Divers	O
,	O
by	O
their	O
jostling	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
hearing	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
many	O
Minutes	O
before	O
been	O
charg	O
'd	O
with	O
an	O
Offence	O
of	O
the	O
like	O
Nature	O
she	O
tax	O
'd	O
them	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
when	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Archer	I-pers
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
pay	O
what	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
would	O
say	O
the	O
had	O
lost	O
.	O
This	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
made	O
it	O
appear	O
against	O
Archer	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
but	O
the	O
cunning	O
Fox	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
John	B-pers
Barrow	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Lombard-street	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Clough	I-pers
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
appearing	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Adcock	I-pers
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Egerton	I-pers
10	O
d.	O
William	B-pers
Bayley	I-pers
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Lambert	I-pers
39s	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Covey	I-pers
Single	O
felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Buckstone	I-pers
6d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
David	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
Single	O
Felony	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Rebecca	B-pers
English	I-pers
Single	O
Felony	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Burdet	I-pers
4s	O
.	O
and	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Brillard	I-pers
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Boswell	I-pers
4s	O
.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Beal	I-pers
45.	O
and	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Hutton	I-pers
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samuel	B-pers
Butt	I-pers
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Salter	I-pers
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Current	I-pers
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Willson	I-pers
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Pitcher	I-pers
Single	O
Felony	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
David	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Gerhard	I-pers
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Katherine	B-pers
Bryan	I-pers
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Boystone	I-pers
4s	O
.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samuel	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Phillip	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Waller	I-pers
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
following	O
,	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
Evidence	O
,	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
Jasper	B-pers
Hatton	I-pers
Martha	B-pers
Pew	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Presgrave	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Ryan	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Fotherby	I-pers
,	O
Bridget	B-pers
Coffell	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Wiltshire	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
,	O
at	O
their	O
being	O
discharg	O
'd	O
,	O
begg	O
'd	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
favourable	O
Report	O
might	O
be	O
made	O
to	O
his	O
Majesty	O
,	O
with	O
regard	O
to	O
Joseph	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
and	O
Anthony	B-pers
Beadle	I-pers
,	O
that	O
they	O
might	O
be	O
Transported	O
.	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
ended	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
follows	O
:	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
29.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Burden	I-pers
,	O
Anthony	B-pers
Beadle	I-pers
,	O
Heither	O
Landell	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Jynkins	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Prince	I-pers
,	O
Susanna	B-pers
Vine	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Hendron	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Pendergrass	I-pers
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Rawlins	I-pers
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Ashby	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hulks	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Cobbs	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Benson	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Gale	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Croweder	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Toon	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Septon	I-pers
,	O
Lawrence	B-pers
ClinSmith	I-pers
,	O
Ben	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Russell	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Holden	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Crouch	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Par	I-pers
,	O
Since	O
dead	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Hornby	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
2.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Fuller	I-pers
,	O
for	O
Manslaughter	O
,	O
and	O
Peter	B-pers
Field	I-pers
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
marrying	O
two	O
Wives	O
.	O
Transportation	O
39.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Adcock	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Mountague	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bayley	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Lannbert	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Covey	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Buckstone	I-pers
,	O
David	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
,	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Inglish	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Burdett	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Brisland	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Boswell	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Beal	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hutton	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Butt	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Salter	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Currant	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Willson	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Pitcher	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Lewin	I-pers
,	O
David	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Gerbard	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Perkins	I-pers
,	O
Katharine	O
Bryan	O
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Boystone	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
Philip	B-pers
Laurence	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Waller	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Cobitch	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Yellop	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
,	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Drew	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
.	O
ADVERTISEMENTS	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
bad	O
of	O
JAMES	B-pers
DALTON	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Wood-Street	O
Compter	O
,	O
A	O
promiscuous	O
Mixture	O
of	O
Iniquity	O
,	O
Ingenuity	O
,	O
and	O
facetious	O
Drollery	O
,	O
being	O
A	O
GENUINE	O
NARRATIVE	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
STREET-ROBBERIES	O
committed	O
by	O
James	B-pers
Dalton	I-pers
and	O
his	O
Accomplices	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
tried	O
this	O
Sessions	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
whom	O
Dalton	O
(	O
called	O
their	O
Captain	O
)	O
and	O
Neaves	O
were	O
admitted	O
Evidences	O
