TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
At	O
the	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
And	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
16th	O
,	O
17th	O
,	O
18th	O
,	O
19th	O
,	O
and	O
21st	O
,	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
1728	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Second	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
EDWARD	B-pers
BECHER	I-pers
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Raymond	I-pers
;	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Hale	I-pers
;	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Denton	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
Raby	O
,	O
Deputy-Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
other	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
aforesaid	O
;	O
Together	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
,	O
Char	B-pers
Erreskine	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Fidoe	I-pers
,	O
Humphry	B-pers
Pew	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Clarkson	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Hays	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Gigner	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Tuckey	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
,	O
Edw	B-pers
Holloway	I-pers
,	O
Will	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ingram	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Fenerell	I-pers
,	O
Thom	B-pers
Richman	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Frith	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Samms	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
Benj	B-pers
Timbrell	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Tame	I-pers
,	O
Nich	B-pers
Sanders	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Elkins	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Lacy	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Spicer	I-pers
.	O
James	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Ewers	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Gile	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Draper	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Tho	O
.	O
Draper	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
another	O
Person	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Tankard	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
whilst	O
the	O
Servant	O
went	O
to	O
fetch	O
Change	O
,	O
after	O
they	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
pay	O
,	O
they	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
getting	O
some	O
Information	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
at	O
an	O
ill	O
House	O
in	O
White-Horse-Alley	O
,	O
near	O
Chick-Lane	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
thirty	O
nine	O
Shillings	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Churchill	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
Bottles	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Vault	O
belonging	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Nevill	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
;	O
and	O
another	O
Peruke	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Tho-Boyce	B-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
eight	O
Broad-Pieces	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
twenty	O
three	O
Shillings	O
each	O
;	O
four	O
Broad-Pieces	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
twenty	O
five	O
Shillings	O
each	O
;	O
three	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
thirty	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Glawson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
tho	O
'	O
the	O
Circumstances	O
were	O
pretty	O
strong	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
appearing	O
to	O
her	O
Character	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Coulson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Box-Iron	O
,	O
Value	O
two	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Winkles	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White-Chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Duroy	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
two	O
cloth	O
Coats	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Walter	B-pers
Gaven	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
asleep	O
,	O
on	O
Board	O
the	O
Scipio-Galley	O
,	O
then	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
River	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
Key	O
of	O
his	O
Chest	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
Key	O
he	O
opened	O
the	O
Chest	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
put	O
on	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
on	O
his	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Watch	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Parrot	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Allard	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
George	O
Allard	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
Tho	B-pers
Carey	I-pers
,	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Tankard	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
under	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
conceal	O
it	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drinking	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
just	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
Bar-Keeper	O
if	O
she	O
miss	O
'd	O
nothing	O
,	O
who	O
looking	O
about	O
,	O
miss	O
'd	O
a	O
Tankard	O
,	O
which	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
by	O
this	O
Deponent	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
very	O
well	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
Bar-Keeper	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Tankard	O
to	O
surprize	O
her	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
contrary	O
Excuse	O
,	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
The	O
Bar-Keeper	O
had	O
given	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
fetch	O
her	O
some	O
Water	O
in	O
;	O
but	O
before	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
sign	O
'd	O
his	O
Confession	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
own	O
Hand	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
the	O
plain	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Pryor	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
steel	O
Chain	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Baxter	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
so	O
lewd	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
ask	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
a	O
Brandy-Shop	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
silly	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
comply	O
;	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
said	O
upon	O
Oath	O
,	O
He	O
had	O
no	O
more	O
Familiarity	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
than	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Dram	O
with	O
her	O
when	O
she	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
what	O
haste	O
she	O
could	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
;	O
at	O
which	O
the	O
People	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
asked	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
nothing	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
feeling	O
for	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
found	O
it	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
positive	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
first	O
into	O
her	O
Company	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
's	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Lagden	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
two	O
Shillings	O
and	O
Sixpence	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lagden	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
passing	O
between	O
Holloway-Lane	B-place
and	O
Hog-Lane	B-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
an	O
Alley	O
,	O
and	O
turning	O
short	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
If	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
any	O
Money	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
startled	O
at	O
the	O
Suddenness	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
coming	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
held	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
against	O
his	O
Will	O
and	O
Consent	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
then	O
seiz	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
for	O
Help	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
any	O
Assistance	O
came	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
beat	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
had	O
almost	O
lost	O
his	O
Breath	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
then	O
one	O
Samuel	B-pers
Boyce	I-pers
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
;	O
that	O
presently	O
Samuel	O
Boyce	O
recover	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
call	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
came	O
and	O
apprehended	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Samuel	O
Boyce	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
and	O
Place	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
struggling	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
saying	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
got	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
advised	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
his	O
half	O
Crown	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
about	O
his	O
Business	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
at	O
length	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
the	O
half	O
Crown	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
;	O
soon	O
after	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
call	O
Help	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
proved	O
resolute	O
,	O
and	O
beat	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
delivered	O
him	O
his	O
half	O
Crown	O
again	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
heard	O
an	O
Outcry	O
of	O
a	O
Street-Robber	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-House	O
for	O
Help	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
but	O
one	O
Watchman	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
refused	O
to	O
go	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
went	O
by	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
when	O
several	O
were	O
got	O
round	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
had	O
laid	O
Hands	O
on	O
him	O
,	O
one	O
saying	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
dangerous	O
Fellow	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
seize	O
him	O
for	O
twenty	O
Pounds	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
's	I-place
White-Chappel	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
seven	O
hundred	O
Weight	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
Value	O
four	O
Pounds	O
eleven	O
Shillings	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Scales	I-pers
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Tbo	O
.	O
Scales	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Scales	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
at	O
several	O
Times	O
,	O
a	O
considerable	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
melting	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
some	O
Ladles	O
full	O
had	O
in	O
the	O
Sand	O
.	O
His	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
at	O
several	O
Times	O
given	O
of	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Lead	O
to	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
and	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
which	O
James	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
had	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Lead	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
Brooks	O
in	O
all	O
about	O
seven	O
hundred	O
Weight	O
.	O
This	O
Confession	O
being	O
sign	O
'd	O
with	O
his	O
own	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
voluntarily	O
,	O
without	O
either	O
Menaces	O
,	O
Threats	O
,	O
or	O
Promises	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
James	O
Brooks	O
,	O
to	O
prove	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
Lead	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
,	O
though	O
it	O
was	O
plainly	O
proved	O
he	O
was	O
concerned	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
only	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Brooks	O
:	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
Nathanael	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hornsey	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Maud	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
Value	O
five	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
Value	O
one	O
Shilling	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Charles	B-pers
Acton	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
Place	O
,	O
(	O
being	O
near	O
the	O
Devil's-Gate	B-place
Hornsey-Lane	I-place
)	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Brass	O
Buckles	O
,	O
Value	O
Sixpence	O
,	O
and	O
Twopence	O
Halfpenny	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Maud	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
he	O
,	O
with	O
two	O
of	O
his	O
School-Fellows	O
,	O
were	O
going	O
from	O
Hornsey	O
to	O
Highgate	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Hornsey-Lane	O
,	O
they	O
met	O
three	O
Men	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
whom	O
asked	O
him	O
for	O
Three-half-pence	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Drink	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
looking	O
at	O
his	O
Ring	O
,	O
said	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
Gold	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
saying	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
Gold	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
afterwards	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
silk	O
Handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
Being	O
asked	O
which	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
did	O
this	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
Nathanael	O
Walker	O
;	O
but	O
for	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
to	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Acton	I-pers
confirm	O
'd	O
every	O
Part	O
of	O
this	O
Evidence	O
,	O
adding	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
Walker	O
took	O
the	O
Ring	O
and	O
Handkerchief	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Maud	O
,	O
as	O
likewise	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Buckles	O
,	O
and	O
Twopence	O
Halfpenny	O
from	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
Evans	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
presently	O
after	O
a	O
Coach	O
came	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
told	O
the	O
Coachman	O
of	O
their	O
being	O
robb	O
'd	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
stood	O
about	O
twelve	O
Yards	O
Distance	O
from	O
the	O
young	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
robb	O
'd	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
Walker	O
take	O
the	O
Ring	O
from	O
the	O
Finger	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Maud	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
the	O
very	O
Men	O
who	O
did	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
a	O
plain	O
Sight	O
of	O
them	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
them	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Coach	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
others	O
in	O
Pursuit	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Birch	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
on	O
his	O
Coach-Box	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
young	O
Gentlemen	O
told	O
him	O
they	O
were	O
robb	O
'd	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
left	O
his	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
pursu	O
'd	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
them	O
begin	O
to	O
run	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
first	O
espy	O
'd	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
almost	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
Taylor	O
say	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
presently	O
took	O
Evans	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
neither	O
the	O
Ring	O
,	O
nor	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
came	O
out	O
for	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
Money	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
:	O
He	O
further	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
scarce	O
lost	O
Sight	O
of	O
them	O
till	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
taken	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
White	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
hearing	O
a	O
Noise	O
of	O
Highwaymen	O
,	O
went	O
in	O
Pursuit	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
he	O
took	O
Walker	O
in	O
an	O
Elm-Tree	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Ring	O
and	O
Handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
given	O
him	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Company	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
himself	O
.	O
The	O
Ring	O
and	O
Handkerchief	O
were	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Maud	O
,	O
the	O
Ring	O
being	O
very	O
remarkable	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Funeral	O
Ring	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Maud	O
's	O
Grandfather	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
his	O
Name	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
Humphry	O
Primate	O
.	O
Other	O
Witnesses	O
confirming	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
before	O
they	O
were	O
well	O
out	O
of	O
Sight	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Time	O
of	O
their	O
being	O
first	O
pursu	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
ran	O
,	O
and	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
escape	O
from	O
the	O
Hands	O
of	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
acknowledg	O
'd	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
Company	O
together	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
all	O
three	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Meagre	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
's	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Wainwright	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Perspective-Glass	O
,	O
Value	O
Onepenny	O
,	O
and	O
Twopence	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
an	O
open	O
Place	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
Moorfields	B-place
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Henry	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
Value	O
two	O
Shillings	O
and	O
Sixpence	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
an	O
open	O
Place	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
Moorfields	B-place
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
Time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Beal	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
in	O
an	O
open	O
Place	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
Moorfields	B-place
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Cotton	O
Cap	O
,	O
Value	O
one	O
Shilling	O
,	O
a	O
Frock	O
,	O
and	O
and	O
Iron	O
Key	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
first	O
Indictment	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Wainwright	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
Twelve	O
and	O
One	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
assaulted	O
him	O
in	O
Moorfields	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
holding	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
demanding	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
then	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Perspective-Glass	O
,	O
and	O
Twopence	O
Farthing	O
in	O
Money	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Perspective-Glass	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
so	O
dark	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
plainly	O
see	O
and	O
distinguish	O
him	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
second	O
Indictment	O
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
about	O
Eleven	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Person	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
middle	O
Moor-Fields	B-place
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
Blood	O
if	O
you	O
speak	O
a	O
Word	O
I	O
'll	O
shoot	O
you	O
through	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
holding	O
a	O
Pistol	O
presented	O
at	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
no	O
Money	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
saying	O
it	O
was	O
better	O
than	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
must	O
change	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
his	O
own	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
a	O
light	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
plainly	O
discover	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
held	O
the	O
Pistol	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
last	O
Indictment	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Beal	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
August	O
between	O
Twelve	O
and	O
One	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
from	O
Bartholomew-Fair	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Moor-Fields	B-place
in	O
the	O
Foot-Path	O
way	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Man	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
holding	O
a	O
Pistol	O
presented	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
D	O
-	O
m	O
you	O
we	O
have	O
been	O
Gaming	O
,	O
and	O
must	O
have	O
Money	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
told	O
them	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
rifled	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Cotton	O
Cap	O
,	O
an	O
Iron	O
Key	O
,	O
a	O
Brass	O
Shilling	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Fustian	O
Frock	O
which	O
they	O
made	O
him	O
pull	O
off	O
,	O
but	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
because	O
it	O
would	O
not	O
sit	O
the	O
other	O
Person	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
held	O
the	O
Pistol	O
at	O
his	O
Breast	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
plainly	O
discovered	O
him	O
to	O
have	O
on	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
,	O
a	O
black	O
Cap	O
,	O
a	O
flaxen	O
Whig	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Fustian	O
Frock	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
on	O
at	O
his	O
Trial	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Three	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Mackcullister	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Hyrons	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Thomas	B-pers
Myers	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
Value	O
two	O
Shillings	O
,	O
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
Value	O
five	O
Shillings	O
,	O
a	O
Cane	O
,	O
Value	O
five	O
Shillings	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Gold	O
Buttons	O
,	O
and	O
eighteen	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Myers	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
September	O
between	O
One	O
and	O
Two	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
through	O
Shorts-Garden	B-place
,	O
and	O
somebody	O
kick	O
'd	O
his	O
Legs	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
about	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
was	O
John	B-pers
Hyrons	I-pers
with	O
another	O
Man	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
why	O
he	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
walk	O
faster	O
that	O
he	O
still	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
ill	O
Language	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
some	O
distance	O
from	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
he	O
first	O
assaulted	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
struck	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
kick	O
'd	O
up	O
his	O
Heels	O
,	O
that	O
then	O
the	O
others	O
with	O
Hyrons	O
fell	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
Peruke	O
,	O
Cane	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Gold	O
Buttons	O
a	O
Seal	O
and	O
eighteen	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Buckles	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
stich	O
'd	O
to	O
his	O
Strap	O
,	O
the	O
Shank	O
being	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
unbuckle	O
the	O
Shoe	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
tore	O
it	O
off	O
with	O
Violence	O
:	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
bright	O
Moon-light	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
could	O
plainly	O
distinguish	O
John	B-pers
Hyrons	I-pers
,	O
and	O
pursu	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
without	O
his	O
Shoes	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
one	O
Rouse	O
a	O
Watchman	O
,	O
who	O
he	O
charg	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
Rouse	O
pretended	O
he	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
mad	O
to	O
Charge	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
at	O
which	O
time	O
Hyron	O
got	O
away	O
by	O
the	O
Management	O
of	O
the	O
Watchman	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Briggs	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
took	O
Mackcullister	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
and	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
then	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Myers	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
one	O
Street	O
who	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
to	O
sell	O
Mr.	O
Myers	O
's	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
likewise	O
a	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
for	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
Sold	O
:	O
At	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
he	O
told	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
Sold	O
the	O
Buckles	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
his	O
Directions	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecuter	O
.	O
Justice	O
Ellis	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Mackcullister	O
confess	O
'd	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
with	O
one	O
Street	O
Sold	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Buckles	O
to	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Holiday	O
who	O
keeps	O
a	O
Silversmiths-Shop	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
for	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
Sold	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
after	O
some	O
Trouble	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Holiday	O
produced	O
the	O
Buckles	O
by	O
the	O
Directions	O
of	O
Mackcullister	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Travers	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
bought	O
a	O
Hat	O
of	O
Mackcullister	O
(	O
which	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Day	O
after	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
)	O
for	O
Ninepence	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
Brandy-Shop	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Hat	O
was	O
wore	O
pretty	O
much	O
about	O
the	O
Rim	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
Holes	O
,	O
or	O
Slits	O
in	O
it	O
:	O
This	O
Hat	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Description	O
she	O
gave	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
was	O
like	O
his	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
wore	O
about	O
the	O
Edges	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
some	O
Holes	O
,	O
or	O
Slits	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Travers	I-pers
having	O
sold	O
the	O
Hat	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
she	O
bought	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
Tho	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
hearing	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
had	O
committed	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
belonging	O
to	O
his	O
Company	O
,	O
he	O
enquired	O
further	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Mackcullister	O
had	O
quitted	O
his	O
Post	O
at	O
the	O
Tilt-Yard	O
Guard	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
Neglect	O
of	O
Duty	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
committed	O
to	O
the	O
Savoy	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Savoy	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
by	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Exciseman	O
(	O
Mr.	O
Myers	O
)	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Hand	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
,	O
with	O
Street	O
,	O
sold	O
the	O
Buckles	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
this	O
Information	O
,	O
this	O
Deponent	O
gave	O
Notice	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Ellis	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
him	O
brought	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Warrant	O
and	O
there	O
this	O
Deponent	O
heard	O
Mackcullister	O
confess	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
for	O
which	O
the	O
Buckles	O
were	O
sold	O
,	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
Buckles	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
,	O
after	O
some	O
Trouble	O
,	O
apprehended	O
John	B-pers
Hyrons	I-pers
,	O
and	O
confining	O
him	O
under	O
a	O
Guard	O
,	O
this	O
Robbery	O
being	O
mentioned	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
the	O
Wig	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
worth	O
Two	O
pence	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Company	O
that	O
Night	O
with	O
those	O
who	O
committed	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Rowse	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Watchman	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
He	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
Nailor	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
found	O
Mackcullister	O
in	O
Southwark	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
You	O
have	O
done	O
finely	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
committed	O
a	O
Robbery	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
answered	O
,	O
It	O
is	O
too	O
late	O
,	O
I	O
fear	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
suffer	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Leves	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Vaux	I-pers
,	O
Stephen	B-pers
Burnet	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Barnet	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Barnham	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Featherby	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
Value	O
four	O
Pounds	O
,	O
a	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
,	O
three	O
Pounds	O
,	O
eleven	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
fourteen	O
Guineas	O
in	O
Gold	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Yard	I-place
of	I-place
Farringdon	I-place
without	I-place
.	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
between	O
Twelve	O
and	O
One	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
Coach	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Inner-Temple	O
,	O
and	O
near	O
the	O
great	O
Toy-Shop	O
,	O
by	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Persons	O
dogging	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
scarce	O
lost	O
Sight	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
Water-Lane	O
,	O
when	O
Barnham	O
and	O
Vaux	O
bid	O
the	O
Coachman	O
stand	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
Head	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
them	O
very	O
plainly	O
,	O
when	O
immediately	O
Levee	O
and	O
Featherby	O
assaulted	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
a	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
(	O
which	O
he	O
has	O
since	O
found	O
by	O
the	O
Direction	O
of	O
Levee	O
)	O
and	O
eleven	O
Shillings	O
,	O
Levee	O
being	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
Ring	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
Featherby	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
holding	O
a	O
Pistol	O
at	O
his	O
Breast	O
;	O
that	O
Levee	O
saying	O
he	O
had	O
still	O
more	O
Money	O
,	O
search	O
'd	O
further	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
his	O
Pocket	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
fourteen	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
which	O
Pocket	O
he	O
violently	O
tore	O
off	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
tore	O
down	O
his	O
Breeches	O
with	O
the	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Billers	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Peter	B-pers
Levee	I-pers
confess	O
'd	O
this	O
Robbery	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
Vaux	O
,	O
Barnham	O
-	O
and	O
Featherby	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Confession	O
he	O
likewise	O
told	O
of	O
several	O
other	O
Robberies	O
committed	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
and	O
sign	O
'd	O
the	O
confession	O
with	O
his	O
own	O
Hand	O
,	O
freely	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
Promises	O
or	O
Threathnings	O
.	O
This	O
Confession	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
the	O
Confession	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Barnham	I-pers
-	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
likewise	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
,	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
sign	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Hand	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Barnham	I-pers
.	O
Tho	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
take	O
Featherby	O
,	O
with	O
one	O
Kale	O
,	O
in	O
Blew-Boar's-Head-Alley	O
,	O
Barbican	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
each	O
snapp	O
'd	O
a	O
Pistol	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
neither	O
of	O
them	O
would	O
go	O
off	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Vaux	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
after	O
desiring	O
she	O
might	O
not	O
be	O
oblig	O
'd	O
to	O
say	O
any	O
Thing	O
against	O
her	O
Husband	O
(	O
which	O
indeed	O
is	O
not	O
allow	O
'd	O
off	O
by	O
Law	O
)	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
Barnham	O
stop	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
over-against	O
Water-Lane	O
,	O
when	O
Levee	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
rifled	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
all	O
four	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Their	O
Behaviour	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
was	O
surprising	O
,	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
seeming	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
least	O
Regret	O
,	O
but	O
on	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
they	O
all	O
four	O
laugh	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
the	O
utmost	O
Contempt	O
despised	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
who	O
swore	O
against	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
tho	O
they	O
could	O
say	O
nothing	O
in	O
their	O
own	O
Vindication	O
,	O
they	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
careless	O
,	O
negligent	O
and	O
confident	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bleak	I-pers
Cowland	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
detestable	O
Sin	O
of	O
Sodomy	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Breach	O
of	O
the	O
Statute	O
against	O
the	O
said	O
Sin	O
made	O
and	O
provided	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Parrey	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
in	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
he	O
first	O
came	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
one	O
Muff	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Black-Lion-Yard	B-place
,	I-place
White-Chappel	I-place
.	O
That	O
in	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
Home	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
he	O
perswaded	O
him	O
to	O
commit	O
the	O
Sin	O
of	O
Sodomy	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
consented	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
,	O
actually	O
commit	O
the	O
Sin	O
of	O
Sodomy	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
afterwards	O
in	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
actually	O
commit	O
the	O
said	O
Sin	O
of	O
Sodomy	O
twice	O
more	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
.	O
This	O
Deponent	O
farther	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
weary	O
of	O
this	O
wicked	O
and	O
detestable	O
Practice	O
,	O
took	O
a	O
Resolution	O
to	O
betray	O
the	O
Company	O
which	O
met	O
together	O
,	O
to	O
commit	O
such	O
filthy	O
Actions	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
he	O
gave	O
Information	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
contrived	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
others	O
were	O
apprehended	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Muss	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
Black-Lion-Yard	O
,	O
White-Chappel	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
only	O
went	O
to	O
Muff	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
to	O
learn	O
to	O
play	O
on	O
the	O
Violin	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
false	O
which	O
Parrey	O
had	O
swore	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Brother	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
knew	O
Parrey	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
idle	O
vagabond	O
Fellow	O
,	O
that	O
would	O
swear	O
a	O
Cow	O
is	O
a	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Oath	O
was	O
therefore	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
believing	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchre	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bay	O
Gelding	O
,	O
Value	O
four	O
Pounds	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
Sept	O
.	O
Last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Willington	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Gelding	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Field	O
near	O
Peckham	B-place
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
saw	O
an	O
Hostler	O
upon	O
the	O
Back	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
without	O
a	O
Saddle	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
asked	O
the	O
Hostler	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
Gelding	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
was	O
who	O
said	O
Yes	O
and	O
asked	O
five	O
Pounds	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
perhaps	O
buy	O
it	O
cheaper	O
of	O
the	O
Owner	O
,	O
and	O
desiring	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Hostler	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
Owner	O
of	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
for	O
a	O
Friend	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
four	O
Pounds	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Collar	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
He	O
should	O
bate	O
every	O
Penny	O
but	O
a	O
Halter	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
caused	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
apprehended	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
him	O
of	O
a	O
Friend	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
one	O
Swindal	O
,	O
who	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Sea	O
,	O
and	O
promised	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
but	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
no	O
such	O
Person	O
could	O
be	O
found	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Winn	O
in	O
particular	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
intrusted	O
him	O
with	O
150	O
l.	O
Worth	O
of	O
Plate	O
at	O
a	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
behaved	O
very	O
honestly	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchre	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Norton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Day-Time	O
,	O
no	O
Person	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
wainscoat	O
Box	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
one	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Crowns	O
besides	O
,	O
some	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Norton	I-pers
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Norton	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
being	O
absent	O
from	O
her	O
House	O
some	O
Hours	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
Home	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Wall	O
joining	O
to	O
the	O
Door-Post	O
broken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Lock	O
forced	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
searching	O
further	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
one	O
Ann	B-pers
Ellison	I-pers
was	O
suspected	O
to	O
have	O
done	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
charg	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
but	O
she	O
cleared	O
herself	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
out	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
produced	O
the	O
Goods	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
bringing	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
Lap	O
;	O
which	O
Goods	O
being	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
House	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
apprehending	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Bag	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Slaughter	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Constable	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Money	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
hid	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
searching	O
,	O
found	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
for	O
some	O
Time	O
trifled	O
and	O
equivocated	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
directed	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
Place	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
for	O
six	O
Shillings	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
Place	O
they	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
made	O
a	O
very	O
trifling	O
Defence	O
,	O
pretending	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Guinea	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
besides	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
she	O
pick	O
'd	O
them	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
contrary	O
appearing	O
evident	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Oney	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Honey	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
returning	O
from	O
Transportation	O
,	O
it	O
appearing	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
twelfth	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
late	O
Majesty	O
,	O
he	O
feloniously	O
stole	O
four	O
Weather-Sheep	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
for	O
which	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
December	O
following	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
try	O
'd	O
and	O
convicted	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
transported	O
,	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Plantations	O
in	O
America	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Space	O
of	O
seven	O
Years	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
found	O
at	O
large	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
now	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Breach	O
of	O
the	O
Statute	O
in	O
that	O
Case	O
made	O
and	O
provided	O
.	O
Several	O
Witnesses	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
was	O
convicted	O
,	O
and	O
actually	O
transported	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
the	O
Fact	O
aforementioned	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
at	O
his	O
Return	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
aged	O
,	O
and	O
infirm	O
,	O
that	O
no	O
one	O
would	O
buy	O
,	O
or	O
employ	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
rambled	O
,	O
and	O
begg	O
'd	O
about	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
considerable	O
Time	O
,	O
a	O
Captain	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Pass	O
to	O
England	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
likewise	O
a	O
Part	O
of	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
he	O
further	O
adding	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
design	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
England	O
,	O
but	O
go	O
for	O
Ireland	O
,	O
(	O
but	O
that	O
being	O
in	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Dominions	O
,	O
is	O
contrary	O
to	O
the	O
Statute	O
)	O
that	O
in	O
America	O
they	O
put	O
him	O
on	O
Board	O
against	O
his	O
Will	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
seventy	O
four	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
almost	O
lost	O
his	O
Sight	O
in	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Service	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
Chain	O
,	O
a	O
Seal	O
,	O
and	O
silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Goodale	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
Sept	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
accidentally	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
being	O
his	O
Countrywoman	O
,	O
(	O
a	O
Calledonean	O
)	O
they	O
agreed	O
to	O
drink	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
one	O
Smith	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
Charing-Cross	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
fell	O
a-sleep	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
,	O
like	O
a	O
muckle	O
wicked	O
Woman	O
,	O
took	O
away	O
his	O
Goods	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
apprehended	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
might	O
as	O
well	O
take	O
it	O
as	O
another	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
we	O
will	O
snack	O
it	O
between	O
us	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
mortally	O
fuddled	O
,	O
and	O
dropp	O
'd	O
both	O
his	O
Watch	O
and	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
Landlord	O
have	O
taken	O
Care	O
of	O
'em	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
honest	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
did	O
an	O
ill	O
Thing	O
in	O
her	O
Life	O
;	O
nor	O
in	O
this	O
did	O
she	O
design	O
any	O
other	O
than	O
to	O
take	O
Care	O
of	O
her	O
Countryman	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
being	O
too	O
officious	O
in	O
her	O
Care	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Marcum	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Le	I-place
Bone	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
six	O
China	O
Bowls	O
,	O
sixty	O
China	O
Cups	O
and	O
Saucers	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Edmond	B-pers
Lewen	I-pers
,	O
which	O
being	O
very	O
plainly	O
proved	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London-Bridge	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
ten	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Tea	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Sugar	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
Instant	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Matth.ew	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstans	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Coffoy	O
Coach-Seats	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
Instant	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Burn	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
,	O
with	O
one	O
Laurence	B-pers
Plunkett	I-pers
,	O
did	O
privately	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
steal	O
a	O
Linnen-Bag	O
,	O
Value	O
one	O
Penny	O
,	O
and	O
forty	O
Guineas	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Sadler	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
George	O
Sadler	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
deluded	O
by	O
this	O
Laurence	B-pers
Plunkett	I-pers
,	O
and	O
that	O
by	O
his	O
Perswasion	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
her	O
Master	O
's	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
given	O
him	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
rob	O
her	O
Master	O
,	O
which	O
Opportunity	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Money	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
tempted	O
her	O
to	O
rob	O
her	O
Master	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
at	O
such	O
a	O
Time	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
should	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Part	O
of	O
her	O
Master	O
's	O
Counting-House	O
,	O
the	O
Keys	O
were	O
often	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
Draws	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
were	O
Money	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Principal	O
not	O
being	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
being	O
only	O
Accessory	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
participated	O
of	O
the	O
Booty	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Baugh	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Copper	O
Pot-Lid	O
,	O
a	O
Copper	O
Sauce-Pan	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Bellows	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Books	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Pocklington	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
very	O
officious	O
at	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
at	O
Hatton-Garden	O
,	O
and	O
pretended	O
to	O
help	O
off	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
affrightned	O
Sufferers	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Lloyd	O
seeing	O
him	O
loaded	O
with	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
remembering	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
suspected	O
he	O
had	O
stolen	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
apprehended	O
him	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Goods	O
with	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
the	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
single	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Woodward	B-pers
Tudor	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
an	O
Iron	O
Clever	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Tucker	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Tillard	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
velvet	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Satten	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Agnes	B-pers
Kite	I-pers
,	O
and	O
two	O
Silver	O
scallop	O
Shells	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Talbot	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Talbot	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
and	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Donevan	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
but	O
tho	O
'	O
the	O
Fact	O
appeared	O
plain	O
against	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Tillard	I-pers
,	O
both	O
by	O
her	O
own	O
Confession	O
,	O
and	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
produc	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
found	O
out	O
by	O
her	O
Directions	O
,	O
yet	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
sufficient	O
Witness	O
,	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Donevan	I-pers
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Tillard	I-pers
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Norton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Lombard-Street	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
several	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Hews	I-pers
,	O
deceas	O
'd	O
and	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
who	O
was	O
Executor	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Hews	I-pers
aforesaid	O
,	O
begg	O
'd	O
the	O
Court	O
would	O
have	O
Compassion	O
on	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
send	O
her	O
Abroad	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
an	O
Object	O
of	O
Pitty	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
when	O
they	O
brought	O
in	O
their	O
Verdict	O
,	O
likewise	O
begg	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
Favour	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Gascoin	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Copper	O
Tea-Kettle	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Mellekin	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
plain	O
upon	O
Gascoin	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
but	O
John	O
Brown	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Bark	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
the	I-place
Evangelist	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
several	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Money	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Wallden	I-pers
,	O
which	O
appearing	O
very	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Critchet	I-pers
of	O
Aldgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
August	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
taking	O
thence	O
Four	O
Shirts	O
,	O
Two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Trowsers	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Callimancoe	O
Wastecoat	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
Shop	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
aforesaid	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
soon	O
after	O
of	O
a	O
Woman	O
's	O
going	O
to	O
a	O
Pawnbrokers	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
,	O
and	O
suspecting	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
searching	O
found	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
afterwards	O
to	O
the	O
Pawnbrokers	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
remembring	O
her	O
,	O
caused	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Yarp	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
Four	O
Shirts	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
Pawn	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
afterwards	O
stopp	O
'd	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Bugulary	O
not	O
appearing	O
plain	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
only	O
found	O
Guilty	O
single	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Martha	B-pers
Potter	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Aubry	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
four	O
Pound	O
Money	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Wager	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
walking	O
along	O
Peter's-Street	B-place
he	O
met	O
Jane	B-pers
Aubry	I-pers
,	O
as	O
they	O
being	O
acquainted	O
before	O
,	O
fell	O
into	O
Conversation	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
persuaded	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Dram	O
,	O
and	O
directed	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
where	O
they	O
sat	O
very	O
lovingly	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
a	O
Dram	O
or	O
two	O
;	O
when	O
Aubry	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
trust	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
flung	O
down	O
a	O
Shilling	O
and	O
drank	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Humour	O
,	O
they	O
drank	O
to	O
the	O
Tune	O
of	O
fourteen	O
Quarterns	O
of	O
Geneva	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
fell	O
asleep	O
till	O
Three	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
then	O
awaked	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
quarrelling	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
Cunning	O
,	O
lay	O
in	O
a	O
Dog's-sleep	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
they	O
desputed	O
about	O
the	O
Division	O
of	O
his	O
Money	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
felt	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
and	O
found	O
as	O
his	O
Money	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
every	O
Farthing	O
,	O
which	O
all	O
his	O
Cunning	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
again	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
staid	O
till	O
Seven	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
Some	O
People	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
thinks	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Jane	B-pers
Aubry	I-pers
upon	O
an	O
ill	O
Design	O
;	O
but	O
was	O
Harmless	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
Civil	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
Chaste	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
Honest	O
tho	O
'	O
they	O
were	O
otherwise	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
said	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
in	O
their	O
Company	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
Drunk	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
for	O
he	O
went	O
home	O
with	O
Jane	O
Aubry	O
and	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
some	O
Pig	O
and	O
other	O
Dainties	O
,	O
and	O
play	O
'd	O
the	O
D	O
-	O
l	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
his	O
Money	O
;	O
his	O
Drunkenness	O
and	O
Extravagance	O
being	O
considered	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Bartlett	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
and	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Henry	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
employ	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
sometime	O
past	O
as	O
a	O
Chairwoman	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
with	O
a	O
false	O
Key	O
she	O
had	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Drawers	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
and	O
Money	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
reposing	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Confidence	O
in	O
her	O
,	O
had	O
suffered	O
themselves	O
to	O
be	O
Cheated	O
and	O
Defrauded	O
for	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
;	O
but	O
finding	O
Money	O
missing	O
frequently	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Wells	O
laid	O
wait	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
by	O
taking	O
Notice	O
of	O
what	O
Money	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Drawers	O
,	O
and	O
watching	O
her	O
,	O
found	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
upon	O
her	O
when	O
apprehended	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
carried	O
before	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
she	O
there	O
made	O
Confession	O
,	O
and	O
sign	O
'd	O
the	O
Confession	O
with	O
her	O
own	O
Hand	O
,	O
without	O
either	O
Threatnings	O
,	O
Menaces	O
or	O
Promises	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
single	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Carvenor	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
,	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Linnen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
two	O
Pillows	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
small	O
Value	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gibbons	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Burdet	O
Gown	O
,	O
Value	O
Eighteen	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Huntington	I-pers
,	O
but	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Romane	I-pers
,	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Porridge-Pot	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
's	I-place
White-Chapple	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
and	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Necklace	O
,	O
Value	O
Five	O
Pounds	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Caywood	I-pers
;	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
about	O
Three	O
Years	O
since	O
he	O
lost	O
a	O
Gold	O
Necklace	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
told	O
him	O
lately	O
that	O
Anne	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
stole	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
herself	O
received	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
what	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
told	O
him	O
,	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Anne	O
Parker	O
,	O
nor	O
could	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
herself	O
be	O
found	O
Guilty	O
as	O
Accessory	O
,	O
before	O
Anne	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
as	O
Principal	O
:	O
They	O
were	O
therefore	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Start	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Starkey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cock	O
and	O
Six	O
Ducks	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Burbridge	I-pers
:	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
apprehended	O
,	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
sign	O
'd	O
his	O
Confession	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
Drunk	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Wainsford	I-pers
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Kelly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Gerrun	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Stick	O
,	O
Valve	O
2	O
d.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
September	O
about	O
Twelve	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
Kelly	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
where	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
him	O
said	O
Kelly	O
knock	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
biggest	O
of	O
the	O
Two	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
to	O
be	O
Wainsford	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
Kelly	O
knocked	O
him	O
down	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
then	O
Wainsford	O
took	O
his	O
Stick	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
Kelly	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
take	O
off	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
tore	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
some	O
coming	O
to	O
his	O
Assistance	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
Kelly	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Mills	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
Disturbance	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
the	O
Matter	O
was	O
when	O
Kelly	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
his	O
Company	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
larger	O
Size	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
Wainsford	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
he	O
apprehended	O
Wainsford	O
,	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
at	O
a	O
House	O
of	O
ill	O
Character	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
saw	O
the	O
Fray	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
demanded	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
it	O
appear	O
plainly	O
,	O
that	O
Wainsford	O
was	O
there	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Sanders	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
Purse	O
,	O
Value	O
1	O
d.	O
one	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
desired	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
the	O
Liberty	O
to	O
object	O
against	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
formerly	O
convicted	O
of	O
Forgery	O
,	O
and	O
thereby	O
his	O
Oath	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
,	O
in	O
any	O
Court	O
of	O
Judicature	O
.	O
The	O
Records	O
being	O
examined	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
actually	O
convicted	O
of	O
Forgery	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Conspiracy	O
,	O
in	O
publishing	O
Forged	O
Writing	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
Judgment	O
pass	O
'd	O
on	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
is	O
usual	O
in	O
such	O
Cases	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Court	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
withdrew	O
,	O
and	O
proceded	O
to	O
examine	O
witnesses	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Varney	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
near	O
Edmonton	O
heard	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
near	O
his	O
Masters	O
House	O
,	O
between	O
two	O
Persons	O
,	O
the	O
bidding	O
the	O
other	O
deliver	O
his	O
Money	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
a	O
Fowling	O
Piece	O
,	O
and	O
mounting	O
a	O
Coach-Horse	O
,	O
pursu	O
'd	O
the	O
Highwayman	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
informing	O
him	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
robb	O
'd	O
;	O
that	O
a	O
Tottenham	O
he	O
overtook	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
answer	O
the	O
Description	O
of	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
rob	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
his	O
Mistress	O
and	O
the	O
Maid	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
on	O
Dark	O
Wig	O
,	O
or	O
his	O
own	O
Hair	O
,	O
and	O
white	O
Stockings	O
,	O
yet	O
he	O
caused	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
apprehended	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Swan	O
at	O
Tottenham	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
put	O
up	O
his	O
Horse	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Sanders	O
,	O
coming	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
gone	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Sanders	O
,	O
and	O
view	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Horse	O
,	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Sanders	O
said	O
was	O
the	O
Horse	O
which	O
the	O
Person	O
rode	O
who	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
afterwards	O
went	O
and	O
viewed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
had	O
those	O
very	O
Cloaths	O
on	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
Sanders	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
was	O
no	O
Evidence	O
,	O
Sander	O
's	O
Oath	O
not	O
being	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
,	O
his	O
Tale	O
to	O
this	O
Deponent	O
could	O
have	O
no	O
weight	O
with	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
besides	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Description	O
of	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
robb	O
'd	O
Sanders	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Mistress	O
,	O
and	O
Maid	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
describ	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
this	O
Deponent	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
on	O
a	O
dark	O
Wig	O
,	O
on	O
his	O
own	O
Hair	O
,	O
and	O
white	O
Stockings	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
this	O
Deponent	O
overtook	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
not	O
long	O
after	O
this	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
on	O
a	O
white	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
Boots	O
,	O
so	O
as	O
his	O
Stockings	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
seen	O
.	O
This	O
Deponent	O
further	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
he	O
overtook	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
riding	O
an	O
even	O
Trot	O
,	O
and	O
stopping	O
at	O
the	O
Swan	O
at	O
Tottenham	O
,	O
asked	O
how	O
far	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
told	O
four	O
Miles	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
put	O
up	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
being	O
tir	O
'd	O
,	O
supp	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
publick	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
staying	O
there	O
some	O
Time	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
rode	O
forty	O
Miles	O
that	O
Day	O
,	O
upon	O
a	O
very	O
indifferent	O
Horse	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Banson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
Bed	O
of	O
secure	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
search	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
only	O
two	O
Shillings	O
and	O
a	O
few	O
Farthings	O
about	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
Deponent	O
being	O
very	O
ready	O
at	O
Swearing	O
,	O
farther	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
robb	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Sanders	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
accidentally	O
dropped	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
a	O
Purse	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Sanders	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
hid	O
the	O
Pistol	O
which	O
he	O
held	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Sanders	O
's	O
Breast	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
Manger	O
,	O
where	O
his	O
Horse	O
stood	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Swan	O
,	O
at	O
Tottenham	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
digg	O
'd	O
under	O
the	O
Manger	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Pistol	O
;	O
this	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
before	O
several	O
others	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
Garden	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
of	O
those	O
People	O
appearing	O
,	O
before	O
whom	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Servants	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
other	O
Person	O
Present	O
,	O
when	O
as	O
he	O
pretended	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Pistol	O
under	O
the	O
Manger	O
,	O
this	O
Deponent	O
gain	O
'd	O
but	O
little	O
Credit	O
in	O
this	O
Relation	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Legg	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
put	O
up	O
his	O
Horse	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Swan	O
,	O
at	O
Tottenham	O
,	O
and	O
supp	O
'd	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
publick	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
behaving	O
himself	O
very	O
orderly	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
least	O
Appearance	O
of	O
a	O
Robbery	O
,	O
or	O
suspicious	O
Person	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Pistol	O
about	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
assaulted	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
used	O
his	O
Servants	O
to	O
search	O
very	O
narrowly	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
Manger	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
the	O
Stable	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Horse	O
stood	O
,	O
but	O
after	O
the	O
most	O
strick	O
Search	O
,	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
any	O
Pistol	O
.	O
It	O
likewise	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
charg	O
'd	O
another	O
Person	O
with	O
this	O
Robbery	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
kept	O
in	O
Custody	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Banson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
modest	O
Swearer	O
abovementioned	O
,	O
but	O
of	O
this	O
he	O
took	O
no	O
Notice	O
,	O
till	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
other	O
Evidence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Samuel	B-pers
Roult	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
value	O
eight	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
Hatband	O
value	O
one	O
Shilling	O
and	O
Sixpence	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
coming	O
from	O
Red-Lion-Street	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
standing	O
at	O
a	O
Brandy-Shop	O
Door	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Field-Lane	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
himself	O
went	O
up	O
Field-Lane	B-place
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
above	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Doors	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
following	O
,	O
jostled	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
thinking	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Pick-Pocket	O
,	O
mended	O
his	O
Pace	O
,	O
when	O
presently	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
others	O
followed	O
,	O
and	O
surrounding	O
him	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
knocked	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
mourning	O
Crape	O
Hatband	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Woman	O
coming	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
they	O
all	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
perswaded	O
him	O
into	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
to	O
clean	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
whilst	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
doing	O
,	O
the	O
Woman	O
who	O
brought	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Persons	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Appleyard	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
heard	O
a	O
Noise	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
been	O
abused	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
perswaded	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
into	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
that	O
presently	O
a	O
Woman	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
listned	O
very	O
attentively	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Tale	O
,	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
assaulted	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
a	O
Man	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
whom	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
kept	O
out	O
,	O
for	O
by	O
some	O
Signs	O
she	O
look	O
'd	O
on	O
him	O
as	O
a	O
suspicious	O
Person	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Woman	O
desiring	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
let	O
in	O
,	O
the	O
opened	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
shut	O
it	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
assaulted	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Persons	O
who	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
But	O
as	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
appear	O
'd	O
who	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
depos	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
when	O
this	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Pew	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Issac	B-pers
Cradon	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Tottoiseshell	O
Case	O
,	O
studded	O
with	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
eight	O
Pounds	O
,	O
and	O
19	O
Shillings	O
and	O
Sixpence	O
Money	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
Aug	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
Deposed	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
twelve	O
at	O
Night	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
over	O
Little-Tower-Hill	B-place
,	O
when	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
person	O
,	O
who	O
demanded	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
then	O
demanded	O
his	O
Watch	O
which	O
he	O
likewise	O
gave	O
them	O
.	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
advised	O
to	O
search	O
them	O
in	O
Bartholomew-Fair	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
having	O
a	O
plain	O
Idea	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
went	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
find	O
him	O
there	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
then	O
find	O
him	O
,	O
from	O
,	O
thence	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
an	O
Aquaintance	O
up	O
Holbourn	O
where	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
others	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
positive	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
.	O
It	O
being	O
a	O
clear	O
star-light	O
Night	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Moon	O
scarce	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
meeting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
thus	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
he	O
dogg	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
Company	O
,	O
till	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Horse	O
Shoe	O
Ale-House	O
within	O
Temple-Bar	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
with	O
his	O
Friend	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
some	O
Time	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
himself	O
fixing	O
their	O
Eyes	O
upon	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
jump	O
'd	O
over	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
sitting	O
with	O
his	O
Companions	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
then	O
without	O
taking	O
Leave	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
pursu	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
his	O
companion	O
being	O
gone	O
for	O
an	O
Officer	O
)	O
and	O
overtook	O
him	O
in	O
Bell-Yard	O
near	O
Temple-Bar	O
,	O
when	O
his	O
Friend	O
one	O
Richard	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
likewise	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
deposd	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
told	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Horse-Shoe	O
Ale-House	O
near	O
Temple-Bar	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
who	O
sat	O
there	O
in	O
Company	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
went	O
for	O
an	O
Officer	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
coming	O
back	O
towards	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
in	O
Bell-Yard	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
stopp	O
'd	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Bartholomew	O
Fair	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
their	O
asking	O
him	O
why	O
he	O
left	O
his	O
Company	O
so	O
abruptly	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
broke	O
some	O
Windows	O
at	O
Mount-Mill	O
,	O
and	O
feared	O
they	O
wanted	O
to	O
apprehend	O
him	O
on	O
that	O
Occasion	O
He	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
House	O
all	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
to	O
prove	O
which	O
he	O
produc	O
'd	O
the	O
following	O
Witnesses	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hitchcock	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
last	O
Day	O
of	O
August	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
Home	O
all	O
Night	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
Mother	O
at	O
twelve	O
or	O
one	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
to	O
carry	O
Sage-Tea	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
Bed	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Occasion	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Mother	O
was	O
delirous	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
fear	O
'd	O
she	O
should	O
do	O
herself	O
a	O
mischief	O
.	O
Easter	B-pers
Mash	I-pers
deposd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Hitchcock	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
all	O
that	O
Evening	O
.	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Hitchcock	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Bed	O
with	O
her	O
Mother	O
,	O
and	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
at	O
one	O
o	O
'	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
all	O
Night	O
,	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
deposing	O
to	O
the	O
like	O
Effect	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
in	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
of	O
Value	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Raven	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
John	O
Raven	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquainted	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Dyer's-Arms	B-place
at	I-place
the	I-place
Three-Cranes	I-place
,	O
and	O
tho	O
'	O
they	O
were	O
cautious	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
knowing	O
he	O
had	O
but	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
Character	O
,	O
being	O
charg	O
'd	O
with	O
several	O
Robberies	O
before	O
,	O
yet	O
he	O
took	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
get	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
which	O
Goods	O
he	O
took	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
going	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Daughter	O
heard	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
he	O
went	O
directly	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
her	O
Mother	O
,	O
she	O
fear	O
'd	O
they	O
were	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
who	O
going	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
nothing	O
less	O
,	O
for	O
her	O
Money	O
and	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
Box	O
,	O
up	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
,	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
Sarah	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Daughter	O
,	O
went	O
in	O
Search	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
acquainted	O
at	O
Newgate	O
,	O
after	O
some	O
Trouble	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
by	O
the	O
Directions	O
of	O
the	O
People	O
there	O
where	O
he	O
lodg	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
politick	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
only	O
pretended	O
that	O
his	O
Wife	O
was	O
come	O
to	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
sick	O
,	O
staid	O
at	O
her	O
Father	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
hesitating	O
,	O
she	O
argu	O
'd	O
the	O
indispensable	O
Duty	O
he	O
lay	O
under	O
to	O
visit	O
a	O
loving	O
Wife	O
,	O
that	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
ill	O
in	O
the	O
journey	O
,	O
he	O
at	O
length	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
Means	O
she	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
had	O
him	O
taken	O
into	O
Custody	O
,	O
the	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
being	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
being	O
found	O
by	O
his	O
Directions	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
Shillings	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Bradey	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
.	O
Tho	B-pers
Nicholls	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
about	O
a	O
Year	O
since	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
frequently	O
came	O
to	O
their	O
House	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
Gill	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
King's-Arms	B-place
in	I-place
Newgate-Street	I-place
,	O
and	O
about	O
that	O
Time	O
they	O
loosing	O
a	O
silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
had	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
Instant	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
resolved	O
to	O
try	O
his	O
Honesty	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
going	O
backwards	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
clean	O
Spoon	O
,	O
and	O
greas	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
he	O
laid	O
it	O
upon	O
some	O
foul	O
Plates	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
back	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
Wine	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
drew	O
it	O
,	O
ordering	O
all	O
the	O
other	O
Servants	O
to	O
keep	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
the	O
Spoon	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
this	O
Deponent	O
drew	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Sword	O
,	O
fearing	O
he	O
might	O
do	O
Mischief	O
,	O
and	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Spoon	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
flung	O
down	O
,	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
the	O
Servants	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
apprised	O
of	O
the	O
policy	O
of	O
this	O
Deponent	O
,	O
lay	O
in	O
wait	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
fling	O
down	O
the	O
Spoon	O
,	O
the	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Purse	O
Value	O
one	O
Penny	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Symon	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Symon	O
Thompson	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2nd	O
Instant	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
drink	O
at	O
the	B-place
Castle	I-place
in	I-place
Rotten-Row	I-place
in	I-place
Old-Street	I-place
,	O
and	O
falling	O
asleep	O
,	O
had	O
his	O
Pocket	O
pick	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
his	O
Money	O
and	O
Purse	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
afterwards	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Purse	O
he	O
knew	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
its	O
Fellow	O
,	O
for	O
being	O
industrious	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
an	O
old	O
Cabbage-Net	O
,	O
the	O
Piece	O
of	O
Cabbage-Net	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
that	O
was	O
his	O
Purse	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
other	O
Evidences	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Pocket	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
then	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
a	O
long	O
Tale	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
buying	O
a	O
Bunch	O
of	O
Carrots	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
a	O
Green-Grocer	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
perswaded	O
her	O
to	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
some	O
Meat	O
to	O
his	O
carrots	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
his	O
Cabbage	O
Net	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
,	O
bidding	O
her	O
go	O
Home	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
do	O
so	O
and	O
so	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
very	O
innocently	O
went	O
Home	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
after	O
she	O
found	O
he	O
had	O
fallen	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
awaking	O
,	O
the	O
Fit	O
had	O
left	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
chang	O
'd	O
his	O
Purpose	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
her	O
apprehended	O
,	O
tho	O
when	O
the	O
Constable	O
came	O
up	O
Stairs	O
with	O
his	O
Staff	O
,	O
she	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
come	O
full	O
of	O
Love	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
to	O
the	O
Stair	O
Head	O
,	O
with	O
open	O
Arms	O
,	O
to	O
receive	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
herself	O
disappointed	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
Story	O
smelt	O
so	O
strong	O
of	O
Newgate	O
's	O
Invention	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Tilbury	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Suits	O
of	O
Head	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
two	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Merriot	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Francis	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Hannah	B-pers
Becket	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
brass	O
Pot-Lid	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Myrum	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sheet	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Bellows	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Ridge	I-pers
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Aaron	B-pers
Bateman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Ravishing	O
,	O
and	O
Carnally	O
knowing	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bowcock	I-pers
,	O
against	O
her	O
Will	O
and	O
Consent	O
,	O
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assisting	O
Aaron	B-pers
Bateman	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Rape	O
upon	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bowcock	I-pers
;	O
the	O
poor	O
Girl	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
a	O
Field	O
near	O
Islington	B-place
and	O
they	O
were	O
rude	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
their	O
Hands	O
up	O
her	O
Coats	O
and	O
tumbled	O
her	O
down	O
under	O
a	O
Hedge	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
Bateman	O
beat	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
she	O
went	O
by	O
Battle-Bridge	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
them	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
Bateman	O
asked	O
her	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Green-Dragon	B-place
,	O
and	O
there	O
the	O
naughty	O
Men	O
did	O
lie	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
Men	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
all	O
lie	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
one	O
after	O
another	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
willing	O
to	O
let	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
would	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
thousand	O
Men	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
told	O
,	O
she	O
must	O
mind	O
what	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
was	O
upon	O
her	O
Oath	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Lives	O
of	O
two	O
Men	O
lay	O
at	O
stake	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
believe	O
their	O
were	O
not	O
quite	O
a	O
Thousand	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
sure	O
their	O
were	O
more	O
than	O
ten	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
would	O
all	O
have	O
ravished	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
was	O
so	O
kind	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
stand	O
by	O
her	O
and	O
fought	O
her	O
Way	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
.	O
That	O
when	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
ravish	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
knee'ed	O
down	O
upon	O
her	O
Knees	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
poor	O
Girl	O
,	O
and	O
lived	O
at	O
the	O
famous	O
Anodyne	O
Necklace	O
near	O
Temple-Bar	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
satisfy	O
'd	O
,	O
till	O
they	O
had	O
all	O
three	O
laid	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
did	O
believe	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
Child	O
by	O
them	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
Mother	O
what	O
they	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
Hands	O
of	O
a	O
Lawyer	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
indicted	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
King's-Bench	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bowcock	I-pers
Senior	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
her	O
Daugther	O
had	O
been	O
abus	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
told	O
her	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
by	O
Bateman	O
and	O
Cook	O
,	O
whom	O
she	O
had	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
Hands	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Tibbalds	O
to	O
manage	O
them	O
at	O
his	O
Pleasure	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
done	O
so	O
justly	O
as	O
he	O
ought	O
to	O
have	O
done	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
Girl	O
of	O
no	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
a	O
Witness	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
her	O
lay	O
upon	O
the	O
Grass	O
,	O
behind	O
a	O
Hedge	O
,	O
with	O
3	O
Boys	O
one	O
on	O
each	O
Side	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Leversage	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
kept	O
the	O
Green	B-place
Dragon	I-place
at	I-place
Battle	I-place
Bridge	I-place
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
drink	O
together	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
drank	O
freely	O
with	O
'em	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
put	O
their	O
Hands	O
up	O
her	O
Coats	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
keeping	O
a	O
very	O
orderly	O
House	O
,	O
would	O
not	O
suffer	O
them	O
to	O
commit	O
any	O
Familiarity	O
of	O
that	O
Nature	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
all	O
that	O
was	O
done	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Tibbalds	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
in	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
employ	O
'd	O
him	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
account	O
of	O
an	O
Assault	O
,	O
she	O
and	O
her	O
Mother	O
saying	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
beat	O
and	O
abus	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
any	O
mention	O
was	O
then	O
made	O
of	O
a	O
Rape	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
not	O
agreeing	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
asked	O
fifty	O
Pounds	O
Damages	O
,	O
the	O
Girl	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
her	O
Mother	O
would	O
indict	O
then	O
for	O
a	O
Rape	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
another	O
Time	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
Meeting	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
agreed	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
three	O
Pounds	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
Acquittances	O
were	O
drawn	O
,	O
Bateman	O
snatch	O
'd	O
the	O
Money	O
again	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
know	O
in	O
this	O
Case	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
indict	O
them	O
for	O
Street-Robbers	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
seeing	O
they	O
were	O
a	O
wicked	O
contentious	O
People	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
next	O
News	O
he	O
heard	O
,	O
was	O
of	O
this	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
the	O
Matter	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Nixson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
buying	O
twenty	O
Harness	O
Buckles	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
,	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Toung	I-pers
being	O
formerly	O
convicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Timothy	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gallon	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Cask	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Winchmore	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Dalton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchre	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Dennis	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
Value	O
five	O
Shillings	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
cross	O
Smithfield	B-place
,	O
he	O
heard	O
Murder	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
ran	O
up	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
the	O
Matter	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
Woman	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
by	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saying	O
it	O
was	O
unfair	O
to	O
use	O
a	O
Woman	O
so	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
damn	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
after	O
fell	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
several	O
Blows	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
off	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
with	O
.	O
He	O
likewise	O
call	O
'd	O
another	O
Witness	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
effect	O
,	O
but	O
several	O
sufficient	O
House-Keepers	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
appearing	O
on	O
the	O
Behalf	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
gave	O
the	O
Court	O
a	O
fair	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Transaction	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
no	O
Design	O
to	O
rob	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
,	O
occasion	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
picking	O
up	O
a	O
Woman	O
of	O
the	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
asking	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Mind	O
for	O
a	O
Whore	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Chidly	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
thirty	O
Handkerchiefs	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Wrapson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
eleven	O
Pence	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
Sepetember	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
an	O
extraordinary	O
Character	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Rice	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Abb-Church-Lane	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twelve	O
Flasks	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
Value	O
eighteen	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
saying	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Wine	O
was	O
left	O
by	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Master	O
being	O
paid	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
therefore	O
his	O
Right	O
by	O
the	O
Custom	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Austin	O
being	O
favourable	O
,	O
acknowledged	O
it	O
might	O
probably	O
be	O
so	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
value	O
eight	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Cane	O
value	O
four	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
laid	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Cane	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
at	O
Peel	B-place
's	I-place
Coffee-House	I-place
in	I-place
Fleetstreet	I-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
there	O
,	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
his	O
own	O
Hat	O
behind	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Hat	O
and	O
Cane	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
felonious	O
Intent	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Prisly	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Iron	O
Well-Buckets	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Niplet	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
Boddington	I-pers
,	O
but	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
sufficient	O
evidence	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
three	O
Pounds	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
appearing	O
plain	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Julius	B-pers
Cesar	I-pers
Taylor	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Burgess	I-pers
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
commit	O
that	O
horrid	O
and	O
detestable	O
Sin	O
of	O
Sodomy	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
keeping	O
a	O
disorderly	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
entertaining	O
wicked	O
abandon	O
'd	O
Men	O
,	O
who	O
commit	O
sodomitical	O
Practices	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Depositions	O
of	O
divers	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
sit	O
on	O
the	O
Lap	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Burgess	I-pers
,	O
when	O
they	O
committed	O
such	O
indecent	O
and	O
effeminate	O
Actions	O
,	O
as	O
are	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
mentioned	O
:	O
that	O
the	O
Company	O
who	O
resorted	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
launch	O
'd	O
into	O
such	O
Extravagance	O
,	O
as	O
was	O
scarce	O
ever	O
heard	O
off	O
.	O
When	O
any	O
Member	O
enter	O
'd	O
into	O
their	O
Society	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
christned	O
by	O
a	O
female	O
Name	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Geneva	O
thrown	O
in	O
his	O
Face	O
;	O
one	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
Orange	O
Deb	O
,	O
another	O
Nel	B-pers
Guin	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
third	O
Flying	O
Horse	O
Moll	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Accessary	O
in	O
these	O
unnatural	O
Actions	O
.	O
It	O
likewise	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Depositions	O
of	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
kept	O
a	O
disorderly	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
none	O
to	O
appear	O
for	O
his	O
Character	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
Indictment	O
,	O
for	O
keeping	O
a	O
disorderly	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
second	O
Indictment	O
,	O
for	O
an	O
Assault	O
upon	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
John	O
Burgess	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Burgess	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Julius	B-pers
Cesar	I-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
commit	O
that	O
detestable	O
Sin	O
of	O
Sodomy	O
with	O
the	O
said	O
Julius	B-pers
Cesar	I-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Holstone	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Blackwell	I-pers
Severally	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Julius	B-pers
Cesar	I-pers
Taylor	I-pers
commit	O
filthy	O
lewd	O
Actions	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
not	O
bear	O
mentioning	O
to	O
a	O
modest	O
Ear	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
appeard	O
equally	O
pleas	O
'd	O
,	O
Julius	B-pers
Cesar	I-pers
Taylor	I-pers
using	O
undecent	O
Gestures	O
,	O
and	O
Burgess	O
suffering	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
they	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Zachary	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
several	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
suspected	O
of	O
Sodomy	O
,	O
but	O
on	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
had	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
vertuous	O
modest	O
sober	O
Man	O
.	O
Katherine	B-pers
Maranda	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
too	O
fond	O
of	O
a	O
pretty	O
Girl	O
,	O
to	O
fall	O
into	O
sodomnitical	O
Actions	O
;	O
and	O
this	O
I	O
know	O
by	O
Experience	O
,	O
upon	O
my	O
Word	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
oath	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Honour	O
.	O
Several	O
others	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
like	O
Effect	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
two	O
Witnesses	O
being	O
positive	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
filthy	O
ludicrous	O
Actions	O
,	O
with	O
Julius	B-pers
Cesar	I-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Taylor	O
in	O
Tottenham-Court	B-place
Road	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Assault	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Challoner	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
's	I-place
White-Chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Branch	I-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
commit	O
that	O
wicked	O
and	O
detestable	O
Sin	O
of	O
Sodomy	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Branch	I-pers
Harris	I-pers
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Parrey	I-pers
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
commit	O
the	O
said	O
sin	O
of	O
Sodomy	O
,	O
with	O
him	O
the	O
said	O
Jonathan	O
Parrey	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Parrey	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
in	O
February	O
last	O
he	O
first	O
came	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
that	O
they	O
about	O
that	O
Time	O
lay	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
equally	O
committed	O
filthy	O
undecent	O
and	O
effeminate	O
Actions	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
likewise	O
did	O
the	O
same	O
at	O
Muffs	B-place
House	I-place
in	I-place
Black-Lion-Yard	I-place
White-Chappel	I-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
Lodging	O
in	O
an	O
Alley	O
near	O
White-Chappel	O
Church	O
,	O
in	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Challoner	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Branch	I-pers
Harris	I-pers
came	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
their	O
Hands	O
into	O
each	O
other	O
's	O
Breeches	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
into	O
an	O
Arbour	O
in	O
the	O
Garden	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
they	O
did	O
there	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ames	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
in	O
assaulting	O
Joseph	B-pers
Vincent	I-pers
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
commit	O
that	O
heinous	O
Sin	O
of	O
Sodomy	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
said	O
Joseph	B-pers
Vincent	I-pers
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
prove	O
him	O
Guilty	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Joshua	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
that	O
whereas	O
several	O
Persons	O
assaulted	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
Richard	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
to	O
wit	O
,	O
Owen	O
,	O
Medling	O
,	O
and	O
Harris	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
executed	O
pursuant	O
to	O
their	O
Sentence	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
Joshua	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
well	O
knowing	O
the	O
Premises	O
,	O
did	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Trial	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Owen	O
,	O
Medling	O
,	O
and	O
Harris	O
,	O
endeavour	O
to	O
perswade	O
Richard	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
to	O
compound	O
the	O
said	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
such	O
Evasion	O
and	O
corrupting	O
Justice	O
,	O
endeavoured	O
and	O
contrived	O
Means	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Owen	O
,	O
Medling	O
,	O
and	O
Harris	O
to	O
escape	O
unpunish	O
'd	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
ignorant	O
Fellow	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
was	O
through	O
Inadvertency	O
,	O
not	O
knowing	O
the	O
Laws	O
which	O
are	O
made	O
against	O
such	O
Transactions	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Plewit	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
silver	O
Spurs	O
,	O
two	O
Linnen	O
Shirts	O
,	O
two	O
silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Cartwright	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Marsden	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
the	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
very	O
plain	O
against	O
Plewit	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
but	O
Thomas	B-pers
Marsden	I-pers
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
