TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
:	O
AND	O
On	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Baily	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
17th	O
,	O
18th	O
,	O
19th	O
,	O
and	O
20th	O
,	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
1727	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
First	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
EDWARD	B-pers
BECHER	I-pers
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	B-pers
Pengelly	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Reynolds	O
,	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Cooper	O
,	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
,	O
Serjeant	O
at	O
Law	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Turminer	O
aforesaid	O
:	O
Together	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
.	O
Price	O
four	O
Pence	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Birch	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Hutchins	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
John	B-pers
Rutford	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Cowdery	I-pers
,	O
Aaron	B-pers
Peters	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Lovett	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Winter	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Carpenter	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Peat	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Holloway	I-pers
:	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Prater	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Goodge	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Gillmore	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Fortescue	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Sharpless	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Brunker	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Blackwell	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Ren	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Power	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hearding	I-pers
.	O
George	B-pers
Sanders	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Aldermanbury	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
6	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Plestoe	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
put	O
up	O
his	O
Goods	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
Information	O
,	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Hands	O
,	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Smallman	I-pers
,	O
and	O
another	O
Pawnbroker	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Smallman	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Sanders	O
brought	O
4	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Mark	O
and	O
other	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
they	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
.	O
Joshua	B-pers
Nason	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Simpson	O
brought	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
suspecting	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
stopped	O
them	O
:	O
they	O
likewise	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Sampson	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
George	O
Sanders	O
and	O
John	O
Simpson	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
begg	O
'd	O
he	O
would	O
appear	O
before	O
the	O
Pawn-broker	O
,	O
and	O
say	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
employ	O
'd	O
'em	O
to	O
pawn	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s	O
,	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bottolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Furgerson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
Jan	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
coming	O
over	O
Tower-hill	B-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
snatch	O
'd	O
his	O
Hat	O
from	O
,	O
his	O
Head	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
another	O
Person	O
,	O
who	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Indictment	O
not	O
being	O
said	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
and	O
Robbing	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
only	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
single	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Pool	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Childrens	O
Coats	O
,	O
2	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
2	O
Frocks	O
,	O
2	O
Dimety	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Hat	O
,	O
2	O
Shirts	O
,	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Musling	O
Head-Cloaths	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
December	O
Last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
her	O
Tenant	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
missing	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
suspected	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
Child	O
's	O
Frock	O
at	O
a	O
Pawnbrokers	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
him	O
by	O
Sarah	B-pers
Pool	I-pers
,	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Pawnbroker	O
,	O
confirming	O
this	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Deposition	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Piddington	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
,	I-place
Anne	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Sheet	O
and	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
Jan	O
.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Vestry	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodging	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Sheet	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
own	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Ring	O
she	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Montgomery	O
,	O
who	O
produced	O
it	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
away	O
from	O
his	O
House	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Selby	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Iron-Vice	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Noble	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Appleby	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coach-glass	O
,	O
4	O
Brass	O
Tops	O
of	O
a	O
Chariot	O
,	O
Part	O
of	O
a	O
Harness	O
,	O
a	O
Drag	O
Chain	O
,	O
2	O
Collars	O
,	O
2	O
Leather	O
Saddles	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Coat	O
and	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cope	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Depositions	O
of	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
without	O
the	O
Knowledge	O
and	O
Consent	O
of	O
Colonel	O
Cope	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
Part	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gun	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Dealer	O
in	O
Coach	O
Harnesses	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Hews	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
's	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Firkin	O
of	O
Soap	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
Firkin	O
of	O
Soap	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
deliver	O
'd	O
to	O
a	O
Comrade	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
and	O
this	O
Deponent	O
and	O
others	O
suspecting	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
Thieves	O
,	O
stopped	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
where	O
Mr.	O
Allen	O
proved	O
the	O
Firkin	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
by	O
the	O
Mark	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
making	O
but	O
a	O
weak	O
and	O
frivolous	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Martha	B-pers
Rimus	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Faith	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Fan	O
,	O
value	O
:	O
18	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Pickard	I-pers
;	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
appearing	O
to	O
the	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Brass	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Filks	I-pers
;	O
but	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cap	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Shervill	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Ramsey	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Vox	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
single	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Hannah	B-pers
Rowse	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
Shillings	O
and	O
8	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
;	O
but	O
for	O
,	O
want	O
of	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Grag	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
's	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
a	O
Pewter	O
pint	O
Pot	O
.	O
Value	O
20	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
;	O
her	O
Confession	O
being	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
sign	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
own	O
Hand	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Heath	B-pers
Goulden	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
,	I-place
New	I-place
Fish-street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
25	O
pounds	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
value	O
33	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Gallopine	I-pers
.	O
Peregrine	B-pers
Tawney	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
looking	O
about	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
for	O
some	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
watching	O
him	O
,	O
saw	O
him	O
go	O
in	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
Box	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
and	O
running	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
this	O
Deponent	O
pursued	O
and	O
caught	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susan	B-pers
Broston	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Bishopsgate-street	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Deal	O
Box	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
80	O
Cakes	O
of	O
Ginger-bread	O
,	O
value	O
48	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Willy	I-pers
;	O
which	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Hodges	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bayl	I-pers
.	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
10	O
Watches	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
other	O
Persons	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
very	O
plainly	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
which	O
were	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
proved	O
by	O
the	O
Deposition	O
of	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
under	O
an	O
Arrest	O
.	O
and	O
actually	O
a	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Poulstone	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Bailiff	O
,	O
in	O
Newtoner	O
's	O
Lane	O
;	O
though	O
3	O
of	O
the	O
Watches	O
being	O
found	O
at	O
a	O
Pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
William	O
chapman	O
,	O
gave	O
the	O
Court	O
Occasion	O
to	O
inspect	O
narrowly	O
into	O
the	O
Affair	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
Witnesses	O
making	O
Oath	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
one	O
that	O
for	O
some	O
Years	O
had	O
bought	O
and	O
sold	O
Curiosities	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Snuff-Box	O
Maker	O
and	O
Graver	O
:	O
He	O
having	O
an	O
extraordinary	O
Character	O
from	O
a	O
Cloud	O
of	O
reputable	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
after	O
a	O
Trial	O
which	O
lasted	O
near	O
four	O
Hours	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Madam	O
Margaret	B-pers
Massenburg	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Design	O
to	O
steal	O
and	O
bear	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Massernburg	I-pers
aforesaid	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Whitcomb	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Madam	O
Massenburg	O
's	O
House	O
having	O
been	O
robbed	O
three	O
Times	O
,	O
himself	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Haskey	I-pers
,	O
took	O
a	O
Resolution	O
to	O
sit	O
up	O
till	O
they	O
caught	O
the	O
Thief	O
;	O
that	O
after	O
5	O
Weeks	O
watching	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
December	O
at	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
a	O
Person	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Window	O
by	O
climbing	O
up	O
the	O
Rails	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
lifted	O
up	O
the	O
Sash	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
Body	O
half	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
when	O
this	O
Deponent	O
snapping	O
a	O
Pistol	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
dropp	O
'd	O
down	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
this	O
Deponent	O
cried	O
,	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
alarmed	O
Mr.	O
Willis	O
at	O
next	O
Door	O
,	O
who	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
found	O
a	O
Silver	O
headed	O
Cane	O
at	O
his	O
Door	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Glove	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Willis	O
shewing	O
the	O
Cane	O
to	O
this	O
Deponent	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Haskey	I-pers
,	O
they	O
believed	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Cane	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
had	O
him	O
taken	O
upon	O
Suspicion	O
.	O
Several	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Cane	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
believe	O
the	O
Cane	O
,	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
very	O
same	O
.	O
But	O
to	O
confront	O
them	O
and	O
vindicate	O
his	O
Character	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Snoddey	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
Bed	O
all	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
till	O
11	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
,	O
he	O
concluded	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Cane	O
which	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
Wife	O
and	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
Lodgers	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Snoddey	O
,	O
all	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
Home	O
all	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
his	O
Business	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
what	O
Methods	O
he	O
maintain	O
'd	O
himself	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
the	O
Author	O
of	O
some	O
Performances	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
made	O
him	O
acquainted	O
with	O
some	O
generous	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
by	O
whose	O
Benevolence	O
he	O
had	O
lived	O
in	O
Credit	O
;	O
though	O
sometimes	O
under	O
poetical	O
Circumstances	O
.	O
Several	O
Gentlemen	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
serv	O
'd	O
,	O
appear	O
'd	O
on	O
his	O
Behalf	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
behaved	O
himself	O
very	O
honestly	O
,	O
but	O
having	O
a	O
poetical	O
Genius	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
apply	O
himself	O
to	O
Business	O
:	O
Upon	O
summing	O
up	O
the	O
Whole	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Trapshaw	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
8	O
Nutmegs	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Tea	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Simpcock	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
8	O
Saw	O
and	O
Chissel	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
;	O
but	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hazard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Copper	O
Scummer	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bencridge	I-pers
;	O
his	O
Confession	O
being	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
sign	O
'd	O
with	O
his	O
own	O
Hand	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Sedgwick	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
11	O
Quarts	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
Jan	O
.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Limposs	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
burnt	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
late	O
Fire	O
in	O
Butcher-Row	B-place
,	O
he	O
fasten	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
his	O
Vault	O
or	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
some	O
Goods	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
in	O
particular	O
some	O
Barrels	O
of	O
Beer	O
and	O
Brandy	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
the	O
Cellar	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
some	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
fastening	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
again	O
broke	O
open	O
divers	O
Times	O
;	O
upon	O
this	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
employ	O
'd	O
a	O
Watchman	O
to	O
attend	O
near	O
the	O
Place	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
it	O
were	O
possible	O
,	O
to	O
surprize	O
the	O
Thief	O
in	O
the	O
Action	O
:	O
Accordingly	O
about	O
7	O
at	O
Night	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
Instant	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
,	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
enter	O
'd	O
in	O
with	O
an	O
empty	O
Cash	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
going	O
to	O
fill	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
This	O
being	O
confirmed	O
by	O
the	O
Deposition	O
of	O
the	O
Watchman	O
who	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
single	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Daniel	B-pers
Dew	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Cheeses	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
5	O
th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
;	O
but	O
for	O
want	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Tea	O
and	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Went	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Hedge	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Topping	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Bibles	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
1725	O
;	O
but	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Norcoat	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hen	O
and	O
a	O
Drake	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Mansum	I-pers
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Velvet	O
Hood	O
,	O
Silk	O
Scarf	O
,	O
3	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
considerable	O
Quantity	O
of	O
other	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Denney	I-pers
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Giles	B-pers
Pratling	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
3	O
Brass	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
a	O
Tea	O
Spoon	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Cullendar	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
but	O
taken	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
a	O
clandestine	O
Manner	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Burglary	O
not	O
being	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
single	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
May	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
58	O
Ivory	O
Combs	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Rook	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
20	O
yards	O
of	O
Black	O
Silk	O
,	O
two	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cambrick	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pearl	O
Necklace	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Barret	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Riding-hood	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Waring	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
single	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Ross	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
two	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
Half	O
Guineas	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Owen	B-pers
Pritcher	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
near	O
Shoe-Lane	B-place
,	I-place
Fleet-street	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
Instant	O
at	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
a	O
Woman	O
pick	O
'd	O
him	O
up	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
Bawdy-house	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
there	O
they	O
fell	O
into	O
company	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
treated	O
them	O
with	O
three	O
Quarterns	O
of	O
Cherry	O
Brandy	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
then	O
they	O
pull	O
'd	O
up	O
their	O
Coats	O
,	O
and	O
invited	O
him	O
to	O
more	O
Familiarity	O
in	O
such	O
Words	O
as	O
are	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
express	O
'd	O
with	O
Modestty	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
refusing	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
;	O
to	O
convince	O
;	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
Mistake	O
,	O
he	O
shew	O
'd	O
them	O
two	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
Half	O
,	O
that	O
soon	O
after	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
one	O
Hand	O
got	O
him	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Button	O
of	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
-	O
Walter	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
Thus	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
Public	O
House	O
near	O
Street-Lane	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
the	O
this	O
Deponent	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
demanded	O
Entrance	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
refused	O
it	O
;	O
after	O
this	O
they	O
agreed	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
next	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
detect	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
this	O
Deponent	O
and	O
he	O
met	O
a	O
Day	O
or	O
two	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
walking	O
down	O
Fleet-Street	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
pick	O
'd	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
the	O
very	O
Room	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
before	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
:	O
This	O
Deponent	O
being	O
the	O
Manager	O
of	O
this	O
Affair	O
,	O
no	O
sooner	O
saw	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
a	O
Watchman	O
,	O
and	O
demanding	O
Entrance	O
they	O
were	O
let	O
in	O
;	O
when	O
asking	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
charg	O
'd	O
the	O
Watchman	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Woman	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
who	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
accordingly	O
they	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
quitted	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
Garret	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
took	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
she	O
innocently	O
became	O
acquainted	O
in	O
the	O
Streets	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
having	O
no	O
Mind	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
public	O
House	O
,	O
she	O
modestly	O
took	O
him	O
home	O
to	O
her	O
own	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
him	O
before	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
she	O
know	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
for	O
which	O
she	O
stood	O
indicted	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
her	O
Modesty	O
,	O
her	O
Honesty	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Innocence	O
,	O
consisted	O
only	O
in	O
Words	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Bannister	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Toot	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
walking	O
up	O
Cheapside	B-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
jostling	O
between	O
him	O
and	O
his	O
Friends	O
,	O
he	O
felt	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
slip	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
he	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
near	O
Bow-Church	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
immediately	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
Sight	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Garedon	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
single	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hews	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Reaves	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Porringer	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Moulstone	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
House	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Dish	O
of	O
Soop	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
Silver	O
Porringer	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
the	O
Porringer	O
was	O
missing	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
apprehended	O
them	O
both	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
being	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
produce	O
no	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
of	O
their	O
having	O
taken	O
it	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
several	O
Credible	O
People	O
to	O
appear	O
for	O
their	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
acknowledging	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
appear	O
'd	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
bound	O
to	O
Prosecute	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Martinday	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Prosecutor	O
appearing	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
China	O
Tea	O
Cannisters	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cumberland	I-pers
;	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Barret	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Barret	I-pers
,	O
(	O
his	O
Son	O
,	O
aged	O
11	O
)	O
by	O
flinging	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
Bruise	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
;	O
to	O
both	O
which	O
Indictments	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Belcher	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
Decemb	O
.	O
about	O
Noon	O
at	O
the	O
Vault	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
in	O
,	O
his	O
Father	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
having	O
shoul	O
'd	O
himself	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
kick	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
Dog	O
and	O
Son	O
of	O
a	O
B	O
-	O
h	O
;	O
and	O
going	O
up	O
Stairs	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
turned	O
,	O
and	O
kick	O
'd	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
without	O
Provocation	O
,	O
repeating	O
it	O
again	O
at	O
the	O
Stair-Case	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
desired	O
this	O
Deponent	O
might	O
be	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
If	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
followed	O
bad	O
Courses	O
?	O
To	O
which	O
be	O
answered	O
,	O
He	O
only	O
heard	O
of	O
this	O
once	O
staying	O
out	O
all	O
Night	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
in	O
Bed	O
some	O
Time	O
before	O
this	O
happen	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
without	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Arms	O
were	O
beat	O
black	O
and	O
blue	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
the	O
Pot	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
Father	O
would	O
not	O
suffer	O
it	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
go	O
down	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
returning	O
,	O
his	O
Father	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
foul	O
'd	O
himself	O
before	O
he	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
Vault	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
then	O
shov	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
fell	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
then	O
kick	O
'd	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
;	O
that	O
this	O
Deponent	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
The	O
Boy	O
is	O
dying	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
only	O
fallen	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
a	O
Cat	O
of	O
Nine	O
Tails	O
,	O
he	O
hit	O
him	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Slashes	O
as	O
he	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
that	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
kick	O
'd	O
or	O
stamp	O
'd	O
on	O
him	O
he	O
never	O
spoke	O
more	O
,	O
but	O
gave	O
14	O
or	O
15	O
Breathes	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
departed	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
likewise	O
confirm	O
'd	O
in	O
every	O
particular	O
by	O
another	O
Evidence	O
,	O
they	O
both	O
agreeing	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
very	O
weak	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
scarcely	O
creep	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
Stairs	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Rainby	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
desir	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
Neighbouring	O
Justice	O
to	O
examine	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
he	O
observed	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
bruised	O
in	O
several	O
Places	O
,	O
particularly	O
the	O
Head	O
:	O
for	O
dividing	O
the	O
common	O
Teguments	O
,	O
a	O
Confusion	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
small	O
Tumour	O
without	O
a	O
Wound	O
,	O
appeared	O
on	O
the	O
Left	O
side	O
,	O
extending	O
from	O
the	O
sore	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
back	O
Part	O
;	O
the	O
Skull	O
being	O
laid	O
bare	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Fracture	O
nor	O
Depression	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
might	O
probably	O
to	O
owing	O
to	O
the	O
Tenderness	O
of	O
the	O
Bony	O
Fibres	O
in	O
so	O
young	O
a	O
Subject	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
off	O
the	O
upper	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Cranium	O
,	O
and	O
dividing	O
the	O
external	O
Membrane	O
of	O
the	O
Brain	O
,	O
a	O
great	O
Quantity	O
of	O
extravasated	O
Blood	O
lay	O
between	O
this	O
and	O
the	O
Membrane	O
that	O
immediately	O
covers	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
must	O
have	O
been	O
occasioned	O
by	O
some	O
Violence	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
likely	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
produced	O
the	O
external	O
Contusion	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
undoubtedly	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
Some	O
witnesses	O
appeared	O
in	O
Behalf	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
before	O
this	O
Time	O
been	O
a	O
very	O
loving	O
,	O
indulgent	O
Father	O
to	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
present	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
's	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Burglariously	O
breaking	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Melcher	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
January	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
Justice	O
Harwood	O
,	O
Brewer	O
,	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
attend	O
in	O
the	O
Brewhouse	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
all	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
having	O
Occasion	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
for	O
some	O
Refreshments	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
safely	O
lock	O
'd	O
some	O
Hours	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
feeling	O
about	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
Tom	O
,	O
Let	O
me	O
go	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
holding	O
him	O
fast	O
he	O
grew	O
resolute	O
,	O
and	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
force	O
himself	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
struggled	O
some	O
Time	O
before	O
any	O
one	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Assistance	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
the	O
Officer	O
of	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
both	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
Kennel	O
,	O
and	O
remembering	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
,	O
with	O
others	O
,	O
had	O
that	O
Night	O
cheated	O
him	O
of	O
some	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
more	O
ready	O
to	O
assist	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
prosecutors	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Money	O
Drawers	O
had	O
been	O
pulled	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Money	O
and	O
a	O
Pack	O
or	O
two	O
of	O
Cards	O
scatter	O
'd	O
about	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
near	O
the	O
Door	O
they	O
found	O
several	O
pick-lock	O
Keys	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Spoon	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drop	O
at	O
the	O
Threshold	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
being	O
in	O
Drink	O
he	O
stumbled	O
against	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
of	O
nothing	O
further	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
making	O
it	O
appear	O
that	O
he	O
lock	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
some	O
Hours	O
before	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
and	I-pers
William	I-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mr.	O
William	B-pers
Trehern	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
4	O
Perukes	O
,	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
hilted	O
Sword	O
,	O
a	O
ouring	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Gold	O
headed	O
Cane	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23rd	O
of	O
December	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
William	B-pers
Mathews	I-pers
being	O
his	O
Servant	O
the	O
Time	O
that	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
he	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
being	O
Accessory	O
to	O
the	O
Crime	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
denied	O
,	O
but	O
after	O
some	O
hesitation	O
,	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
his	O
Brother	O
was	O
guilty	O
,	O
and	O
directed	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
where	O
he	O
might	O
find	O
him	O
;	O
accordingly	O
by	O
his	O
Directions	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
another	O
Person	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
at	O
Lodgings	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
in	O
Gray's-Lane	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
Room	O
there	O
were	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
which	O
are	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
:	O
At	O
which	O
Time	O
John	O
Mathews	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
whole	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
directed	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
where	O
he	O
might	O
find	O
the	O
other	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Window	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Study	O
,	O
or	O
Office	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Help	O
of	O
an	O
empty	O
Barrel	O
,	O
which	O
stood	O
under	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
down	O
the	O
upper	O
Sash	O
,	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Study	O
or	O
Office	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
without	O
the	O
Assistance	O
of	O
his	O
Brother	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
opened	O
the	O
back	O
Door	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
going	O
his	O
Rounds	O
found	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
back	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
the	O
Window	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Good	O
,	O
saying	O
very	O
oddly	O
about	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Pillow	O
Cases	O
fill	O
'd	O
with	O
Goods	O
,	O
as	O
pack	O
'd	O
up	O
to	O
carry	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
this	O
Deponent	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
William	B-pers
Mathews	I-pers
lay	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
Accessory	O
to	O
what	O
was	O
done	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
coming	O
and	O
charging	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
his	O
Brother	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
agreed	O
with	O
his	O
Brother	O
to	O
rob	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
no	O
ways	O
Assistance	O
in	O
this	O
Action	O
.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Tard	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
fastened	O
the	O
Doors	O
before	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
with	O
Bolts	O
and	O
Lock	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
she	O
found	O
them	O
open	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Whole	O
,	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
proved	O
upon	O
William	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
but	O
John	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Sherwood	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Hobs	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hobs	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Weedon	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Hews	I-pers
,	O
Joshua	B-pers
Payn	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Pope	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Meak	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
Jan	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
12	O
Gloucester	O
Cheeses	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Meak	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
at	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
her	O
Door	O
was	O
fast	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Window	O
safe	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
Four	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
the	O
Watch	O
Call	O
'd	O
them	O
up	O
.	O
when	O
the	O
Window	O
Shutters	O
were	O
cut	O
through	O
,	O
the	O
House	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Cheeses	O
gone	O
;	O
that	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
being	O
in	O
Custody	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Cheeses	O
at	O
Joshua	O
Payn	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
House	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
all	O
lived	O
together	O
before	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
with	O
other	O
Officers	O
surrounded	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
slung	O
Glass	O
Bottles	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
at	O
them	O
,	O
our	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Cheeses	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
mark	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Mark	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Charley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Hatch	I-pers
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
like	O
Effect	O
,	O
adding	O
,	O
When	O
they	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
they	O
found	O
two	O
Chissels	O
,	O
a	O
large	O
Gimlet	O
,	O
a	O
dark	O
Lanthorn	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Knife	O
of	O
monstrous	O
size	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Payn	I-pers
made	O
herself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
let	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
Rooms	O
to	O
Sherwood	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
another	O
bed	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
Sherwood	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
lay	O
in	O
one	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
helped	O
them	O
to	O
George	O
Weedon	O
and	O
Henry	O
Hews	O
,	O
as	O
Lodgers	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
Bed	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
disturbed	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
that	O
Sherwood	O
and	O
Weedon	O
brought	O
in	O
the	O
Cheeses	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
Officers	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
they	O
threatned	O
to	O
cut	O
her	O
Throat	O
if	O
the	O
let	O
them	O
in	O
.	O
This	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
plain	O
upon	O
Hobs	O
only	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
all	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Ellingham	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
some	O
Brandy	O
and	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
proved	O
upon	O
Hobs	O
and	O
Weedon	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
3d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cogdale	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
eight	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
and	O
twenty	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
fasten	O
'd	O
her	O
Doors	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
by	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
when	O
her	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
gone	O
;	O
which	O
Goods	O
she	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Joshua	B-pers
Payn	I-pers
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Deposition	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Payn	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
brought	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
by	O
Hobs	O
,	O
Hews	O
,	O
and	O
Weedon	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Sherwood	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
Weedon	I-pers
were	O
a	O
fourth	O
Time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Wallford	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
January	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
Hat	O
and	O
Cane	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
proved	O
upon	O
them	O
by	O
Deposition	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Payn	I-pers
and	O
several	O
concurring	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
wig	O
and	O
Cane	O
being	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
But	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
Facts	O
being	O
proved	O
upon	O
Joshua	B-pers
Payn	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
or	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Pope	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hobs	I-pers
having	O
a	O
Husband	O
convicted	O
for	O
the	O
Fact	O
they	O
four	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Spurgins	I-pers
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Rowell	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Paul	B-pers
Chamberlain	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Cloath	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Linsey	O
Woolsey	O
Apron	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
On	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
about	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
towards	O
Stock	B-place
's	I-place
Market	I-place
with	O
Greens	O
,	O
I	O
being	O
a	O
Gardener	O
,	O
two	O
Persons	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
tallest	O
(	O
which	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
Rowell	O
)	O
put	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
my	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
Deliver	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
shoot	O
me	O
through	O
the	O
Body	O
if	O
I	O
refused	O
;	O
upon	O
this	O
,	O
he	O
dragg	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
a	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
beat	O
me	O
in	O
a	O
barbarous	O
Manner	O
,	O
the	O
shortest	O
(	O
which	O
is	O
Spurgins	O
)	O
did	O
not	O
strike	O
me	O
,	O
nor	O
use	O
me	O
ill	O
,	O
though	O
the	O
other	O
took	O
off	O
my	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
bound	O
my	O
Feet	O
with	O
a	O
Cord	O
and	O
left	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Snow	O
;	O
the	O
shortest	O
would	O
fain	O
have	O
loos	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
would	O
not	O
suffer	O
it	O
;	O
after	O
some	O
Time	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
shortest	O
coming	O
back	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Newgate	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
Compassion	O
on	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
wiped	O
the	O
Blood	O
from	O
my	O
Mouth	O
,	O
which	O
flow	O
'd	O
in	O
abundance	O
from	O
the	O
Blows	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
had	O
given	O
me	O
;	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
he	O
bound	O
my	O
Head	O
with	O
his	O
own	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
over	O
me	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
his	O
first	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
led	O
this	O
Course	O
of	O
Life	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
left	O
it	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
kill	O
'd	O
:	O
After	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
being	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
my	O
Shoes	O
on	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Newgate	O
and	O
charg	O
'd	O
it	O
on	O
Spurgins	O
,	O
who	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
and	O
Ned	O
(	O
meaning	O
Rowell	O
)	O
were	O
guilty	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
Compassion	O
on	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
begg	O
'd	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
the	O
same	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Conoway	I-pers
and	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Benson	I-pers
severally	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
heard	O
Spurgins	O
's	O
Confession	O
:	O
Upon	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
in	O
their	O
Verdict	O
,	O
that	O
Spurgins	O
was	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
But	O
acquitted	O
Rowell	O
,	O
by	O
Reason	O
the	O
Prosecuter	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
his	O
Person	O
.	O
However	O
,	O
they	O
intimated	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
though	O
they	O
were	O
obliged	O
to	O
bring	O
in	O
this	O
Verdict	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
his	O
Confession	O
,	O
yet	O
they	O
hoped	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
represented	O
as	O
an	O
Object	O
of	O
Mercy	O
.	O
This	O
Rowell	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
to	O
an	O
Indictment	O
laid	O
against	O
him	O
and	O
Spurgins	O
for	O
stealing	O
Pidgeons	O
.	O
[	O
Rowell	O
:	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
the	I-place
Martyr	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
her	O
Female	O
Bastard	O
Child	O
,	O
by	O
suffocating	O
,	O
strangling	O
,	O
and	O
breaking	O
the	O
Neck	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Bastard	O
Child	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
it	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
;	O
to	O
both	O
which	O
Indictments	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Barbary	B-pers
James	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
lay	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
for	O
a	O
single	O
Woman	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
ill	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
and	O
complain	O
'd	O
of	O
a	O
Hurt	O
she	O
has	O
received	O
,	O
which	O
have	O
her	O
great	O
Pain	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
told	O
this	O
Deponent	O
of	O
her	O
Design	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
from	O
her	O
Place	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
deponent	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
of	O
any	O
Preparation	O
she	O
had	O
made	O
for	O
the	O
Reception	O
of	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
she	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
say	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
,	O
when	O
taken	O
into	O
Custody	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Perkinson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Case	O
,	O
from	O
Barbary	O
James	O
's	O
telling	O
of	O
her	O
Illness	O
,	O
and	O
asking	O
her	O
for	O
something	O
to	O
comfort	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
in	O
Consequence	O
of	O
this	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
diligent	O
in	O
the	O
Discovery	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Child	O
in	O
the	O
Necessary	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
Deponent	O
could	O
not	O
perceive	O
any	O
Mark	O
of	O
Violence	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
offered	O
to	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
neither	O
could	O
she	O
form	O
an	O
Opinion	O
whether	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
Still-born	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Busher	O
,	O
the	O
Midwife	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
being	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Child	O
after	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Vault	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
Opinion	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
smotherd	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
Help	O
in	O
the	O
Birth	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
breaking	O
of	O
the	O
Neck	O
,	O
this	O
Deponent	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
done	O
without	O
Violence	O
;	O
which	O
indeed	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
might	O
happen	O
by	O
its	O
being	O
slung	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
Vault	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
six	O
Foot	O
deep	O
.	O
This	O
Deponent	O
further	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
How	O
she	O
could	O
commit	O
such	O
an	O
Action	O
?	O
To	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
replied	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
believe	O
she	O
had	O
3	O
Months	O
to	O
go	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
her	O
not	O
so	O
forward	O
as	O
making	O
Provision	O
as	O
she	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
Still-born	O
.	O
Her	O
Examination	O
before	O
Robert	B-pers
Thornhill	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
delivered	O
of	O
a	O
dead	O
Child	O
whilst	O
her	O
Fellow	O
Servant	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
received	O
Damage	O
by	O
ringing	O
out	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
which	O
brought	O
on	O
her	O
Pains	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
thought	O
would	O
go	O
off	O
,	O
believing	O
she	O
had	O
then	O
10	O
or	O
12	O
Weeks	O
to	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
made	O
Preparation	O
for	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
Reception	O
;	O
in	O
particular	O
,	O
2	O
Caps	O
,	O
2	O
Forehead-cloths	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Shift	O
.	O
Correspondent	O
to	O
this	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hewlet	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
was	O
order	O
'd	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
there	O
a	O
Belly-band	O
,	O
2	O
Stays	O
,	O
2	O
Sleeves	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Child-bed	O
Linnen	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Whole	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Mitchell	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
convicted	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Mac-Masters	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
very	O
remarkable	O
,	O
were	O
put	O
off	O
till	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
ended	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgement	O
as	O
follows	O
:	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
7.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Barrett	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Sherwood	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Hobs	O
,	O
George	B-pers
Weedon	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Hews	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Spurgins	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
hand	O
1.	O
John	B-pers
Mitchell	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
convicted	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
.	O
Transportation	O
23.	O
George	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
Joshua	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Pool	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Piddington	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Selby	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Appleby	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hews	I-pers
,	O
Heath	B-pers
Goulden	I-pers
,	O
Susanna	B-pers
Broston	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Ramsey	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Grag	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Trapshaw	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hazard	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Sedgwick	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Barratt	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bannister	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Rowell	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Tryals	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Mac-Masters	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
very	O
remarkable	O
,	O
were	O
put	O
off	O
till	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Savage	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Gregory	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Wilcox	O
,	O
were	O
admitted	O
to	O
Bail	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
their	O
pleading	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Pardon	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENT	O
.	O
This	O
way	O
was	O
published	O
,	O
Printed	O
for	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
Joseph	B-pers
Marshal	I-pers
,	O
at	O
she	O
Bible	O
is	O
Newgate-Street	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
A	O
Whip	O
for	O
the	O
Quack	O
,	O
or	O
some	O
Remarks	O
on	O
M-N	O
,	O
Supplement	O
to	O
his	O
ONANIA	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
full	O
Answer	O
and	O
Consulation	O
of	O
his	O
boasted	O
of	O
and	O
long	O
promised	O
curious	O
Piece	O
from	O
Sekceider	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
all	O
their	O
Arguments	O
for	O
the	O
Seed	O
's	O
return	O
into	O
the	O
Blood	O
after	O
it	O
Secretion	O
.	O
By	O
Muth	O
Rosos	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Stitch	O
'd	O
Where	O
may	O
likewise	O
be	O
had	O
Onania	O
Examined	O
and	O
Detected	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s	O
,	O
6	O
d.	O
2	O
.	O
Military	O
Discipline	O
,	O
the	O
Words	O
of	O
Command	O
,	O
and	O
Directions	O
for	O
Excercising	O
the	O
Musker	O
and	O
Bayoner	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
by	O
the	O
Genalemen	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Horse	O
and	O
Foot	O
Guards	O
,	O
with	O
Observations	O
of	O
the	O
several	O
Beats	O
if	O
the	O
Drum	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Approv	O
'd	O
of	O
by	O
several	O
great	O
Commanders	O
,	O
and	O
Adjutants	O
.	O
price	O
Bound	O
1	O
s.	O
3	O
.	O
The	O
Life	O
and	O
miraculous	O
Convertion	O
,	O
from	O
Property	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Percy	I-pers
,	O
in	O
three	O
Parts	O
1	O
.	O
The	O
Glory	O
of	O
Divine	O
Grace	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
The	O
Protection	O
of	O
Divine	O
Providence-	O
3	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Goodness	O
of	O
God	O
manisfested	O
.	O
The	O
3d	O
Edition	O
,	O
written	O
by	O
himself	O
.	O
Price	O
Bound	O
1	O
s.	O
4	O
.	O
A	O
Warning	O
to	O
Youth	O
,	O
the	O
Life	O
and	O
Death	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
twice	O
executed	O
at	O
Ratcliff	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Maid-Servant	O
.	O
Illustrated	O
with	O
Cuts	O
,	O
never	O
done	O
before	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
is	O
added	O
,	O
a	O
Sermon	O
preach	O
'd	O
at	O
his	O
Funeral	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Price	O
stitch	O
6	O
d.	O
5	O
.	O
Heaven	O
began	O
here	O
on	O
Earth	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
Help	O
to	O
young	O
Persons	O
,	O
under	O
their	O
first	O
Convictions	O
,	O
and	O
Closure	O
with	O
the	O
Lord	O
Christ	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
continued	O
.	O
In	O
these	O
Dialogues	O
,	O
between	O
a	O
Minister	O
and	O
a	O
private	O
Christian	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Drawn	O
up	O
for	O
the	O
advancing	O
of	O
the	O
free	O
Grace	O
of	O
God	O
in	O
a	O
dear	O
Redeemer	O
to	O
the	O
Chief	O
of	O
Sinners	O
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
in	O
Calf	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
6	O
.	O
Baptism	O
Discovered	O
plainly	O
and	O
faithfully	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Word	O
of	O
God	O
;	O
wherein	O
is	O
for	O
forth	O
the	O
glorious	O
Pattern	O
of	O
our	O
Blessed	O
Saviour	O
Jesus	O
Christ	O
,	O
the	O
Pattern	O
of	O
all	O
Believers	O
.	O
By	O
John	B-pers
Noscot	I-pers
.	O
Price	O
bound	O
6	O
d.	O
7	O
.	O
A	O
Further	O
Guide	O
to	O
Parish	O
Clerks	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
full	O
Account	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Psalm	O
Tunes	O
and	O
what	O
Psalms	O
are	O
sung	O
to	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
with	O
an	O
Introduction	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
By	O
Daniel	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
.	O
Price	O
6	O
d	O
.	O
