TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Baily	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
and	O
COUNTRY	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
5th	O
,	O
6th	O
,	O
and	O
7th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
1728	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
First	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
Six	O
Pence	O
.	O
)	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
EDWARD	B-pers
BECHER	I-pers
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Carter	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Page	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Serjeant	O
at	O
Law	O
;	O
and	O
other	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
aforesaid	O
;	O
Together	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
.	O
LONDON	O
JURY	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Cheesbrook	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Best	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Vear	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Palleday	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Symonds	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Evat	I-pers
,	O
Symon	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Walley	I-pers
.	O
MIDDLESEX	O
JURY	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stanley	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Tankard	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Kentish	I-pers
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Farmton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Spinnage	I-pers
,	O
Arthur	B-pers
Rawlinson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Dorcent	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
Fredrick	B-pers
Waldron	I-pers
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Katherine	I-place
Cree-Church	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
2	O
Yards	O
and	O
a	O
Half	O
of	O
Cambrick	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Pond	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Pond	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
House	O
under	O
presence	O
of	O
buying	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
shewing	O
her	O
,	O
4	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Cambrick	O
to	O
look	O
on	O
,	O
presently	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
charging	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
search	O
'd	O
her	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
between	O
her	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
thrust	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
Stays	O
.	O
She	O
call	O
'd	O
two	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
positive	O
Oath	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Grille	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
29	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
a	O
Women	O
pick	O
'd	O
him	O
up	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
drank	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Drams	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
after	O
some	O
Time	O
the	O
Woman	O
which	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
him	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
Time	O
he	O
felt	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
and	O
found	O
his	O
Money	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
sitting	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
tumbling	O
him	O
down	O
she	O
unbutton	O
'd	O
his	O
Breeches	O
and	O
got	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
their	O
laying	O
some	O
Time	O
in	O
that	O
indecent	O
Posture	O
,	O
she	O
likewise	O
left	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
searching	O
his	O
Pockets	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
his	O
Money	O
was	O
all	O
gone	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
enquired	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Time	O
after	O
found	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
kept	O
Company	O
with	O
several	O
Whores	O
and	O
several	O
Whores	O
,	O
and	O
produced	O
two	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
brought	O
the	O
Woman	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
She	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
Home	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
nor	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
home	O
for	O
some	O
Days	O
before	O
:	O
Upon	O
the	O
Whole	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Hubberfield	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Diaper	O
Napkin	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Ells	O
of	O
Holland	O
;	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
;	O
but	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Street	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
considerable	O
Quantity	O
of	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
divers	O
Persons	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
Lodging	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
the	O
Apparel	O
of	O
several	O
Sea-faring	O
Men	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
confess	O
'd	O
to	O
her	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
all	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Murry	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Curtis	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Sharp	I-pers
,	O
confirming	O
likewise	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
present	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
him	O
confess	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
for	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Frith	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
April	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
late	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
4	O
other	O
Persons	O
drinking	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
;	O
(	O
a	O
publick	O
House	O
)	O
that	O
he	O
begg	O
'd	O
they	O
would	O
go	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
weary	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
another	O
Room	O
and	O
fell	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
awaking	O
,	O
found	O
his	O
Watch	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
Home	O
,	O
and	O
believing	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
or	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Company	O
(	O
who	O
had	O
paid	O
their	O
Reckoning	O
and	O
were	O
gone	O
)	O
that	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
pursued	O
and	O
Overtook	O
them	O
in	O
Leather-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
catching	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
before	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
amongst	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bid	O
him	O
he	O
easy	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
see	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
seeing	O
a	O
Watchman	O
,	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
others	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
prevented	O
,	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
the	O
Watch	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Hand	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
to	O
play	O
the	O
Rogue	O
,	O
and	O
design	O
'd	O
to	O
bring	O
it	O
again	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
.	O
Luck	O
the	O
Watchman	O
,	O
confirm	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
delivered	O
the	O
Watch	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
in	O
his	O
Presence	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
prosecuted	O
for	O
it	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
should	O
not	O
live	O
long	O
:	O
The	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Conolly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
and	O
Chain	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Jacob	B-pers
Blaney	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Blaney	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
two	O
others	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
and	O
pretended	O
they	O
wanted	O
a	O
Warrant	O
,	O
when	O
about	O
two	O
Hours	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
which	O
hung	O
upon	O
a	O
Nail	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
others	O
were	O
;	O
and	O
advertising	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
Publick	O
News	O
Paper	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
him	O
by	O
a	O
Pawnbroker	O
,	O
one	O
Granger	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Pawnbroker	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
persons	O
concerned	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
in	O
Court	O
:	O
However	O
,	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
her	O
own	O
Confession	O
,	O
sign	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
own	O
Hand	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
Bridget	B-pers
Coffell	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Wiltshire	I-pers
,	O
agreed	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
that	O
Coffell	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
and	O
Wiltshire	O
being	O
present	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
Eccling	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
them	O
Ten	O
Pounds	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
Confession	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
not	O
denying	O
it	O
even	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Ash	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Copper	O
Cover	O
of	O
a	O
Pot	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Brass	O
Cover	O
of	O
another	O
Pot	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
missing	O
the	O
two	O
Covers	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
the	O
Windows-Shutters	O
being	O
taken	O
down	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
fastened	O
but	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
,	O
he	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
searching	O
Ward	O
's	O
House	O
he	O
found	O
Davis	O
in	O
an	O
empty	O
,	O
cutting	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
Leaden	O
Cistern	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
his	O
House	O
but	O
not	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
his	O
2	O
Potlids	O
or	O
Covers	O
;	O
at	O
which	O
Time	O
Davis	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
Ward	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
taken	O
all	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
prevented	O
;	O
this	O
he	O
likewise	O
confess	O
'd	O
before	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
.	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Bromley	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Francis	B-pers
Bromley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Grange	O
,	O
all	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
were	O
present	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
;	O
that	O
Ward	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
directed	O
them	O
where	O
they	O
found	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Cistern	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
to	O
Davis	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
another	O
Room	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
under	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
confess	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
yet	O
his	O
hiding	O
himself	O
when	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Cistern	O
being	O
too	O
large	O
and	O
heavy	O
to	O
be	O
conveniently	O
brought	O
away	O
by	O
Ward	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
were	O
of	O
Opinion	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
equally	O
concerned	O
,	O
and	O
according	O
brought	O
in	O
their	O
Verdict	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jinkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
's	I-place
Hanover-Square	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tea-Kettle	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Lamp	O
,	O
a	O
Chavingdish	O
,	O
a	O
Soop	O
Ladle	O
,	O
a	O
top	O
of	O
a	O
Cruet	O
,	O
3	O
Forks	O
,	O
12	O
Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
Milk-pot	O
,	O
5	O
Tea-Spoons	O
,	O
all	O
of	O
Silver	O
,	O
besides	O
two	O
Silver	O
Baskets	O
,	O
several	O
Silver	O
Hasted	O
Knives	O
and	O
Forks	O
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
a	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
valuable	O
Goods	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
400	O
l.	O
and	O
82	O
l.	O
16	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
not	O
liking	O
him	O
,	O
turned	O
him	O
away	O
on	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
this	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
finding	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
that	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broken	O
and	O
the	O
Plate	O
gone	O
,	O
he	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
employed	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Mombray	O
to	O
search	O
after	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Mombray	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
got	O
two	O
Warrants	O
(	O
one	O
to	O
search	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
to	O
apprehend	O
)	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Brother-in-Laws	O
House	O
,	O
(	O
Wills	O
Coffee-House	O
near	O
Temple-Bar	O
)	O
and	O
finding	O
the	O
prisoner	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
him	O
his	O
Name	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
willing	O
to	O
own	O
,	O
he	O
charged	O
a	O
Constable	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
searching	O
him	O
,	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
pockets	O
5	O
Silver	O
Tea-Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Top	O
of	O
a	O
Cruet	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Crest	O
engraven	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Coggs	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
search	O
'd	O
him	O
at	O
Will	O
's	O
Coffe-House	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Plate	O
in	O
his	O
Pockets	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
could	O
give	O
no	O
Account	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Tringuan	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Morning	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
him	O
confess	O
that	O
the	O
Plate	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Saracen's-Head	O
in	O
Friday-street	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Box	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
Number	O
22	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
them	O
gave	O
this	O
Deponent	O
2	O
Keys	O
,	O
one	O
for	O
the	O
Chamber-Door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
the	O
Box	O
;	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Saracen's-Head	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
opened	O
with	O
the	O
Key	O
he	O
had	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
found	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Plate	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
Plate	O
being	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
Swore	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
,	O
it	O
bearing	O
his	O
Coat	O
of	O
Arms	O
.	O
Roger	B-pers
Yarnton	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
House	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
by	O
missing	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
with	O
his	O
Fellow	O
Servants	O
searching	O
to	O
find	O
how	O
the	O
Thief	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
their	O
Master	O
's	O
Dressing-Room	O
Window	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Iron	O
Bars	O
,	O
through	O
which	O
a	O
Light	O
came	O
to	O
their	O
Vault	O
)	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Mould	O
being	O
rais	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Stones	O
in	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
fastened	O
,	O
grated	O
,	O
they	O
could	O
perceive	O
it	O
was	O
newly	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
by	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Marks	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
's	O
Foot	O
being	O
under	O
the	O
Dressing-Room	O
Window	O
,	O
they	O
concluded	O
that	O
the	O
Thief	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Bars	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
which	O
Window	O
he	O
shut	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Woodgate	I-pers
confirmed	O
that	O
the	O
Bars	O
had	O
been	O
opened	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
by	O
the	O
appearance	O
of	O
the	O
Mould	O
and	O
Stones	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
new	O
done	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
but	O
a	O
very	O
frivolous	O
Defence	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
Drunk	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
Plate	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
that	O
at	O
the	O
Saracen's-Head	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
how	O
it	O
came	O
there	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Whole	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shift	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gibbs	I-pers
;	O
four	O
Shifts	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Barbary	B-pers
Pinfold	I-pers
,	O
and	O
five	O
Aprons	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
other	O
Persons	O
;	O
which	O
Goods	O
being	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Custody	O
by	O
the	O
Constable	O
who	O
apprehended	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
giving	O
but	O
a	O
very	O
indifferent	O
Account	O
of	O
herself	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mackool	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Dionas	B-pers
Loglin	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Day-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
there	O
several	O
Napkins	O
,	O
Table-cloaths	O
Aprons	O
,	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
Mobbs	O
,	O
Russles	O
,	O
Gloves	O
,	O
Pillowbiers	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Dionas	O
Loglin	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
left	O
his	O
Wife	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
home	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
key	O
in	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Drawers	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
of	O
their	O
being	O
gone	O
till	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
following	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Loglin	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
some	O
Hours	O
after	O
her	O
Husband	O
went	O
from	O
home	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
a	O
Woman	O
which	O
Lay-in	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
put	O
the	O
Key	O
over	O
the	O
door	O
(	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
lock	O
'd	O
it	O
)	O
in	O
a	O
Place	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
no	O
Body	O
knew	O
but	O
herself	O
and	O
Husband	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
home	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
suspecting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
knowing	O
her	O
by	O
Sight	O
,	O
made	O
a	O
strict	O
Enquiry	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
of	O
her	O
Goods	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Hands	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Carew	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Sherley	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Adney	O
,	O
who	O
being	O
all	O
three	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
severally	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
had	O
each	O
a	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
brought	O
to	O
them	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
breaking	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
not	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
having	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Character	O
was	O
very	O
good	O
before	O
this	O
happened	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
only	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Hews	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Mr.	B-pers
Bartholomew	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
of	O
Value	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
was	O
bid	O
to	O
consider	O
the	O
Consequence	O
of	O
pleading	O
Guilty	O
to	O
a	O
Capital	O
Offence	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
Death	O
without	O
Benefit	O
of	O
the	O
Clergy	O
,	O
yet	O
he	O
persisted	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
refusing	O
to	O
put	O
himself	O
upon	O
his	O
Trial	O
,	O
saying	O
again	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
Guilty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Bryan	B-pers
Mackguire	I-pers
,	O
did	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
assault	O
Henry	B-pers
Bunn	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
in	O
an	O
open	O
Place	O
near	B-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
2	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Foreign	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
s.	O
and	O
8	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
likewise	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
Time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Bryan	B-pers
Mackguire	I-pers
,	O
did	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
assault	O
Philip	B-pers
Dowling	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
in	O
an	O
open	O
Place	O
near	B-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
.	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
and	O
2s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
likewise	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
4th	O
Time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Bryan	B-pers
Mackguire	I-pers
,	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
did	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
assault	O
Richard	B-pers
Bridger	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
in	O
an	O
open	O
Place	O
near	O
Islington	B-place
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
6	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
5th	O
Time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Bryan	B-pers
Mackguire	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Sefton	I-pers
,	O
(	O
executed	O
last	O
Sessions	O
)	O
did	O
assault	O
Edward	B-pers
Carroll	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
four	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
and	O
to	O
this	O
Indictment	O
he	O
continued	O
to	O
plead	O
Guilty	O
,	O
for	O
being	O
conscious	O
of	O
his	O
Crimes	O
,	O
he	O
resolutely	O
took	O
the	O
Shortest	O
Method	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
expected	O
nothing	O
but	O
Death	O
.	O
Bryan	B-pers
Mackguire	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Henry	B-pers
Bunn	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
in	O
an	O
open	O
Place	O
near	O
Islington	B-place
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
2	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Foreign	O
Gold	O
value	O
11	O
s.	O
and	O
8	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
willing	O
to	O
see	O
his	O
Accusers	O
,	O
put	O
himself	O
upon	O
his	O
Trial	O
.	O
Henry	O
Bunn	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
coming	O
from	O
Cambray	O
House	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Hews	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Sefton	I-pers
,	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
executed	O
last	O
Sessions	O
for	O
this	O
Fact	O
)	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
when	O
Hews	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
Blood	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
make	O
any	O
Noise	O
I	O
ll	O
shoot	O
you	O
through	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
who	O
assisted	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
they	O
all	O
went	O
off	O
together	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Bryan	B-pers
Mackguire	I-pers
,	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
William	O
Sefton	O
,	O
and	O
Richard	O
Hews	O
,	O
did	O
assault	O
Philip	B-pers
Dowling	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
in	O
an	O
open	O
Place	O
near	B-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Cloath	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Dowling	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
Easter	O
Monday	O
about	O
9	O
or	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
between	O
Kentish	O
Town	O
and	O
St.	O
Pancras	O
,	O
William	O
Sefton	O
,	O
Richard	O
Hews	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
stopp	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
his	O
asking	O
what	O
they	O
meant	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
tell	O
him	O
presently	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
they	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
some	O
Time	O
after	O
,	O
hearing	O
that	O
William	O
Sefton	O
was	O
convicted	O
and	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
enquired	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
inform	O
him	O
of	O
any	O
of	O
his	O
Things	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
Time	O
Sefton	O
directed	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Bryan	O
Mackguire	O
;	O
who	O
had	O
the	O
Peruke	O
then	O
upon	O
his	O
Head	O
which	O
they	O
took	O
from	O
this	O
Deponent	O
;	O
the	O
Wig	O
being	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
same	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Mackguire	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Direction	O
of	O
Sefton	O
;	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
he	O
was	O
likewise	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Bryan	O
Mackguire	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
Time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Richard	B-pers
Bridger	I-pers
(	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
accompanied	O
with	O
the	O
same	O
Persons	O
aforementioned	O
)	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
in	O
an	O
open	O
Place	O
near	B-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
six	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Bridger	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
That	O
Hews	O
,	O
Sefton	O
,	O
and	O
Mackguire	O
,	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
Field	O
near	O
Islington	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
others	O
,	O
Hews	O
and	O
Sefton	O
robb	O
'd	O
his	O
Companions	O
,	O
and	O
Hews	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Bryan	B-pers
Mackguire	I-pers
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
Blood	O
,	O
why	O
are	O
not	O
you	O
doing	O
Business	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
Mackguire	O
demanded	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
,	O
being	O
six	O
Shillings	O
and	O
some	O
Half-pence	O
,	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
the	O
Jury	O
likewise	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
4th	O
Time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
others	O
aforementioned	O
,	O
did	O
assault	O
Edward	B-pers
Carrol	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
near	B-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
4	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
and	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Carrol	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
the	O
others	O
)	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
four	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
off	O
his	O
Ring	O
,	O
Mackguire	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
it	O
off	O
readily	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
put	O
this	O
Deponent	O
's	O
Finger	O
in	O
his	O
Mouth	O
,	O
and	O
violently	O
pull	O
'd	O
it	O
off	O
with	O
his	O
Teeth	O
,	O
insomuch	O
that	O
he	O
dreaded	O
he	O
would	O
bite	O
off	O
his	O
Finger	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
four	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Benson	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Cater	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Margaret	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Pocket	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
.	O
Penny	O
,	O
3	O
Keys	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
a	O
Thimble	O
,	O
value	O
a	O
Half-penny	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
Margaret	O
Sutton	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
the	O
7	B-place
Dials	I-place
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
her	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
snatch	O
'd	O
,	O
or	O
cut	O
off	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Money	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
confident	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
Person	O
who	O
robb	O
'd	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
her	O
Pocket	O
she	O
cut	O
the	O
Strings	O
of	O
her	O
Hood	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
taken	O
that	O
too	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
Deponent	O
recovering	O
herself	O
,	O
struggled	O
for	O
it	O
and	O
overcame	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
desired	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
might	O
be	O
asked	O
,	O
Whether	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
owe	O
Money	O
to	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
convicted	O
last	O
Sessions	O
for	O
Street-Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
executed	O
)	O
and	O
whether	O
she	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
did	O
any	O
other	O
than	O
demand	O
that	O
Money	O
of	O
her	O
as	O
a	O
Debt	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
answered	O
,	O
She	O
was	O
so	O
far	O
from	O
owing	O
Money	O
to	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
Money	O
was	O
not	O
demanded	O
as	O
a	O
Debt	O
,	O
but	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
Money	O
and	O
Keys	O
,	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
by	O
Violence	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
desired	O
she	O
might	O
be	O
asked	O
another	O
Question	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
having	O
the	O
Discretion	O
to	O
stay	O
till	O
it	O
was	O
asked	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
Was	O
not	O
I	O
at	O
your	O
House	O
this	O
Day	O
Month	O
to	O
ask	O
you	O
for	O
Money	O
which	O
you	O
owed	O
me	O
?	O
To	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
answered	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
a	O
Month	O
Tomorrow	O
since	O
you	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
same	O
Token	O
that	O
you	O
stole	O
away	O
three	O
Silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
pretend	O
I	O
owed	O
you	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
run	O
away	O
last	O
I	O
should	O
catch	O
you	O
;	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
further	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
the	O
caused	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
apprehended	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
wish	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
stop	O
her	O
from	O
being	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
any	O
Body	O
else	O
for	O
the	O
future	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
plain	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Ormondy	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Lovey	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Kirk	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Burglary	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Shearman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
40	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
Mr.	O
Shearman	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
Shop	O
being	O
broken	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
Suspicion	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
had	O
them	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Shearman	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
March	O
her	O
Servant	O
shut	O
up	O
the	O
Doors	O
and	O
Windows	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
some	O
Body	O
knock	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
who	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
a	O
Person	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
believed	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
Half	O
an	O
Ounce	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
did	O
believe	O
the	O
Key	O
was	O
stole	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Pin	O
of	O
the	O
Window-Shutter	O
,	O
for	O
next	O
Morning	O
she	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
up	O
by	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
them	O
that	O
their	O
Shop	O
was	O
broke	O
up	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
perceived	O
was	O
done	O
by	O
the	O
taking	O
out	O
the	O
Pin	O
of	O
the	O
Window-shutter	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dickson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
five	O
Fellows	O
lurking	O
about	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
about	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
knock	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
others	O
waited	O
for	O
his	O
coming	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
taking	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
pack	O
of	O
Rogues	O
,	O
took	O
particular	O
Notice	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sure	O
that	O
James	O
Kirk	O
was	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
Anderson	O
was	O
another	O
;	O
but	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
found	O
upon	O
them	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Circumstances	O
alledged	O
against	O
them	O
not	O
being	O
strong	O
enough	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
appearing	O
to	O
their	O
Character	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Harper	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
some	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Flemming	I-pers
,	O
and	O
two	O
pound	O
of	O
Worsted	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Deakon	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
some	O
Time	O
since	O
been	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
Dye-house	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
which	O
Goods	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
Dyed	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
after	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
this	O
Deponent	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
upon	O
this	O
Confession	O
went	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
pawn	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	I-pers
of	I-pers
St.	I-pers
Leonard	I-pers
's	I-pers
Shoreditch	I-pers
,	I-pers
and	I-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
his	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
,	O
(	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Rug	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Smithurst	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
took	O
a	O
Room	O
of	O
him	O
ready	O
Furnish	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
Time	O
he	O
made	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
with	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
intrusted	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Room	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
make	O
this	O
Charge	O
appear	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Killestone	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Calloway	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Copper	O
Pot	O
and	O
Cover	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Ladle	O
,	O
20	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
Iron	O
,	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Dish	O
,	O
a	O
Copper	O
,	O
a	O
Pick-Ax	O
,	O
eight	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ogbourn	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shed	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
April	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
Woman	O
being	O
stopp	O
'd	O
selling	O
the	O
Pick-Ax	O
,	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
her	O
being	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
out	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
against	O
whom	O
she	O
was	O
admitted	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
her	O
Information	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
all	O
at	O
a	O
Brandy	O
Shop	O
some	O
Days	O
after	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Couzens	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
Year	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Night	O
at	O
a	O
Brandy	O
Shop	O
they	O
asked	O
her	O
to	O
assist	O
them	O
in	O
robbing	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Persuasion	O
,	O
she	O
consented	O
,	O
they	O
telling	O
her	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
a	O
great	O
Prize	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
at	O
Midnight	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
coming	O
there	O
,	O
Wilson	O
bid	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
lift	O
him	O
over	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
stood	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Yards	O
at	O
a	O
Distance	O
as	O
a	O
Spy	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
any	O
Body	O
came	O
by	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
might	O
give	O
them	O
Intelligence	O
;	O
that	O
presently	O
after	O
Wilson	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
he	O
opened	O
a	O
Door	O
and	O
let	O
Thomas	B-pers
Killerstone	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Calloway	I-pers
in	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
Time	O
they	O
brought	O
out	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
the	O
Pewter	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
melted	O
at	O
a	O
Brandy	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Goods	O
they	O
sold	O
and	O
divided	O
the	O
Money	O
amongst	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
gave	O
her	O
nothing	O
for	O
her	O
Share	O
of	O
the	O
Booty	O
but	O
a	O
Pick-Ax	O
,	O
in	O
selling	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
and	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Being	O
asked	O
severally	O
what	O
they	O
had	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
,	O
they	O
all	O
confidently	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
protested	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
only	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Couzens	I-pers
,	O
nor	O
had	O
ever	O
seen	O
her	O
before	O
;	O
and	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
alledged	O
against	O
them	O
was	O
false	O
,	O
they	O
produced	O
the	O
following	O
Witnesses	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
had	O
a	O
Room	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
he	O
lodged	O
all	O
Night	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
let	O
him	O
in	O
at	O
10	O
o	O
'	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
heard	O
him	O
talking	O
to	O
his	O
Mother	O
till	O
four	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
his	O
Mother	O
being	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
comfort	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Colloway	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
her	O
Son	O
William	O
Colloway	O
,	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
all	O
that	O
Night	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
Oath	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
,	O
that	O
her	O
Son	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
all	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
stir	O
out	O
on	O
any	O
Occasion	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Osbourn	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Evidence	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Couzens	I-pers
,	O
say	O
,	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
Custody	O
,	O
that	O
to	O
save	O
herself	O
she	O
would	O
hang	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
right	O
or	O
wrong	O
:	O
Upon	O
the	O
Whole	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kelly	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Sauce-pan	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
but	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hammit	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
and	O
forty	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
appearing	O
his	O
Recognizance	O
was	O
estreated	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Jackman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Le	I-place
Bone	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
,	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Jackman	I-pers
,	O
did	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
feloniously	O
steal	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Bed	O
Curtains	O
,	O
value	O
twenty-three	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Hissingbottle	I-pers
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
Recognizance	O
was	O
estreated	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Godfrey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
100	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Indigo	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
1724	O
.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
100	O
weight	O
of	O
Cochineal	O
,	O
value	O
100	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Alesworth	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
employ	O
'd	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
,	O
(	O
a	O
Warehouse-keeper	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
South-Sea	O
Company	O
)	O
to	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
Warehouses	O
in	O
Mark-Lane	B-place
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
employed	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
as	O
a	O
Porter	O
,	O
(	O
but	O
in	O
a	O
Station	O
something	O
above	O
this	O
Deponent	O
)	O
he	O
would	O
frequently	O
take	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
Pounds	O
of	O
Cochincal	O
at	O
a	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
honest	O
Deponent	O
)	O
helped	O
him	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
this	O
Pretence	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
the	O
more	O
excusable	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
threatned	O
to	O
have	O
him	O
turned	O
away	O
if	O
he	O
offered	O
to	O
betray	O
him	O
,	O
in	O
one	O
Week	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
carried	O
away	O
100	O
Pounds	O
or	O
upwards	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
sold	O
to	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Austin	O
a	O
Person	O
who	O
used	O
to	O
buy	O
Goods	O
which	O
were	O
stole	O
by	O
Warehouse	O
Men	O
,	O
and	O
Porters	O
working	O
in	O
Cellars	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
Keys	O
;	O
this	O
Cochineal	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
weighed	O
at	O
the	O
Castle	O
in	O
Tower-street	O
about	O
5	O
Pounds	O
in	O
a	O
Parcel	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
all	O
about	O
20	O
Parcels	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
put	O
up	O
in	O
Linnen	O
Bags	O
,	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Austin	O
had	O
made	O
and	O
contrived	O
for	O
the	O
Conveniency	O
of	O
his	O
carrying	O
it	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
more	O
Secrecy	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lamberson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sold	O
the	O
Cochineal	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Austin	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
brought	O
it	O
in	O
little	O
Bags	O
which	O
Mrs.	O
Austin	O
had	O
made	O
him	O
for	O
that	O
End	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
sometimes	O
would	O
bring	O
in	O
Parcels	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Times	O
a	O
Day	O
,	O
each	O
Parcel	O
weighing	O
about	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Pounds	O
,	O
that	O
sometimes	O
he	O
would	O
sell	O
it	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Austin	O
for	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Pound	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
cheaper	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
perfectly	O
innocent	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
accused	O
out	O
of	O
Malice	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
two	O
Witnesses	O
who	O
swore	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
were	O
People	O
of	O
such	O
ill	O
Fame	O
,	O
that	O
their	O
Oaths	O
ought	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
,	O
they	O
having	O
cohabited	O
together	O
at	O
a	O
Time	O
that	O
Alesworth	O
had	O
a	O
Wife	O
and	O
three	O
Children	O
which	O
lay	O
upon	O
the	O
Parish	O
;	O
and	O
to	O
invalidate	O
their	O
Evidence	O
and	O
strengthen	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
Frances	B-pers
Ingram	I-pers
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
lodg	O
'd	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
when	O
a	O
Woman	O
made	O
an	O
uproar	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
Character	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Basingdine	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
severally	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
had	O
work	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
Cellars	O
,	O
and	O
Warehouses	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
of	O
an	O
ill	O
Thing	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
but	O
on	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Ward	I-place
of	I-place
the	I-place
Tower	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
150	O
Pounds	O
Weight	O
of	O
Indigo	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
1724	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
200	O
Weight	O
of	O
Cochineal	O
,	O
value	O
200	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
South	B-pers
Sea	I-pers
Company	I-pers
as	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Alesworth	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
as	O
a	O
Porter	O
to	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
Warehouses	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
South-Sea	O
Company	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
Servant	O
under	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
working	O
together	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
several	O
Times	O
carry	O
several	O
Bags	O
of	O
Cochineal	O
home	O
,	O
which	O
Cochineal	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
with	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
intrusted	O
,	O
and	O
conveying	O
it	O
away	O
privately	O
,	O
he	O
converted	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
Use	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
this	O
Deponent	O
had	O
several	O
Times	O
seen	O
him	O
carry	O
Bags	O
full	O
of	O
Cochineal	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
weighing	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
sell	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
Harry	B-pers
Sanders	I-pers
a	O
Person	O
who	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
made	O
a	O
Sort	O
of	O
Mill	O
,	O
or	O
Funnel	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Cochineal	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Company	O
's	O
Bags	O
with	O
more	O
Ease	O
and	O
Expedition	O
:	O
That	O
at	O
this	O
Time	O
Philip	B-pers
Godfrey	I-pers
used	O
to	O
be	O
intrusted	O
with	O
the	O
Keys	O
always	O
on	O
a	O
Saturday	O
,	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
used	O
to	O
ride	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
Pleasure	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Godfrey	O
's	O
Place	O
to	O
search	O
(	O
or	O
in	O
their	O
Language	O
,	O
to	O
stroke	O
down	O
)	O
the	O
Gaublers	O
and	O
Porters	O
who	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
attend	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
connive	O
at	O
what	O
Austin	O
did	O
,	O
doing	O
the	O
same	O
himself	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
this	O
Cochineal	O
he	O
said	O
Austin	O
would	O
sell	O
for	O
15	O
or	O
16	O
Shillings	O
per	O
Pound	O
,	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
worth	O
20	O
or	O
21	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
sometimes	O
take	O
Cochineal	O
that	O
was	O
ready	O
gaubled	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
other	O
Times	O
that	O
which	O
was	O
not	O
gaubled	O
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
then	O
used	O
to	O
gauble	O
it	O
herself	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
that	O
at	O
divers	O
Times	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
carry	O
away	O
above	O
200	O
Pounds	O
Weight	O
of	O
Cochineal	O
,	O
and	O
above	O
150	O
Pounds	O
Weight	O
of	O
Indigo	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
this	O
Deponent	O
did	O
not	O
approve	O
of	O
their	O
Proceedings	O
,	O
but	O
Godfrey	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
no	O
Business	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
him	O
turned	O
away	O
if	O
he	O
mentioned	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
further	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
at	O
length	O
he	O
being	O
turned	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Place	O
,	O
some	O
Time	O
after	O
he	O
drew	O
up	O
a	O
Petition	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Eyles	I-pers
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
presented	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
hinder	O
'd	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
,	O
who	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
present	O
the	O
Petition	O
,	O
but	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
turn	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lamberton	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
and	O
sold	O
several	O
Parcels	O
of	O
Cochineal	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
apprehended	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
the	O
Cochineal	O
himself	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
his	O
Wife	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
Philip	O
Godfrey	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
as	O
Philip	B-pers
Godfrey	I-pers
had	O
done	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
saying	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
false	O
and	O
malicious	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
hop	O
'd	O
the	O
Court	O
would	O
consider	O
the	O
ill	O
Character	O
of	O
the	O
People	O
who	O
swore	O
against	O
him	O
:	O
He	O
then	O
likewise	O
call	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Basingdine	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
adding	O
,	O
that	O
Alesworth	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
one	O
,	O
insomuch	O
,	O
that	O
in	O
their	O
Opinion	O
,	O
his	O
Oath	O
was	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
minded	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
considering	O
each	O
Circumstance	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
Alesworth	O
and	O
Elizabeth	O
Lamberton	O
,	O
they	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Books	O
,	O
value	O
12s	O
.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bradly	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
keeping	O
a	O
Place	O
to	O
sell	O
Books	O
in	O
Bow-lane	B-place
,	I-place
Cheapside	I-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Books	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
from	O
off	O
his	O
Stall	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
taken	O
,	O
he	O
himself	O
found	O
the	O
Books	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
plain	O
Evidence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Fuller	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
June	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Mathews	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
about	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
a-Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
passing	O
under	O
Ludgate	B-place
,	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
hastily	O
cross	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
he	O
pursu	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
chang	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
before	O
he	O
could	O
well	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
dropp	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Deponent	O
said	O
immediately	O
before	O
he	O
dropp	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
just	O
discover	O
a	O
Sight	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Bosom	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
a	O
Coach	O
coming	O
along	O
,	O
he	O
run	O
to	O
avoid	O
Mischief	O
,	O
fearing	O
to	O
be	O
run	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
crossing	O
the	O
Way	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
frivolous	O
Excuse	O
gaining	O
but	O
little	O
Credit	O
with	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Christopher	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Broad-street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Airis	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
walking	O
along	O
Cheapside	B-place
with	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Webb	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
,	O
he	O
thought	O
,	O
look	O
'd	O
like	O
a	O
Pick-pocket	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
bid	O
his	O
Master	O
take	O
Care	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
that	O
presently	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
close	O
up	O
to	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Webb	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Deponent	O
pursuing	O
him	O
he	O
ran	O
down	O
a	O
Turning	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
Baker	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
following	O
,	O
saw	O
him	O
fling	O
four	O
Handkerchiefs	O
into	O
the	O
Bin	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
searching	O
him	O
strictly	O
,	O
found	O
Mr.	O
Webb	O
's	O
Handkerchief	O
crowded	O
into	O
his	O
Breeches	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
cross	O
Stocks-Market	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
all	O
Bundled	O
up	O
together	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Excuse	O
of	O
a	O
Pickpocket	O
having	O
but	O
very	O
little	O
Weight	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Coe	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Day-time	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
thence	O
two	O
Gowns	O
,	O
two	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
two	O
Penknives	O
,	O
a	O
Box-Iron	O
and	O
Heaters	O
,	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Head-Cloaths	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
a	O
Fire-Shovel	O
,	O
Poker	O
,	O
Tongs	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	O
Coe	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Coe	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
being	O
a	O
poor	O
Washerwoman	O
went	O
out	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
they	O
were	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
to	O
do	O
half	O
a	O
Day	O
's	O
Work	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
home	O
at	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Chamber-Door	O
broke	O
all	O
to	O
Pieces	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
their	O
Goods	O
gone	O
that	O
could	O
conveniently	O
be	O
carried	O
away	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
complaining	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
of	O
her	O
Misfortune	O
,	O
she	O
learn	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
a	O
Woman	O
had	O
been	O
seen	O
to	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
House	O
with	O
two	O
Bundles	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Frying-Pan	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
with	O
other	O
Neighbours	O
to	O
Rag-Fair	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
no	O
sooner	O
got	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
heard	O
a	O
Woman	O
crying	O
,	O
Who	O
will	O
buy	O
a	O
Frying-Pan	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Tongs	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
Poker	O
;	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
,	O
found	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
those	O
stolen	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
House	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
seiz	O
'd	O
the	O
Woman	O
in	O
whose	O
Custody	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
brought	O
out	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
of	O
whom	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Gown	O
in	O
her	O
Lap	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
House	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hews	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
loaded	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Gown	O
in	O
her	O
Lap	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
bought	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Coe	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
for	O
4s	O
.	O
that	O
Day	O
,	O
about	O
12	O
a-Clock	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
,	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Coe	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
home	O
till	O
Two	O
or	O
Three	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
nothing	O
could	O
be	O
more	O
ridiculous	O
,	O
than	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
should	O
take	O
up	O
a	O
Woman	O
for	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
which	O
she	O
herself	O
had	O
sold	O
,	O
besides	O
her	O
saying	O
she	O
bought	O
the	O
Goods	O
for	O
four	O
Shillings	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
worth	O
above	O
forty	O
,	O
did	O
but	O
confirm	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
her	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
not	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4s	O
.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Josiah	B-pers
Amos	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Petty	O
Larceny	O
,	O
in	O
stealing	O
four	O
Pounds	O
Weight	O
of	O
Brass	O
Nails	O
,	O
and	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
to	O
his	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
(	O
upon	O
an	O
Act	O
made	O
in	O
the	O
9th	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
late	O
Majesty	O
,	O
called	O
the	O
Black	O
Act	O
)	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
another	O
Person	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
Bob	O
the	O
Drover	O
,	O
did	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
last	O
,	O
kill	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
two	O
Fallow	O
Deer	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
our	O
Sovereign	O
Lord	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Place	O
enclosed	O
with	O
Hedges	O
,	O
&	O
C.	O
call	O
'd	O
,	O
Enfield	B-place
Chase	I-place
.	O
George	B-pers
Ebbs	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
looking	O
for	O
a	O
Horse	O
in	O
Enfield	O
Chase	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
last	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Bob	O
the	O
Drover	O
,	O
with	O
Fire-Arms	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Chase	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
standing	O
at	O
some	O
Distance	O
,	O
saw	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
shoot	O
a	O
Deer	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Place	O
call	O
'd	O
,	O
Roe-Bottoms	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
Dispute	O
arising	O
,	O
whether	O
or	O
no	O
Enfield	O
Chase	O
was	O
enclos	O
'd	O
all	O
round	O
with	O
Hedges	O
,	O
&	O
C.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
at	O
Kicks-End	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
High	O
Road	O
is	O
open	O
into	O
Enfield	O
Chase	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
this	O
Flaw	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bradley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
three	O
Sacks	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Ravish	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	B-pers
Haddington	I-pers
,	O
and	O
other	O
Persons	O
;	O
but	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Sheet	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Vest	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
Pillowber	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Randal	I-pers
;	O
but	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Hollingshead	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Aprons	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Nose	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hiltrop	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
by	O
her	O
to	O
Iron	O
and	O
get	O
up	O
Linnen	O
of	O
other	O
People	O
's	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
she	O
was	O
intrusted	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
weaker	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
4	O
Aprons	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
but	O
she	O
being	O
great	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
Compassion	O
to	O
a	O
Woman	O
in	O
that	O
Condition	O
,	O
they	O
begg	O
'd	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
might	O
not	O
be	O
transported	O
to	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Plantations	O
,	O
but	O
receive	O
such	O
Corporal	O
Punishment	O
as	O
the	O
Court	O
should	O
think	O
convenient	O
to	O
inflict	O
on	O
her	O
.	O
Frances	B-pers
Halfhide	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Pepper-Box	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Handle	O
of	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Handle	O
of	O
a	O
Fork	O
,	O
6	O
Yards	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Goods	O
and	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wait	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Joseph	O
Barnard	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
Mr.	O
Joseph	O
Barnard	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
taken	O
away	O
several	O
Things	O
(	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
House	O
)	O
belonging	O
to	O
himself	O
,	O
his	O
Brother	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
they	O
had	O
Suspicion	O
on	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
charging	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Theft	O
,	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
and	O
sign	O
'd	O
the	O
Confession	O
with	O
her	O
own	O
Hand	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
freely	O
and	O
voluntarily	O
,	O
without	O
being	O
either	O
intimidated	O
by	O
Menaces	O
,	O
or	O
prevail	O
'd	O
with	O
by	O
Promises	O
;	O
in	O
which	O
Confession	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
several	O
Persons	O
above	O
mentioned	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Joseph	O
Barnard	O
,	O
and	O
pawned	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Rogers	O
in	O
Short's-Gardens	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
to	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Carter	O
,	O
who	O
both	O
appearing	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
Goods	O
to	O
them	O
which	O
were	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
;	O
however	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
several	O
to	O
appear	O
for	O
her	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
even	O
Mr.	O
Barnard	O
himself	O
(	O
tho	O
'	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
)	O
generously	O
acknowledging	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
heard	O
her	O
Reputation	O
was	O
blasted	O
before	O
this	O
Time	O
,	O
but	O
on	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
in	O
general	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
guilty	O
only	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Boystone	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Linnen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Newstop	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
's	I-place
Hanover-Square	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Pot	O
,	O
a	O
Barber	O
's	O
Bason	O
,	O
2	O
Napkins	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Shaving-Cloth	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
24	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Yarro	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
And	O
John	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Yarro	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
her	O
Servant	O
,	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
to	O
this	O
Deponent	O
's	O
Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
stopping	O
there	O
,	O
this	O
Deponent	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
see	O
why	O
she	O
stopp	O
'd	O
at	O
her	O
Chamber	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
into	O
the	O
Garret	O
;	O
yet	O
tho	O
she	O
thought	O
this	O
a	O
little	O
odd	O
,	O
and	O
forasmuch	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
given	O
her	O
any	O
Orders	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
her	O
Chamber	O
,	O
yet	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
mistrust	O
in	O
the	O
least	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
away	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
yet	O
by	O
what	O
she	O
heard	O
afterwards	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
Opinion	O
that	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
;	O
for	O
soon	O
after	O
missing	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
expressing	O
her	O
Dissatisfaction	O
at	O
the	O
Loss	O
,	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
informed	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
some	O
Familiarities	O
had	O
pass	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
Sight	O
between	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Sarah	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
John	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
;	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
sifted	O
narrowly	O
into	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
but	O
too	O
much	O
Reason	O
to	O
believe	O
it	O
true	O
,	O
they	O
carried	O
her	O
before	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
who	O
,	O
after	O
examining	O
her	O
,	O
committed	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Round-House	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Morning	O
after	O
her	O
Commitment	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
it	O
to	O
John	O
Jackson	O
,	O
which	O
concurring	O
with	O
what	O
she	O
was	O
told	O
of	O
by	O
her	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
they	O
likewise	O
thought	O
fit	O
to	O
prosecute	O
him	O
for	O
being	O
Accessory	O
to	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
looking	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Window	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Sarah	O
Jones	O
,	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Master	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
some	O
Distance	O
stood	O
John	O
Jackson	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
some	O
Confabulation	O
she	O
gave	O
him	O
something	O
into	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
he	O
seem	O
'd	O
pleas	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
chuck	O
'd	O
her	O
under	O
the	O
Chin	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
perceive	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
she	O
gave	O
him	O
,	O
yet	O
he	O
believing	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
Intrigue	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
went	O
and	O
informed	O
her	O
Master	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
further	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
Sarah	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
was	O
committed	O
to	O
the	O
Round-House	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
her	O
confess	O
her	O
taking	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
John	O
Jackson	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
this	O
Deponent	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
them	O
together	O
from	O
his	O
Window	O
.	O
Sarah	O
Jones	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
true	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Master	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
John	O
Jackson	O
.	O
John	O
Jackson	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
and	O
Sarah	O
Jones	O
having	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
a	O
Respect	O
for	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Design	O
to	O
marry	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Ring	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
said	O
he	O
saw	O
her	O
give	O
something	O
into	O
his	O
Hands	O
.	O
Several	O
Gentlemen	O
appear	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
John	O
Jackson	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
honest	O
industrious	O
Person	O
,	O
that	O
maintained	O
himself	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Credit	O
and	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
depos	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
Behalf	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Yarro	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
said	O
in	O
their	O
Hearing	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
would	O
hang	O
him	O
right	O
or	O
wrong	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
;	O
this	O
being	O
considered	O
with	O
the	O
good	O
Character	O
he	O
bore	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
(	O
for	O
what	O
Sarah	O
Jones	O
said	O
was	O
not	O
Evidence	O
)	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
though	O
the	O
Information	O
Sarah	O
Jones	O
gave	O
against	O
Jackson	O
,	O
was	O
of	O
no	O
Effect	O
,	O
yet	O
in	O
Consequence	O
of	O
her	O
own	O
Confession	O
at	O
the	O
Round-House	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hoar	I-pers
and	O
Katharine	B-pers
Hoar	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Peck	O
of	O
Wheat	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Vincint	I-pers
Clark	I-pers
;	O
which	O
appearing	O
very	O
plain	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
9	O
Guineas	O
,	O
2	O
Half	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Moidores	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Scandred	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Country	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
knowing	O
the	O
Ways	O
of	O
the	O
Town	O
,	O
was	O
pick	O
'd	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
Gin	O
Shop	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
spent	O
3	O
d.	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
afterwards	O
went	O
to	O
another	O
House	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
spent	O
something	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
then	O
parted	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
soon	O
after	O
which	O
he	O
felt	O
for	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
gone	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
another	O
Woman	O
,	O
one	O
Hannah	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
,	O
being	O
still	O
in	O
his	O
Company	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
put	O
in	O
a	O
Way	O
how	O
to	O
find	O
her	O
out	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
next	O
Morning	O
.	O
Hannah	O
Powel	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
Money	O
,	O
not	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
to	O
lose	O
,	O
tho'he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
14	O
Guineas	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
that	O
Morning	O
taken	O
for	O
some	O
Pigs	O
which	O
he	O
brought	O
out	O
of	O
Hareford	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
fix	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
sighing	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
He	O
had	O
brought	O
his	O
Hogs	O
to	O
a	O
fine	O
Market	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Tomlinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Aldersgate-street	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
eight	O
Guineas	O
,	O
a	O
Broad	O
Piece	O
,	O
and	O
15	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bartlet	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Heytof	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Third	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bartlet	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Country	O
Carrier	O
,	O
took	O
Lodgings	O
whilst	O
he	O
staid	O
in	O
Town	O
at	O
an	O
Inn	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Tapster	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
at	O
Night	O
whilst	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
his	O
Money	O
was	O
stole	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
put	O
safe	O
under	O
his	O
Head	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
Suspicion	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
confessed	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Breeches	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Belderstone	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Bannister	I-pers
both	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
'd	O
in	O
their	O
Hearing	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Breeches	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
persuaded	O
to	O
confess	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
they	O
pretending	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
the	O
better	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Field	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Ludgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Mary	B-pers
Faulkoner	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Silver	O
Snuff-Box	O
.	O
Value	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
appearing	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
in	O
defrauding	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Kinder	I-pers
,	O
of	O
seven	O
Shillings	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Kinder	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
Shop	O
(	O
a	O
Baker	O
's	O
)	O
in	O
Cloth-Fair	B-place
,	O
and	O
pretended	O
they	O
wanted	O
a	O
Quartern	O
Brick	O
she	O
telling	O
them	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
Bricks	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
a	O
Loaf	O
,	O
and	O
George	O
Smith	O
flinging	O
down	O
a	O
Guinca	O
,	O
bid	O
her	O
give	O
him	O
Change	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
William	O
Gardner	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
might	O
take	O
her	O
Change	O
again	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Shilling	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
Smith	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
the	O
Change	O
,	O
finding	O
their	O
wanted	O
7	O
Shillings	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
them	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
denied	O
knowing	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
continuing	O
to	O
demand	O
her	O
Money	O
,	O
they	O
both	O
run	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Clifton	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
her	O
charge	O
them	O
with	O
cheating	O
her	O
of	O
7	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
run	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
he	O
ran	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
gone	O
back	O
,	O
but	O
Smith	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
Blood	O
Ill	O
not	O
go	O
back	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Ridgley	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
hearing	O
an	O
Out-cry	O
of	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
running	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
,	O
stopped	O
Gardner	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
the	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
never	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Fray	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
this	O
Deponent	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
Half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
above	O
making	O
an	O
Advantage	O
of	O
letting	O
a	O
Villain	O
escape	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
held	O
him	O
till	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
secured	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
charg	O
'd	O
an	O
Officer	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
They	O
pretended	O
that	O
they	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
their	O
Character	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
plain	O
against	O
them	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Chickwell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
's	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Guineas	O
,	O
2	O
Half	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Silver	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bocket	I-pers
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
Bocket	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
(	O
tho	O
'	O
but	O
a	O
meer	O
Child	O
)	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Evening	O
when	O
this	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
gone	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
missing	O
the	O
Money	O
thought	O
fit	O
to	O
detain	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
charg	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
trifled	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
several	O
Stories	O
which	O
were	O
Contradictions	O
,	O
till	O
they	O
tired	O
with	O
her	O
Evasions	O
,	O
went	O
for	O
an	O
Officer	O
,	O
and	O
charging	O
him	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
carried	O
her	O
before	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
sign	O
'd	O
the	O
Confession	O
with	O
her	O
own	O
Hand	O
,	O
but	O
neither	O
the	O
Justice	O
who	O
committed	O
her	O
,	O
nor	O
his	O
Clerk	O
,	O
attending	O
in	O
Court	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Confession	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
Connell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
20	O
Guineas	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bushell	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hazard	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
She	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
20	O
Guineas	O
at	O
several	O
Times	O
,	O
and	O
suspecting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
put	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
half	O
by	O
itself	O
in	O
her	O
Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
the	O
Time	O
that	O
she	O
put	O
there	O
to	O
the	O
Time	O
of	O
its	O
being	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
Family	O
above	O
Stairs	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Orpheus	B-pers
Shoemart	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
employed	O
him	O
to	O
Watch	O
in	O
her	O
Bed-Chamber	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
she	O
could	O
catch	O
the	O
Thief	O
who	O
stole	O
her	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
waited	O
several	O
Days	O
successively	O
,	O
at	O
length	O
he	O
heard	O
some	O
Body	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
being	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
between	O
sleeping	O
and	O
awaking	O
,	O
was	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
and	O
tumbled	O
off	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
see	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Purdue	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
Orpheus	O
Shoemart	O
fell	O
off	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
he	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
this	O
Deponent	O
,	O
being	O
below	O
Stairs	O
,	O
ran	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
the	O
Stairs	O
coming	O
down	O
in	O
haste	O
;	O
but	O
these	O
Circumstances	O
not	O
being	O
strong	O
enough	O
to	O
convict	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Bridget	B-pers
Willedon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Dowley	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
sent	O
her	O
Stays	O
to	O
her	O
Father	O
's	O
to	O
be	O
lined	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
stole	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
afterwards	O
she	O
found	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
,	O
hung	O
up	O
for	O
Sale	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
one	O
who	O
see	O
her	O
buy	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
who	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
hang	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
publick	O
Shop	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Sadler	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
4	O
Guineas	O
,	O
a	O
Moidore	O
,	O
some	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Buckle	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Marshal	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
(	O
otherways	O
call	O
'd	O
New-Prison	B-place
)	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
appearing	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Walton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
tame	O
Fallow	O
Deer	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Richard	B-pers
Buckley	I-pers
and	O
Mr.	O
Edward	B-pers
Buckley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
Cripplegate	O
.	O
Mr.	O
North	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
3	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
carrying	O
a	O
Basket	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
something	O
covered	O
with	O
a	O
Cloth	O
all	O
Bloody	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
watched	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
they	O
had	O
done	O
something	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
honest	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
hearing	O
afterwards	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Buckley	O
had	O
advertised	O
a	O
Deer	O
in	O
the	O
News	O
Papers	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
informed	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Buckley	O
of	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
further	O
Enquiry	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
found	O
out	O
and	O
apprehended	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Hopping	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
drinking	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
Noble-street	O
early	O
the	O
Morning	O
on	O
which	O
the	O
Deer	O
was	O
stole	O
,	O
Walton	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
kill	O
a	O
Deer	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Buckley	O
's	O
,	O
that	O
Parker	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
they	O
returned	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
this	O
Deponent	O
,	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
fetched	O
the	O
Deer	O
out	O
of	O
Parker	O
's	O
Shed	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
Mother	O
's	O
Shed	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
Parker	O
cut	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
they	O
sold	O
it	O
in	O
Quarters	O
.	O
Other	O
Witnesses	O
corroborating	O
what	O
this	O
Deponent	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Osbourn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
24	O
Ewe	O
Sheep	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
weak	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hews	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
l	O
and	O
four	O
Silver	O
Watches	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
l.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Morran	I-pers
,	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
plain	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Stiles	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Newington	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
Katharine	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
;	O
but	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Vaughn	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Quilt	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Crawford	I-pers
;	O
which	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Simon	B-pers
Ryan	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Lovey	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Saucepan	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Pinfold	I-pers
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
appearing	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Butterfield	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Alice	B-pers
Wilkins	I-pers
;	O
but	O
she	O
not	O
appearing	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Perton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
stealing	O
a	O
Horse	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Tyler	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Scawell	I-pers
,	O
but	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Garell	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Plumpton	I-pers
;	O
which	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
One	O
Francis	B-pers
Clifton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
attend	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
in	O
Contempt	O
of	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Court	O
,	O
had	O
published	O
two	O
Pamphlets	O
,	O
one	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Proceedings	O
at	O
the	O
Sessions	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
the	O
pretended	O
Dying	O
Speech	O
of	O
the	O
Convicts	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
last	O
executed	O
,	O
was	O
repremanded	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
his	O
Submission	O
,	O
begging	O
Pardon	O
,	O
and	O
promising	O
never	O
to	O
do	O
the	O
like	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
ended	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
follows	O
:	O
Received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
8.	O
Richard	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Conolly	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Hews	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jinkins	I-pers
,	O
Bryan	B-pers
Macguire	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Benson	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
2.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Covey	I-pers
.	O
Transportation	O
23.	O
Jane	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	O
Street	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mackool	I-pers
,	O
Alexander	B-pers
Harper	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Puller	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Josiah	B-pers
Amos	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Halshide	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Boystone	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hoar	I-pers
,	O
Katherine	B-pers
Hoar	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Tomlinson	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Walton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Stiles	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Vaughn	I-pers
,	O
Simon	B-pers
Rayn	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Garrell	I-pers
.	O
George	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
,	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
cheating	O
a	O
Woman	O
out	O
of	O
seven	O
Shillings	O
in	O
changing	O
a	O
Guinea	O
were	O
fin	O
'd	O
5	O
Marks	O
each	O
,	O
to	O
remain	O
in	O
Prison	O
till	O
its	O
paid	O
.	O
ADVERTISEMENT	O
.	O
A	O
Water	O
that	O
perfectly	O
cures	O
the	O
ITCH	O
,	O
or	O
Itching	O
Humour	O
in	O
any	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
short	O
Time	O
,	O
having	O
no	O
offensive	O
Scent	O
:	O
Prepared	O
and	O
Sold	O
only	O
by	O
A	O
.	O
Downing	O
,	O
Chymist	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
and	O
Ball	O
in	O
George-Court	O
in	O
St.	O
John's-Lane	O
near	O
Hick's-Hall	O
.	O
Price	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Bottle	O
.	O
Also	O
the	O
true	O
Essence	O
or	O
Spirits	O
of	O
Scurvy-Grass	O
,	O
both	O
Purging	O
and	O
Plain	O
,	O
most	O
Excellent	O
for	O
all	O
Degrees	O
of	O
the	O
Scurvy	O
,	O
at	O
8	O
d.	O
a	O
Bottle	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
great	O
Elixir	O
of	O
Life	O
,	O
called	O
Daffy	O
's	O
Elixir	O
,	O
truly	O
prepared	O
,	O
so	O
very	O
useful	O
in	O
all	O
Families	O
in	O
the	O
greatest	O
Exigencies	O
.	O
Price	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Half-Pint	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
E.	O
Symon	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
;	O
and	O
Sold	O
by	O
J.	O
Roberts	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Oxford-Arms	O
in	O
Warwick-Lane	O
.	O
