TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
FOR	O
THE	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
:	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
15th	O
,	O
16th	O
,	O
17th	O
,	O
18th	O
and	O
20th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
1729	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Third	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
ROBERT	B-pers
BAYLIS	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Rt	O
.	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
Raymond	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Baron	B-pers
Hales	I-pers
;	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Denton	O
;	O
the	O
Worshipful	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
Raby	O
,	O
Deputy-Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Blunt	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Storer	I-pers
.	O
Manly	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
.	O
Nathan	B-pers
Dell	I-pers
.	O
James	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ingram	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Tame	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Richmond	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Thrift	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Aliff	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Henshaw	I-pers
.	O
David	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Spicer	I-pers
.	O
George	B-pers
Gerrard	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
.	O
Ursula	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bow	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Grace	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Hellen	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Perriwigs	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Burdet	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Rolph	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
25	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Sugar	O
lay	O
at	O
Dice-Key	B-place
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
apprehended	O
taking	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Hogshead	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Deborah	B-pers
Chubbs	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
6	O
Shirts	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Whaley	I-pers
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
having	O
been	O
washing	O
,	O
had	O
left	O
the	O
Linnen	O
in	O
the	O
Tub	O
while	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
Dinner	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
while	O
the	O
Linnen	O
was	O
stolen	O
,	O
and	O
Part	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Hare	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Box-Iron	O
,	O
two	O
Sheets	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
Lodgers	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
,	O
each	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Kilburn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
come	O
into	O
her	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
immediately	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
and	O
seizing	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
down	O
the	O
Handkerchiefs	O
into	O
a	O
Chair	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
gotten	O
them	O
under	O
a	O
Rug	O
Coat	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ranger	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Linnen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	B-place
Precinct	I-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Katherine	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
5	O
Half-Peck	O
Loaves	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Peck	O
of	O
Flour	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Journeyman	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
Baker	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
carry	O
out	O
the	O
Loaves	O
privately	O
,	O
unknown	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
;	O
which	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Egglin	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Eliz	B-pers
Dark	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Edmund	B-pers
Frier	I-pers
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
against	O
John	B-pers
Egglin	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Dark	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
4	O
Linnen	O
Shifts	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Norcliff	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Bed-Curtains	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Mattox	I-pers
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
took	O
a	O
Lodging	O
ready	O
furnish	O
'd	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
by	O
Elizabeth	O
Sheppard	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
privy	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Shurt	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
7	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Katherine	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bye	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Grace	B-pers
Bezament	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Price	I-pers
;	O
but	O
no-body	O
appearing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Betts	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Henderson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Geese	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Milbourn	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
:	O
But	O
no-body	O
appearing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Unthank	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Parnel	I-pers
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Alphage	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Whitford	I-pers
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
to	O
sell	O
Oysters	O
,	O
took	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Spoons	O
;	O
the	O
Spoons	O
were	O
found	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ruth	B-pers
Herenhausen	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Precinct	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Katherine	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Batty	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
8	O
Shirts	O
,	O
8	O
Shifts	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Linnen	O
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Batty	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
having	O
been	O
washing	O
,	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
were	O
folded	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
lying	O
on	O
a	O
Dresser	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
over	O
Night	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
she	O
was	O
inform	O
'd	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Linnen	O
gone	O
;	O
she	O
found	O
a	O
Ladder	O
at	O
the	O
outside	O
of	O
the	O
Pales	O
;	O
a	O
Square	O
of	O
Glass	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Linnen	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
suppos	O
'd	O
,	O
taken	O
out	O
at	O
that	O
Opening	O
;	O
that	O
hearing	O
a	O
Bell-man	O
crying	O
a	O
Pot	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
hers	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
appehended	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
an	O
Apron	O
of	O
hers	O
before	O
her	O
;	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
of	O
her	O
Maid	O
's	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
Maid	O
's	O
Shifts	O
on	O
her	O
Back	O
.	O
Her	O
Evidence	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
her	O
Maid	O
,	O
Martha	B-pers
Alcock	I-pers
.	O
Humphry	B-pers
Christopher	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
going	O
to	O
his	O
Business	O
about	O
five	O
a-Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
he	O
stumbled	O
over	O
a	O
Bundle	O
of	O
Linnen	O
,	O
a	O
Porridge-Pot	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
an	O
Alley	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
Alley	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
there	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
laid	O
up	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
7	O
a-Clock	O
that	O
Morning	O
got	O
them	O
cry	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
her	O
having	O
the	O
Apron	O
,	O
Shift	O
,	O
and	O
Handkerchief	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
but	O
pleaded	O
she	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
ill	O
Fame	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Dyer	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Abraham	B-pers
Dumbleton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Topping	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
20	O
Yards	O
of	O
printed	O
Linnen	O
,	O
also	O
Russia	O
Linnen	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
Value	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Shop	O
was	O
broken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goodstolen	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
Part	O
of	O
them	O
at	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Hodgkins	O
's	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hodgkins	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Margaret	B-pers
Dyer	I-pers
Wife	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Dyer	I-pers
,	O
brought	O
two	O
Gowns	O
made	O
of	O
the	O
printed	O
Linnen	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
own	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Linnen	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
Sheets	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
likewise	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Dumbleton	O
's	O
Wife	O
was	O
with	O
Margaret	B-pers
Dyer	I-pers
when	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
That	O
himself	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
did	O
break	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
between	O
2	O
and	O
3	O
a-Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
Day	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
cut	O
a	O
Hole	O
in	O
the	O
Shutter	O
,	O
put	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
Pane	O
,	O
opened	O
the	O
Shutter	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
handed	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
to	O
Dyer	O
and	O
Dumbleton	O
,	O
who	O
stood	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
carried	O
the	O
goods	O
to	O
a	O
Turning	O
where	O
were	O
some	O
Logs	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
emptied	O
the	O
Bag	O
and	O
went	O
again	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
more	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
carried	O
the	O
Goods	O
into	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
leaving	O
Dyer	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
what	O
they	O
had	O
left	O
;	O
he	O
and	O
Dumbleton	O
carried	O
each	O
a	O
Bundle	O
to	O
Dyer	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Wives	O
had	O
each	O
a	O
Gown	O
made	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Linnen	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
the	O
Linnen	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
Sheets	O
made	O
of	O
Russia	O
Linnen	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
Dyer	O
pleaded	O
that	O
Henry	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
had	O
sworn	O
against	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
Malice	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
being	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
a	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
got	O
out	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
prejudicial	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Cole	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
cohabit	O
with	O
Dyer	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
but	O
swore	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
did	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
Newgate	O
they	O
were	O
very	O
familiar	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
commit	O
several	O
Robberies	O
together	O
besides	O
this	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
planily	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dyer	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Abraham	B-pers
Dumbleton	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Henry	B-pers
Bradley	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Cane	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Day	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
at	O
about	O
12	O
a-Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
Home	O
,	O
in	O
Great	B-place
Kirby-Street	I-place
,	O
near	O
Hatton-Garden	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
attack	O
'd	O
by	O
three	O
Persons	O
,	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
Cane	O
;	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
thinks	O
he	O
may	O
be	O
positive	O
of	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Dyer	O
,	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Good	O
Morrow	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
catching	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
short	O
Truncheon	O
struck	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
he	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
,	O
they	O
all	O
laying	O
on	O
him	O
with	O
Blows	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
they	O
could	O
strike	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
miserably	O
bruised	O
,	O
cut	O
to	O
the	O
Scull	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Fingers	O
bruised	O
to	O
Pieces	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
intirely	O
lost	O
the	O
Use	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
on	O
this	O
,	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
which	O
raised	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
two	O
Gold	O
small	O
Picture-Frames	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
lost	O
,	O
but	O
were	O
afterwards	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
himself	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
went	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
from	O
Dyer	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
Cow-Lane	O
,	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
of	O
Geneva	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
full	O
Resolution	O
to	O
rob	O
,	O
they	O
having	O
no	O
Money	O
;	O
that	O
going	O
to	O
Hatton-Garden	O
,	O
they	O
saw	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Person	O
that	O
had	O
Money	O
,	O
they	O
cross	O
'd	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
Dyer	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
bid	O
him	O
Good	O
Morrow	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
Dumbleton	O
and	O
himself	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
of	O
them	O
did	O
lay	O
on	O
him	O
with	O
their	O
Sticks	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
upon	O
Mr.	O
Bradley	O
's	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
People	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
were	O
alarm	O
'd	O
;	O
that	O
this	O
oblig	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
make	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
People	O
looking	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
Windows	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
his	O
Stick	O
up	O
at	O
the	O
Windows	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
did	O
fire	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
threw	O
the	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
into	O
an	O
Area	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
,	O
cut	O
the	O
Cane	O
and	O
Wig	O
to	O
Pieces	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
the	O
Hat	O
in	O
Long-Lane	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
reason	O
they	O
cut	O
the	O
Wig	O
to	O
Pieces	O
was	O
because	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
very	O
good	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
find	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
Drugs	O
,	O
and	O
yield	O
but	O
little	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
this	O
Witness	O
being	O
coherent	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
also	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Paddington	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Weather	O
Sheep	O
,	O
value	O
39	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Sheep	O
were	O
Scotch	O
Sheep	O
,	O
a	O
Sort	O
that	O
scarce	O
any-body	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
had	O
but	O
himself	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Sheep	O
were	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
Enquiry	O
hearing	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
Roundhouse	O
upon	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
stealing	O
Sheep	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
inform	O
'd	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
kill	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
alive	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Sheep	O
;	O
but	O
could	O
produce	O
no	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
whereupon	O
,	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Savoury	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Pattens	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
divers	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jasper	B-pers
Horn	I-pers
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wallixelson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
All-Saints	B-place
,	I-place
London-Wall	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
23	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hammers	I-pers
.	O
-	O
Vivian	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
at	O
the	O
farther-end	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Loaf	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
apprehended	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
the	O
Sugar	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
taking	O
and	O
dropping	O
the	O
Sugar	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
another	O
Evidence	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Everet	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
;	O
but	O
no-body	O
appearing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bartholomew	I-place
the	I-place
Less	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Clogs	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dionysius	I-place
Back-Church	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
some	O
Bees-Wax	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Haws	I-pers
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Miles	B-pers
Conner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchre	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
no-body	O
appearing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bruckin	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Goetree	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminister	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pistol	O
and	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Berresford	I-pers
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
,	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shift	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Petty	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Shift	O
hung	O
on	O
a	O
Line	O
to	O
dry	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
seen	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
was	O
pursued	O
and	O
taken	O
with	O
it	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Godfrey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Linnen	O
Cloth	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Mackmurdy	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
taken	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
gone	O
away	O
,	O
was	O
pursued	O
and	O
taken	O
,	O
having	O
first	O
thrown	O
down	O
the	O
Cloth	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Tennard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Islington	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brown	O
Mare	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
lent	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
Mare	O
,	O
to	O
ride	O
3	O
Miles	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
rode	O
her	O
up	O
to	O
London	O
and	O
sold	O
her	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Thistlewood	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Mare	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
4	O
Guineas	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
John	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Jane	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
a	O
Brandy-Shop	O
,	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
in	O
his	O
Arms	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
her	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
Canal	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
lost	O
her	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
seperal	O
Evidences	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
throw	O
her	O
down	O
;	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
by	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Rayner	I-pers
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
present	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Siggins	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Perkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Christ-Church	B-place
in	I-place
Spittle-Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hartley	I-pers
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
him	O
5	O
Days	O
,	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
having	O
stolen	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Carpenter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
taking	O
a	O
Shirt	O
and	O
some	O
Money	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Drury-Lane	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
King's-Court	B-place
in	I-place
Russel-Street	I-place
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
him	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
willing	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
,	O
she	O
pull	O
'd	O
him	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
shut	O
the	O
Door	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
feeling	O
her	O
fumbling	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Shirt	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
she	O
ran	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
he	O
follow	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
a	O
Soldier	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
who	O
hector	O
'd	O
him	O
and	O
threatened	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
be	O
gone	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Dawes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Blunket	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Coats	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Burglary	O
not	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
that	O
;	O
but	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Downing	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Christ-Church	B-place
,	I-place
Spittle-Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
,	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Absalom	B-pers
Crouch	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Tappy	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
stealing	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
But	O
the	O
Burglary	O
not	O
being	O
sufficiently	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
of	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Reason	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Ephraim	B-pers
Goatley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Fustian	O
Frock	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Ivory	I-pers
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
sufficient	O
affect	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Amy	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Kippling	I-pers
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Alice	B-pers
Haley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Judith	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
several	O
Pieces	O
of	O
silk	O
Ribbon	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Colebach	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
Evidences	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Yard	O
of	O
Ribbon	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
being	O
suspected	O
of	O
having	O
taken	O
something	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
told	O
they	O
should	O
be	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
Judith	O
Smith	O
was	O
seen	O
privately	O
to	O
lay	O
down	O
one	O
Piece	O
,	O
and	O
Alice	O
Haley	O
had	O
four	O
conceal	O
'd	O
under	O
her	O
Riding-Hood	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Hargest	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bow	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Cartwright	I-pers
Web	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Hurst	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
in	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
Katherine	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Infant	O
of	O
5	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Woollen	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
seen	O
with	O
the	O
Child	O
at	O
the	O
Land	B-place
of	I-place
Promise	I-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
Hoxton	I-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
seen	O
to	O
come	O
back	O
without	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
have	O
some	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Child	O
crying	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
pursued	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
at	O
Norton	O
Falgate	O
,	O
having	O
the	O
Stays	O
in	O
her	O
Apron	O
,	O
but	O
having	O
sold	O
the	O
Petticoat	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Banks	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Dutler	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
10	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cherry	O
Derry	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Mackoon	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
her	O
Child	O
about	O
six	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Calamanca	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
being	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
miss	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
follow	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
under	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
Riding-Hood	O
;	O
it	O
did	O
appear	O
likewise	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
take	O
something	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
by	O
the	O
Direction	O
or	O
Privity	O
of	O
the	O
Mother	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Esther	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Snuff	O
Box	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
8	O
l.	O
Diamond	O
Ear-rings	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
l.	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Head-cloaths	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
four	O
Gowns	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
great	O
Value	O
,	O
49	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Money	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
138	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Thorold	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
pay	O
a	O
Visit	O
about	O
5	O
a-Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
the	O
Day	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
returning	O
Home	O
betwixt	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
Entrance	O
;	O
whereupon	O
her	O
Footman	O
went	O
round	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
in	O
the	O
Back	O
Way	O
,	O
finding	O
the	O
Doors	O
backward	O
all	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
opening	O
the	O
Fore-Door	O
,	O
let	O
her	O
in	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
Madam	O
you	O
are	O
robb	O
'd	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
going	O
into	O
her	O
Rooms	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
Cabinet	O
broken	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Drawers	O
and	O
Band-Boxes	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
all	O
thrown	O
about	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
her	O
Servant	O
.	O
Betty	B-pers
Loyd	I-pers
,	O
and	O
examining	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
pretended	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
bound	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Robbery	O
had	O
been	O
committed	O
by	O
two	O
Persons	O
,	O
who	O
she	O
did	O
believe	O
were	O
Men	O
in	O
Women	O
's	O
Cloaths	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Servants	O
did	O
not	O
own	O
for	O
a	O
considerable	O
time	O
who	O
committed	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Loyd	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
when	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
her	O
carry	O
out	O
a	O
Bundle	O
under	O
her	O
Riding-Hood	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
came	O
to	O
Madam	O
Thorold	O
's	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
Madam	O
Thorold	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
said	O
they	O
would	O
rob	O
Madam	O
Thorold	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
was	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
binding	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
Margaret	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
bound	O
her	O
,	O
Esther	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
holding	O
her	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
:	O
and	O
that	O
Margaret	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
said	O
she	O
would	O
rob	O
Madam	O
Thorold	O
for	O
Spite	O
and	O
Revenge	O
.	O
Lucy	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Maragaret	O
Lawrence	O
came	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
they	O
committed	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
to	O
Madam	O
Thorold	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
there	O
all	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
till	O
Madam	O
Thorold	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
;	O
that	O
about	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
gone	O
up	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
to	O
carry	O
some	O
Headcloaths	O
of	O
her	O
Mistress	O
's	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
Ironing	O
,	O
she	O
heard	O
Betty	B-pers
Loyd	I-pers
shriek	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
turning	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
to	O
come	O
down	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
met	O
her	O
upon	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
they	O
would	O
rob	O
Madam	O
Thorold	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
desired	O
them	O
not	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
do	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
forc	O
'd	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
Bound	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
shriek	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
If	O
she	O
made	O
any	O
Noise	O
she	O
would	O
kill	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
Betty	B-pers
Loyd	I-pers
was	O
then	O
below	O
stairs	O
in	O
the	O
Back	O
Kitchin	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
unbound	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
should	O
be	O
lock	O
'd	O
up	O
;	O
forc	O
'd	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
Garret	O
up	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
lock	O
'd	O
her	O
in	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
lock	O
'd	O
up	O
about	O
3	O
Hours	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Madam	O
Thorold	O
's	O
,	O
went	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
Esther	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
one	O
Forster	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
Shoemaker	O
in	O
Tash-Street	O
,	O
along	O
with	O
Madam	O
Thorold	O
's	O
Footman	O
;	O
but	O
was	O
told	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
demanded	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
her	O
Room	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
finding	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Goods	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
menacing	O
the	O
People	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
was	O
inform	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
carried	O
out	O
some	O
Goods	O
to	O
a	O
Trunkmaker	O
's	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
which	O
by	O
Enquiry	O
he	O
found	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
there	O
inform	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
bought	O
a	O
large	O
Trunk	O
and	O
having	O
put	O
divers	O
Goods	O
into	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
carried	O
away	O
by	O
a	O
Porter	O
;	O
that	O
thereupon	O
he	O
made	O
Enquiry	O
after	O
the	O
Porter	O
who	O
carried	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
found	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Bushy	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
Trunk	O
mark	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
first	O
Letters	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Name	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
;	O
that	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
Trunk	O
he	O
found	O
divers	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Goods	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
Snuff-Box	O
30	O
Guineas	O
&	O
c.	O
John	B-pers
Darnbrough	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Forster	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
there	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
to	O
carry	O
a	O
Box	O
and	O
a	O
Bundle	O
to	O
a	O
Trunkmaker	O
's	O
in	O
Holborn	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
agreed	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
3	O
d.	O
and	O
he	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Langston	O
's	O
a	O
Trunkmaker	O
's	O
;	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
what	O
Goods	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Box	O
and	O
Bundle	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
carried	O
the	O
Trunk	O
from	O
the	O
Trunkmaker	O
's	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Angel	O
over-gainst	O
Bloomsbury	O
,	O
in	O
Holborn	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
going	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bushy	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
several	O
Years	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
her	O
before	O
for	O
a	O
Year	O
or	O
two	O
;	O
but	O
accidentally	O
meeting	O
her	O
that	O
Day	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
Lodging	O
in	O
an	O
honest	O
House	O
,	O
whereupon	O
she	O
offer	O
'd	O
her	O
one	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
soon	O
after	O
sent	O
in	O
the	O
Trunk	O
before-mentioned	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
about	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
away	O
by	O
the	O
same	O
Porter	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
about	O
6	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
to	O
Madam	O
Thorold	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
afterwards	O
appear	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Christian	B-pers
Frederick	I-pers
Peterson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Cuff	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Proof	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Spoon	O
being	O
afterwards	O
found	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brady	I-pers
,	O
Anthony	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Egglin	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
le	I-place
Grand	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
3	O
first	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
7	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
;	O
and	O
Thomas	O
Jennings	O
for	O
receiving	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
against	O
the	O
3	O
first	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
,	O
each	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
against	O
the	O
latter	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Trevilian	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Burglary	O
not	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
of	O
small	O
Value	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gardener	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Rose	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bride	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
marrying	O
Thomas	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
,	O
her	O
former	O
Husband	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
being	O
still	O
alive	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
Evidence	O
of	O
the	O
Marriages	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Emmerson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Trinity	B-place
Minories	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Shoes	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Dallin	I-pers
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
insufficient	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Hatch	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Sonrwood	I-pers
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Proof	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Trevilian	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
the	I-place
Martyr	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
Cloak	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Camilla	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
;	O
but	O
no-body	O
appearing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Coven	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hand-Saw	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Pincers	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Darnel	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Proof	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
marrying	O
Mary	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
his	O
former	O
Wife	O
being	O
alive	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Proof	O
of	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
Marriages	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Egglin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
7	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lankey	I-pers
,	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Michael	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Hannah	B-pers
Farrington	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Gallons	O
of	O
strong	O
Beer	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ploughman	I-pers
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
a	O
Brewer	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Michael	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
having	O
a	O
Store-Cellar	O
near	O
Cripplegate	B-place
,	O
and	O
Hannah	B-pers
Farrington	I-pers
being	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
a	O
Customer	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
dwelt	O
hard-by	O
this	O
Store-Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
supplied	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servants	O
with	O
some	O
Necessaries	O
they	O
wanted	O
when	O
at	O
the	O
Store-Cellar	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Michael	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
or	O
some	O
other	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servants	O
,	O
had	O
at	O
Times	O
,	O
in	O
Return	O
,	O
given	O
her	O
three	O
Mugs	O
of	O
Beer	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Michael	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
having	O
given	O
an	O
Information	O
to	O
the	O
Commissioners	O
of	O
the	O
Excise	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
using	O
Molasses	O
in	O
his	O
brewing	O
Drink	O
,	O
did	O
set	O
on	O
foot	O
this	O
Prosecution	O
;	O
giving	O
the	O
Drink	O
not	O
appearing	O
in	O
the	O
Eye	O
of	O
the	O
Law	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
malicious	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
granted	O
them	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
their	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
Hanover-Square	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Macnorton	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Hambletou	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Seneff	I-pers
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
remov	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Dispute	O
about	O
some	O
Rent	O
in	O
Arrear	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Tea-Board	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
carried	O
away	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
which	O
both	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
Prisoner	O
laid	O
Claim	O
.	O
But	O
upon	O
a	O
full	O
Hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
appearing	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
to	O
be	O
malicious	O
,	O
they	O
granted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
her	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bennet	I-place
's	I-place
Fink	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Spoon	O
,	O
Muslin	O
Stock	O
,	O
and	O
Buckle	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
as	O
a	O
Scullian	O
Woman	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Spoon	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Which	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hanwell	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
four	O
Bushel	O
of	O
Beans	O
and	O
a	O
Sack	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Holworthy	I-pers
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Nibblet	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
three	O
pewter	O
Plates	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
;	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
;	O
which	O
Fact	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susannah	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Rinch	I-pers
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
:	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pewter	O
Dish	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
;	O
which	O
Fact	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Christopher	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Timberwell	I-pers
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Amy	B-pers
Armstrong	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
taking	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Drury-Lane	O
,	O
at	O
about	O
12	O
a-Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
of	O
the	O
Day	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
Windsor-Court	B-place
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
together	O
to	O
a	O
publick	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Pints	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
been	O
there	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
her	O
Lodging	O
;	O
that	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
talking	O
with	O
her	O
about	O
something	O
or	O
another	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
directly	O
,	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
follow	O
'd	O
her	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
being	O
Men	O
with	O
Lights	O
,	O
he	O
charg	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
having	O
taken	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
charg	O
'd	O
the	O
Watch	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
also	O
charg	O
'd	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
both	O
went	O
to	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
Roundhouse	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
gave	O
Sixpence	O
for	O
a	O
Bed	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
pleaded	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
Windsor-Court	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
lodg	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
so	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
afterwards	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
her	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
18	O
d.	O
to	O
lie	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
a	O
Shilling	O
more	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
refusing	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
swear	O
she	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
Round-house	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
come	O
to	O
Bed	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Upon	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Bryan	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Gunthorp	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
8	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jacob	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop-Window	O
:	O
Which	O
Fact	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Fry	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
Hanover-Square	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Bilby	I-pers
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Roger	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Pancrass	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
of	O
getting	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Rings	O
:	O
Which	O
Fact	O
being	O
painly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bristol	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
into	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Purl	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
down	O
to	O
draw	O
it	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Shirt	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dresser-Drawer	O
;	O
that	O
Thompson	O
went	O
away	O
immediately	O
,	O
but	O
Bishop	O
staid	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
charg	O
'd	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
Satisfaction	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
help	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
Thompson	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Bishop	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Precinct	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Catherine	I-place
's	I-place
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Tobacco-Box	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
Moidores	O
,	O
8	O
Rubles	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
9	O
l.	O
of	O
current	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Stag	I-pers
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
latter	O
for	O
receiving	O
of	O
5	O
Moidores	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Master	O
of	O
a	O
Ship	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
;	O
that	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
ashore	O
,	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Cabin	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
having	O
apprehended	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
Rachel	B-pers
Anvil	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
Ann	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
's	O
House	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
Mother	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
gave	O
his	O
Mother	O
4	O
Moidores	O
,	O
and	O
14	O
s.	O
telling	O
his	O
Mother	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
receiv	O
'd	O
it	O
as	O
his	O
Wages	O
for	O
his	O
Voyage	O
;	O
the	O
Tobacco-Box	O
which	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
in	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
against	O
William	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
that	O
Ann	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
had	O
any	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
being	O
stolen	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
Hanover-Square	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Girl	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
taken	O
into	O
his	O
House	O
out	O
of	O
Charity	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
seduced	O
by	O
a	O
Woman	O
who	O
came	O
frequently	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
the	O
Things	O
from	O
time	O
to	O
time	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Francis	B-pers
Skinner	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Barden	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Barton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
36	O
China	O
Milk-Pots	O
,	O
20	O
Dozen	O
of	O
China	O
Saucers	O
,	O
and	O
300	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Tea	O
,	O
value	O
150	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Sims	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
while	O
the	O
Ship	B-place
Harrison	I-place
lay	O
at	O
Black-Wall	B-place
,	O
they	O
were	O
plundering	O
of	O
it	O
continually	O
every	O
Day	O
;	O
that	O
John	B-pers
Barton	I-pers
plunder	O
'd	O
within	O
the	O
Ship	O
,	O
and	O
Francis	O
Skinner	O
without	O
in	O
the	O
Lighter	O
;	O
that	O
Barton	O
handed	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
to	O
Skinner	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
employ	O
'd	O
two	O
Boys	O
with	O
Boats	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
continually	O
carrying	O
the	O
Goods	O
ashore	O
,	O
and	O
returning	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
Tea	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Ship	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
every	O
Day	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
Skinner	O
break	O
open	O
Chests	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
out	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Milk-Pots	O
,	O
Tea-Pots	O
,	O
and	O
Saucers	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Hugginson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
on	O
Board	O
the	O
Ship	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
take	O
12	O
Milk-Pots	O
,	O
and	O
40	O
Saucers	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
threw	O
out	O
Tea	O
in	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
Rags	O
and	O
little	O
Bags	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
swore	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
They	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
on	O
Board	O
the	O
Ship	O
to	O
work	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
Thieve	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
every	O
Finger	O
was	O
a	O
Fish-Hook	O
.	O
-	O
Austin	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
one	O
Ogden	O
,	O
broke	O
open	O
Chests	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Quantity	O
of	O
8	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Saucers	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
and	O
that	O
two	O
Water-Boys	O
were	O
continually	O
employd	O
to	O
carry	O
;	O
that	O
while	O
one	O
went	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
came	O
back	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Lighter	O
lay	O
along-side	O
of	O
the	O
Ship	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
Barton	O
in	O
the	O
Ship	O
plunder	O
the	O
Chests	O
of	O
Tea	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
out	O
Tea	O
,	O
and	O
hand	O
it	O
to	O
Skinner	O
in	O
the	O
Hoy	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
there	O
was	O
to	O
the	O
Quantity	O
of	O
half	O
a	O
Chest	O
plunder	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
pleaded	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
was	O
set	O
on	O
foot	O
for	O
Spite	O
because	O
they	O
took	O
Tea	O
away	O
from	O
those	O
Evidences	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
carrying	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Ship	O
;	O
and	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
employ	O
'd	O
as	O
Tide-Waiters	O
to	O
the	O
Customs	O
for	O
many	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
Tea	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
from	O
the	O
Evidences	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
7	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Tea	O
from	O
Sims	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
others	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Sims	O
threatned	O
them	O
to	O
turn	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
Employment	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Evidence	O
went	O
in	O
a	O
Bum-Boat	O
to	O
pilfer	O
and	O
plunder	O
what	O
they	O
could	O
get	O
of	O
Merchants	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Stores	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
thing	O
:	O
They	O
call	O
'd	O
likewise	O
Evidences	O
as	O
to	O
Sims	O
's	O
Character	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
but	O
a	O
very	O
indifferent	O
one	O
;	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Rut	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
heard	O
Tims	O
say	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
harm	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
hinder	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
let	O
them	O
rob	O
the	O
Company	O
of	O
all	O
they	O
had	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
;	O
but	O
swore	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
mn	O
his	O
Blood	O
he	O
would	O
hang	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
call	O
'd	O
divers	O
to	O
their	O
own	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
a	O
full	O
Hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Claxton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
,	O
indicted	O
for	O
unlawfully	O
,	O
maliciously	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
setting	O
Fire	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
frequently	O
get	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
quarrelsome	O
and	O
disturbing	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
spoke	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
desiring	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
quiet	O
,	O
telling	O
her	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
bear	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
about	O
a	O
Week	O
before	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
set	O
on	O
Fire	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
fighting	O
with	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
all	O
of	O
a	O
gore	O
Blood	O
asking	O
her	O
for	O
some	O
Vinegar	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
blaming	O
her	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Fire-Shovel	O
and	O
broke	O
the	O
Windows	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
be	O
reveng	O
'd	O
of	O
her	O
for	O
taking	O
her	O
Husband	O
's	O
Part	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
telling	O
her	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
Warning	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Room	O
,	O
she	O
(	O
as	O
she	O
suppos	O
'd	O
)	O
took	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
set	O
Fire	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
the	O
Day	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
:	O
that	O
about	O
Candlelight	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
with	O
an	O
Acquaintance	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Fire	O
any	O
where	O
in	O
the	O
lower	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
they	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
a	O
great	O
Smoke	O
,	O
a	O
strong	O
smell	O
of	O
Burning	O
;	O
that	O
searching	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Fire	O
in	O
a	O
Closet	O
under	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
behind	O
the	O
Parlour	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
a	O
Candle	O
burning	O
in	O
her	O
Apartment	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
walking	O
about	O
the	O
Yard	O
smoaking	O
Tobacco	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Fire	O
flam	O
'd	O
out	O
like	O
the	O
Mouth	O
of	O
an	O
Oven	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
caus	O
'd	O
by	O
setting	O
Fire	O
to	O
some	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
Hoop-Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Things	O
that	O
hung	O
there	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Fire	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
that	O
Help	O
coming	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
throwing	O
Water	O
,	O
they	O
got	O
it	O
out	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
never	O
assisted	O
in	O
quenching	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
kept	O
walking	O
about	O
the	O
Yard	O
unconcern	O
'd	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
telling	O
her	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
this	O
,	O
she	O
damn	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
calling	O
her	O
Pale-fac	O
'd	O
her	O
before	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
a	O
Bed	O
to	O
lie	O
on	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
also	O
abus	O
'd	O
Martha	B-pers
Underhill	I-pers
,	O
who	O
help	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
out	O
;	O
calling	O
her	O
a	O
meddle-making	O
Jade	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
no	O
Business	O
to	O
trouble	O
herself	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
pack	O
'd	O
up	O
her	O
Cloaths	O
in	O
a	O
Box	O
which	O
stood	O
on	O
a	O
Cane-Chair	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
ready	O
to	O
be	O
carried	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Evidence	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
Mary	B-pers
Higginson	I-pers
,	O
Martha	B-pers
Underhill	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Minors	I-pers
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
also	O
added	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
saw	O
her	O
near	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
the	O
Fire	O
began	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Candle	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
;	O
also	O
saw	O
her	O
afterwards	O
stoop	O
down	O
and	O
look	O
into	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
suspect	O
what	O
she	O
was	O
about	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
set	O
the	O
Things	O
on	O
Fire	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
a	O
full	O
Hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Trinity	B-place
Minories	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
Chain	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
value	O
30	O
l.	O
and	O
19	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Watch	O
stolen	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
suspect	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
his	O
Journeyman	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
his	O
Apprentice	O
;	O
'till	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
his	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
bought	O
his	O
Gold	O
Seal	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
gave	O
him	O
Notice	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
him	O
by	O
a	O
Boy	O
belonging	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Kings	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
;	O
that	O
being	O
inform	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Boy	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
sent	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
search	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Lodging	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
Watch	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
examin	O
'd	O
,	O
pretended	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Seal	O
in	O
a	O
Field	O
going	O
to	O
Limehouse	O
.	O
The	O
Boy	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
receiv	O
'd	O
the	O
Seal	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
sent	O
him	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
drinking	O
in	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Name	O
,	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
Money	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Rock	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
going	O
again	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Lodging	O
and	O
pressing	O
him	O
to	O
declare	O
the	O
Truth	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
afterwards	O
take	O
the	O
Watch	O
from	O
behind	O
the	O
Bed's-head	O
,	O
and	O
deliver	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
Constable	O
likewise	O
confirm	O
'd	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
at	O
last	O
own	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
Watch	O
and	O
19	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
11	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
going	O
Home	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Fob	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
beside	O
,	O
into	O
his	O
Breeches	O
.	O
However	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
insisted	O
upon	O
it	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
he	O
was	O
elsewhere	O
all	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
could	O
not	O
possibly	O
commit	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
which	O
tho	O
'	O
they	O
came	O
pretty	O
near	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
amount	O
to	O
a	O
satisfactory	O
Proof	O
:	O
He	O
also	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Persons	O
to	O
his	O
Character	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
one	O
;	O
as	O
also	O
did	O
his	O
Master	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
so	O
clearly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Allhallows	B-place
Staining	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Esther	B-pers
Gomes	I-pers
Serra	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Men	O
's	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Esther	O
and	O
Moses	B-pers
Gomes	I-pers
Serra	I-pers
the	O
23d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
broken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
stolen	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
who	O
did	O
the	O
Robbery	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
a	O
Pawn-broker	O
's	O
by	O
the	O
Information	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	O
Pickard	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Suit	O
of	O
Cloaths	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
her	O
by	O
Sarah	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
lent	O
12	O
Shillings	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
3	O
Days	O
after	O
she	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
(	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
)	O
and	O
brought	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
she	O
lent	O
them	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Suit	O
of	O
Cloaths	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
were	O
afterwards	O
brought	O
again	O
by	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
who	O
order	O
'd	O
that	O
they	O
should	O
be	O
deliver	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Person	O
that	O
had	O
laid	O
them	O
in	O
before	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
May	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
afterwards	O
she	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
She	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
her	O
Husband	O
was	O
(	O
Joseph	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
executed	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Sessions	O
since	O
)	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
inform	O
'd	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
committed	O
a	O
Robbery	O
on	O
a	O
Jew	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Sarah	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
's	O
Mother	O
had	O
lent	O
them	O
a	O
Dark	O
Lanthorn	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
)	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
made	O
away	O
with	O
all	O
the	O
Things	O
but	O
the	O
Watch	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
carried	O
the	O
Watch	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Pickard	O
's	O
by	O
all	O
their	O
Orders	O
,	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
out	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
themselves	O
were	O
fearful	O
of	O
disposing	O
of	O
the	O
Watch	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
all	O
a	O
Share	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
of	O
their	O
Neighbours	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
them	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Character	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
but	O
that	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
,	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
committing	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Oliver	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
William	I-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Lawrence	I-place
Jury	I-place
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
47	O
Guineas	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hepworth	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
North	I-pers
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
Prisoner	O
were	O
both	O
Servant	O
s	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
North	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
while	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
opening	O
his	O
Box	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Pendrel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Blackfryers	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Simons	I-pers
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
lead	O
him	O
Home	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
Tavern	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Post-boy	B-place
at	I-place
Ludgate	I-place
,	O
and	O
drank	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Pints	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
coming	O
out	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
his	O
Ring	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
pleaded	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
lie	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
asking	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
?	O
that	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
Half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
but	O
3	O
s.	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Ring	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
only	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Daniel	B-pers
Church	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Forster	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
9	O
d.	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Forster	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
from	O
her	O
own	O
House	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
Child	O
,	O
about	O
20	O
Doors	O
off	O
,	O
about	O
7	O
o-Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
came	O
and	O
jostled	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
almost	O
thrown	O
her	O
down	O
;	O
that	O
thereupon	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
Fellow	O
could	O
you	O
not	O
go	O
along	O
without	O
shoving	O
me	O
?	O
that	O
thereupon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
turnining	O
back	O
and	O
damning	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
Bitch	O
,	O
hit	O
her	O
a	O
slap	O
on	O
the	O
Face	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
saying	O
,	O
Why	O
do	O
you	O
strike	O
me	O
so	O
?	O
he	O
struck	O
her	O
several	O
times	O
;	O
that	O
being	O
come	O
up	O
to	O
a	O
Barrow-Woman	O
and	O
her	O
Daughter	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
Why	O
do	O
you	O
abuse	O
the	O
Woman	O
so	O
?	O
she	O
is	O
an	O
honest	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
fell	O
a	O
beating	O
them	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
the	O
Woman	O
's	O
Husband	O
coming	O
,	O
they	O
all	O
fell	O
to	O
fighting	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
feeling	O
a	O
Pocket-Book	O
under	O
her	O
Feet	O
,	O
felt	O
for	O
her	O
Money	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket-Apron	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
all	O
gone	O
too	O
:	O
She	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
striking	O
her	O
,	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
Apron	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
rather	O
a	O
drunken	O
Frolick	O
than	O
a	O
Felony	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
the	O
Womans	O
Money	O
was	O
lost	O
.	O
Upon	O
a	O
full	O
Hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Catherine	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
Chain	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Seals	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stibbs	I-pers
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
coming	O
Home	O
about	O
9	O
a-Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
Day	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
being	O
well	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
order	O
'd	O
that	O
no-body	O
should	O
disturb	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
undressing	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
let	O
his	O
Breeches	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Feet	O
of	O
the	O
Bed	O
;	O
and	O
seeing	O
her	O
have	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
what	O
the	O
did	O
with	O
it	O
?	O
and	O
she	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
She	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Breeches	O
to	O
lay	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
;	O
that	O
perceiving	O
Mary	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
wanted	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
To	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
for	O
Dinner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
to	O
buy	O
something	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
her	O
come	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
asking	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
came	O
for	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
To	O
bring	O
the	O
Change	O
of	O
the	O
Half	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Watch	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
call	O
'd	O
down	O
to	O
Dinner	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
din	O
'd	O
he	O
wrote	O
a	O
Letter	O
,	O
and	O
wanting	O
to	O
seal	O
it	O
,	O
sent	O
Ann	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
up	O
for	O
his	O
Watch	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
coming	O
down	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
;	O
not	O
could	O
it	O
ever	O
be	O
found	O
since	O
:	O
That	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
no-body	O
in	O
his	O
Room	O
all	O
that	O
time	O
but	O
himself	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
she	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
following	O
Evidence	O
:	O
Robert	B-pers
Slater	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
September	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Harrard	O
's	O
Court	O
,	O
near	O
Rag-Fair	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Emery	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
that	O
was	O
lost	O
?	O
and	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
had	O
heard	O
something	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
reply	O
'd	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
heard	O
something	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
She	O
had	O
the	O
Watch	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
hearing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
bailed	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
Bail	O
being	O
his	O
Acquaintance	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
's	O
Waterman	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
acquainted	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
going	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Emery	O
's	O
,	O
were	O
told	O
the	O
whole	O
Story	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
inform	O
'd	O
that	O
Ann	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
was	O
the	O
first	O
Person	O
that	O
produced	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
got	O
Intelligence	O
where	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
Brandy-shop	O
in	O
Rag	O
Fair	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
apprehended	O
by	O
a	O
tor	O
,	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
Justice	O
Danet	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
one	O
Ann	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
(	O
who	O
was	O
since	O
run	O
away	O
)	O
and	O
herself	O
,	O
did	O
take	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
sold	O
for	O
5	O
Guineas	O
,	O
besides	O
the	O
Chain	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
herself	O
had	O
30	O
s.	O
for	O
her	O
Share	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Emery	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Sware	O
had	O
a	O
Child	O
at	O
Nurse	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
at	O
proper	O
Times	O
to	O
suckle	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
Night	O
she	O
staying	O
lodger	O
than	O
ordinary	O
,	O
she	O
chode	O
her	O
for	O
staying	O
so	O
long	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
she	O
shew	O
'd	O
her	O
a	O
fine	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
open	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
fine	O
one	O
indeed	O
,	O
the	O
finest	O
she	O
had	O
ever	O
seen	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
many	O
fine	O
ones	O
;	O
that	O
it	O
had	O
a	O
Gold	O
Chain	O
,	O
2	O
Seals	O
,	O
one	O
Gold	O
and	O
one	O
Silver	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
but	O
a	O
mean	O
Woman	O
,	O
asked	O
her	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
?	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
From	O
one	O
Ann	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
;	O
that	O
Ann	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
came	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Swares	O
(	O
who	O
is	O
since	O
run	O
away	O
)	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Ann	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Here	O
,	O
take	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Emery	O
sees	O
that	O
I	O
give	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Danker	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
Ann	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
Ann	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
and	O
while	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Maid	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
William	I-pers
s	O
took	O
the	O
Watch	O
off	O
from	O
the	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
while	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
lay	O
asleep	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
stood	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Stairs	O
below	O
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
gave	O
the	O
Watch	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Ann	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
shew	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Grubber	O
,	O
who	O
broke	O
the	O
Watch	O
in	O
Pieces	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
old	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Woman	O
and	O
Grubber	O
are	O
run	O
away	O
:	O
A	O
Confession	O
to	O
this	O
Purpose	O
was	O
made	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
Justice	O
Danet	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
not	O
sign	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
credible	O
Persons	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Character	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
a	O
full	O
Hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
said	O
Watch	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lamb	I-pers
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
order	O
'd	O
to	O
send	O
a	O
full	O
Pot	O
of	O
Beer	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Burcher	O
's	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
dozen	O
Doors	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
Change	O
for	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Boy	O
carrying	O
the	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
brought	O
a	O
Pennyworth	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
too	O
,	O
bidding	O
him	O
run	O
back	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
Boy	O
was	O
return	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
This	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
said	O
,	O
is	O
a	O
Stratagem	O
much	O
used	O
at	O
the	O
other	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
Town	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Isabella	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
one	O
Jane	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
(	O
since	O
deceas	O
'd	O
)	O
pick	O
'd	O
him	O
up	O
near	O
Monmouth-Street	O
,	O
about	O
8	O
a-Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
together	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Diet-street	B-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
;	O
that	O
there	O
Jane	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
took	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
privately	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
perceiving	O
it	O
,	O
got	O
it	O
away	O
from	O
her	O
again	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
violently	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
behind	O
her	O
Back	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Man	O
came	O
and	O
bully	O
'd	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
He	O
was	O
come	O
to	O
rob	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
kick	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
Stairs	O
;	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
found	O
where	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
pawn	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Wildman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminister	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
taking	O
8	O
Guineas	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Barnfellow	I-pers
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
meeting	O
him	O
,	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Gun-Tavern	B-place
in	I-place
German-street	I-place
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
drank	O
together	O
for	O
about	O
two	O
Hours	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Money	O
;	O
that	O
a	O
Constable	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
charg	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
stripp	O
'd	O
and	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
but	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
1	O
d.	O
Whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
John	B-pers
Showswood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Gold	O
Watches	O
,	O
value	O
75	O
l.	O
2	O
Diamond	O
Rings	O
,	O
a	O
Pistol	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Buchan	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Journeyman	O
,	O
and	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Night	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
Country	O
;	O
and	O
going	O
up	O
Stairs	O
to	O
dress	O
himself	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
of	O
breaking	O
open	O
his	O
Scriptore	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
he	O
know	O
what	O
was	O
become	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
'till	O
he	O
receiv	O
'd	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
him	O
from	O
Bristol	O
,	O
acquainting	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
in	O
Custody	O
,	O
being	O
taken	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
Mayor	O
;	O
and	O
also	O
acquainting	O
him	O
that	O
his	O
Gold	O
repeating	O
Watch	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Hands	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Innings	O
a	O
Pawn-broker	O
,	O
and	O
begging	O
his	O
Mercy	O
and	O
Favour	O
in	O
his	O
prosecuting	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Innings	O
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
him	O
a	O
Gold	O
repeating	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
thirty	O
Pieces	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
would	O
have	O
taken	O
ten	O
;	O
that	O
one	O
Mac	O
Gregar	O
,	O
his	O
Confederate	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
had	O
another	O
Watch	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
suspecting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
stopp	O
'd	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
advertiz	O
'd	O
it	O
:	O
He	O
produced	O
the	O
Watch	O
in	O
Court	O
;	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
;	O
and	O
both	O
Mr.	O
Innings	O
and	O
his	O
Servant	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Allen	O
,	O
a	O
Clergyman	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
seeing	O
a	O
Mob	O
about	O
the	O
Tolsey	O
at	O
Bristol	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
the	O
Mayor	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
own	O
the	O
stealing	O
of	O
a	O
Watch	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
deliver	O
'd	O
into	O
his	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
's	O
)	O
Hand	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sworn	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
which	O
was	O
stolen	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
with	O
the	O
Watches	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
notwithstanding	O
,	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
that	O
the	O
Letter	O
was	O
his	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
so	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Tereza	B-pers
Dugood	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Dourdant	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Leather	O
Mounts	O
for	O
Fans	O
,	O
28	O
Fans	O
and	O
Fan-sticks	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
2	O
last	O
for	O
receiving	O
them	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Tereza	B-pers
Dugood	I-pers
was	O
his	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
Fans	O
from	O
time	O
to	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
length	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
Leathers	O
being	O
brought	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Workmen	O
to	O
mount	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
Notice	O
given	O
him	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
examining	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
deluded	O
by	O
Jane	B-pers
Dourdant	I-pers
to	O
give	O
her	O
Mounts	O
,	O
Fans	O
,	O
and	O
Sticks	O
,	O
at	O
divers	O
times	O
,	O
she	O
telling	O
her	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Money	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
promising	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
Money	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
amends	O
:	O
A	O
great	O
many	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Fans	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
pawned	O
for	O
Jane	B-pers
Dourdant	I-pers
's	O
Use	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
clearly	O
proved	O
against	O
Tereza	B-pers
Dugood	I-pers
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Dourdant	I-pers
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Proof	O
against	O
Mary	O
Arnold	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Dugood	O
:	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Dourdant	O
:	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Lunt	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Window-Curtains	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Green	I-pers
:	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Pool	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Heathcot	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchre	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Men	O
's	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
Shirts	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
12	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rostock	I-pers
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Evatt	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bartholomew	I-place
's	I-place
Exchange	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Tankard	O
and	O
Ladle	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
carry	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
betimes	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
got	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Lothbury	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Cup	O
and	O
Cover	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Mackenilly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Sparrow	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Stephen	I-place
's	I-place
Wallbrook	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Fork	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Fork	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hickman	I-pers
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
carried	O
out	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
pawn	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Peter	B-pers
Coffee	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
forging	O
an	O
Indorsement	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Gardener	I-pers
,	O
on	O
a	O
promisory	O
Note	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Payment	O
of	O
18	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
Defect	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
quash	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
continued	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
for	O
another	O
Indictment	O
to	O
be	O
drawn	O
the	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Laycock	I-pers
,	O
of	O
All-Saints	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
18	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Iron	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Proof	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchre	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
45	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Pool	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Pool	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
recommended	O
to	O
her	O
one	O
Michael	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
,	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
Abroad	O
on	O
Sunday	O
,	O
her	O
Door	O
was	O
broken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
Moore	O
gone	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
ty	O
'd	O
up	O
,	O
lying	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Table	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
should	O
have	O
her	O
Money	O
again	O
in	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Days	O
,	O
Michael	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
left	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
there	O
,	O
would	O
come	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
only	O
for	O
Fun	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Evidences	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
Michael	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
liv	O
'd	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
taken	O
for	O
Man	O
and	O
Wife	O
.	O
Upon	O
a	O
full	O
Hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Polton	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Polton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Edmington	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tacks	I-pers
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
;	O
the	O
Burglary	O
being	O
not	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
of	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
Elizabeth	O
Polton	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
;	O
but	O
Sarah	B-pers
Polton	I-pers
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Branch	I-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
an	O
Assault	O
on	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
commit	O
the	O
detestable	O
Sin	O
of	O
Sodomy	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
concealing	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Effects	O
,	O
with	O
design	O
to	O
defraud	O
his	O
Creditors	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
a	O
Bankrupt	O
:	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
