TOKEN	NE
SESSIONS	O
HOUSE	O
,	O
OLD	O
BAILEY	O
.	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
3d	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
4th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
5th	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
1729	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Third	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
First	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	B-pers
BROCAS	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1730	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
I.	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
YEAR	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
T.	O
PAYNE	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
in	O
Ivy-Lane	O
,	O
near	O
Pater-noster-Row	O
.	O
M.DCC.XXX	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
Six	O
Pence	O
.	O
)	O
THE	O
Undertakers	O
of	O
the	O
Sessions	O
Paper	O
,	O
think	O
proper	O
to	O
acquaint	O
their	O
Readers	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
hope	O
no	O
Objections	O
will	O
be	O
made	O
against	O
its	O
being	O
Printed	O
in	O
a	O
Size	O
different	O
from	O
the	O
former	O
;	O
they	O
apprehending	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
thought	O
much	O
more	O
Commodious	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
following	O
Reasons	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
1st	O
,	O
By	O
this	O
Method	O
,	O
there	O
will	O
be	O
more	O
Room	O
to	O
enlarge	O
upon	O
Trials	O
,	O
they	O
,	O
being	O
resolv	O
'd	O
(	O
with	O
all	O
Regard	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
)	O
to	O
have	O
each	O
Proceeding	O
related	O
in	O
the	O
fullest	O
and	O
clearest	O
Manner	O
,	O
both	O
with	O
Respect	O
to	O
the	O
Crime	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
2dly	O
,	O
It	O
is	O
designed	O
always	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
carefully	O
and	O
correctly	O
.	O
Printed	O
,	O
on	O
a	O
good	O
Letter	O
and	O
Paper	O
,	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
really	O
worth	O
Six	O
Pence	O
,	O
beyond	O
which	O
it	O
is	O
never	O
intended	O
to	O
be	O
Rated	O
,	O
even	O
when	O
a	O
Sessions	O
happens	O
to	O
be	O
larger	O
than	O
Ordinary	O
.	O
3dly	O
,	O
By	O
this	O
Method	O
,	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
in	O
every	O
ones	O
Power	O
to	O
preserve	O
them	O
clean	O
to	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Year	O
,	O
when	O
there	O
shall	O
be	O
an	O
Alphabetical	O
Index	O
to	O
the	O
whole	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
by	O
Binding	O
them	O
up	O
together	O
,	O
they	O
will	O
have	O
a	O
Handsome	O
Volume	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Complete	O
Annual	O
Register	O
of	O
these	O
Proceedings	O
,	O
and	O
thereby	O
make	O
it	O
,	O
not	O
worth	O
any	O
ones	O
while	O
to	O
Reprint	O
them	O
in	O
Volumes	O
,	O
which	O
has	O
been	O
done	O
at	O
extraordinary	O
Rates	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
could	O
only	O
be	O
necessary	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Destraction	O
of	O
those	O
Printed	O
on	O
bad	O
Paper	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Sheet	O
Size	O
;	O
thus	O
also	O
,	O
the	O
Expence	O
of	O
twice	O
Purchasing	O
the	O
same	O
Accounts	O
will	O
be	O
avoided	O
.	O
These	O
Proceedings	O
shall	O
be	O
Published	O
with	O
the	O
atmost	O
Dispatch	O
after	O
the	O
finishing	O
of	O
each	O
Session	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
designed	O
to	O
give	O
all	O
possible	O
Satisfaction	O
in	O
the	O
Conduct	O
and	O
Management	O
,	O
so	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
doubted	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
will	O
have	O
the	O
Countenance	O
and	O
the	O
Encouragement	O
of	O
the	O
Publick	O
.	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
For	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
AND	O
ON	O
The	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
3d	O
,	O
4th	O
,	O
5th	O
,	O
and	O
6th	O
of	O
December	O
1729	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Third	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	B-pers
BROCAS	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
Eyre	O
,	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Reynolds	O
,	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Worshipful	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
Raby	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Pool	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Michael	I-pers
Harneck	I-pers
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mallet	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Liddell	I-pers
.	O
Austin	B-pers
Tyre	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Lyon	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Hews	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Beather	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wyton	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Baxter	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Underwood	I-pers
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Beck	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Dick	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Leach	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Hubbard	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Ward	I-place
of	I-place
Billinsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Pound	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
November	O
29	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
no	O
visible	O
way	O
of	O
Livelihood	O
,	O
but	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
frequently	O
with	O
a	O
Bag	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
to	O
a	O
Coblers	O
in	O
that	O
Neighbourhood	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
gave	O
1	O
Penny	O
per	O
Day	O
for	O
Warehouse-room	O
,	O
upon	O
searching	O
the	O
Cobler	O
's	O
Stall	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
Bag	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
4	O
Pound	O
Weight	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
.	O
-	O
Sheppard	O
,	O
another	O
Evidence	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
go	O
in	O
there	O
once	O
or	O
twice	O
a	O
Day	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Bag	O
or	O
Bags	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
worked	O
upon	O
the	O
Keys	O
,	O
that	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Tobacco	O
was	O
given	O
him	O
by	O
those	O
that	O
employ	O
'd	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
he	O
pickt	O
upon	O
the	O
Keys	O
.	O
The	O
value	O
being	O
claiming	O
Property	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Katharine	B-pers
Winder	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Langely	I-pers
Esq	O
,	O
Nov.	O
24	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Kaye	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
having	O
the	O
Care	O
of	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Plate	O
,	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Spoon	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hardy	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
Spoon	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
detain	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
a	O
Porter	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Langley	O
,	O
upon	O
whose	O
coming	O
,	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Spoon	O
was	O
his	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Oliver	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Magnus	I-place
the	I-place
Martyr	I-place
in	I-place
Bridge-Ward	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cheshire-Cheese	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Collyer	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
24	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
shutting	O
up	O
Shop	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
go	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
Cheese	O
,	O
that	O
upon	O
pursuing	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Cheese	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
a	O
Boy	O
came	O
by	O
and	O
dropt	O
the	O
Cheese	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
positive	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
both	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
drop	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Hellens	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Wyat	I-pers
,	O
October	O
31	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Wyat	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
October	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Tankard	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
sensible	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
about	O
One	O
or	O
Two	O
a	O
Clock	O
that	O
Day	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
it	O
while	O
Six	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
caus	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
advertis	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Daily-Post	O
,	O
offering	O
two	O
Guineas	O
Reward	O
to	O
have	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
Mr.	O
William	B-pers
Hardy	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
brought	O
some	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Plate	O
,	O
cut	O
and	O
mangled	O
,	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
that	O
upon	O
examining	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
judged	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
Tankard	O
Lid	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
seen	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Advertisement	O
,	O
suspected	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
Plate	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
asked	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wyat	O
's	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
consented	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
she	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
,	O
acknowledging	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
at	O
round	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
Bag	O
hid	O
under	O
her	O
Pillow	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
produced	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Lid	O
cut	O
in	O
almost	O
twenty	O
Pieces	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
pretended	O
,	O
that	O
two	O
People	O
who	O
took	O
a	O
Room	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
owing	O
her	O
Money	O
,	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Tankard	O
for	O
the	O
Debt	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
produce	O
no	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
adding	O
to	O
his	O
former	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
the	O
Day	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
there	O
:	O
The	O
Fact	O
appeared	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Keys	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bow	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Ward	I-place
of	I-place
Cheap	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
One	O
Guinea	O
and	O
Five	O
Shillings	O
,	O
from	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
November	O
15	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
Stall	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
cheapned	O
some	O
Meat	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
agreed	O
with	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Beef	O
that	O
weighed	O
4	O
Pounds	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
at	O
two	O
Pence	O
a	O
Pound	O
,	O
which	O
came	O
to	O
9	O
d.	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
offered	O
her	O
a	O
Shilling	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
seeing	O
some	O
half	O
Pence	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
this	O
Deponent	O
desired	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
15	O
d.	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
return	O
her	O
6	O
d.	O
but	O
,	O
upon	O
looking	O
for	O
Change	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
all	O
her	O
Money	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
just	O
before	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seized	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
before	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Biliers	I-pers
,	O
and	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
thither	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
more	O
Money	O
than	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
very	O
little	O
;	O
though	O
upon	O
searching	O
her	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
One	O
Guinea	O
,	O
Ten	O
single	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
Crown	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ayres	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Rainford	I-pers
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
who	O
searched	O
her	O
,	O
gave	O
a	O
particular	O
Account	O
how	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
dispos	O
'd	O
,	O
as	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
three	O
Shillings	O
in	O
one	O
Pocket	O
,	O
One	O
Guinea	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
in	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
7	O
Shillings	O
in	O
a	O
third	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Nicholson	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
About	O
4	O
Days	O
before	O
this	O
happened	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
me	O
thirty	O
Shillings	O
to	O
keep	O
,	O
unknown	O
to	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
to	O
buy	O
her	O
a	O
Cloak	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Day	O
this	O
happened	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
a-Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
demanded	O
her	O
Money	O
,	O
requesting	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
buy	O
this	O
Cloak	O
but	O
I	O
being	O
a	O
little	O
angry	O
that	O
she	O
wanted	O
her	O
Money	O
so	O
soon	O
,	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
let	O
her	O
have	O
One	O
Guinea	O
and	O
Ten	O
Shillings	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Cummins	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
on	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
aalong	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
buy	O
her	O
a	O
Cloak	O
,	O
telling	O
me	O
her	O
own	O
had	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
must	O
buy	O
her	O
another	O
unknown	O
to	O
her	O
Husband	O
;	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
as	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
nor	O
could	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
say	O
,	O
notwithstanding	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
her	O
Money	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
felt	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
meddle	O
with	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lewin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Magnus	I-place
the	I-place
Martyr	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Ward	I-place
of	I-place
Billinsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hogshead	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
November	O
29	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
and	O
committed	O
on	O
a	O
violent	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
Day	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
that	O
afterwards	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
requested	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
carried	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Confession	O
,	O
thinking	O
thereby	O
to	O
be	O
admitted	O
as	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
his	O
Accomplices	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
carried	O
before	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Billers	I-pers
,	O
he	O
there	O
confessed	O
,	O
that	O
himself	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
Persons	O
,	O
whose	O
Names	O
were	O
then	O
mention	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
a	O
Hogshead	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Lighter	O
,	O
at	O
Botolph	B-place
Wharf	I-place
,	O
that	O
they	O
carried	O
it	O
cross	O
the	O
Water	O
to	O
Robert	B-pers
Friends	I-pers
,	O
who	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
for	O
8	O
Pounds	O
11	O
s.	O
which	O
Money	O
was	O
divided	O
among	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
an	O
equal	O
share	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
excepting	O
2	O
s	O
;	O
his	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
to	O
support	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dennis	I-pers
Labourer	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Criplegate	I-place
,	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Hester	B-pers
his	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
her	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
3	O
Inches	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
left	O
Breast	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
instantly	O
died	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
Murder	O
.	O
Frances	B-pers
Cotterill	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
Bed	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
light	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
Room	O
;	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
he	O
came	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
lend	O
him	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
came	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
and	O
called	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
have	O
killed	O
her	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
Floor	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
could	O
speak	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
,	O
God	O
forgive	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
all	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
this	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
a	O
Knife	O
at	O
her	O
;	O
being	O
asked	O
(	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
)	O
if	O
she	O
thought	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
this	O
Evidence	O
answered	O
,	O
she	O
believed	O
;	O
not	O
,	O
notwithstanding	O
it	O
was	O
then	O
between	O
3	O
and	O
4	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Oxener	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
Frances	B-pers
Cotterill	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
killed	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
his	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
killed	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
lay	O
Dead	O
on	O
the	O
Floor	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
Knife	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
find	O
none	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
her	O
Cloths	O
and	O
Stays	O
on	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Dodd	I-pers
,	O
Officer	O
of	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Body	O
lie	O
Dead	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
wringing	O
his	O
Hands	O
,	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
What	O
have	O
I	O
done	O
!	O
What	O
have	O
I	O
done	O
!	O
The	O
Wound	O
was	O
under	O
the	O
left	O
Breast	O
,	O
I	O
prob	O
'd	O
it	O
with	O
a	O
Tobacco-pipe	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
3	O
Inches	O
deep	O
,	O
-	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
carrying	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
New	O
Prison	O
,	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
Blood	O
for	O
Blood	O
,	O
Blood	O
for	O
Blood	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
he	O
meant	O
by	O
that	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
thus	O
made	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
Home	O
before	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
(	O
meaning	O
his	O
Wife	O
)	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
Home	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
sate	O
with	O
my	O
Landlady	O
whilst	O
she	O
did	O
come	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
after	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
not	O
doing	O
so	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
my	O
self	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
to	O
Sleep	O
till	O
about	O
3	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
wak	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
no	O
Body	O
by	O
my	O
Side	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
Bed	O
and	O
thought	O
I	O
heard	O
somebody	O
Whisper	O
on	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
heard	O
Company	O
go	O
out	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
is	O
one	O
Will	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
that	O
kept	O
Company	O
with	O
her	O
before	O
I	O
had	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
since	O
I	O
had	O
her	O
;	O
for	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
durst	O
not	O
speak	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
into	O
Company	O
she	O
lik	O
'd	O
better	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
was	O
sorry	O
she	O
should	O
like	O
any	O
Company	O
better	O
than	O
mine	O
,	O
with	O
that	O
she	O
upt	O
with	O
something	O
to	O
throw	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
would	O
send	O
it	O
again	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
felt	O
something	O
hit	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
which	O
by	O
the	O
Blow	O
I	O
took	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Patten	O
,	O
but	O
feeling	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
threw	O
the	O
Knife	O
at	O
her	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
Lord	O
God	O
what	O
's	O
come	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
with	O
that	O
I	O
ran	O
up	O
Stairs	O
to	O
light	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
found	O
her	O
very	O
bad	O
,	O
ran	O
up	O
Stairs	O
again	O
to	O
call	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
then	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
some	O
Water	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
any	O
.	O
Being	O
asked	O
(	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
)	O
what	O
became	O
of	O
the	O
Knife	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
:	O
Then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
House-Keepers	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
all	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
;	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
play	O
on	O
the	O
Violin	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
never	O
knew	O
or	O
heard	O
of	O
any	O
Harm	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslanghter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White-Chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
35	O
Pound	O
of	O
Raw	O
Silk	O
,	O
2	O
Neck	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
a	O
Hoop-Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
Half	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Sloan	I-pers
,	O
November	O
28	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Sloan	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
28th	O
of	O
Nov	O
.	O
I	O
desir	O
'd	O
my	O
Wife	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
Silk	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
carried	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
thinking	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
I	O
enquired	O
if	O
any	O
Body	O
was	O
above	O
,	O
they	O
answered	O
me	O
no	O
,	O
however	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Silk	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
Blind	O
broke	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Sloan	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
lost	O
2	O
Neck-Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
a	O
half	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
a	O
Hoop-Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
Mobb	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Pockets	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Cap	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Clement	B-pers
Corde-Roy	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
small	O
things	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
the	O
Silk	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
supposed	O
was	O
carried	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
more	O
than	O
one	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
Robery	O
.	O
-	O
Humpbreys	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Sash	O
was	O
down	O
between	O
4	O
and	O
5	O
o'Clock	O
that	O
Evening	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Young	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
comeing	O
by	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Sloan	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
out	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Sloan	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
Fire	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
look	O
'd	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
fling	O
up	O
the	O
Sash	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
stept	O
up	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
just	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Sloan	O
's	O
Brother	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
the	O
Parlour	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
there	O
was	O
somebody	O
above	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
he	O
would	O
Catch	O
them	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
steping	O
out	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
down	O
from	O
the	O
Blind	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wortley	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
Friday	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
his	O
Neighbour	O
call	O
Watch	O
,	O
Thieves	O
,	O
and	O
Fire	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
seiz	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
he	O
got	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Petticoat	O
and	O
Stays	O
between	O
the	O
Pallisadoes	O
,	O
just	O
under	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
upon	O
searching	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
a	O
dark	O
Lanthorn	O
,	O
a	O
strong	O
Knife	O
,	O
2	O
Bullets	O
and	O
a	O
Chissel	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
is	O
scarce	O
worth	O
mentioning	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
only	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
things	O
lie	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
pickt	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
came	O
out	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Bodington	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shore-Ditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bushel	O
of	O
Coals	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Loyd	I-pers
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Loyd	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
frequently	O
lost	O
Coals	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
difficulty	O
to	O
know	O
how	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
employ	O
'd	O
4	O
Men	O
to	O
watch	O
in	O
a	O
Yard	O
were	O
the	O
Coals	O
lay	O
;	O
the	O
2d	O
Night	O
between	O
1	O
and	O
2	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
2	O
Men	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
then	O
heard	O
the	O
Padlock	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
next	O
the	O
Stock	O
lock	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
came	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
a	O
Brother	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
George	B-pers
Bodington	I-pers
,	O
that	O
they	O
look	O
'd	O
at	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
let	O
them	O
alone	O
,	O
and	O
first	O
they	O
fill	O
'd	O
a	O
Basket	O
,	O
next	O
a	O
Bag	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
they	O
had	O
completed	O
that	O
,	O
they	O
rushed	O
out	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
Brother	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nightingale	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
he	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
no	O
Account	O
of	O
himself	O
,	O
then	O
asking	O
for	O
the	O
Keys	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
his	O
Brother	O
had	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
no	O
Defence	O
further	O
then	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
but	O
took	O
nothing	O
from	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
laid	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Earle	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Fryer	I-pers
,	O
November	O
6	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Fryer	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
Shop	O
the	O
6th	O
Day	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
convey	O
a	O
pair	O
into	O
his	O
Coat-sleeve	O
,	O
he	O
then	O
dropt	O
his	O
Cane	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
stooping	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
shifted	O
the	O
Stockings	O
from	O
his	O
Sleeve	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
made	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
dropt	O
the	O
Stockings	O
in	O
a	O
corner	O
of	O
my	O
Shop	O
,	O
while	O
my	O
Servant	O
was	O
telling	O
the	O
Stockings	O
over	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
knew	O
how	O
many	O
pair	O
I	O
had	O
show	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
insisted	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
pair	O
wanting	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
lies	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
pointing	O
to	O
a	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
just	O
remov	O
'd	O
from	O
;	O
I	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
where	O
,	O
upon	O
searching	O
him	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
3	O
pair	O
of	O
Scarlet	O
Stockings	O
,	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
another	O
Colour	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
pieces	O
of	O
Ribband	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
carrying	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
along	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
some	O
Persons	O
(	O
Strangers	O
to	O
him	O
)	O
call	O
'd	O
cut	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
What	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
got	O
the	O
Stocking-man	O
?	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
having	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Stocking	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
Stockings	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
kept	O
Fairs	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
with	O
Wiggs	O
,	O
and	O
barter	O
'd	O
Wiggs	O
for	O
Stockings	O
,	O
particularly	O
at	O
Kingston	O
Fair	O
;	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
some	O
Persons	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
they	O
knew	O
no	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
notwithstanding	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Stokes	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Foster	I-pers
,	I-pers
of	I-pers
Chiswick	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
2	O
Silver	O
Forks	O
,	O
1	O
Silver	O
Soop	O
Spoon	O
,	O
1	O
Silver	O
Soop	O
Ladle	O
,	O
1	O
Silver	O
Marrow	O
Spoon	O
,	O
1	O
Silver	O
Milk	O
Pot	O
,	O
1	O
small	O
Silver	O
Salver	O
,	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Snuffers	O
and	O
Snuffer-pan	O
,	O
and	O
1	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Katharine	B-pers
Bourne	I-pers
,	O
October	O
19	O
.	O
Katharine	O
Bourne	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
lost	O
her	O
Plate	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Closet	O
in	O
her	O
Bed-chamber	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
Williams	O
,	O
alias	O
Foster	O
,	O
had	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
7	O
Days	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
her	O
House	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
Night	O
before	O
she	O
lost	O
her	O
Goods	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
her	O
Plate	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
October	O
at	O
Noon	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
it	O
till	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
21st	O
following	O
.	O
Jonas	B-pers
Clifton	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
with	O
4	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
(	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
a	O
Marrow	O
Spoon	O
)	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Fork	O
,	O
offering	O
them	O
for	O
sale	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
question	O
'd	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
her	O
Father	O
was	O
an	O
Apothecary	O
,	O
lately	O
Dead	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Mother	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
this	O
Deponent	O
giving	O
Credit	O
to	O
this	O
plausible	O
Pretence	O
,	O
bought	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Walkingshaw	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
he	O
receiv	O
'd	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Bourne	O
,	O
desiring	O
him	O
to	O
Advertise	O
and	O
give	O
proper	O
Notice	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
the	O
Plate	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
should	O
be	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
sale	O
,	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
stopt	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
thereupon	O
went	O
to	O
Goldsmiths-Hall	O
and	O
gave	O
such	O
Notice	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
soon	O
after	O
he	O
read	O
an	O
Account	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Ridgley	O
,	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
the	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Margaret	B-pers
Stokes	I-pers
,	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
Boat	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
who	O
,	O
in	O
their	O
Passage	O
confessed	O
to	O
him	O
that	O
her	O
Sister	O
Mary	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
that	O
afterwards	O
carrying	O
them	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
Williams	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
deliver	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
a	O
Ring	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
in	O
exchange	O
for	O
the	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Jeweller	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Ridgley	O
bought	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
that	O
Kind	O
,	O
he	O
always	O
sent	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
have	O
his	O
Opinion	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
he	O
saw	O
Stokes	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
brought	O
it	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Whiteway	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Snuffers	O
and	O
Snuff-pan	O
,	O
the	O
Milk	O
Pot	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
small	O
Salver	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
the	O
Persons	O
that	O
sold	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
apprehended	O
Stokes	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
then	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
Hand	O
in	O
stealing	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
(	O
her	O
Sister	O
did	O
that	O
)	O
but	O
confess	O
'd	O
she	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
Sister	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
,	O
not	O
knowing	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Pope	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Waterman	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
brought	O
Margaret	B-pers
Stokes	I-pers
to	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
her	O
own	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Sister	O
stole	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
which	O
Williams	O
confess	O
'd	O
.	O
Williams	O
took	O
the	O
Felony	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
possible	O
upon	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
telling	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Sister	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
herself	O
found	O
the	O
Plate	O
ty	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Towel	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
(	O
not	O
believing	O
Williams	O
had	O
been	O
so	O
lucky	O
)	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
and	O
acquitted	O
Stokes	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Drummond	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Jacob	B-pers
Wakeling	I-pers
Jun	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
a	O
Seal	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
a	O
Cane	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
an	O
Iron	O
Key	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Wakeling	I-pers
junr	O
.	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
October	O
going	O
to	O
Bow	B-place
,	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Person	O
:	O
James	B-pers
Drummond	I-pers
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
Home	O
;	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
deliver	O
your	O
Money	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
refusing	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
strike	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
other	O
draws	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
prick	O
'd	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Arm	O
,	O
then	O
feeling	O
for	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
I	O
fumbled	O
,	O
hoping	O
to	O
save	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
suspecting	O
I	O
was	O
about	O
to	O
conceal	O
something	O
,	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
cheat	O
them	O
?	O
then	O
took	O
my	O
Watch	O
from	O
me	O
and	O
broke	O
the	O
Chain	O
in	O
so	O
doing	O
;	O
he	O
also	O
took	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Buckles	O
from	O
my	O
Shoes	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
assuring	O
him	O
the	O
Buckles	O
were	O
not	O
Silver	O
,	O
he	O
returned	O
them	O
again	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
bind	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
my	O
requesting	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
he	O
charg	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
a	O
by-way	O
and	O
acquaint	O
no	O
body	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
he	O
would	O
kill	O
me	O
,	O
then	O
taking	O
my	O
Cane	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
notwithstanding	O
I	O
begg	O
'd	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
because	O
it	O
was	O
dark	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
well	O
walk	O
without	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
return	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
walk	O
'd	O
off	O
without	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
Watchman	O
and	O
other	O
Assistants	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
meet	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
soon	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Companion	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
Persons	O
that	O
Robb	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
Drummond	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
threatning	O
to	O
shoot	O
me	O
,	O
coming	O
up	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
fir	O
'd	O
a	O
Pistol	O
under	O
my	O
Arm	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
on	O
Horseback	O
and	O
got	O
off	O
.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Wakeling	I-pers
senr	O
.	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
lost	O
a	O
small	O
Key	O
of	O
a	O
Padlock	O
.	O
Simon	B-pers
Potter	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
being	O
upon	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
Jacob	B-pers
Wakeling	I-pers
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Beadle	O
went	O
with	O
us	O
towards	O
Bow	O
,	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
both	O
saw	O
the	O
Highway-men	O
,	O
and	O
Jacob	B-pers
Wakeling	I-pers
knew	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
on	O
Foot	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
the	O
Horseman	O
circling	O
about	O
and	O
threatning	O
to	O
shoot	O
them	O
if	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
let	O
them	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
fir	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
well	O
done	O
,	O
then	O
fir	O
'd	O
at	O
them	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
rode	O
off	O
;	O
then	O
taking	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
searching	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
2	O
Silver	O
Watches	O
,	O
upwards	O
of	O
28	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
a	O
Knife	O
and	O
a	O
Chisel	O
;	O
Jacob	B-pers
Wakeling	I-pers
swore	O
to	O
his	O
Watch	O
and	O
2	O
Keys	O
,	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
and	O
some	O
halfpence	O
.	O
The	O
Watches	O
were	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Pistol	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
fir	O
'd	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Best	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
28	O
l.	O
and	O
2	O
Watches	O
,	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Mathew	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Watchman	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
took	O
28	O
l.	O
and	O
2	O
Watches	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Pistol	O
fir	O
'd	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
but	O
a	O
very	O
trifling	O
Defence	O
,	O
saying	O
.	O
That	O
coming	O
from	O
home	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
2	O
Watches	O
in	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
and	O
pick	O
'd	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Money	O
too	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
great	O
Scuffle	O
and	O
Noise	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
believes	O
they	O
might	O
be	O
drop	O
'd	O
then	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
2	O
Persons	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
one	O
was	O
his	O
Landlord	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
many	O
Years	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
now	O
,	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
his	O
Brother	O
drew	O
him	O
into	O
it	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
Boatswain	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Ships	O
now	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Sea	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
James	O
Drummond	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
and	O
robbing	O
William	B-pers
Isgrigg	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
16	O
Guineas	O
,	O
7	O
half	O
Guineas	O
,	O
3	O
Broad	O
Pieces	O
,	O
1	O
Moidore	O
,	O
about	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
October	O
the	O
29th	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Isgrigg	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
going	O
to	O
Bow	B-place
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
October	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Man	O
on	O
Horseback	O
turn	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
of	O
his	O
Money	O
and	O
Watch	O
,	O
that	O
afterwards	O
hearing	O
a	O
Highway	O
man	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
lost	O
a	O
Watch	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
Simon	B-pers
Potter	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Watch	O
then	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Isgrigg	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Watch	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
28	O
l.	O
odd	O
Money	O
was	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
?	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
the	O
Court	O
any	O
trouble	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Birch	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Helens	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pocket	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Aaron	B-pers
Colock	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
Aaron	B-pers
Colock	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
standing	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	B-place
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Cockney	O
's	O
Procession	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
of	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Hand	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Helens	I-place
,	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
1	O
Pound	O
and	O
half	O
of	O
Spanish	O
Snuff	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
2	O
Tin	O
Cannisters	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Walter	B-pers
Ray	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Hackabout	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Canary	O
Birds	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
and	O
6	O
Canary	O
Birds	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Tims	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Bodice	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Crow	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
order	O
'd	O
the	O
Recognizance	O
to	O
be	O
Estreated	O
.	O
Joanna	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cambrick	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Vanderboel	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Vanderhoel	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
On	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
November	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
Shop	O
with	O
a	O
Woman	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
Mother	O
,	O
who	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
some	O
Cambricks	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
shew	O
'd	O
her	O
several	O
Pieces	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
liking	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
immediately	O
missing	O
one	O
Piece	O
,	O
went	O
after	O
her	O
about	O
a	O
dozen	O
Doors	O
from	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
her	O
Mother	O
bought	O
the	O
Cambrick	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
to	O
carry	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
(	O
meaning	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
)	O
came	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
stop	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
her	O
Mother	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
has	O
not	O
heard	O
of	O
her	O
since	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cotton	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
Muslin	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
black	O
Hood	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Belford	I-pers
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Belford	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
when	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
prove	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
be	O
hers	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Belford	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
body	O
at	O
home	O
but	O
a	O
Child	O
of	O
six	O
Months	O
old	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
self	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
out	O
again	O
presently	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
for	O
afterwards	O
going	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Locks	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
gone	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
would	O
advance	O
Money	O
to	O
redeem	O
them	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Baty	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
lent	O
her	O
16	O
s.	O
on	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
proving	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
hers	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Manly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hashfield	I-pers
,	O
November	O
the	O
11th	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
one	O
more	O
,	O
came	O
with	O
a	O
pretence	O
to	O
buy	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shop	O
long	O
,	O
before	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
six	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
but	O
two	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
drinking	O
at	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Partner	O
wanting	O
some	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
suppos	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
(	O
the	O
Partner	O
)	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
:	O
But	O
that	O
not	O
being	O
believ	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
body	O
appearing	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bellamy	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edmund	B-pers
Noy	I-pers
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Cows	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mr.	O
,	O
October	O
the	O
23d	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Fantla	O
Roy	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
lost	O
four	O
Beasts	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Grounds	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Possession	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Neale	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
brought	O
four	O
Cows	O
to	O
the	O
George	O
Inn	O
near	O
Clare	O
market	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
enquiring	O
for	O
a	O
Chapman	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
this	O
deponent	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
Fat	O
?	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
see	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
the	O
Beasts	O
were	O
worth	O
24	O
l.	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
sell	O
them	O
for	O
20	O
l.	O
at	O
length	O
they	O
agreed	O
for	O
12	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deponent	O
gave	O
him	O
1	O
s.	O
Earnest	O
,	O
but	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
on	O
of	O
a	O
much	O
greater	O
Value	O
,	O
this	O
Deponent	O
got	O
a	O
Constable	O
and	O
secur	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
4	O
Beasts	O
on	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
near	O
Hounslow	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
Hammersmith	O
Turnpike	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
no	O
Money	O
,	O
left	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
in	O
pawn	O
for	O
the	O
Toll	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
drove	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
George	O
Inn	O
,	O
but	O
cou	O
'd	O
find	O
no	O
Owner	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
offer	O
'd	O
them	O
for	O
Sale	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joanna	B-pers
Wakefield	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Moran	I-pers
,	O
October	O
the	O
30th	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Moran	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
take	O
,	O
to	O
have	O
Robb	O
'd	O
me	O
of	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
my	O
Master	O
to	O
the	O
Castle	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
no	O
farther	O
occasion	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
home	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Companion	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
come	O
Souse	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
swore	O
I	O
must	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
lug	O
me	O
along	O
into	O
Angel	B-place
Court	I-place
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
spend	O
no	O
Money	O
,	O
nor	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
got	O
me	O
in	O
,	O
some	O
pull	O
'd	O
my	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
my	O
Coat	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
got	O
about	O
my	O
Waist	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
same	O
Strain	O
of	O
Love	O
again	O
,	O
whips	O
one	O
Hand	O
into	O
my	O
Breeches	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
into	O
my	O
Fobb	O
,	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
my	O
Watch	O
presently	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
Robb	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
deny	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
chattering	O
above	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
they	O
said	O
I	O
might	O
come	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
Stairs	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
firebrand	O
Woman	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Face	O
like	O
a	O
Lion	O
,	O
enough	O
to	O
frighten	O
any	O
Man	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
my	O
Watch	O
very	O
foolishly	O
,	O
promised	O
me	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
could	O
get	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
being	O
positive	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Boquett	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Boquett	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Saucepan	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sherman	B-pers
Saving	I-pers
,	O
November	O
the	O
15th	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
full	O
against	O
Elizabeth	O
as	O
to	O
her	O
taking	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Pawning	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
Mary	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
Elizabeth	O
Guilty	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
acquitted	O
Mary	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Bull	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Gilfillon	I-pers
,	O
November	O
the	O
5th	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Gilfillon	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lay	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
making	O
Search	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
Gravesend	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
for	O
Legborne	O
,	O
stop	O
'd	O
at	O
Gravsend	O
,	O
but	O
intended	O
to	O
bring	O
them	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Adam	B-pers
Mash	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Harrow	B-place
on	I-place
the	I-place
Hill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Wickedly	O
and	O
Wilfully	O
burning	O
,	O
consuming	O
,	O
and	O
setting	O
Fire	O
to	O
a	O
Sheep-House	O
and	O
Stables	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	O
November	O
the	O
6th	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
On	O
November	O
the	O
6th	O
betwen	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
a	O
Sheep-House	O
,	O
Hen-House	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Granges	O
belonging	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
were	O
on	O
fire	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
about	O
9	O
the	O
same	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
discover	O
'd	O
the	O
Fire	O
about	O
12	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Tiles	O
flying	O
against	O
my	O
Window	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
threatned	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
great	O
Fire	O
that	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
living	O
about	O
six	O
Miles	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
been	O
at	O
a	O
Sisters	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Reason	O
why	O
he	O
bore	O
such	O
Malice	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
him	O
Money	O
enough	O
for	O
Reaping	O
some	O
Wheat	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Widgington	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Stable	O
that	O
was	O
burnt	O
down	O
the	O
Night	O
the	O
Fire	O
happen	O
'd	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
from	O
the	O
Sheep-House	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Weedon	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
that	O
Night	O
the	O
Fire	O
happen	O
'd	O
,	O
to	O
ask	O
Relief	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
relieve	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
curs	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Newman	O
,	O
and	O
play	O
'd	O
antick	O
Tricks	O
about	O
the	O
Yard	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Read	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Newman	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
gave	O
him	O
some	O
Victnals	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
that	O
was	O
good	O
for	O
?	O
upon	O
which	O
this	O
Deponent	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
great	O
Fire	O
.	O
Job	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Barn	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lay	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
why	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
help	O
Mr.	O
Newman	O
at	O
the	O
Fire	O
?	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
wore	O
out	O
his	O
Shoes	O
already	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
only	O
made	O
a	O
little	O
Fire	O
by	O
the	O
Sheep-House	O
to	O
warm	O
himself	O
,	O
but	O
wish	O
'd	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
a	O
fire	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Newman	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Other	O
Evidences	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
effect	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
wishing	O
Mr.	O
Newman	O
's	O
House	O
on	O
Fire	O
,	O
adding	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Morning	O
after	O
the	O
Fire	O
was	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Newman	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
why	O
he	O
wish	O
'd	O
him	O
so	O
much	O
hurt	O
?	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
forgive	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
do	O
so	O
no	O
more	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
only	O
angry	O
that	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
me	O
Money	O
enough	O
for	O
reaping	O
some	O
Wheat	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
transported	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
Mr.	O
Newman	O
a	O
Mischief	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
seven	O
Years	O
hence	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
his	O
speaking	O
the	O
Words	O
to	O
the	O
Effect	O
in	O
the	O
Depositions	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
deny	O
'd	O
his	O
Committing	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Ticking	O
Pocket	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Silk	O
Girdle	O
with	O
a	O
Silver	O
Buckle	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
46	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Oades	I-pers
,	O
November	O
the	O
29th	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Oades	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
Old	B-place
Gravel	I-place
Lane	I-place
about	O
9	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
two	O
Basket-Women	O
were	O
a	O
scolding	O
,	O
I	O
staid	O
a	O
little	O
to	O
hear	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stood	O
close	O
by	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
felt	O
something	O
give	O
a	O
twitch	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
thinking	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
miss	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
46	O
l.	O
and	O
18	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
Pocket	O
immediately	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
after	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Father	O
brought	O
29	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Pocket	O
,	O
the	O
Girdle	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
half	O
Crowns	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Redford	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Father	O
not	O
bringing	O
all	O
the	O
Money	O
which	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
a	O
Candle	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Pocket	O
,	O
to	O
try	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
find	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
scatter	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
none	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Snellgrove	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
coming	O
home	O
with	O
her	O
Mother	O
,	O
they	O
stopp	O
'd	O
to	O
hear	O
the	O
Basket-Women	O
scold	O
;	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
near	O
her	O
Mother	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Basket-Woman	O
had	O
her	O
Hand	O
upon	O
her	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
nobody	O
was	O
near	O
her	O
Mother	O
on	O
that	O
side	O
the	O
Pocket	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
thus	O
made	O
his	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
Pocket	O
lie	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
Father	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
29	O
Guineas	O
and	O
some	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Father	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
young	O
Rogue	O
,	O
where	O
did	O
you	O
get	O
this	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
;	O
about	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
Guineas	O
Reward	O
;	O
so	O
we	O
carry	O
'd	O
it	O
home	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
but	O
two	O
Guineas	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Father	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Money	O
his	O
Son	O
brought	O
him	O
,	O
was	O
29	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
half	O
Crowns	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
Things	O
in	O
the	O
Pocket	O
into	O
the	O
Boy	O
's	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
lock	O
'd	O
them	O
up	O
till	O
they	O
were	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
Boy	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
honest	O
.	O
another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
effect	O
.	O
A	O
Woman	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
the	O
Gentlewoman	O
came	O
by	O
,	O
the	O
Boy	O
was	O
at	O
her	O
Shop	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
there	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
go	O
by	O
;	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
how	O
she	O
could	O
see	O
so	O
well	O
?	O
she	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Lamp	O
that	O
was	O
burning	O
in	O
her	O
Shop	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
might	O
have	O
kept	O
all	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
probably	O
have	O
come	O
to	O
no	O
Damage	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
greatest	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
being	O
return	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Christ-Church	B-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Ward	I-place
of	I-place
Farringdon	I-place
Within	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
wooden	O
Box	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
14	O
Pound	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Latham	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	O
November	O
1	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
his	O
Compting-House	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stole	O
the	O
Box	O
off	O
of	O
his	O
Counter	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
stept	O
out	O
and	O
overtook	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Box	O
on	O
his	O
Back	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Kingsley	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
almost	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
Sight	O
when	O
he	O
acquainted	O
Mr.	O
Arnold	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
him	O
down	O
Warwick-Lane	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
making	O
a	O
trifling	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
Candleweek	I-place
Ward	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
l.	O
a	O
Gold	O
Chain	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
a	O
Seal	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
,	O
November	O
15	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
me	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
she	O
stole	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
might	O
take	O
it	O
from	O
my	O
Beds-head	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
from	O
me	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Granger	O
,	O
a	O
Pawnbroker	O
,	O
advertised	O
the	O
Case	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
Watch-maker	O
to	O
see	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
mine	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
afterwards	O
with	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
Drury-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Watch	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
search	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Pawnbroker	O
's	O
Clark	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
feign	O
himself	O
fudled	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Friend	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
then	O
we	O
secured	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
her	O
to	O
her	O
Master	O
that	O
waited	O
hard	O
by	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ockley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
's	I-place
Wood-Street	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
100	O
Weight	O
of	O
Ingot	O
Brass	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Weal	I-pers
,	O
November	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Thomas	I-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twenty	O
Yards	O
of	O
Dyed	O
Linen	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Phipps	I-pers
,	O
November	O
29	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Golding	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
on	O
Saturday	O
,	O
November	O
29.	O
his	O
Master	O
had	O
been	O
shewing	O
some	O
Linen	O
forwards	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
turning	O
himself	O
about	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
finding	O
himself	O
pursued	O
,	O
laid	O
the	O
Goods	O
down	O
upon	O
a	O
Bulk	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
brought	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Shop	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Phipps	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
back	O
by	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
assisting	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Emerson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Riccards	I-pers
,	O
October	O
21	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Camblet	O
Cloak	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
:	O
The	O
Facts	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
on	O
both	O
Indictments	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Magnus	I-place
,	I-place
Newfish-Street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twelve	O
Looking-Glasses	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
December	O
the	O
First	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Anderton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
a	O
Chain	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
four	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Haydon	I-pers
,	O
October	O
16	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Haydon	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
16th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
Fleet-Street	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
near	O
a	O
11	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
picked	O
up	O
by	O
two	O
Women	O
,	O
who	O
hauled	O
me	O
into	O
an	O
Alley	O
in	O
Shoe-Lane	B-place
,	O
and	O
then	O
pulled	O
my	O
Cloaths	O
almost	O
off	O
my	O
Back	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Women	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
away	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Handkerchief	O
violently	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pulled	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
desired	O
to	O
have	O
my	O
Watch	O
again	O
:	O
They	O
first	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
their	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
rifled	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
be	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
Liquor	O
indeed	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pushed	O
me	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
and	O
her	O
Companion	O
pulled	O
the	O
Shirt	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
since	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
Proposals	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
my	O
Goods	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Money	O
but	O
Six	O
Pence	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Brandy	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
with	O
another	O
Women	O
;	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
Six	O
Pence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
to	O
buy	O
Brandy	O
with	O
;	O
being	O
asked	O
,	O
which	O
of	O
the	O
Women	O
robbed	O
him	O
?	O
He	O
answered	O
,	O
Both	O
,	O
Both	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
to	O
the	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
which	O
of	O
the	O
Women	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
October	O
20	O
:	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Macartny	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
18	O
Shilling	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
November	O
24	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
24th	O
of	O
November	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
George-Yard	B-place
in	O
Seacoal-Lane	O
,	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Macartny	I-pers
picked	O
me	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
me	O
to	O
Walter	B-pers
James	I-pers
's	O
Room	O
,	O
up	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
Mary	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
down	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
both	O
put	O
their	O
Hands	O
in	O
my	O
Breeches	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
got	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
my	O
Money	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
James	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Macartny	O
would	O
have	O
given	O
her	O
a	O
Watch	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
about	O
12	O
a-Clock	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
refused	O
it	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
in	O
meddle	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Joice	O
Briggen	O
,	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Bed	O
when	O
Mary	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
was	O
called	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
she	O
asked	O
Spencer	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
loved	O
a	O
Fair	O
or	O
a	O
Black	O
Thing	O
best	O
?	O
Then	O
Macartny	O
said	O
,	O
Let	O
me	O
come	O
and	O
see	O
how	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
is	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
kiss	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
were	O
so	O
loving	O
together	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
tumbled	O
upon	O
my	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
I	O
saw	O
Macartny	O
lay	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Floor	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Man	O
(	O
meaning	O
Spencer	O
)	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
Macartny	O
take	O
something	O
from	O
him	O
when	O
they	O
got	O
up	O
;	O
Macartny	O
said	O
to	O
Wild	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
something	O
more	O
,	O
something	O
heavy	O
yet	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
bid	O
the	O
Man	O
stand	O
off	O
,	O
pretending	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
make	O
Water	O
,	O
takes	O
a	O
red	O
Pan	O
,	O
goes	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
further	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
When	O
he	O
found	O
he	O
was	O
Robbed	O
,	O
he	O
called	O
the	O
Watch	O
in	O
,	O
but	O
Macartny	O
having	O
a	O
Patch	O
on	O
when	O
he	O
first	O
saw	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
taken	O
it	O
off	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
her	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
charged	O
the	O
Watch	O
with	O
Wild	O
,	O
Wild	O
charged	O
the	O
Watch	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
committed	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
asked	O
,	O
When	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Watch	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
Not	O
till	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
;	O
Wild	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
paid	O
her	O
Fees	O
at	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Alexander	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Undershaft	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cotton	O
Gown	O
,	O
2	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
1	O
Cloth	O
Wastecoat	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
November	O
4	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
about	O
a	O
Month	O
,	O
during	O
which	O
time	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
several	O
Goods	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
gone	O
away	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
as	O
a	O
Visiter	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
Wife	O
's	O
Cotton	O
Gown	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Yard	O
;	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Gown	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
let	O
her	O
come	O
to	O
Newgate	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
also	O
confessed	O
before	O
Justice	O
Dennis	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Yard	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Heard	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
have	O
the	O
Gown	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Wastecoat	O
was	O
sold	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Brown	O
in	O
Nightingale-Lane	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
Spite	O
and	O
Malice	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Hellens	I-place
,	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
a	O
Canvas	O
Frock	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Skinner	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
,	O
November	O
26	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
plain	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Caustin	I-pers
and	O
Jeoffry	B-pers
Younger	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
Hanover-Square	I-place
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Bowman	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
one	O
Guinea	O
and	O
13	O
Shillings	O
,	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bowman	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
Five	O
Fields	O
from	O
Chelsea	B-place
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
Home	O
,	O
he	O
past	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
asked	O
,	O
What	O
a	O
Clock	O
it	O
was	O
?	O
And	O
that	O
afterwards	O
they	O
overtook	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
struck	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
Robbed	O
him	O
of	O
one	O
Guinea	O
and	O
thirteen	O
Shillings	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Bradley	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
We	O
all	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
Rob	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Chelsea	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
Home	O
met	O
with	O
this	O
Man	O
(	O
meaning	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
)	O
Jeoffry	O
Younger	O
struck	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
Caustin	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
but	O
17	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
though	O
we	O
all	O
thought	O
there	O
was	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Caustin	O
had	O
cheated	O
us	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
confess	O
'd	O
they	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
Chairman	O
in	O
the	O
five	O
Fields	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Alston	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
Bradley	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
committed	O
to	O
the	O
County	O
goal	O
of	O
Surry	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
admitted	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
Caustin	O
in	O
Westminster	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
deny	O
'd	O
he	O
knew	O
Bradley	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
owned	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
this	O
Robbery	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
had	O
4	O
s.	O
for	O
his	O
Share	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Banks	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
On	O
Sunday	O
was	O
Fortnight	O
last	O
I	O
took	O
Younger	O
in	O
White-Chappel	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
him	O
gone	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
refused	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
got	O
2	O
Men	O
to	O
assist	O
me	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
committed	O
but	O
this	O
Robbery	O
by	O
Chelsea	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
on	O
Finchley-Common	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Newborn	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Younger	O
made	O
a	O
Resistance	O
against	O
Mr.	O
Banks	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
assisted	O
Mr.	O
Banks	O
.	O
Russell	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
heard	O
Younger	O
confess	O
he	O
committed	O
the	O
Robbery	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
made	O
no	O
manner	O
of	O
Defence	O
,	O
or	O
deny	O
'd	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Fowles	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
29	O
Yards	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
8	O
Yards	O
of	O
Velvet	O
,	O
16	O
Yards	O
of	O
green	O
Burdett	O
,	O
12	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cotton	O
and	O
Silk	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Bart	O
.	O
Sir	O
John	O
Brown	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
Servant	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
Footman	O
about	O
a	O
Year	O
,	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
of	O
several	O
Goods	O
that	O
were	O
under	O
Lock	O
and	O
Key	O
in	O
a	O
back	O
Parlour	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
which	O
caus	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
distrust	O
him	O
was	O
missing	O
of	O
Goods	O
which	O
I	O
knew	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sent	O
a	O
Deal-Box	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
House	O
to	O
Covent-Garden	O
,	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Moor	O
's	O
,	O
directed	O
to	O
Ann	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
,	O
when	O
that	O
Box	O
was	O
discovered	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ran	O
away	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
which	O
amount	O
to	O
about	O
20	O
s	O
..	O
Mrs.	O
Moore	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Box	O
was	O
sent	O
by	O
a	O
Porter	O
,	O
directed	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
Mrs.	O
Herbert	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
in	O
Sir	O
John	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
acquainting	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
John	O
sent	O
has	O
Coachman	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
afterwards	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
for	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
his	O
Masters	O
,	O
who	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
go	O
home	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sent	O
a	O
Box	O
directed	O
for	O
Mrs.	O
Herbert	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
saw	O
Velvet	O
,	O
Holland	O
and	O
Silks	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
Sir	O
John	O
's	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
Sir	O
John	O
's	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
Ann	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
bought	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Man	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
Herbert	O
gave	O
him	O
3	O
d.	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Cord	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
corded	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
seal	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
it	O
away	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Moore	O
's	O
by	O
her	O
Order	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Shilling	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Porter	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
spoke	O
of	O
a	O
Letter	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
receiv	O
'd	O
from	O
Herbert	O
,	O
the	O
Contents	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
would	O
be	O
of	O
much	O
Service	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
produce	O
it	O
,	O
notwithstanding	O
he	O
had	O
time	O
allow	O
'd	O
him	O
for	O
that	O
purpose	O
:	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
that	O
affected	O
Dorothy	O
Fowles	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Edmonton	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stilliards	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Linen-Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
1	O
Iron	O
Chopper	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Storey	I-pers
,	O
October	O
23	O
.	O
William	O
Storey	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
the	O
Landlord	O
of	O
the	O
Cock	O
Ale-house	O
at	O
Edmonton	O
told	O
him	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
no	O
Body	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Brewers	O
Servant	O
s	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
his	O
Horse	O
and	O
rode	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
his	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Brewers	O
fining	O
Pail	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
,	O
that	O
either	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
or	O
his	O
Fellow-servant	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
must	O
not	O
only	O
know	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
steal	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
Servant	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
being	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
to	O
the	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
whether	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
they	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Christian	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
14	O
Yards	O
of	O
Edging	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
4	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
,	O
October	O
15	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
some	O
Edging	O
,	O
I	O
shew	O
'd	O
her	O
several	O
sorts	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
seem	O
'd	O
very	O
difficult	O
to	O
be	O
pleas	O
'd	O
,	O
some	O
were	O
not	O
good	O
enough	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
were	O
too	O
dear	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
without	O
buying	O
any	O
;	O
soon	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Edging	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
shew	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Revees	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
her	O
Aunt	O
shew	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
great	O
Variety	O
of	O
Edgings	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
away	O
a	O
piece	O
was	O
missing	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Night	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
the	O
Edging	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
a	O
piece	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Burdet	O
Gown	O
,	O
Value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Bowman	I-pers
,	O
August	O
the	O
25th	O
,	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
her	O
Absence	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Box	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Purdom	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
Value	O
6	O
l.	O
a	O
Shagg	O
Coat	O
with	O
Silver	O
Buttons	O
,	O
Value	O
8	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
28	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Purdom	I-pers
,	O
November	O
the	O
3d	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Purdom	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
near	O
the	O
Dog-House	O
,	O
between	O
Goswell-Street	B-place
and	O
Islington	B-place
,	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
spoke	O
rough	O
Words	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
noise	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
another	O
struck	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
a	O
Bag	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
wherein	O
was	O
8	O
Guineas	O
and	O
28	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
my	O
Shagg	O
Coat	O
with	O
Silver	O
Buttons	O
,	O
and	O
abus	O
'd	O
me	O
very	O
much	O
;	O
some	O
short	O
time	O
after	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
know	O
the	O
Rogue	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
he	O
could	O
help	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
sight	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Gibbon	O
's	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
Man	O
nam	O
'd	O
Richard	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
more	O
of	O
that	O
Name	O
than	O
one	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Rope-walk	O
,	O
then	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Horse	O
and	O
Groom	O
over-against	O
Swan-Alley	O
,	O
I	O
staid	O
in	O
the	O
Riding	O
place	O
out	O
of	O
sight	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Horse	O
and	O
Groom	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
perfectly	O
well	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
my	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
New-Prison	O
-	O
afterwards	O
hearing	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
up	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
I	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Samuel	O
Cope	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
heard	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
pretty	O
much	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Cope	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
by	O
Charles	B-pers
Thorrowby	I-pers
,	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
one	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
in	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Thorrowby	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Mr	O
.	O
Cope	O
's	O
from	O
4	O
,	O
till	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Country	O
Acquaintance	O
,	O
then	O
went	O
home	O
,	O
but	O
having	O
some	O
difference	O
there	O
,	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
under	O
an	O
Hay-Rick	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
good	O
Words	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
sate	O
down	O
by	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
carry	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Cope	O
's	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
us	O
in	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
fell	O
asleep	O
,	O
I	O
supposing	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Thief	O
,	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shears	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
penny	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Cope	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Thorrwby	O
brought	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
our	O
House	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
pick	O
'd	O
up	O
this	O
dirty	O
Fellow	O
?	O
Thorrowgood	O
said	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
Bushel	O
;	O
the	O
Fellow	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
,	O
shew	O
'd	O
his	O
Hands	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
honest	O
Fellow	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
enquir	O
'd	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
Robb	O
'd	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
what	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
one	O
in	O
a	O
blue	O
Jacket	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
blue	O
Jacket	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
had	O
nothing	O
about	O
him	O
but	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shears	O
and	O
2	O
Half-pence	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Ibbottson	I-pers
thus	O
Depos	O
'd	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
from	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
till	O
a	O
quarter	O
past	O
10	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Neighbours	O
about	O
three	O
Doors	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
there	O
till	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
past	O
ten	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Rose	O
and	O
Crown	O
between	O
5	O
and	O
6	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
above	O
three	O
Minutes	O
till	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
after	O
ten	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Garrett	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Company	O
from	O
four	O
o'Clock	O
till	O
past	O
eleven	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Brandy-shop	O
and	O
had	O
two	O
Quarters	O
of	O
Gin	O
,	O
from	O
thence	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
St.	O
John	O
Street	O
,	O
had	O
two	O
Pints	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
parted	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gill	O
,	O
the	O
Beadle	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Watch	O
house	O
about	O
eleven	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
come	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
about	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
an	O
Highway-man	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
let	O
him	O
in	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
sate	O
there	O
till	O
five	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Watch	O
broke	O
up	O
.	O
Eleazar	B-pers
Gibbon	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
many	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
work	O
'd	O
for	O
him	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Man	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
hath	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
from	O
his	O
Childhood	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
trusted	O
him	O
considerably	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
found	O
him	O
honest	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
both	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
effect	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Newbury	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
Susan	B-pers
Newbury	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
her	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
'd	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
broke	O
the	O
Hinges	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
up	O
at	O
Work	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
before	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
she	O
heard	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
who	O
was	O
there	O
?	O
and	O
no	O
body	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
violently	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
jump	O
'd	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
whereupon	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Watch	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
his	O
Rounds	O
at	O
2	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
Williams	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
Thieves	O
,	O
Murder	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bullock	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
fast	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Tumult	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
)	O
they	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
going	O
thither	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
Money	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
thus	O
made	O
his	O
Defence	O
;	O
Williams	O
's	O
Sister	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
lived	O
in	O
a	O
Cellar	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Woman	O
used	O
to	O
wash	O
some	O
Things	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
that	O
Day	O
had	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Spatter-dashes	O
wash	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
forgot	O
my	O
Buckle	O
Garters	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Day	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Sister	O
had	O
not	O
time	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
meeting	O
with	O
three	O
young	O
Fellows	O
that	O
were	O
a	O
quarrelling	O
,	O
I	O
prevented	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
made	O
me	O
drink	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
light	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
,	O
somebody	O
answer	O
'd	O
me	O
(	O
for	O
I	O
thought	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
get	O
my	O
Garters	O
I	O
might	O
be	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Savoy	O
)	O
I	O
pull	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
came	O
open	O
;	O
Williams	O
bid	O
me	O
go	O
about	O
my	O
Business	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
about	O
ten	O
Persons	O
that	O
lodge	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Trigthorpe	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bow	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Blankets	O
,	O
a	O
Rug	O
,	O
a	O
Pillowbier	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bostock	I-pers
,	O
November	O
the	O
6th	O
.	O
It	O
appearing	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutors-House	O
,	O
and	O
convey	O
'd	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Furniture	O
in	O
her	O
Room	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
and	I-pers
Anne	I-pers
Bibby	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
24	O
Pewter	O
Candle	O
Moulds	O
,	O
value	O
24	O
s.	O
2	O
Brass	O
Sauce	O
pans	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
,	O
December	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
Edmund	B-pers
Popplewell	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
,	O
lost	O
24	O
Candle-Moulds	O
and	O
2	O
Brass	O
Sauce-pans	O
that	O
Morning	O
the	O
Fire	O
happen	O
'd	O
.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Moulds	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bibby	I-pers
,	O
that	O
he	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
sell	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
Night	O
,	O
about	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
this	O
Deponent	O
not	O
being	O
well	O
,	O
was	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
prevail	O
'd	O
on	O
his	O
Wife	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
2	O
s.	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
charg	O
'd	O
a	O
Constable	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Rose	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
they	O
knowing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
occasion	O
?	O
the	O
2	O
Sauce-pans	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
brought	O
them	O
home	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Rose	O
,	O
behaving	O
been	O
employ	O
'd	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Rose	O
in	O
helping	O
him	O
to	O
remove	O
his	O
Goods	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
Fire	O
.	O
Edmund	B-pers
Popplewell	I-pers
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
(	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
)	O
how	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
Molds	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Masters	O
?	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
by	O
certain	O
Marks	O
they	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
Frames	O
,	O
they	O
exactly	O
fitted	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Rose	O
to	O
assist	O
in	O
saving	O
his	O
Goods	O
at	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
2	O
Sauce-pans	O
home	O
to	O
secure	O
them	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Rose	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Candle-Moulds	O
he	O
found	O
in	O
Old-street	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
assist	O
in	O
saving	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Proof	O
could	O
be	O
given	O
of	O
his	O
finding	O
the	O
Candle	O
Moulds	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
acquitted	O
his	O
Wife	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Galloway	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
45	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Theophila	B-pers
Pierson	I-pers
,	O
November	O
the	O
30th	O
.	O
Theophila	O
Pierson	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
:	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
on	O
Sunday	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodged	O
four	O
Nights	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
about	O
6	O
o'Clock	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Cup	O
on	O
Monday	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Baugh	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Red-lion-street	O
with	O
a	O
Pistol	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Cup	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
who	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Cup	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
he	O
left	O
the	O
Cup	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Direction	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Baugh	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Cup	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
shewn	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
she	O
swore	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
hers	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
but	O
a	O
trifling	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bambridge	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	I-place
London	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1	O
Feather	O
Bed	O
,	O
a	O
Bolster	O
,	O
2	O
Pillows	O
,	O
2	O
Blankets	O
,	O
1	O
Quilt	O
,	O
2	O
Cane-Chairs	O
,	O
1	O
Easy-Chair	O
and	O
Cushion	O
,	O
2	O
Stuff	O
Chairs	O
,	O
2	O
Tables	O
,	O
a	O
Looking-Glass	O
,	O
Fire	O
Shovel	O
and	O
Tongs	O
,	O
Gridiron	O
,	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
Bellows	O
,	O
3	O
pair	O
of	O
Window-Curtains	O
,	O
China	O
Ware	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
Head	O
of	O
Mecclin	O
Lace	O
,	O
Value	O
10	O
l.	O
a	O
Head	O
of	O
Flanders	O
Lace	O
,	O
Value	O
6	O
l.	O
6	O
Silver	O
handled	O
Knives	O
,	O
Value	O
3	O
l.	O
6	O
Silver	O
Forks	O
,	O
Value	O
40	O
s.	O
2	O
Tea	O
Spoons	O
,	O
Strainer	O
and	O
Tongs	O
,	O
4	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Gold	O
Lace	O
,	O
Value	O
10	O
l.	O
2	O
Gold	O
Seals	O
,	O
1	O
Emerald	O
,	O
Value	O
3	O
l.	O
5	O
Diaper	O
Napkins	O
,	O
1	O
piece	O
of	O
Dimity	O
,	O
a	O
Sable	O
Typet	O
,	O
Value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
blew	O
and	O
white	O
Sattin	O
,	O
Value	O
7	O
l.	O
2	O
Stone	O
Seals	O
,	O
set	O
in	O
Gold	O
,	O
Value	O
3	O
l.	O
3	O
Silk	O
Gowns	O
,	O
Value	O
6	O
l.	O
2	O
pieces	O
of	O
Sarcenet	O
,	O
Value	O
55	O
s.	O
1	O
Garnet	O
Ring	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
of	O
considerable	O
Value	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Barkley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
October	O
1727	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
this	O
Effect	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Fleet	O
,	O
October	O
1727	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Barkley	O
lodg	O
'd	O
within	O
3	O
Rooms	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
Upholder	O
by	O
Trade	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
into	O
Mrs.	O
Barkly	O
's	O
Room	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Pindar	O
,	O
to	O
appraise	O
her	O
Goods	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
an	O
Inventory	O
of	O
what	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Boxes	O
were	O
mentioned	O
in	O
gross	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
opened	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Person	O
they	O
call	O
'd	O
Constable	O
,	O
after	O
they	O
said	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Bambridge	O
sent	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Barkley	O
for	O
her	O
Keys	O
,	O
she	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
send	O
them	O
,	O
whereupon	O
Mr.	O
Bambridge	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Boxes	O
,	O
and	O
wrote	O
the	O
Title	O
of	O
an	O
Inventory	O
on	O
loose	O
Paper	O
,	O
and	O
order	O
'd	O
I	O
should	O
Copy	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
of	O
my	O
Inventory	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
to	O
this	O
Effect	O
,	O
An	O
Inventory	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Berkley	I-pers
,	O
for	O
56	O
l.	O
Rent	O
,	O
due	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Huggins	O
,	O
October	O
23d	O
,	O
1	O
Bedstead	O
with	O
Sacking	O
Bottom	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
gave	O
Mr.	O
Bambridge	O
a	O
particular	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Value	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
for	O
his	O
disposing	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
2d	O
Inventory	O
consisted	O
of	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
China	O
,	O
Rings	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
with	O
precious	O
Stones	O
and	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
all	O
made	O
up	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Bambridge	O
being	O
told	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
usual	O
to	O
Distrain	O
necessary	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
set	O
down	O
such	O
and	O
such	O
things	O
sufficient	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
:	O
I	O
brought	O
them	O
in	O
at	O
first	O
30	O
l.	O
Mr.	O
Bambridge	O
thought	O
that	O
too	O
much	O
,	O
alledging	O
there	O
was	O
Charges	O
attending	O
the	O
Appraisement	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
brought	O
it	O
in	O
at	O
27	O
l.	O
16	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
It	O
is	O
customary	O
to	O
have	O
two	O
Appraisors	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
none	O
but	O
my	O
self	O
-	O
after	O
the	O
Appraisement	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Bambridge	O
put	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Silver	O
Tea	O
Spoons	O
,	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
small	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
into	O
a	O
Portmantua	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Brush	O
found	O
which	O
is	O
used	O
for	O
cleaning	O
of	O
Diamonds	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Bambridge	O
said	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
there	O
must	O
be	O
Diamonds	O
,	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
looking	O
every	O
where	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Rings	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Barkley	O
look	O
'd	O
very	O
Chagrin	O
during	O
this	O
Rifling	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
turn	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
Common-Side	O
,	O
without	O
a	O
Bed	O
to	O
lie	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
Bed	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
my	O
Imprisonment	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
afterwards	O
very	O
much	O
out	O
of	O
Order	O
,	O
talked	O
wildly	O
,	O
would	O
assert	O
that	O
the	O
Lord	O
Harcourt	O
was	O
not	O
Dead	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
punish	O
such	O
Rogues	O
as	O
robb	O
'd	O
her	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bambridge	O
,	O
desir	O
'd	O
this	O
Evidence	O
to	O
tell	O
the	O
Court	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
order	O
him	O
to	O
put	O
every	O
thing	O
down	O
,	O
who	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
given	O
30	O
l.	O
for	O
the	O
Goods	O
himself	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
knew	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
worth	O
so	O
much	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
lower	O
'd	O
the	O
price	O
to	O
27	O
l.	O
at	O
Bambridges	O
's	O
desire	O
;	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
Conversation	O
he	O
heard	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
Mr.	O
