TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
FOR	O
THE	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
:	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
9th	O
,	O
10th	O
,	O
11th	O
,	O
and	O
12th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
1729	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Second	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
Six	O
Pence	O
.	O
)	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
ROBERT	B-pers
BAYLIS	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Rt	O
.	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	B-pers
Pengelly	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Reynolds	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Worshipful	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
Raby	O
,	O
Deputy-Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
other	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Broadhurst	I-pers
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Southwel	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Pointer	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
.	O
James	B-pers
Arnson	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Westlock	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Chappel	I-pers
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Beard	I-pers
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
.	O
George	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Burdon	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Barton	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Prior	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Elliot	I-pers
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Redhead	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Swan	I-pers
.	O
George	B-pers
Gillet	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Salter	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Allhallows	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Unwin	I-pers
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
Young	O
,	O
the	O
one	O
but	O
11	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
12	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Fountain	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchre	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Felkin	I-pers
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
:	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Street	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
marrying	O
John	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
,	O
her	O
first	O
Husband	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
,	O
being	O
alive	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
first	O
Marriage	O
not	O
being	O
satisfactorily	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Hawes	I-pers
.	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
cutting	O
the	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
privately	O
stealing	O
Money	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Motteux	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
July	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
in	O
Thames-street	B-place
,	O
she	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
her	O
Pocket	O
to	O
be	O
cut	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Money	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
at	O
that	O
Instant	O
;	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stopp	O
'd	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
done	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
would	O
have	O
return	O
'd	O
her	O
her	O
Money	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
being	O
advis	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
him	O
secur	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
committed	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
James	I-pers
Grundy	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
his	O
Window	O
was	O
broken	O
open	O
between	O
Eleven	O
and	O
One	O
a-Clock	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
call	O
'd	O
up	O
by	O
his	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
up	O
the	O
Chimney	O
,	O
standing	O
upon	O
the	O
Pole	O
that	O
the	O
Pot-Hangers	O
were	O
on	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
no	O
Defence	O
to	O
make	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
being	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
a	O
Young-Man	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
saw	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
too	O
late	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
Lodging	O
,	O
he	O
invited	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
Lodging	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
out	O
a	O
Newgate	O
Plea	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
Death	O
.	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Neal	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Budd	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Bone-Lace	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
William	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
,	O
16th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
Shop	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
Lace	O
,	O
about	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
a-Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
measuring	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Lace	O
of	O
about	O
10	O
Yards	O
,	O
Neal	O
swore	O
,	O
Her	O
Yard	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
she	O
measur	O
'd	O
,	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
just	O
Measure	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
abusive	O
;	O
that	O
upon	O
this	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Budd	I-pers
desir	O
'd	O
her	O
not	O
to	O
take	O
any	O
Notice	O
of	O
what	O
her	O
Husband	O
said	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
;	O
and	O
her	O
(	O
Mrs.	O
Jennings	O
's	O
)	O
Husband	O
being	O
a	O
Dyer	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Budd	I-pers
pull	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
fore-part	O
of	O
her	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
over	O
some	O
Lace	O
,	O
asking	O
what	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
for	O
Dying	O
it	O
?	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
that	O
,	O
upon	O
this	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
immediately	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
missing	O
the	O
Lace	O
,	O
sent	O
her	O
Maid	O
after	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Maid	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
Master	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Mistress	O
crying	O
out	O
she	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
follow	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
her	O
crying	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
apprehended	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Crisp	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
upon	O
the	O
Out-cry	O
of	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
after	O
Mary	B-pers
Budd	I-pers
,	O
and	O
apprehended	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
Neal	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
jostling	O
close	O
up	O
to	O
one	O
another	O
,	O
he	O
parted	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
their	O
being	O
parted	O
,	O
the	O
Lace	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
betwixt	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
and	O
Neal	O
desiring	O
to	O
be	O
let	O
go	O
,	O
Budd	O
bid	O
him	O
not	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Lace	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
dropping	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
other	O
Evidences	O
to	O
confirm	O
those	O
before-mentioned	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Sharlot	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
:	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Hill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Peniel	I-pers
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
July	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Tea-Kettle	O
,	O
Value	O
2s	O
.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Picket	I-pers
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Hatfield	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
her	O
Husband	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
her	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
upon	O
her	O
Back	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10d	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Billingsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
4	O
lb	O
.	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
d.	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Slingsby	B-pers
Bethel	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
The	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Tailor	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Burleigh	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bartholomew	I-place
's	I-place
the	I-place
Exchange	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Tew	I-pers
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
was	O
immediately	O
taken	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Longford	B-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
County	I-place
of	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Ann	B-pers
,	I-pers
the	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
William	I-pers
Franklin	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
6	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
two	O
others	O
,	O
having	O
obtain	O
'd	O
Warrants	O
for	O
the	O
apprehending	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Franklin	I-pers
,	O
upon	O
an	O
Information	O
of	O
one	O
-	O
for	O
being	O
concern	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
some	O
Robberies	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
did	O
go	O
several	O
times	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
Ann	B-pers
Franklin	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
came	O
arm	O
'd	O
with	O
Pistols	O
and	O
a	O
Hanger	O
,	O
and	O
forc	O
'd	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
violent	O
Manner	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
constrain	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
open	O
her	O
Drawers	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
out	O
her	O
Husband	O
's	O
Money	O
,	O
being	O
6	O
Guineas	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
took	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
telling	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
take	O
the	O
Bed	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
,	O
all	O
her	O
Husband	O
's	O
Goods	O
being	O
forfeited	O
to	O
the	O
Lord	O
of	O
the	O
Manour	O
;	O
having	O
the	O
better	O
to	O
colour	O
the	O
Design	O
,	O
took	O
a	O
Constable	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
at	O
another	O
Time	O
,	O
he	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
Accomplices	O
,	O
did	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
away	O
two	O
Horses	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
House	O
and	O
Stable	O
Furniture	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
Value	O
which	O
they	O
brought	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
under	O
Pretence	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
where	O
forfieted	O
to	O
the	O
Lord	O
of	O
the	O
Manour	O
,	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
also	O
making	O
use	O
of	O
a	O
Constable	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
,	O
when	O
instead	O
of	O
carrying	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Lord	O
of	O
the	O
Manour	O
,	O
they	O
bringing	O
them	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
going	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
safe	O
deliver	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Lord	O
of	O
the	O
Manour	O
(	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Country	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
ignored	O
of	O
such	O
Affairs	O
)	O
objecting	O
against	O
their	O
carrying	O
the	O
goods	O
be	O
knew	O
not	O
where	O
,	O
after	O
that	O
manner	O
,	O
they	O
turn	O
'd	O
him	O
off	O
when	O
they	O
had	O
gotten	O
the	O
goods	O
to	O
London	O
him	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Power	O
,	O
for	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Constable	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Town	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
no	O
Constable	O
at	O
London	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
did	O
produce	O
some	O
Warrants	O
for	O
apprehending	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
as	O
before	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
sufficient	O
Ground	O
for	O
the	O
Warrants	O
for	O
apprehending	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
they	O
lay	O
only	O
against	O
his	O
Person	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
against	O
his	O
Goods	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
fraudulent	O
and	O
illegal	O
Proceeding	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Judith	B-pers
Waggins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
2	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Street	I-pers
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
July	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
having	O
come	O
from	O
on	O
Board	O
a	O
Ship	O
,	O
went	O
into	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
to	O
drink	O
;	O
he	O
there	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
home	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
her	O
Lodging	O
,	O
he	O
staid	O
there	O
'till	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
there	O
lost	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
no-body	O
in	O
his	O
Company	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
meeting	O
her	O
at	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
follow	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
needs	O
go	O
in	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
her	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
had	O
some	O
Brandy	O
,	O
would	O
lie	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
consented	O
,	O
on	O
Condition	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
promis	O
'd	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
one	O
Half-Crown	O
before	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Bed	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
the	O
other	O
Half-Crown	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
Bed	O
again	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
he	O
being	O
provok	O
'd	O
,	O
abus	O
'd	O
her	O
and	O
threatned	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
swear	O
she	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
by	O
way	O
of	O
Revenge	O
.	O
She	O
deny	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
his	O
Guineas	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
had	O
but	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
her	O
amends	O
at	O
another	O
time	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
Guineas	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Circumstances	O
confirming	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Evidence	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
take	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Frances	B-pers
Clifford	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Trevanion	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pocket	O
with	O
23	O
s.	O
a	O
Bunch	O
of	O
Keys	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Dennis	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Day-time	O
,	O
no	O
Person	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	B-pers
Dennis	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Grace	B-pers
Conniers	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Tench	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
Day	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
:	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Linnen	O
hung	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop-Window	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Kennelly	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Baldwin	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
taking	O
6	O
Guineas	O
and	O
3	O
Half-Guines	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
July	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Proof	O
against	O
Baldwin	O
and	O
Fox	O
,	O
and	O
only	O
Suspicion	O
against	O
Kennelly	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Burdus	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Alban	I-place
's	I-place
Woodstreet	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Spurs	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
July	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Willful	O
and	O
corrupt	O
Perjury	O
,	O
by	O
an	O
Answer	O
made	O
in	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Oliver	I-pers
,	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
willful	O
and	O
corrupt	O
Perjury	O
,	O
in	O
swearing	O
himself	O
into	O
a	O
Commission	O
of	O
Bankruptcy	O
against	O
Richard	B-pers
Hoare	I-pers
:	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
make	O
good	O
the	O
Charge	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Rowland	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Clergyman	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
for	O
writing	O
and	O
publishing	O
a	O
false	O
and	O
scandalous	O
Libel	O
,	O
signed	O
Sodomastix	O
,	O
directed	O
to	O
the	O
Rt	O
.	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
of	O
the	O
King's-Bench	O
,	O
containing	O
several	O
scandulous	O
Expression	O
against	O
the	O
Worshipful	O
Thomas	B-pers
Raylton	I-pers
,	O
Nath	B-pers
Blackerby	I-pers
,	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
in	O
regard	O
to	O
the	O
Execution	O
of	O
their	O
Office	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
their	O
letting	O
several	O
Persons	O
escape	O
that	O
were	O
brought	O
before	O
them	O
for	O
Sodomitical	O
Practices	O
,	O
insinuating	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
either	O
for	O
the	O
sake	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
or	O
some	O
other	O
Personal	O
Views	O
.	O
The	O
Charge	O
being	O
made	O
to	O
appear	O
in	O
Court	O
to	O
be	O
groundless	O
and	O
false	O
also	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
both	O
write	O
and	O
publish	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
[	O
Pillory	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Alexander	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Robottome	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Hughes	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
no-body	O
appearing	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Pugh	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
3	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pick	O
'd	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
to	O
fighting	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
lost	O
in	O
the	O
Scuffle	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Rawlins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cotton	O
Gown	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Nightingale	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Woollam	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Woollard	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
7	O
Heifers	O
,	O
value	O
21	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Bellis	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Beasts	O
were	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Grounds	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Heather	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
said	O
Beasts	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
15	O
l.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
John	O
Woollam	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
7	O
Pigs	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
Boar	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Shadbolt	I-pers
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
:	O
This	O
Fact	O
likewise	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Barrow	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Beecher	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Gilpin	I-pers
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
July	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Sterling	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Clogs	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Inglebird	I-pers
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Forster	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Day-time	O
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
no	O
Person	O
being	O
therein	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Michael	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Iron	O
Hoops	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Mackenzy	I-pers
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
July	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cane	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
returning	O
from	O
Transportation	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidences	O
against	O
him	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
continued	O
till	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Hackney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Franklin	I-pers
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Sheets	O
were	O
hung	O
out	O
in	O
an	O
Orchard	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Paget	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Furnace	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
,	O
affix	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Freehold	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	B-pers
Paget	I-pers
,	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
satisfactory	O
prov	O
'd	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Sarah	B-pers
Tinsley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.Dunstan	B-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
and	O
Clogs	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Beal	I-pers
,	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kingston	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
July	O
;	O
but	O
no-body	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Morley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bushel	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Wheaten	O
Flour	O
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Ibel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
20	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Wheaten	O
Flour	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Tull	I-pers
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Milton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Cheeseman	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
July	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Linnen	O
hung	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop-Window	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Pantry	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Hackney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
brown	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Stokes	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Horse	O
was	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pasture	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
early	O
the	O
same	O
Morning	O
kill	O
'd	O
and	O
stea	O
'd	O
at	O
Little-Heath	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Forest	O
,	O
in	O
Essex	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Miles	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
up	O
at	O
between	O
3	O
and	O
4	O
a-Clock	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
brought	O
a	O
Horse	O
for	O
the	O
Dogs	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
lay	O
by	O
the	O
Dog-Kennel	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Horse	O
kill	O
'd	O
;	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
why	O
he	O
kill	O
'd	O
such	O
a	O
Horse	O
?	O
and	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Owner	O
would	O
have	O
him	O
kill	O
'd	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
good	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
him	O
work	O
any	O
more	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Saunderson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
a	O
Box	O
of	O
Mathematical	O
Instruments	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hennessy	I-pers
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sheet	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Darney	I-pers
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
3d	O
time	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samnel	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
4th	O
time	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
5th	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Buckles	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
lodg	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
All	O
which	O
Facts	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
upon	O
each	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Little	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
,	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
his	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Foot-Boy	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
from	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Service	O
,	O
carrying	O
away	O
his	O
Livery	O
Cloaths	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
being	O
afterwards	O
apprehended	O
,	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Long	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Greenwood	I-pers
,	O
did	O
break	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
by	O
his	O
own	O
Confession	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Burglary	O
not	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Rountree	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchre	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Roger	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
Shop-Door	O
had	O
been	O
missing	O
for	O
several	O
Days	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
a-Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
unlock	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
apprehended	O
,	O
pretended	O
at	O
one	O
time	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Maid	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
another	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
for	O
3d	O
.	O
that	O
lay	O
upon	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Drink	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Persons	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Borket	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Ray	I-pers
,	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jane	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Theobalds	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Fireball	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
taking	O
2	O
Guineas	O
and	O
14	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Silver	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
Francis	B-pers
Billings	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
Day	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
July	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
having	O
been	O
at	O
Work	O
on	O
Shipboard	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
on	O
Shore	O
to	O
get	O
some	O
Drink	O
;	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Sign	B-place
of	I-place
the	I-place
Queens-Head	I-place
,	O
he	O
there	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
after	O
drinking	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Pints	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
invited	O
him	O
Home	O
to	O
her	O
Lodgings	O
:	O
that	O
going	O
with	O
her	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
when	O
he	O
awak	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
no-body	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
Company	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
having	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
Alehouse	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
follow	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
needs	O
force	O
himself	O
into	O
her	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
Home	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
he	O
would	O
needs	O
Lie	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
telling	O
her	O
,	O
Indeed	O
then	O
he	O
had	O
butlittle	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
her	O
amends	O
another	O
time	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
never	O
saw	O
but	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
of	O
Money	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
spent	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
gave	O
her	O
to	O
lie	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
Riding	O
St.	O
George	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
to	O
confirm	O
that	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
considering	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
might	O
possibly	O
lose	O
it	O
some	O
other	O
Way	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Edmund	B-pers
Rabbot	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
divers	O
Carpenters	O
Tools	O
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
stealing	O
of	O
the	O
Tools	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Burglary	O
not	O
being	O
made	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
they	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
latter	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
only	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Hannah	B-pers
Hatley	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Hartley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Can	O
and	O
other	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Plate	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Ascough	I-pers
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Sash-Window	O
being	O
open	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
might	O
see	O
the	O
Plate	O
standing	O
in	O
the	O
Bouffet	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
unlock	O
'd	O
the	O
Parlour-Door	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Plate	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
seen	O
by	O
two	O
Persons	O
at	O
Work	O
over-against	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
was	O
immediately	O
apprehended	O
with	O
the	O
Plate	O
in	O
her	O
Apron	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Parsons	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Hughs	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Piccard	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
thence	O
36	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
Stone	O
Rings	O
,	O
3	O
silver	O
Watches	O
,	O
several	O
pieces	O
of	O
silver	O
Plate	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
considerable	O
Value	O
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
her	O
House	O
was	O
fast	O
shut	O
at	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
a-Clock	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
broken	O
open	O
about	O
5	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
being	O
an	O
Auger	O
and	O
a	O
strong	O
short	O
Knife	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
she	O
shewing	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
Kemp	O
,	O
a	O
Relation	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
,	O
he	O
seem	O
'd	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
the	O
Knife	O
for	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
endeavour	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
some	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Owner	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
deliver	O
him	O
the	O
Knife	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
brought	O
it	O
back	O
,	O
telling	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
inform	O
'd	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Knife	O
.	O
Mr.Kemp	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
shewn	O
the	O
Knife	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
was	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
inform	O
'd	O
by	O
his	O
Daughter	O
Joanna	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
such	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
Knife	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
possession	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
come	O
one	O
Night	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Gravesend	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
displeased	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
entertain	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
knowing	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
disorderly	O
Person	O
.	O
Joanna	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
,	O
coming	O
to	O
their	O
House	O
was	O
whetting	O
that	O
Knife	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
an	O
uncommon	O
one	O
,	O
she	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
see	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
the	O
Knife	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
Knife	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
him	O
whetting	O
;	O
that	O
not	O
knowing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Habitation	O
,	O
they	O
enquir	O
'd	O
of	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Lewis	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
inform	O
'd	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
see	O
several	O
Things	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
of	O
her	O
Watches	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gerard	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Hoskins	O
and	O
Joanna	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
desiring	O
him	O
,	O
being	O
Constable	O
of	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
to	O
assist	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
apprehending	O
a	O
Felon	O
;	O
another	O
Constable	O
also	O
desiring	O
his	O
Assistance	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
desperate	O
Persons	O
;	O
that	O
accordingly	O
they	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
apprehend	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
did	O
seize	O
several	O
pieces	O
of	O
Plate	O
,	O
Watches	O
,	O
a	O
Child	O
's	O
Coral	O
,	O
Ring	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
;	O
that	O
carrying	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
before	O
Justice	O
Osbourn	O
,	O
he	O
committed	O
Joseph	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
to	O
New-Prison	O
;	O
that	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
was	O
resolutely	O
bent	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Newgate	O
with	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
saying	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
assisted	O
in	O
carrying	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
likewise	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
swore	O
,	O
That	O
if	O
ever	O
she	O
got	O
out	O
,	O
She	O
would	O
do	O
something	O
to	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
herself	O
in	O
a	O
Sessions	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
reveng	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
Persons	O
that	O
had	O
betray	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
one	O
being	O
his	O
Uncle	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
is	O
Cousin	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Hoskins	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
Joanna	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
they	O
being	O
shewn	O
the	O
House	O
by	O
another	O
Woman	O
;	O
that	O
being	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
pulling	O
out	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
buy	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
,	O
took	O
change	O
with	O
him	O
another	O
Watch	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
afterwards	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
of	O
those	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
lost	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
with	O
the	O
Constable	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
apprehend	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
sound	O
divers	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
his	O
Room	O
and	O
the	O
Plate	O
was	O
wrapp	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Great	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
cover	O
'd	O
with	O
a	O
Rug	O
;	O
that	O
upon	O
this	O
Joseph	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
;	O
but	O
desir	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
use	O
him	O
handsomely	O
.	O
Josiah	B-pers
Charding	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
asking	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
how	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
?	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
no	O
Person	O
else	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
so	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Joseph	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
had	O
nothing	O
material	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Defence	O
;	O
but	O
insisted	O
upon	O
having	O
about	O
6l	O
.	O
that	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
when	O
apprehended	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
pretended	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
Money	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
not	O
proving	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
rather	O
appearing	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
rais	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Sale	O
of	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Rings	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
stolen	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
granted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
,	O
she	O
pleaded	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
them	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Uncle	O
-	O
Kemp	O
,	O
and	O
invested	O
against	O
Joanna	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
and	O
Mr.	O
Hoskins	O
for	O
betraying	O
them	O
,	O
coming	O
to	O
their	O
House	O
pretending	O
to	O
be	O
Sweethearts	O
;	O
which	O
,	O
if	O
true	O
,	O
could	O
be	O
of	O
no	O
avail	O
,	O
Upon	O
a	O
full	O
Hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
Joseph	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
But	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
as	O
acting	O
under	O
the	O
Direction	O
and	O
Power	O
of	O
her	O
Husband	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
bringing	O
in	O
this	O
Verdict	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
very	O
pressingly	O
insisted	O
upon	O
being	O
brought	O
in	O
Guilty	O
,	O
affirming	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
equally	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
Hang	B-pers
'd	I-pers
with	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Court	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
meet	O
to	O
gratifie	O
her	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
,	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
depo	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Doors	O
and	O
Windows	O
were	O
made	O
fast	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
a-Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
House	O
broken	O
open	O
between	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
John	B-pers
Knap	I-pers
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
making	O
himself	O
a	O
voluntary	O
Evidence	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
give	O
him	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
4	O
Burglaries	O
and	O
Roberies	O
committed	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
himself	O
,	O
one	O
at	O
Westminster	O
,	O
one	O
in	O
Spittle-Fields	O
,	O
one	O
in	O
Goodman's-Fields	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
in	O
Oldstreet	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Knap	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
himself	O
was	O
present	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
committing	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
as	O
producing	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
confirming	O
his	O
Evidence	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
also	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
3d	O
time	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Paget	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
Plate	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
great	O
Value	O
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
John	B-pers
Knap	I-pers
before-mention	O
'd	O
;	O
whose	O
Evidence	O
being	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
other	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
likewise	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
;	O
which	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Holden	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Holden	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Edging	I-pers
;	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Bruise	O
or	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
Stomach	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
;	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Holden	I-pers
being	O
present	O
,	O
aiding	O
,	O
abetting	O
,	O
comforting	O
,	O
and	O
assisting	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Murther	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
John	B-pers
Edging	I-pers
,	O
having	O
been	O
at	O
Work	O
,	O
turning	O
some	O
Corn	O
on	O
Board	O
of	O
Ship	O
,	O
came	O
on	O
Shore	O
with	O
a	O
Flask	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
to	O
get	O
some	O
Drink	O
;	O
that	O
two	O
Boys	O
being	O
fighting	O
on	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
one	O
taking	O
the	O
Part	O
of	O
one	O
Boy	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
that	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
it	O
occasion	O
'd	O
some	O
Words	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
receiv	O
'd	O
a	O
Blow	O
on	O
the	O
Face	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Holden	I-pers
;	O
and	O
that	O
after	O
this	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
complaining	O
it	O
was	O
hard	O
he	O
must	O
receive	O
such	O
Usage	O
for	O
nothing	O
,	O
offering	O
to	O
pull	O
of	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
(	O
as	O
was	O
suppos	O
'd	O
)	O
to	O
fight	O
,	O
the	O
John	B-pers
Holden	I-pers
,	O
while	O
his	O
Arms	O
were	O
extended	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
pull	O
of	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Holden	I-pers
,	O
while	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
in	O
this	O
Posture	O
,	O
did	O
with	O
great	O
Violence	O
give	O
him	O
several	O
Punches	O
on	O
the	O
lower	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Stomach	O
with	O
his	O
Knockles	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
fetch	O
'd	O
one	O
Groan	O
and	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
his	O
side	O
Produc	O
'd	O
some	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
did	O
close	O
in	O
with	O
him	O
immediately	O
before	O
his	O
falling	O
down	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
after	O
a	O
Struggle	O
he	O
fell	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Holden	I-pers
,	O
with	O
great	O
Violence	O
fell	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
thence	O
would	O
infer	O
that	O
his	O
Death	O
was	O
caus	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Fall	O
,	O
rather	O
then	O
by	O
the	O
Blows	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
Circumstance	O
of	O
his	O
closing	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
struggling	O
before	O
the	O
Fall	O
,	O
was	O
not	O
observ	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Boswell	O
,	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
call	O
'd	O
,	O
did	O
bleed	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
he	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
great	O
Bruises	O
,	O
which	O
turned	O
Black	O
on	O
the	O
Pit	O
of	O
his	O
Stomach	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
believe	O
the	O
Blows	O
might	O
be	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
Upon	O
a	O
full	O
Hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
John	B-pers
Holden	I-pers
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
Thomas	B-pers
Holden	I-pers
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Oakley	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Groves	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
l.	O
a	O
Chain	O
and	O
2	O
Seals	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Wilkins	I-pers
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
himself	O
and	O
one	O
Jackson	O
having	O
been	O
early	O
that	O
Morning	O
at	O
New	O
Tunbridge-Wells	O
,	O
were	O
returning	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.Jackson	O
proposing	O
the	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
his	O
Aunt	O
,	O
(	O
as	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
her	O
)	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
inform	O
'd	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
her	O
in	O
Bed	O
with	O
her	O
Husband	O
(	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
)	O
he	O
was	O
for	O
going	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
desir	O
'd	O
they	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
neighbouring	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
come	O
to	O
them	O
immediately	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
directed	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
drinking	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
come	O
again	O
presently	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
several	O
times	O
;	O
that	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
together	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
speak	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
Jackson	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
refused	O
;	O
that	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
gone	O
out	O
twice	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
Fob	O
;	O
but	O
afterwards	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
his	O
Hands	O
on	O
her	O
Shoulders	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
after	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
Company	O
but	O
she	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Jackson	O
;	O
that	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
must	O
go	O
to	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
it	O
unkindly	O
that	O
she	O
staid	O
so	O
long	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
return	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
waited	O
expecting	O
her	O
Return	O
,	O
she	O
having	O
been	O
as	O
good	O
as	O
her	O
Word	O
in	O
returning	O
several	O
times	O
before	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
not	O
returning	O
,	O
he	O
felt	O
for	O
his	O
Watch	O
and	O
Money	O
;	O
that	O
thereupon	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
search	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
found	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
her	O
having	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
entrusted	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Hands	O
of	O
a	O
false	O
Friend	O
(	O
which	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
as	O
he	O
supposed	O
,	O
one	O
Cutbert	O
a	O
Clergyman	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
for	O
her	O
Husband	O
)	O
and	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
had	O
under	O
2	O
Guineas	O
;	O
that	O
upon	O
applying	O
to	O
her	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
Enquiry	O
,	O
found	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
pawn	O
'd	O
for	O
5	O
Guineas	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Cutbert	O
:	O
Application	O
was	O
also	O
made	O
to	O
Cutbert	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
procure	O
the	O
Watch	O
upon	O
advancing	O
5	O
Guineas	O
to	O
redeem	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
and	O
would	O
give	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
a	O
Note	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
for	O
Payment	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Skelton	O
should	O
be	O
join	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Note	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
2	O
Seals	O
should	O
be	O
delivered	O
as	O
a	O
Token	O
to	O
fetch	O
the	O
Watch	O
by	O
:	O
The	O
Watch	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
a	O
Pawn-Brokers	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
laid	O
by	O
a	O
Clergyman	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Jones	O
.	O
The	O
Watch	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
he	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
as	O
to	O
what	O
pass	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
Roger	B-pers
Downs	I-pers
as	O
to	O
the	O
Offers	O
of	O
the	O
Watch	O
being	O
restor	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
her	O
having	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
but	O
pleaded	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
call	O
'd	O
her	O
from	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
having	O
Money	O
,	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Watch	O
to	O
pawn	O
for	O
the	O
Use	O
of	O
her	O
Body	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
after	O
a	O
full	O
Hearing	O
,	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Hill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
from	O
Robert	B-pers
Feniel	I-pers
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
July	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bartholomew	I-place
's	I-place
Exchange	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
4	O
silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Thornhil	I-pers
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Mother	O
being	O
House-keeper	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Thornhil	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
with	O
the	O
Family	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
left	O
at	O
London	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
recommended	O
to	O
her	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
Master	O
Mr.	O
Thornhils	O
Clerks	O
,	O
to	O
tell	O
her	O
her	O
Fortune	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
various	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
deluded	O
her	O
,	O
with	O
Pretences	O
to	O
help	O
her	O
to	O
great	O
Fortunes	O
,	O
and	O
giving	O
her	O
some	O
Papers	O
to	O
wear	O
as	O
Charms	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
that	O
means	O
had	O
from	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
8	O
or	O
9	O
l.	O
which	O
was	O
Money	O
left	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
defray	O
the	O
Expenses	O
of	O
the	O
Family	O
;	O
that	O
coming	O
again	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
she	O
wanted	O
more	O
Money	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
telling	O
her	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
more	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Spoons	O
lying	O
upon	O
the	O
Desk	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
them	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
,	O
this	O
Witness	O
,	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
must	O
not	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
Master	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
part	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
notwithstanding	O
,	O
she	O
carried	O
them	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
after	O
her	O
for	O
the	O
Spoons	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
her	O
have	O
them	O
,	O
telling	O
her	O
,	O
since	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
such	O
good	O
fortune	O
,	O
what	O
need	O
she	O
value	O
Spoons	O
or	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
?	O
and	O
advis	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
beyond-Sea	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Waller	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Bashaw	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Damask	O
silk	O
Gowns	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
missing	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
suspected	O
to	O
have	O
stolen	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
sufficient	O
proof	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
made	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
having	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Wills	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Webb	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
Silk	O
,	O
Linen	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Prudom	I-pers
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
pack	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
to	O
a	O
Carter	O
to	O
be	O
convey	O
'd	O
to	O
Hampstead	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Cart	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
afterwards	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Kentstreet	O
,	O
who	O
could	O
give	O
no	O
better	O
Account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
than	O
that	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Stranger	O
,	O
met	O
him	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
and	O
promis	O
'd	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
Shilling	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
to	O
Kentstreet	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
come	O
there	O
,	O
ran	O
away	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
appearing	O
but	O
a	O
Newgate	O
Plea	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
himself	O
did	O
not	O
carry	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
Kentstreet	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
by	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
the	O
Man	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
he	O
set	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
to	O
pay	O
2	O
d.	O
for	O
bringing	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Susannah	B-pers
Frazier	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Abchurch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
and	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Necklace	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
July	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
being	O
a	O
Girl	O
of	O
about	O
5	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
had	O
the	O
Necklace	O
cut	O
and	O
taken	O
from	O
her	O
Neck	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
out	O
of	O
Place	O
,	O
did	O
lodge	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
both	O
together	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Warwick	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
Seeing	O
the	O
Child	O
there	O
with	O
a	O
Gold	O
Necklace	O
and	O
Locket	O
about	O
its	O
Neck	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
swore	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
thither	O
again	O
and	O
drank	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
drank	O
within	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
and	O
sat	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
sitting	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
Child	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
going	O
into	O
an	O
Alley	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
immediately	O
follow	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
follow	O
'd	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
Necklace	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
while	O
she	O
kiss	O
'd	O
the	O
Child	O
to	O
quiet	O
it	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
Evidences	O
that	O
saw	O
them	O
with	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
both	O
running	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Child	O
crying	O
O	O
my	O
Necklace	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
pursued	O
them	O
running	O
from	O
Sherbourn-Lane	B-place
to	O
Finch-Lane	O
,	O
where	O
being	O
both	O
apprehended	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
some	O
Distance	O
the	O
one	O
from	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
the	O
foremost	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
by	O
many	O
Yards	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Necklace	O
being	O
found	O
thrown	O
away	O
near	O
or	O
behind	O
some	O
Shutters	O
of	O
a	O
Barber	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Spread-Eagle	O
Court	O
,	O
where	O
Mary	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
could	O
not	O
convey	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
must	O
:	O
This	O
bringing	O
the	O
Fact	O
home	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Barton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.Dunstan	B-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Amos	I-pers
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Edgerton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
of	O
Christchurch	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
5l	O
.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jolly	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
herself	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Churchyard	O
the	O
Night	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
they	O
met	O
with	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
who	O
ask	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Wine	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Salutation	B-place
Tavern	I-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bid	O
her	O
make	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
her	O
Way	O
,	O
telling	O
her	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
Watch	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
go	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
staying	O
,	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
got	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
one	O
Walter	B-pers
James	I-pers
put	O
the	O
Watch	O
into	O
his	O
Hands	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
stolen	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jolly	I-pers
,	O
or	O
one	O
of	O
those	O
Women	O
had	O
stolen	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
did	O
not	O
Think	O
fit	O
to	O
appear	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
but	O
that	O
of	O
Elizabeth	O
Jolly	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Coombs	I-pers
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
which	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
She	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Stubbins	I-pers
;	O
which	O
Fact	O
being	O
also	O
prov	O
'd	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
She	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
a	O
3d	O
time	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Bowdry	I-pers
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Wileman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Pancrass	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Hucks	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
Chain	O
,	O
and	O
Seals	O
,	O
value	O
24	O
l.	O
and	O
one	O
Guinea	O
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
his	O
Chariot	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Bottom	O
of	O
Highgate-Hill	B-place
,	O
about	O
5	O
a-Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
by	O
2	O
Persons	O
on	O
Horseback	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
verily	O
believe	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
put	O
a	O
Pistol	O
into	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
more	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
take	O
your	O
Word	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Doyle	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
himself	O
committed	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
up	O
Figtree-Lane	O
towards	O
Hampstead	O
;	O
that	O
meeting	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
Wileman	O
said	O
,	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
has	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
immediately	O
rode	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
stopp	O
'd	O
the	O
Chariot	O
,	O
he	O
keeping	O
then	O
at	O
some	O
Distance	O
from	O
it	O
till	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Watch	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
riding	O
up	O
,	O
went	O
on	O
the	O
contrary	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Chariot	O
to	O
that	O
which	O
Wileman	O
was	O
;	O
that	O
Wileman	O
had	O
then	O
on	O
a	O
dark-colour	O
'd	O
Rug-Coat	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hucks	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
agreed	O
with	O
Doyle	O
's	O
Description	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
be	O
sure	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
?	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
verily	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Man	O
;	O
that	O
indeed	O
the	O
lower	O
Part	O
of	O
his	O
Face	O
was	O
muffled	O
up	O
by	O
his	O
Cape	O
being	O
button	O
'd	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
take	O
particular	O
Notice	O
of	O
the	O
upper	O
Part	O
of	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
taking	O
his	O
Watch	O
and	O
Money	O
his	O
Cape	O
slipp	O
'd	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
seen	O
'd	O
something	O
disorder	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
his	O
Pistol	O
drop	O
while	O
he	O
put	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
mean	O
while	O
he	O
observ	O
'd	O
him	O
very	O
earnestly	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
more	O
he	O
now	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
more	O
he	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
Opinion	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Doyle	I-pers
added	O
,	O
That	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
committed	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
they	O
returned	O
to	O
London	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
give	O
Wileman	O
5	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
for	O
his	O
Share	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
take	O
5	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Wileman	O
for	O
his	O
Share	O
;	O
that	O
Wileman	O
chose	O
to	O
take	O
5	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
pleaded	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
being	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
sick	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
some	O
Evidences	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
Days	O
before	O
Christmass	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sitting	O
over	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Blanket	O
at	O
the	O
Back	O
of	O
the	O
Chair	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Buckley	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
a	O
Woman	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
complain	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
Want	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
this	O
was	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
after	O
Christmass	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
about	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
Days	O
before	O
Christmass-Day	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
ill	O
,	O
had	O
a	O
Looseness	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
a	O
Blanket	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
sitting	O
before	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
he	O
thought	O
it	O
likely	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
he	O
clapp	O
'd	O
.	O
Some	O
Persons	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
so	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Wileman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
for	O
assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Bridges	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
a	O
Pocket-Book	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Bank-Note	O
of	O
20	O
l.	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
Esquire	O
Bridges	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
before	O
mention	O
'd	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Doyle	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
a	O
Week	O
or	O
10	O
Days	O
before	O
Christmass	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
himself	O
went	O
to	O
Highgate	B-place
to	O
rob	O
,	O
and	O
meeting	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
did	O
take	O
from	O
him	O
the	O
things	O
before-mention	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
one	O
being	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
Bedford-Row	O
she	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Wileman	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
Doyle	O
together	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
Booted	O
and	O
Spurr	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
both	O
very	O
dirty	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
large	O
Hat	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Whip	O
;	O
that	O
,	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
she	O
can	O
remember	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
17th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
Week	O
before	O
Christmass	O
;	O
that	O
Doyle	O
enquiring	O
of	O
her	O
concerning	O
a	O
young	O
Woman	O
of	O
their	O
Acquaintance	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stood	O
at	O
a	O
little	O
Distance	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
talking	O
together	O
;	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
Paper	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
reading	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
Doyle	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
20	O
l.	O
Note	O
;	O
Doyle	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
Bank	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
let	O
him	O
see	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
shew	O
'd	O
it	O
him	O
;	O
when	O
Doyle	O
had	O
read	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
folded	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
It	O
is	O
as	O
good	O
Money	O
as	O
any	O
in	O
England	O
;	O
that	O
Doyle	O
having	O
also	O
a	O
Belt	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
wip	O
'd	O
it	O
with	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
it	O
was	O
Gold	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
to	O
his	O
Coat-Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
her	O
,	O
this	O
Evidence	O
,	O
look	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
slipt	O
it	O
by	O
somewhere	O
about	O
his	O
Side	O
.	O
Being	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
she	O
knew	O
the	O
Note	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
hearing	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Bank	O
Note	O
,	O
she	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
it	O
,	O
never	O
having	O
seen	O
one	O
before	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
might	O
know	O
one	O
when	O
she	O
saw	O
it	O
again	O
;	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
shewn	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
Notice	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
Picture	O
of	O
a	O
Woman	O
in	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Bank-Note	O
being	O
shewn	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
believe	O
that	O
to	O
be	O
it	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
read	O
the	O
Name	O
Woollaston	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
and	O
stood	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
off	O
,	O
seeming	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
haste	O
,	O
while	O
Doyle	O
was	O
talking	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
Wileman	O
calling	O
him	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
stay	O
,	O
he	O
,	O
Doyle	O
,	O
answer	O
'd	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
towards	O
Holbourn	O
.	O
Arabella	B-pers
Manning	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
about	O
a	O
Week	O
or	O
8	O
Days	O
before	O
Christmass	O
,	O
at	O
about	O
8	O
or	O
9	O
a-Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
she	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Doyle	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
;	O
that	O
Wileman	O
had	O
a	O
Hat	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
uncock	O
'd	O
and	O
dirty	O
.	O
which	O
Doyle	O
said	O
was	O
not	O
worth	O
taking	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Dram	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
drop	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Paper	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
If	O
he	O
lost	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
loss	O
20	O
l.	O
That	O
she	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
look	O
at	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
one	O
Gordon	O
,	O
a	O
Butcher	O
,	O
a	O
tall	O
Man	O
,	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
looking	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
Doyle	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Wileman	I-pers
had	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
together	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
appointed	O
to	O
meet	O
together	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
at	O
10	O
a-Clock	O
,	O
whisper	O
'd	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
had	O
never	O
seen	O
him	O
till	O
Doyle	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
Newgate	O
with	O
a	O
Straw-Hat	O
on	O
;	O
and	O
objected	O
against	O
the	O
Credit	O
of	O
Arabella	B-pers
Manning	I-pers
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
one	O
Ann	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
heard	O
Doyle	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
reveng	O
'd	O
on	O
Wileman	O
for	O
threatening	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
Wife	O
up	O
for	O
returning	O
from	O
Transportation	O
:	O
He	O
also	O
call	O
'd	O
some	O
Evidence	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
knew	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Ill	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
also	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Barnelly	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Thomas	B-pers
Southgate	I-pers
near	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
and	O
violently	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
9	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
number	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
22d	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
11	O
a-Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Forenoon	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
between	O
Newington-Green	B-place
and	O
Newington	B-place
Church	I-place
;	O
that	O
meeting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
pasting	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
stopp	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
pulling	O
out	O
a	O
Shoemaker	O
's	O
Knife	O
,	O
swore	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
violent	O
manner	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
him	O
his	O
Money	O
he	O
would	O
stab	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
no-body	O
being	O
near	O
to	O
assist	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
3	O
Half-Crowns	O
,	O
a	O
Shilling	O
,	O
and	O
3d	O
.	O
in	O
Halfpence	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
no	O
Defence	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
standing	O
as	O
unconcern	O
'd	O
as	O
to	O
what	O
the	O
Evidence	O
swore	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
heard	O
or	O
understood	O
them	O
,	O
staring	O
now	O
this	O
way	O
,	O
now	O
that	O
way	O
with	O
a	O
wild	O
Air	O
in	O
his	O
Counternance	O
,	O
would	O
make	O
no	O
Answer	O
to	O
any	O
thing	O
was	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Keepers	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
that	O
stood	O
by	O
,	O
but	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
like	O
;	O
but	O
several	O
Persons	O
appear	O
'd	O
on	O
his	O
Behalf	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Member	O
of	O
a	O
Club	O
or	O
Society	O
,	O
who	O
being	O
inform	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
disorder	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
Mind	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
pay	O
him	O
a	O
Weekly	O
Allowance	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
contriving	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
into	O
Bedlam	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
Depositions	O
of	O
other	O
Persons	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Oddness	O
of	O
his	O
Behaviour	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
of	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
Non	O
compos	O
mentis	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Cluff	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
Try	O
'd	O
upon	O
an	O
Appeal	O
lodg	O
'd	O
against	O
him	O
last	O
April	O
Sessions	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Appellant	O
John	O
Green	O
,	O
Heir	O
and	O
Brother	O
of	O
Mary	O
Green	O
after	O
his	O
being	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
the	O
11th	O
Day	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
Appellant	O
having	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
cause	O
,	O
supported	O
the	O
Charge	O
by	O
the	O
following	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Diana	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
were	O
both	O
Servant	O
s	O
to	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
2	O
a-Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
by	O
her	O
with	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
next	O
Door	O
;	O
that	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
10	O
Minutes	O
before	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
had	O
also	O
been	O
at	O
Dinner	O
about	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
before	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
,	O
this	O
Evidence	O
,	O
was	O
walking	O
about	O
the	O
Tap-Room	O
with	O
her	O
Child	O
in	O
her	O
Arms	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
2	O
Men	O
coming	O
in	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
to	O
draw	O
them	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
one	O
Pint	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
for	O
herself	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
carried	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
Dinner	O
:	O
This	O
Evidence	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
any	O
Knife	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
,	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
She	O
saw	O
none	O
:	O
That	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
carried	O
out	O
some	O
Drink	O
,	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
and	O
went	O
directly	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
Mary	O
Green	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
4	O
Minutes	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
Madam	O
,	O
pray	O
come	O
here	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
immediately	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
open	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Floor	O
,	O
sitting	O
on	O
her	O
Backside	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
holding	O
her	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
the	O
Blood	O
running	O
from	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
Quantity	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Lord	O
,	O
James	O
!	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
done	O
?	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
Nothing	O
,	O
Madam	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
said	O
again	O
,	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
her	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
herself	O
?	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
No	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
saw	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
did	O
neither	O
speak	O
nor	O
move	O
,	O
and	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
dead	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
very	O
much	O
affrighted	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
ran	O
for	O
an	O
Apothecary	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Counsel	O
ask	O
'd	O
this	O
Evidence	O
what	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
Box	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
far	O
from	O
her	O
?	O
and	O
if	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
any	O
Noise	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
heard	O
it	O
?	O
She	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
far	O
from	O
the	O
Bar	O
;	O
was	O
open	O
about	O
a	O
Yard	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
from	O
the	O
Ceiling	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
heard	O
no	O
Noise	O
,	O
and	O
must	O
,	O
had	O
there	O
been	O
any	O
made	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
walking	O
about	O
near	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
House	O
being	O
still	O
:	O
She	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
Temper	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
in	O
that	O
Forenoon	O
?	O
She	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
chearful	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
8	O
or	O
9	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Forenoon	O
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
there	O
came	O
a	O
Man	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
that	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Girl	O
(	O
Mary	O
Green	O
)	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
sat	O
down	O
at	O
a	O
Table	O
near	O
the	O
Bar	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
having	O
been	O
washing	O
Rooms	O
above-Stairs	O
,	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
did	O
?	O
and	O
she	O
sat	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
drink	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
having	O
trundled	O
her	O
Mop	O
,	O
went	O
up	O
Stair	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
sat	O
down	O
with	O
him	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
reach	O
'd	O
over	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
and	O
either	O
kiss	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
or	O
whisper	O
'd	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
seem	O
'd	O
not	O
to	O
like	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
ruffled	O
;	O
and	O
tho	O
'	O
the	O
table	O
had	O
been	O
wash	O
'd	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
before	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
Dish-clout	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
to	O
wiping	O
it	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
there	O
did	O
not	O
seem	O
to	O
be	O
any	O
Occasion	O
;	O
that	O
afterwards	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
having	O
din	O
'd	O
,	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Saunders	O
,	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
asking	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
din	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
replying	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
him	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Mutton	O
Pasty	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
set	O
by	O
in	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
accepted	O
the	O
Offer	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
drew	O
2	O
Pints	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
one	O
for	O
a	O
Customer	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
for	O
her	O
own	O
Dinner	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Box	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
then	O
gone	O
to	O
carry	O
out	O
some	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
coming	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Box	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
throwing	O
the	O
Door	O
with	O
an	O
uncommon	O
Violence	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
this	O
Evidence	O
,	O
being	O
fitting	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Saunders	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
4	O
Minutes	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
calling	O
out	O
to	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
before	O
related	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
calling	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
immediately	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
lying	O
as	O
has	O
been	O
before	O
depos	O
'd	O
by	O
his	O
Wife	O
;	O
that	O
asking	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
how	O
it	O
came	O
,	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Villain	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
should	O
give	O
an	O
Account	O
for	O
it	O
before	O
they	O
parted	O
.	O
Being	O
asked	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Knife	O
,	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
saw	O
her	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
with	O
two	O
Pots	O
in	O
her	O
Hands	O
,	O
and	O
come	O
up	O
again	O
with	O
two	O
Pints	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
Knife	O
,	O
for	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
have	O
seen	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
afterwards	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
view	O
'd	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
any	O
Blood	O
,	O
not	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
one	O
Drop	O
,	O
He	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
Temper	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
in	O
that	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Day	O
,	O
before	O
this	O
Accident	O
?	O
He	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
She	O
was	O
Singing	O
and	O
merry	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
doing	O
her	O
Business	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
having	O
come	O
from	O
the	O
South-Sea	O
House	O
,	O
be	O
call	O
'd	O
at	O
Mr	O
.	O
Pain	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
there	O
dine	O
,	O
as	O
had	O
been	O
before	O
depos	O
'd	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
(	O
he	O
suppos	O
'd	O
at	O
Dinner	O
)	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
having	O
sent	O
for	O
some	O
Drink	O
,	O
he	O
carried	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Country	O
Men	O
coming	O
in	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
went	O
down	O
for	O
two	O
Pints	O
of	O
Drink	O
,	O
one	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
herself	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
no	O
Knife	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
;	O
that	O
upon	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Pain	O
's	O
calling	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Pain	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
lying	O
,	O
as	O
before-mentioned	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
one	O
Hand	O
under	O
her	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
Stone	O
Dead	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
how	O
it	O
happen	O
'd	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
leaning	O
her	O
Head	O
upon	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
James	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
dead	O
Woman	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
asking	O
her	O
how	O
it	O
came	O
,	O
she	O
fell	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
This	O
Evidence	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
how	O
long	O
it	O
was	O
from	O
the	O
Time	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
calling	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Pain	O
?	O
He	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
It	O
was	O
about	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Minutes	O
;	O
he	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Print	O
over	O
her	O
Left	O
Ear	O
.	O
Being	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
he	O
heard	O
any	O
Noise	O
while	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
?	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
near	O
that	O
had	O
there	O
been	O
any	O
made	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
have	O
heard	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.Cox	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
about	O
two	O
a-Clock	O
that	O
Day	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
lying	O
upon	O
her	O
Back	O
,	O
her	O
Head	O
supported	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
vast	O
Effution	O
of	O
Blood	O
under	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
thought	O
he	O
did	O
perceive	O
her	O
Lips	O
to	O
change	O
a	O
little	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
;	O
but	O
where	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
Appearance	O
of	O
Life	O
;	O
that	O
turning	O
up	O
her	O
Coats	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Wound	O
in	O
the	O
upper	O
Part	O
of	O
her	O
Thigh	O
;	O
that	O
looking	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
Knife	O
lying	O
among	O
the	O
other	O
Knives	O
,	O
having	O
a	O
little	O
Blood	O
on	O
the	O
Point	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Knife	O
lay	O
with	O
the	O
Handle	O
to	O
the	O
Chimney	O
,	O
about	O
4	O
Foot	O
from	O
where	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
:	O
He	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
supposing	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
herself	O
the	O
Wound	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
afterwards	O
having	O
laid	O
or	O
toss	O
'd	O
the	O
Knife	O
there	O
in	O
the	O
Manner	O
it	O
was	O
laid	O
?	O
He	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
thought	O
not	O
,	O
without	O
a	O
Miracle	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
afterwards	O
examin	O
'd	O
the	O
Wound	O
,	O
comparing	O
it	O
with	O
the	O
Knife	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
had	O
gone	O
5	O
Inches	O
into	O
the	O
Thigh	O
;	O
that	O
it	O
had	O
gone	O
obliquely	O
upwards	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
open	O
'd	O
or	O
divided	O
the	O
Femoral	O
Artery	O
:	O
Being	O
ask	O
'd	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Wound	O
?	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
such	O
,	O
that	O
no	O
Person	O
after	O
such	O
a	O
Wound	O
could	O
live	O
more	O
than	O
a	O
Minute	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
or	O
two	O
Minutes	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
compar	O
'd	O
the	O
Knife	O
with	O
the	O
Cuts	O
in	O
the	O
Deceas'd	O
's	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
answer	O
'd	O
to	O
them	O
exactly	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Wound	O
must	O
needs	O
be	O
given	O
with	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
Force	O
,	O
the	O
Knife	O
being	O
a	O
broad	O
round-pointed	O
Knife	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
gone	O
through	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
a	O
thick	O
quilted	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
coarse	O
strong	O
Shift	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
of	O
Opinion	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
possible	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
could	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
herself	O
:	O
Being	O
ask	O
'd	O
as	O
to	O
what	O
other	O
Marks	O
of	O
Violence	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
Notice	O
of	O
?	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
observe	O
some	O
Marks	O
about	O
her	O
Chin	O
and	O
Left	O
Ear	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
made	O
by	O
the	O
Compression	O
of	O
the	O
Thumb	O
and	O
Fingers	O
,	O
that	O
appear	O
'd	O
livid	O
;	O
that	O
her	O
Left	O
Ear	O
was	O
all	O
contused	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
he	O
must	O
have	O
confin	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
with	O
his	O
left	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
given	O
the	O
Wound	O
with	O
his	O
Right	O
.	O
The	O
Cloaths	O
and	O
Knife	O
were	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Dennis	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
with	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Nature	O
of	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
such	O
,	O
that	O
no	O
Animal	O
could	O
live	O
above	O
2	O
Minute	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
after	O
that	O
Artery	O
had	O
been	O
open	O
'd	O
or	O
divided	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
try	O
'd	O
the	O
Experiment	O
on	O
a	O
Dog	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
dy	O
'd	O
in	O
a	O
Minute	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
;	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
impossible	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
could	O
have	O
given	O
herself	O
the	O
Wound	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
because	O
afterwards	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
move	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
one	O
Step	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
also	O
saw	O
the	O
Marks	O
of	O
Violence	O
before	O
mention	O
'd	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
suppos	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
by	O
a	O
Hand	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
had	O
there	O
not	O
been	O
a	O
Compression	O
by	O
Violence	O
,	O
the	O
Blood	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
there	O
stagnated	O
;	O
because	O
such	O
a	O
Wound	O
being	O
receiv	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Blood	O
flows	O
with	O
so	O
great	O
Impetuosity	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
of	O
Opinion	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
could	O
not	O
possibly	O
lay	O
the	O
Knife	O
where	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
found	O
lying	O
,	O
because	O
a	O
Person	O
having	O
receiv	O
'd	O
such	O
a	O
Wound	O
,	O
falls	O
immediately	O
into	O
Convulsions	O
,	O
and	O
grows	O
insensible	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Baldwin	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
being	O
at	O
Mr	O
.	O
Pain	O
's	O
about	O
9	O
a-Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Forenoon	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
eating	O
Roll	O
and	O
Cheese	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchin	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Discourse	O
passing	O
amongst	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
of	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
She	O
knows	O
what	O
's	O
what	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
a	O
Bastard	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up-stairs	O
;	O
that	O
coming	O
down	O
soon	O
after	O
,	O
she	O
wanted	O
Tea	O
and	O
Sugar	O
for	O
her	O
Mistress	O
,	O
and	O
Mr	O
.	O
Pain	O
being	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
,	O
and	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
said	O
,	O
He	O
was	O
always	O
out	O
when	O
most	O
wanted	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
puddling	O
with	O
the	O
Poker	O
,	O
struck	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Backside	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
Sawcy	O
Slut	O
must	O
my	O
Master	O
give	O
you	O
an	O
Account	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
thought	O
he	O
look	O
'd	O
maliciously	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
thereupon	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
push	O
'd	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
strike	O
me	O
for	O
?	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
thought	O
him	O
an	O
ill-natur	O
'd	O
Fellow	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Duncarton	I-pers
,	O
Mrs.	O
Groves	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Mother	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
Evidence	O
upon	O
the	O
former	O
Trial	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
several	O
times	O
us	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
ill	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
now	O
give	O
their	O
Evidence	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
in	O
Court	O
ready	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
some	O
Persons	O
who	O
us	O
'd	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
to	O
his	O
civil	O
Behaviour	O
towards	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Counsel	O
pleaded	O
strenuously	O
on	O
Behalf	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
remarking	O
on	O
the	O
Testimony	O
of	O
the	O
Appellant	O
's	O
Witness	O
whatsoever	O
they	O
thought	O
might	O
make	O
to	O
the	O
Advantage	O
of	O
the	O
Appellee	O
;	O
not	O
withstanding	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
upon	O
a	O
mature	O
Deliberation	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Murther	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Appellant	O
came	O
into	O
Court	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
when	O
Sentence	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
pass	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
Convicts	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
Judgment	O
on	O
the	O
Appellee	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
accordingly	O
pronounced	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
12	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
the	O
1st	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
walking	O
in	O
Bridges-street	B-place
,	O
near	O
the	O
Playhouse	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
clapp	O
'd	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
round	O
the	O
Waist	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
lie	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
he	O
must	O
do	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
pulling	O
up	O
the	O
Bottom	O
of	O
her	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
laid	O
them	O
before	O
his	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
she	O
held	O
them	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
felt	O
her	O
Hand	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Money	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
her	O
Lodging	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
it	O
should	O
cost	O
him	O
no	O
more	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Design	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Watch	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
met	O
her	O
,	O
was	O
very	O
rude	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
lain	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
because	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
he	O
threatned	O
to	O
swear	O
a	O
Robbery	O
against	O
her	O
.	O
There	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Page	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Gibbs	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Iron	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Smither	I-pers
,	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
Page	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
but	O
acquitted	O
Gibbs	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bambridge	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Warden	O
of	O
the	O
Fleet	O
Prison	O
,	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
his	O
Trial	O
,	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Attorney-General	O
,	O
Solicitor	O
,	O
Counsel	O
,	O
and	O
Evidences	O
,	O
being	O
all	O
present	O
,	O
ready	O
to	O
proceed	O
on	O
the	O
Trial	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
objecting	O
against	O
being	O
Try	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Baron	O
Thompson	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Baron	O
himself	O
signifying	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
Reluctance	O
in	O
his	O
Mind	O
against	O
sitting	O
as	O
Judge	O
on	O
the	O
Trial	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
against	O
whom	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
suppos	O
'd	O
to	O
have	O
entertain	O
'd	O
some	O
Prejudices	O
,	O
and	O
consequently	O
not	O
be	O
an	O
impartial	O
Judge	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Member	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Commons	O
,	O
a	O
Committee	O
of	O
which	O
House	O
were	O
his	O
Prosecutors	O
;	O
and	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
Twelve	O
Judges	O
being	O
in	O
Town	O
,	O
they	O
being	O
gone	O
the	O
Circuits	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
adjourn	O
'd	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
his	O
Trial	O
on	O
Monday	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
July	O
;	O
accordingly	O
on	O
Monday	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
July	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bambridge	I-pers
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Attorney-General	O
,	O
Counsel	O
,	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
were	O
all	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
ready	O
;	O
but	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
Judges	O
being	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
said	O
Baron	O
Thompson	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
not	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
beforemention	O
'd	O
Objections	O
,	O
the	O
Trial	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bambridge	I-pers
was	O
referr	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
N.B	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Tryal	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
and	O
Frances	B-pers
Clifford	I-pers
,	O
Instead	O
of	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
,	O
read	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
ended	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
follows	O
:	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
7.	O
Thomas	B-pers
James	I-pers
Grundy	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
,	O
Hannah	B-pers
Hartley	I-pers
,	O
Susannah	B-pers
Frazier	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Wileman	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Cluff	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Pantry	I-pers
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
1.	O
John	B-pers
Holden	I-pers
.	O
For	O
Transportation	O
,	O
33.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Salter	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Fountain	I-pers
,	O
Laurence	B-pers
Neale	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Budd	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Hawes	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Hatfield	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Wills	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Barton	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Tinsley	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Milton	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Saunderson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Little	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
Grace	B-pers
Conyers	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Burdis	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Rawlins	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Woollam	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Woollard	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Barrow	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Sterling	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Forster	I-pers
,	O
Michael	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Tailor	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Burleigh	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
.	O
Whipt	O
7.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Borket	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cane	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Page	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Page	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Rowland	I-pers
to	O
stand	O
twice	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
,	O
and	O
suffer	O
6	O
Months	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Hartley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Susannah	B-pers
Frazier	I-pers
,	O
pleaded	O
their	O
Bellies	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
Matrons	O
being	O
impannell	O
'd	O
,	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
with	O
quick	O
Child	O
.	O
BOOKS	O
Printed	O
for	O
E.	O
Symon	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Pope's-Head-Alley	O
in	O
Cornhil	O
.	O
THe	O
Present	O
State	O
of	O
Great-Britain	O
,	O
and	O
Ireland	O
,	O
in	O
Three	O
Parts	O
.	O
The	O
I	O
.	O
Of	O
South	O
,	O
the	O
IId	O
.	O
of	O
North	O
Britain	O
.	O
III	O
.	O
Of	O
Ireland	O
.	O
Containing	O
an	O
Accurate	O
and	O
Impartial	O
Account	O
of	O
these	O
famous	O
Islands	O
:	O
Of	O
their	O
several	O
Counties	O
and	O
Inhabitants	O
;	O
the	O
Advantages	O
and	O
Disadvantages	O
of	O
Both	O
,	O
in	O
Respect	O
to	O
Foreign	O
Countries	O
;	O
and	O
their	O
Curiosities	O
of	O
Nature	O
and	O
Art	O
.	O
Of	O
the	O
vast	O
,	O
populous	O
,	O
and	O
opulent	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Metropolis	O
of	O
England	O
;	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
celebrated	O
Universities	O
,	O
Oxford	O
and	O
Cambridge	O
.	O
Of	O
the	O
Britons	O
Original	O
,	O
Language	O
,	O
Temper	O
,	O
Genius	O
,	O
Religion	O
,	O
Morals	O
,	O
Trade	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Their	O
Nobility	O
,	O
Gentry	O
,	O
Clergy	O
,	O
and	O
Commonalty	O
.	O
Their	O
Laws	O
and	O
Government	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
succinct	O
History	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
English	O
Monarchs	O
to	O
this	O
Time	O
.	O
With	O
Lists	O
of	O
the	O
present	O
Officers	O
in	O
Church	O
and	O
State	O
;	O
and	O
of	O
both	O
Houses	O
of	O
Parliament	O
:	O
Also	O
the	O
present	O
State	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Dominions	O
in	O
Germany	O
.	O
The	O
Sixth	O
Edition	O
Corrected	O
.	O
Price	O
Six	O
Shillings	O
.	O
The	O
Adventures	O
of	O
Telemachus	O
,	O
the	O
Son	O
of	O
Ulysses	O
.	O
In	O
Twenty-four	O
Books	O
.	O
With	O
the	O
Adventures	O
of	O
Aristonous	O
.	O
Written	O
by	O
the	O
Archbishop	O
of	O
Cambray	O
.	O
Done	O
into	O
English	O
from	O
the	O
last	O
Paris	O
(	O
which	O
is	O
the	O
only	O
Genuine	O
)	O
Edition	O
.	O
By	O
Mr.	O
Is	O
.	O
Littlebury	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
A.	O
