TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
25th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
26th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
27th	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
1730	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Third	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Third	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	B-pers
BROCAS	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1730	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
III	O
.	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
YEAR	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
T.	O
PAYNE	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
in	O
Ivy-Lane	O
,	O
near	O
Pater-noster-Row	O
.	O
M.DCC.XXX	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
Six	O
Pence	O
.	O
)	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
For	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
AND	O
ON	O
The	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
25th	O
,	O
26th	O
,	O
27th	O
,	O
and	O
28th	O
of	O
February	O
1730	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Third	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	B-pers
BROCAS	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Price	O
,	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Probyn	O
,	O
the	O
Worshipful	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
Raby	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hardwell	I-pers
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Churchill	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Randal	I-pers
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Sowersby	I-pers
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Rosebottom	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lovel	I-pers
.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
.	O
George	B-pers
Halfhyde	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Cowen	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Forster	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Wilton	I-pers
.	O
Simon	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Barrett	I-pers
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wise	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Wilder	I-pers
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Gardener	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Carpenter	I-pers
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Halley	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
.	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Crywater	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Katherine	I-place
's	I-place
Creed-Church	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
and	O
Chain	O
,	O
value	O
22	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Moses	B-pers
Piver	I-pers
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
entrusted	O
in	O
her	O
Mistress	O
's	O
Bed-Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Drawers	O
were	O
left	O
unlock	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Watch	O
being	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
examin	O
'd	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
owned	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
several	O
Pawn	O
brokers	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
in	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
at	O
length	O
one	O
Pawnbroker	O
had	O
lent	O
her	O
a	O
Guinea	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Pointers	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Watch	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Drawer	O
,	O
and	O
wrapped	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
Sheet	O
of	O
white	O
Paper	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
broken	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
thrown	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Common	O
Sewer	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
thrown	O
it	O
down	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
at	O
first	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
,	O
where	O
her	O
Sister	O
had	O
before	O
pawned	O
some	O
Things	O
.	O
But	O
enquiry	O
being	O
made	O
in	O
the	O
several	O
places	O
she	O
had	O
spoken	O
of	O
,	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
knew	O
anything	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
to	O
wait	O
upon	O
a	O
Child	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Crywater	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
several	O
times	O
to	O
do	O
Work	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
left	O
all	O
alone	O
in	O
the	O
Dining-Room	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
Mistress	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
put	O
the	O
Watch	O
into	O
the	O
Drawer	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
discourse	O
she	O
had	O
heard	O
her	O
say	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
the	O
Watch	O
for	O
a	O
Week	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Piver	O
's	O
House	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
after	O
the	O
Watch	O
had	O
been	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
bid	O
her	O
not	O
be	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
that	O
thereupon	O
she	O
came	O
again	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
charged	O
her	O
very	O
strictly	O
with	O
having	O
taken	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
telling	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
where	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
hang	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
discover	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
or	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
redeem	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
forgive	O
her	O
.	O
That	O
thereupon	O
,	O
though	O
she	O
had	O
before	O
deny	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
thrown	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Common	O
Sewer	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
burnt	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
varying	O
thus	O
in	O
her	O
Story	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
you	O
say	O
,	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
done	O
with	O
it	O
?	O
That	O
she	O
deny	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
ever	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
frighten	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Wits	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
being	O
carried	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
before	O
said	O
was	O
in	O
her	O
fright	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
did	O
examine	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
thrown	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Common	O
Sewer	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Nurse	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
saw	O
her	O
Mistress	O
put	O
the	O
Watch	O
into	O
the	O
Drawer	O
a	O
Week	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Drawer	O
had	O
been	O
Lock	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
Day	O
the	O
Girl	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
Day	O
it	O
stood	O
unlock	O
'd	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
having	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
but	O
her	O
own	O
Confession	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
so	O
inconsistent	O
,	O
and	O
seeming	O
to	O
proceed	O
from	O
the	O
fright	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
,	O
upon	O
being	O
charged	O
with	O
the	O
Watch	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
being	O
a	O
young	O
Girl	O
of	O
about	O
12	O
or	O
13	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
Character	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Tod	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
an	O
Amethist	O
Ring	O
set	O
with	O
4	O
Brilliants	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Amethist	O
set	O
with	O
10	O
Brillants	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tea	O
Pot	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Whiting	I-pers
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
's	O
Niece	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
to	O
visit	O
her	O
Daughter	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
Reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
Robbed	O
her	O
twice	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Tea	O
Pot	O
was	O
lost	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Ring	O
lost	O
January	O
the	O
18th	O
,	O
that	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
inform	O
'd	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
sent	O
out	O
the	O
Maid	O
of	O
an	O
Errand	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
only	O
two	O
Children	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
she	O
broke	O
open	O
a	O
Wallnut-Tree	O
Scriptore	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Rings	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
Home	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
following	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
Scriptore	O
was	O
broken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Rings	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
the	O
breaking	O
of	O
the	O
Glass	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
Money	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
other	O
Evidences	O
to	O
confirm	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Rings	O
were	O
found	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Direction	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
pawn	O
'd	O
by	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
her	O
having	O
pawned	O
the	O
Rings	O
;	O
but	O
pleaded	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Glass	O
of	O
the	O
Scriptore	O
was	O
broken	O
by	O
Accident	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Fall	O
of	O
a	O
Curtain	O
Rod	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Board	O
of	O
the	O
Scriptore	O
behind	O
the	O
Glass	O
was	O
not	O
broken	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Daughter	O
,	O
Anne	B-pers
Whiting	I-pers
,	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
Scriptore	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
her	O
take	O
the	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
them	O
on	O
Account	O
of	O
Money	O
she	O
ow	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
having	O
no	O
other	O
way	O
to	O
pay	O
her	O
.	O
It	O
did	O
appear	O
by	O
other	O
Evidences	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
Intimacy	O
between	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Daughter	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Daughter	O
charged	O
the	O
Balance	O
of	O
Accounts	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
desir	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
might	O
be	O
ask	O
'd	O
.	O
If	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
married	O
to	O
her	O
Son	O
?	O
But	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
her	O
Son	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
produce	O
her	O
Certificate	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Mittinens	O
was	O
made	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Tod	I-pers
,	O
she	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
her	O
Name	O
,	O
her	O
Name	O
was	O
Whiting	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Constable	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Persons	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Paul	B-pers
Crowney	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Alhallows	B-place
Barkin	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Barrel	O
of	O
Anchovies	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
de	I-pers
Foe	I-pers
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Neal	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prison	O
bring	O
the	O
Barrel	O
of	O
Anchovies	O
in	O
his	O
Apron	O
from	O
Brown	O
's	O
Key	O
,	O
where	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
more	O
lay	O
to	O
Galley-Key	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
apprehended	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
he	O
was	O
hir	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
Man	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
produce	O
the	O
Person	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Crouch	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
1	O
Pound	O
6	O
Ounces	O
of	O
sewing	O
Silk	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Edgerton	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Anws	I-pers
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Edgerton	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Silk	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
was	O
his	O
.	O
Tho	B-pers
Spicer	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Shop	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Yellow	O
Silk	O
,	O
that	O
taking	O
down	O
several	O
Bundles	O
,	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
he	O
missing	O
a	O
Bundle	O
,	O
follow	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
afterwards	O
the	O
Silk	O
was	O
found	O
dropp	O
'd	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
suppos	O
'd	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
before	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
having	O
taken	O
the	O
Silk	O
not	O
being	O
sufficiently	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Coverly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Alhallows	B-place
London-Wall	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cheese	O
,	O
Value	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Tewet	I-pers
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
seen	O
with	O
the	O
Cheese	O
,	O
and	O
suspected	O
to	O
have	O
stol'n	O
it	O
,	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
threw	O
the	O
Cheese	O
into	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Shopkeeper	O
claiming	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
Prison	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
desired	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
Cheese	O
by	O
a	O
Boy	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
carrying	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Things	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
Pretence	O
not	O
availing	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Norton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
some	O
Fir-Timber	O
,	O
and	O
180	O
Foot	O
of	O
Oak-Timber	O
,	O
Value	O
45	O
s.	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
had	O
lost	O
Timber	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Yard	O
from	O
time	O
to	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Fir-Timber	O
that	O
was	O
his	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Fire	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
swore	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Timber	O
.	O
He	O
call	O
'd	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
did	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
one	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
,	O
take	O
Timber	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Yard	O
,	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
her	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
it	O
into	O
her	O
House	O
.	O
He	O
also	O
call	O
'd	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Journeymen	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
miss	O
'd	O
several	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Timber	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
cut	O
out	O
for	O
Roossing	O
,	O
they	O
being	O
Carpenters	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
pleaded	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Timber	O
of	O
her	O
own	O
,	O
her	O
Husband	O
(	O
since	O
deceas	O
'd	O
)	O
having	O
bought	O
Partitions	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
wooden	O
Stuff	O
belonging	O
to	O
another	O
House	O
:	O
she	O
also	O
alledg	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
was	O
Malicious	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
being	O
Tenant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
after	O
her	O
Husband	O
's	O
Decease	O
,	O
was	O
removing	O
her	O
Goods	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
made	O
a	O
Seizure	O
before	O
any	O
Rent	O
was	O
due	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
Cause	O
she	O
having	O
arrested	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
set	O
on	O
Foot	O
this	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
to	O
prove	O
which	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Evidences	O
.	O
Several	O
Persons	O
of	O
Credit	O
appearing	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Leonard	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Walton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Katharine	I-place
Creed-Church	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
11	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
Value	O
6	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Moses	B-pers
de	I-pers
Medina	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Walthoe	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Robinson	O
,	O
ply	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
in	O
and	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
very	O
frequently	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
left	O
the	O
Spoons	O
at	O
4	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Box	O
in	O
the	O
Plate-House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
about	O
6	O
o'Clock	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
that	O
upon	O
Enquiry	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
told	O
by	O
the	O
Maid	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Leonard	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
suspecting	O
he	O
had	O
stolen	O
them	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Walton	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
his	O
Comrade	O
,	O
and	O
who	O
he	O
had	O
observ	O
'd	O
lurking	O
about	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Walton	O
did	O
Conduct	O
him	O
in	O
finding	O
Robinson	O
;	O
that	O
Robinson	O
being	O
found	O
,	O
did	O
own	O
the	O
stealing	O
the	O
Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
several	O
Places	O
at	O
Windmill-Hill	O
,	O
Hounsditch	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
pawn	O
'd	O
and	O
sold	O
;	O
Robinson	O
's	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
charg	O
'd	O
Walton	O
with	O
going	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
pawn	O
and	O
sell	O
the	O
Spoons	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
other	O
Evidences	O
to	O
confirm	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Confession	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
therefore	O
being	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
against	O
Robinson	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
but	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Proof	O
against	O
Walton	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Hanson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Daniel	B-pers
Beausoy	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
Value	O
19	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Rose	O
Hat-Band	O
,	O
Value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
(	O
a	O
French	O
Clergyman	O
)	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
passing	O
near	O
Bishopsgate	B-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Day	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
his	O
Hat	O
was	O
taken	O
off	O
his	O
Head	O
by	O
some	O
Person	O
who	O
was	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
by	O
whom	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
passing	O
near	O
Bishopsgate	O
,	O
at	O
some	O
small	O
Distance	O
behind	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
snatch	O
off	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
down	O
the	O
White-Horse	O
Inn-Yard	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
ran	O
round	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Hounsditch	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
other	O
Entrance	O
of	O
the	O
White-Horse	O
Inn	O
,	O
and	O
perceiving	O
he	O
had	O
something	O
under	O
his	O
Apron	O
,	O
demanded	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
refusing	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
see	O
,	O
he	O
catch	O
'd	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
struggle	O
receiv	O
'd	O
several	O
Blows	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
fell	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
getting	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
a	O
Street-robber	O
,	O
was	O
pursu	O
'd	O
both	O
by	O
himself	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
running	O
to	O
the	O
Alderman	O
's	O
Walk	O
,	O
his	O
Heels	O
were	O
struck	O
up	O
by	O
a	O
Fishmonger	O
's	O
Man	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Fisher	O
following	O
him	O
,	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
a	O
Street-robber	O
,	O
help	O
,	O
help	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
follow	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
stopp	O
'd	O
,	O
as	O
before	O
,	O
having	O
ran	O
about	O
50	O
Yards	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
apprehended	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
Value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
himself	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
his	O
Snuff-Box	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
Room	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Snuff-Box	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
absconded	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
no	O
more	O
for	O
18	O
Days	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Proof	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stole	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Binham	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Lambourn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
together	O
with	O
Leonard	B-pers
Burt	I-pers
,	O
did	O
feloniously	O
steal	O
a	O
leaden	O
Pump	O
,	O
40	O
lb	O
.	O
Weight	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
latter	O
for	O
receiving	O
it	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Binham	O
and	O
Burt	O
stole	O
the	O
Pump	O
from	O
the	O
Bulk	O
on	O
the	O
out-side	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Cox	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
about	O
7	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
Lambourn	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Scale	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
came	O
to	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
also	O
said	O
here	O
is	O
three	O
of	O
you	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
bring	O
any	O
thing	O
again	O
,	O
come	O
but	O
one	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Rixon	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
missing	O
the	O
Pump	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
Lambourn	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
noted	O
Receiver	O
of	O
stolen	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
suspecting	O
them	O
,	O
put	O
out	O
the	O
Candle	O
,	O
denying	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Pump	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
going	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
8	O
Foot	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
deep	O
in	O
the	O
Soil	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Scale	O
,	O
that	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
Warrant	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
they	O
watch	O
'd	O
the	O
House	O
all	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
gotten	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Manner	O
before	O
related	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
thereupon	O
absconded	O
for	O
3	O
Weeks	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
Month	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
h	O
is	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Pump	O
was	O
bought	O
by	O
his	O
Mother	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
Girl	O
threw	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
Binham	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
Lambourn	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White-Chapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Wooden	O
Till	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
8	O
s.	O
2	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Wolmer	I-pers
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
gone	O
backwards	O
,	O
had	O
left	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
Till	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
return	O
'd	O
,	O
his	O
Till	O
and	O
Money	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
happening	O
to	O
pass	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
putting	O
his	O
Hand	O
over	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
and	O
watching	O
him	O
,	O
saw	O
him	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Box	O
in	O
his	O
Apron	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
seized	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Box	O
;	O
that	O
Charles	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
coming	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
the	O
Box	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
pray	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
no	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Owner	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
as	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
had	O
done	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
Box	O
and	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Grimes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Thomas	B-pers
Exelhy	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
37	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Waggoner	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
bringing	O
Poulterer	O
's	O
Ware	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
from	O
Huntington	B-place
,	O
and	O
coming	O
to	O
Holloway	B-place
early	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
two	O
Men	O
about	O
an	O
hundred	O
Yards	O
distance	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
yerk	O
'd	O
out	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
saying	O
deliver	O
your	O
Money	O
,	O
or	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
,	O
that	O
immediately	O
the	O
other	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
deliver	O
your	O
Money	O
,	O
or	O
you	O
are	O
dead	O
this	O
Minute	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
37	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
come	O
to	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
discoursing	O
with	O
his	O
Brother	O
Waggoners	O
about	O
being	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
describing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Cox	O
heard	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
shew	O
him	O
a	O
Man	O
who	O
answer	O
'd	O
that	O
Description	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
seeing	O
him	O
,	O
knew	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
as	O
much	O
or	O
more	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
than	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
apprehended	O
him	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Cox	O
advis	O
'd	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
then	O
,	O
because	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Persons	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
but	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
might	O
be	O
his	O
Companions	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Cox	O
apprehended	O
him	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Horse-Courser	O
,	O
and	O
himself	O
keeping	O
an	O
Inn	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
set	O
up	O
Horses	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
;	O
that	O
hearing	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
complaining	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
Robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
describing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
talking	O
with	O
him	O
about	O
a	O
Horse	O
for	O
a	O
Friend	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
positive	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
who	O
had	O
Robb	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
procur	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Robe	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
telling	O
a	O
long	O
Story	O
about	O
the	O
manner	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
apprehended	O
,	O
called	O
the	O
following	O
Evidances	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Shortly	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
Home	O
at	O
Christmas-Eve	O
's	O
Eve	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
about	O
7	O
o'clock	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
about	O
Ten	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
a	O
sad	O
Cough	O
,	O
asking	O
him	O
,	O
why	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
get	O
something	O
for	O
it	O
?	O
That	O
he	O
answerved	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
disturbs	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
help	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
England	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
a	O
vinolent	O
vomitting	O
of	O
Blood	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
something	O
that	O
stopp	O
'd	O
his	O
Bleeding	O
;	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
how	O
he	O
did	O
?	O
And	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
was	O
very	O
bad	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
load	O
at	O
his	O
Stomach	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
capable	O
of	O
committing	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
Upon	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Carr	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
of	O
Knives	O
,	O
Scizors	O
,	O
Seals	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Cutlery	O
Ware	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Conquest	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
Conquest	O
Jones	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
missing	O
Goods	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
searching	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
found	O
several	O
of	O
his	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Pitts	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Joanna	B-pers
Shanon	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
fear	O
of	O
her	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
15	O
s.	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1728	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
knew	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
they	O
having	O
before	O
been	O
Fellow-Servants	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
meeting	O
her	O
about	O
10	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
near	O
Lincoln's-Inn-Fields	B-place
,	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
any	O
Money	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
would	O
borrow	O
some	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
not	O
owning	O
she	O
had	O
any	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
see	O
whether	O
she	O
had	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
throwing	O
her	O
down	O
,	O
rifled	O
her	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
pleaded	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
since	O
the	O
time	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
an	O
Intimacy	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
several	O
times	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
had	O
there	O
drank	O
Coffee	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
his	O
Wife	O
a	O
Mantua	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
having	O
Robb	O
'd	O
her	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
Evidences	O
who	O
proved	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
and	O
Peter	B-pers
Rivers	I-pers
of	O
Uxbridge	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Henry	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
3	O
s.	O
4	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
a	O
Cork-screw	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
coming	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Rogers	O
's	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
Islip	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
If	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
Money	O
?	O
and	O
presented	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
his	O
Breast	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
rifled	O
his	O
Pockets	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
Buckles	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
about	O
his	O
Business	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
meeting	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Hedges	I-pers
,	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
Robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
any	O
Body	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
the	O
Robbers	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
agreeing	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
together	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hedges	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
going	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
met	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Gladman	I-pers
,	O
and	O
enquiring	O
if	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
he	O
informed	O
them	O
he	O
did	O
meet	O
two	O
such	O
Men	O
as	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
described	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
went	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gladman	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
Riding	O
to	O
Islip	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
Hedges	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
enquiring	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
Robb	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
back	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
getting	O
sight	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
near	O
Wicomb	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
Men	O
that	O
Robb	O
'd	O
me	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
Care	O
to	O
apprehend	O
them	O
there	O
,	O
because	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
help	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
they	O
pursued	O
them	O
to	O
Uxbridge	O
Town	O
,	O
where	O
Riding	O
before	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
telling	O
William	B-pers
Wyat	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Skinner	I-pers
that	O
there	O
were	O
Highwaymen	O
coming	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
stopped	O
and	O
apprehended	O
just	O
entering	O
upon	O
the	O
Bridge	O
.	O
Several	O
other	O
Evidences	O
who	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
apprehending	O
them	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
upon	O
searching	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
five	O
Pistols	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
three	O
upon	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
upon	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
some	O
hanging	O
within	O
side	O
their	O
Coats	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
in	O
their	O
Pockets	O
;	O
and	O
some	O
small	O
Cords	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
suppos	O
'd	O
were	O
design	O
'd	O
for	O
binding	O
Persons	O
on	O
occasion	O
:	O
And	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Handkerchiefs	O
and	O
Cork-screw	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
Rivers	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Buckles	O
on	O
Carter	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
had	O
known	O
them	O
many	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
Families	O
,	O
even	O
their	O
Fathers	O
and	O
Grandfathers	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
always	O
lived	O
very	O
reputably	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
bore	O
the	O
Characters	O
of	O
very	O
honest	O
Men	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
thereabouts	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
,	O
had	O
Dealings	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
found	O
them	O
very	O
honest	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
never	O
heard	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
them	O
before	O
this	O
Fact	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ingram	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hornsey	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Cotton	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Pistol	O
belonging	O
to	O
Mr	B-pers
Ryland	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Hone	O
and	O
Black	O
Velvet	O
Cap	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Barrett	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servan	O
t	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Cotton	O
,	O
and	O
missing	O
Things	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Compting-House	O
from	O
time	O
to	O
time	O
,	O
they	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
searching	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Cotton	O
's	O
Shoes	O
under	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Pistol	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
Chest	O
in	O
another	O
Room	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Lodging-Room	O
of	O
one	O
Henley	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Goods	O
not	O
being	O
properly	O
in	O
the	O
Custody	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
50	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Manning	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Stockings	O
,	O
but	O
knew	O
not	O
who	O
stole	O
them	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
Chancery-Lane	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nosely	I-pers
,	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	B-place
of	I-place
the	I-place
Crown	I-place
in	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
brought	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Black	O
Stockings	O
in	O
a	O
Paper	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
afterwards	O
Nosely	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
out	O
a	O
Parcel	O
,	O
containing	O
four	O
Dozen	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Stockings	O
of	O
Nosely	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
under	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
followed	O
them	O
to	O
their	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
got	O
in	O
,	O
they	O
shut	O
the	O
Door	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
come	O
in	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
they	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Black	O
Stockings	O
in	O
a	O
Paper	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
some	O
Body	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
had	O
taken	O
fifteen	O
Pair	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
four	O
Dozen	O
:	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
any	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
confirm	O
that	O
of	O
Williamson	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
Stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Cloak	O
;	O
Linen	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Forster	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
pawned	O
them	O
in	O
Baldwin's-Gardens	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
:	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
likewise	O
proved	O
by	O
other	O
Evidences	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Taverner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Finchley	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Poulks	I-pers
,	O
did	O
steal	O
two	O
Ewe	O
Sheep	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Plevin	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Sheep	O
were	O
feeding	O
in	O
the	O
Field	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
he	O
found	O
only	O
the	O
Skins	O
,	O
the	O
Guts	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
young	O
Lambs	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
with	O
young	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Carcasses	O
were	O
carried	O
away	O
.	O
A	O
Watchman	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
crying	O
3	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Field	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
?	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
old	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Taylor	O
by	O
Trade	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
must	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Constable	O
;	O
that	O
examining	O
the	O
Bundle	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
Mutton	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
it	O
at	O
Black	O
Mary	O
's	O
Hole	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
enquiring	O
of	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
out	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
Hampstead	O
for	O
some	O
Work	O
,	O
and	O
getting	O
Drunk	O
,	O
had	O
lain	O
in	O
the	O
Field	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
along	O
found	O
the	O
Bundle	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
Mutton	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
added	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
carrying	O
him	O
to	O
New	O
Prison	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
to	O
come	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
tell	O
him	O
more	O
about	O
the	O
Mutton	O
;	O
and	O
owned	O
,	O
that	O
himself	O
and	O
Foulks	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
four	O
Robberies	O
in	O
stealing	O
Sheep	O
;	O
that	O
Foulks	O
liv	O
'd	O
at	O
Hampstead	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
thither	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
other	O
six	O
Quarters	O
of	O
the	O
Sheep	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
two	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Mutton	O
was	O
that	O
of	O
his	O
Sheep	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
following	O
Reasons	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
off	O
the	O
Skins	O
so	O
bunglingly	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
left	O
pieces	O
of	O
Flesh	O
upon	O
the	O
Skin	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
had	O
cut	O
Holes	O
in	O
the	O
Skins	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Wooll	O
upon	O
the	O
Flesh	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
applying	O
those	O
Places	O
the	O
one	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
they	O
match	O
'd	O
exactly	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Grice	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Luke	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
Value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Nightingale	I-pers
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jaspar	B-pers
Jerbin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
's	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
5	O
Calking	O
Irons	O
,	O
Value	O
1	O
s.	O
an	O
Ax	O
,	O
Value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Nott	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
5	O
Augers	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
Googes	O
,	O
Value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Nott	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
;	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Young	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
keeps	O
a	O
Shipwrights	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Servants	O
were	O
continually	O
complaining	O
of	O
loosing	O
their	O
Tools	O
,	O
and	O
sending	O
his	O
Son	O
to	O
Martin	O
's	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
.	O
Martin	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
bought	O
these	O
Tools	O
so	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
examin	O
'd	O
him	O
whose	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
that	O
dy	O
'd	O
at	O
Sea	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
pleaded	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Tools	O
were	O
given	O
him	O
by	O
a	O
Man	O
to	O
sell	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
his	O
Pains	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
not	O
producing	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Hannah	B-pers
Burridge	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
Value	O
10s	O
.	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
Value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Christian	B-pers
Hanson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Hyde	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
following	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Jenkin	O
Evans	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
suspecting	O
her	O
,	O
stopp	O
'd	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
asking	O
her	O
why	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
she	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
Devil	O
was	O
in	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
now	O
;	O
hang	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
care	O
what	O
becomes	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
gotten	O
a	O
bad	O
Husband	O
.	O
However	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
she	O
ever	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
or	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
:	O
But	O
it	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Gale	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Anthony	B-pers
Lovet	I-pers
,	O
in	O
an	O
open	O
Place	O
near	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
3	O
Keys	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
hit	O
him	O
a	O
Blow	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Man	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
his	O
Hands	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Keys	O
and	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
that	O
this	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
the	O
Upper-steps	O
in	O
Moorfields	O
,	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Tree	O
;	O
that	O
afterwards	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
running	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
bid	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
himself	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
knew	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
nor	O
several	O
Days	O
before	O
and	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
following	O
Evidences	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Capon	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Father	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
because	O
one	O
Cotterel	O
,	O
Read	O
,	O
and	O
Williams	O
were	O
at	O
Law	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
on	O
Sunday	O
,	O
the	O
last	O
Day	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
with	O
him	O
till	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
December	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
left	O
him	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
Home	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
him	O
always	O
at	O
Home	O
.	O
That	O
there	O
came	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
several	O
Persons	O
to	O
their	O
House	O
,	O
as	O
Mary	B-pers
Bull	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
about	O
Four	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
stay	O
'd	O
to	O
Supper	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
merry	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
should	O
be	O
more	O
merry	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Matters	O
were	O
made	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
together	O
till	O
Ten	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
never	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
Company	O
from	O
Two	O
that	O
Day	O
till	O
Ten	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
afraid	O
,	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Gale	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Father	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
between	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
three	O
other	O
Lads	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
put	O
him	O
into	O
New	O
Prison	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
Bailed	O
him	O
three	O
times	O
for	O
an	O
Assault	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Judge	O
's	O
Warrant	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
afraid	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
chargeable	O
,	O
had	O
sent	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Capon	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
He	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
from	O
Sunday	O
to	O
the	O
Thursday	O
following	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
before	O
and	O
after	O
the	O
time	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
:	O
And	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
very	O
frequently	O
with	O
those	O
Persons	O
that	O
had	O
the	O
Quarrel	O
with	O
his	O
Son	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
was	O
put	O
upon	O
this	O
Proseon	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
Both	O
John	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Bull	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Company	O
the	O
Day	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
from	O
Four	O
o'Clock	O
till	O
after	O
Ten	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
never	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
,	O
or	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
Company	O
all	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
One	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
heard	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
hang	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
out	O
of	O
Revenge	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
the	O
Impudence	O
to	O
take	O
out	O
a	O
Warrant	O
against	O
a	O
Friend	O
of	O
his	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
How	O
he	O
could	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
Night	O
?	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
light	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Light	O
of	O
the	O
Lamp	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Polton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Lamp-lighter	O
being	O
called	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Lamp	O
lighted	O
near	O
that	O
place	O
for	O
seventy	O
or	O
eighty	O
Yards	O
,	O
nor	O
had	O
been	O
all	O
that	O
Season	O
.	O
Several	O
persons	O
were	O
call	O
'd	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Dowdle	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bride	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
20l	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
stolen	O
,	O
but	O
knew	O
not	O
by	O
whom	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
he	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
but	O
had	O
Information	O
by	O
a	O
Justice	O
's	O
Clerk	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
Pawn	O
in	O
Market-Lane	O
,	O
at	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Smith	O
's	O
,	O
near	O
St.	O
James's-Market	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Jacombs	O
,	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
Clerk	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
taken	O
up	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
upon	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
stealing	O
a	O
Ring	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
an	O
Information	O
of	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
whom	O
were	O
apprehended	O
upon	O
his	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
this	O
Evidence	O
,	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Smith	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
pawned	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Smith	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
Watch	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
lent	O
seven	O
Guineas	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
pawn	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Comber	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Dowdle	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Treble	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
Dionysius	O
Spere	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
brought	O
a	O
Stone	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
agreed	O
for	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
looking	O
over	O
some	O
Rings	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Diamond	O
Buckle	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
wanted	O
a	O
Buckle	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
Price	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
90	O
l.	O
that	O
in	O
pretending	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Buckle	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
slily	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
missing	O
the	O
Ring	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
advertis	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
heard	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Moss	O
's	O
in	O
Fox-Court	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Moss	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
She	O
lent	O
14	O
Guineas	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
the	O
Ring	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
Ring	O
,	O
but	O
pleaded	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Promise	O
of	O
the	O
Justice	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
gave	O
his	O
Information	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
would	O
endeavour	O
to	O
have	O
him	O
be	O
made	O
an	O
Evidence	O
;	O
which	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
,	O
being	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
did	O
own	O
to	O
be	O
true	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
desired	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
might	O
be	O
recommended	O
to	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Mercy	O
,	O
especially	O
,	O
since	O
by	O
his	O
Discovery	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
had	O
their	O
Goods	O
again	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
's	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Duroy	O
Coat	O
,	O
two	O
Shirts	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Ship	O
,	O
which	O
lay	O
over	O
against	O
Union	B-place
Stairs	I-place
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
seen	O
to	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Ship	O
,	O
was	O
pursued	O
and	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Whitham	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linen	O
Shirt	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Temporal	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
he	O
missing	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
apprehending	O
him	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Shirt	O
under	O
his	O
Coat	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Maylin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchre	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Chalkley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Body	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Recognizance	O
was	O
order	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
Estreated	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Kitchin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Receiving	O
and	O
Buying	O
3	O
lb	O
.	O
13	O
oz	O
.	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
and	O
Mohair	O
twisted	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Filsey	I-pers
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
by	O
Katherine	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
;	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
being	O
clearly	O
prov	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Gerald	B-pers
Fitzgerald	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Whitley	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
near	O
the	O
Right	O
Pap	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Length	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
ten	O
Inches	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
February	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
Died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
slaying	O
the	O
said	O
Robert	B-pers
Whitley	I-pers
.	O
-	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Curson	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Stone	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
Thisle	B-place
and	I-place
Crown	I-place
in	I-place
Charles-Court	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Strand	I-place
,	O
and	O
were	O
playing	O
a	O
Game	O
at	O
Cribbage	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
about	O
Twelve	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
play	O
a	O
Game	O
at	O
All-Fours	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
playing	O
with	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
some	O
Difference	O
arose	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
rose	O
up	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Find	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
draw	O
his	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
received	O
a	O
Wound	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Aggressor	O
,	O
and	O
himself	O
intended	O
no	O
Quarrel	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Curson	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
were	O
playing	O
a	O
Game	O
at	O
Cards	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
Back	O
was	O
towards	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
some	O
Words	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
with	O
much	O
Warmth	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
retired	O
,	O
and	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
held	O
Mr.	O
Fitzgerald	O
till	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
had	O
drawn	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
saying	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
hold	O
me	O
while	O
I	O
am	O
Sacrific	O
'd	O
?	O
He	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
withdraw	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
in	O
a	O
Posture	O
of	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
engag	O
'd	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
Minute	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
,	O
make	O
your	O
escape	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
you	O
can	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Stone	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
the	O
Thistle	O
and	O
Crown	O
,	O
where	O
himself	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Curson	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
to	O
play	O
for	O
a	O
Sneaker	O
of	O
Punch	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
seemed	O
unwilling	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
spend	O
18	O
d.	O
with	O
the	O
Widow	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
play	O
with	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Words	O
arose	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Fitzgerald	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
some	O
Mistake	O
in	O
the	O
Play	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
believes	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
won	O
the	O
first	O
Game	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
propos	O
'd	O
to	O
play	O
for	O
a	O
Two	O
Shilling	O
Sneaker	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
not	O
being	O
willing	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
called	O
him	O
,	O
either	O
Villain	O
,	O
Rascal	O
,	O
or	O
Scoundrel	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
retir	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
drew	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
themselves	O
in	O
a	O
Posture	O
of	O
Defence	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
wounded	O
,	O
desired	O
they	O
would	O
let	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
going	O
Home	O
with	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
Madam	O
Whitley	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
what	O
she	O
expected	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
,	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Bed	O
about	O
3	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
to	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
search	O
'd	O
his	O
Wound	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Right	O
Breast	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Pap	O
,	O
and	O
touch	O
'd	O
the	O
descending	O
Trunk	O
of	O
the	O
Vena	O
Cava	O
,	O
and	O
passed	O
into	O
the	O
Cavity	O
of	O
the	O
Breast	O
,	O
going	O
slanting	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Rib	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Whitley	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
my	O
Dear	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
Aggressor	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Fitzgerald	O
drew	O
first	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
of	O
no	O
Quarrel	O
,	O
my	O
Dear	O
,	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
me	O
in	O
Fault	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Fitzgerald	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
having	O
been	O
at	O
Supper	O
at	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
Home	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
grip	O
'd	O
,	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
Dram	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
found	O
Mr.	O
Stone	O
,	O
and	O
telling	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
Order	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Stone	O
took	O
a	O
Pen	O
and	O
Ink	O
,	O
and	O
prescribed	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
there	O
at	O
Play	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
him	O
play	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
refus	O
'd	O
,	O
not	O
understanding	O
the	O
Game	O
of	O
Cribbage	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
play	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
All-Fours	O
for	O
a	O
Bowl	O
of	O
Punch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
would	O
have	O
him	O
play	O
for	O
another	O
Bowl	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
desiring	O
to	O
be	O
excus	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
thereupon	O
called	O
him	O
Rascal	O
and	O
Scoundrel	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
Language	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Stranger	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
seeing	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
drawing	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
did	O
draw	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
that	O
after	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
had	O
receiv	O
'd	O
the	O
Wound	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
of	O
my	O
seeking	O
,	O
he	O
answered	O
no	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
them	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Persons	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
peaceable	O
,	O
inoffensive	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
not	O
given	O
to	O
Quarrel	O
;	O
but	O
had	O
taken	O
and	O
born	O
patiently	O
such	O
Affronts	O
,	O
as	O
few	O
others	O
would	O
have	O
born	O
;	O
upon	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
Murther	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Swan	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
,	I-place
Hanover-Square	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
12	O
Bottles	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
East	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
Convict	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Shadwel	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Shuttlewel	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Crouch	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wallis	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
passing	O
along	O
White-Chapel	B-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
Swearing	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
not	O
liking	O
their	O
Company	O
,	O
stopp	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
Water	O
that	O
they	O
might	O
pass	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
snatch	O
'd	O
off	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
afterwards	O
found	O
upon	O
Shadwel	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
by	O
Crouch	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Crouch	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
of	O
Shadwel	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Shadwel	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
Deniel	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
of	O
Hendon	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bay	O
Gelding	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
;	O
but	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Rice	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White	I-place
Chapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Yards	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
February	O
;	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
Journeyman	O
Weaver	O
,	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
work	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
cut	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Loom	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
John	B-pers
Rich	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Quantities	O
of	O
Linen	O
Cloth	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
February	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
selling	O
Cloth	O
about	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
had	O
set	O
down	O
his	O
Pack	O
on	O
a	O
Stall	O
in	O
East-Smithfield	B-place
,	O
while	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
that	O
upon	O
enquiry	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
stopp	O
'd	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
carrying	O
it	O
along	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Bond	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
suspecting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
have	O
stolen	O
the	O
Pack	O
,	O
stopp	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
demanding	O
to	O
see	O
his	O
Licence	O
,	O
he	O
not	O
having	O
any	O
,	O
secured	O
him	O
till	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Pack	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
seeing	O
the	O
Pack	O
upon	O
the	O
Stall	O
,	O
and	O
supposing	O
it	O
belonged	O
to	O
No-body	O
,	O
did	O
carry	O
it	O
away	O
himself	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Roper	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Perriwigs	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rutly	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Hind	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
February	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4s	O
.	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Manning	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Linen	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Briggs	I-pers
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
February	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Buck	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Chest	O
,	O
and	O
Carpenters	O
Tools	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Woller	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
by	O
several	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
crazy	O
distracted	O
Person	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hulls	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Edmonton	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Hens	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
February	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Rumsey	I-pers
and	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Ryan	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Whip	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Boots	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Job	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Bostock	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Facts	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
upon	O
each	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Bellas	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Hancock	I-pers
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
February	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Bloxham	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Cocks	O
and	O
two	O
Hens	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Roger	B-pers
Meads	I-pers
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
February	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
7	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lyon	I-pers
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Esther	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Shift	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Linen	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Macey	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
February	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
,	I-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hammer	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Saws	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Postlethwait	I-pers
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Hester	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Rings	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Cadwel	I-pers
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Catlow	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Threlkald	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
Convict	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Meers	B-pers
Dunken	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Note	O
for	O
3	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Ambler	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
Convict	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
ten	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cotton	O
Cloth	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Horn	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
February	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Anne	B-pers
Farney	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Faith	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
February	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samuel	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wakelin	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Inglass	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Leather	O
Clog	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Gill	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Ingleton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
February	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Adderley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Orvius	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
China-Ware	O
Boat	O
,	O
and	O
six	O
Cups	O
and	O
Saucers	O
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
February	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
had	O
been	O
broken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
stolen	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
China	O
Ware	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Possession	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
He	O
selling	O
old	O
Clothes	O
about	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
met	O
a	O
Sailor	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
a	O
Sailor	O
's	O
Habit	O
,	O
who	O
wanted	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Clothes	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
and	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Holland	O
Trader	O
,	O
exchang	O
'd	O
the	O
China-Ware	O
for	O
the	O
Clothes	O
;	O
he	O
called	O
a	O
Witness	O
to	O
prove	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
appearing	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Man	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Simmonds	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Undershaft	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
8	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Oats	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Micajah	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Avery	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
Value	O
15s	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Wynn	I-pers
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Proof	O
of	O
the	O
stealing	O
the	O
Ring	O
,	O
not	O
being	O
satisfactory	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Speed	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Ruffin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bennet	I-place
's	I-place
Paul's-Wharf	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
and	I-pers
Christopher	I-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
stealing	O
45lb	O
.	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Candles	O
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Cellar-Door	O
had	O
been	O
open	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
Speed	O
was	O
found	O
sitting	O
as	O
if	O
a-sleep	O
in	O
the	O
Ware-house	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Sugar	O
put	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Sack	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
waiting	O
for	O
John	O
Rose	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
who	O
,	O
he	O
pretended	O
had	O
induc	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
Francis	O
Speed	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
only	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
John	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Alderman	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Stroud	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Belitha	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
leaden	O
Cistern	O
,	O
Value	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
30	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Iron	O
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Bell	B-place
Tavern	I-place
,	O
being	O
empty	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Bourn	O
,	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
seeing	O
a	O
Light	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Man	O
going	O
about	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
gave	O
Notice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Darby	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
who	O
going	O
with	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Shutter	O
and	O
Sash	O
had	O
been	O
broken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
concealed	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
but	O
nothing	O
had	O
been	O
carried	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
pleaded	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
late	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
there	O
to	O
lie	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
some	O
Persons	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
had	O
been	O
employ	O
'd	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
one	O
being	O
a	O
Bricklayer	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
a	O
Labourer	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Complaint	O
against	O
them	O
for	O
Dishonesty	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
they	O
had	O
work	O
'd	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
many	O
Opportunities	O
to	O
have	O
taken	O
Things	O
of	O
Value	O
;	O
upon	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Shell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Shadwel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Fluck	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
and	O
47l	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
hearing	O
a	O
Noise	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
about	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
Will	O
,	O
Jack	O
,	O
come	O
down	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
Thieves	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
a	O
brown	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Bob-Wig	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
,	O
Damn	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
made	O
any	O
Noise	O
,	O
he	O
'd	O
stab	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
jump	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Men	O
coming	O
down	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Window	O
had	O
been	O
broken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
he	O
suppos	O
'd	O
fell	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Tankard	O
when	O
he	O
Jump	O
'd	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Fluck	O
confirm	O
'd	O
her	O
Husband	O
's	O
Evidence	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
manner	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
as	O
to	O
seeing	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
like	O
was	O
done	O
by	O
Raymond	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
;	O
and	O
the	O
former	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
Man	O
perfectly	O
well	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
latter	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
George	B-pers
Shell	I-pers
was	O
the	O
Man	O
who	O
had	O
Robb	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
other	O
Man	O
;	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
how	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
Jump	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
Voice	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
his	O
Person	O
,	O
the	O
Night	O
being	O
pretty	O
Light	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
the	O
next	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
of	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
flung	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
nothing	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
Sarah	B-pers
Randal	I-pers
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
living	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
saw	O
him	O
put	O
on	O
his	O
Night-Cap	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Bed	O
that	O
Night	O
about	O
a	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Servant	O
being	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
rose	O
and	O
let	O
him	O
in	O
about	O
1	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Floyd	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
Captain	O
Udal	B-pers
about	O
12	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
past	O
1	O
o'Clock	O
when	O
his	O
Master	O
let	O
him	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
being	O
a	O
rainy	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
wet	O
he	O
sate	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
to	O
dry	O
himself	O
till	O
the	O
Watchman	O
call	O
'd	O
past	O
2	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
awake	O
above	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
never	O
heard	O
him	O
go	O
down	O
,	O
or	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
afterwards	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
of	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
;	O
and	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Prosecutor	O
were	O
near	O
Neighbours	O
and	O
Acquaintance	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
had	O
Robb	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
afterwards	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
angry	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
defam	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Fluck	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
mind	O
my	O
Husband	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
this	O
Prosecution	O
was	O
not	O
begun	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
had	O
serv	O
'd	O
a	O
Warrant	O
upon	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
for	O
Desamation	O
;	O
after	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Keys	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Hackney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murther	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
,	O
by	O
shooting	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
own	O
Confession	O
,	O
which	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
;	O
and	O
several	O
Evidences	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
deposing	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
perfectly	O
crazy	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
way	O
at	O
such	O
times	O
,	O
to	O
charge	O
himself	O
with	O
whatsoever	O
Crimes	O
he	O
had	O
heard	O
mentioned	O
of	O
any	O
other	O
Person	O
;	O
several	O
Instances	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
depos	O
'd	O
upon	O
Oath	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Christian	B-pers
Camden	I-pers
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
;	O
which	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Pomfrey	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Linen	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
February	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cotton	O
Gown	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Horn	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
February	O
;	O
which	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Doyle	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Returning	O
from	O
Transportation	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
Indictment	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Newcomb	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
the	O
Houses	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Philip	B-pers
Barret	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Hoar	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
steal	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Barret	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
going	O
upon	O
his	O
Leads	O
,	O
saw	O
a	O
Book	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Hoar	O
's	O
Door	O
open	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Laths	O
had	O
been	O
broken	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
a	O
Hand	O
might	O
be	O
put	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
open	O
the	O
Bolt	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
look	O
'd	O
over	O
the	O
Houses	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
some	O
Noise	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
running	O
a-cross	O
the	O
Leads	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
Black	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
a	O
Chimney	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
found	O
on	O
him	O
a	O
Sack	O
,	O
or	O
Wrapper	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Cock-lost	O
there	O
was	O
found	O
the	O
point	O
of	O
a	O
Sword	O
set	O
into	O
a	O
Handle	O
,	O
something	O
in	O
the	O
Form	O
of	O
a	O
Dagger	O
;	O
that	O
carrying	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
down	O
,	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
break	O
Mr.	O
Hoar	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
Rob	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Sack	O
,	O
or	O
Wrapper	O
,	O
to	O
put	O
into	O
it	O
what	O
he	O
should	O
get	O
.	O
Being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
how	O
he	O
got	O
thither	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
Serjeant's-Inn	O
in	O
Fleet-Street	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
a	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
got	O
out	O
upon	O
the	O
Leads	O
,	O
about	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lain	O
there	O
all	O
Night	O
,	O
laying	O
the	O
Sack	O
under	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
lie	O
the	O
easier	O
.	O
Being	O
sak	O
'd	O
about	O
the	O
Sword	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Point	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
designing	O
to	O
Rob	O
Mr.	O
Hoar	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
did	O
intend	O
to	O
have	O
kill	O
'd	O
himself	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
should	O
miscarry	O
in	O
his	O
Design	O
.	O
This	O
Confession	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
Several	O
other	O
Evidences	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Rowson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
,	O
Ravishing	O
,	O
and	O
Carnally	O
knowing	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bickle	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
Will	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Elizabeth	O
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
February	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bickle	I-pers
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
How	O
old	O
she	O
was	O
?	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
just	O
turn	O
'd	O
of	O
Ten	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
Long-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
promis	O
'd	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Penny	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Victuals	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
her	O
into	O
Islington	B-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
and	O
there	O
laid	O
her	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
down	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
put	O
his	O
Nastiness	O
into	O
her	O
Mouth	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
hurt	O
her	O
very	O
much	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Islington	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
smoaking	O
his	O
Pipe	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
cross	O
a	O
Field	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
Child	O
cry	O
out	O
;	O
that	O
thereupon	O
,	O
he	O
stood	O
still	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
discover	O
'd	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
Cap	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
made	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lying	O
upon	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
she	O
lying	O
on	O
her	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Legs	O
extended	O
,	O
the	O
Child	O
crying	O
out	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
his	O
private	O
Member	O
drawn	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
struggled	O
with	O
him	O
a	O
considerable	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
then	O
he	O
would	O
stay	O
with	O
him	O
all	O
Night	O
;	O
that	O
at	O
length	O
he	O
got	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Spow	O
,	O
and	O
thrust	O
him	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
secur	O
'd	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Goodman	O
,	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
examin	O
'd	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Depression	O
of	O
the	O
interior	O
Parts	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
press	O
'd	O
in	O
,	O
above	O
an	O
Inch	O
.	O
The	O
Child	O
being	O
young	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
fit	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
her	O
Oath	O
;	O
but	O
order	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
should	O
be	O
continu	O
'd	O
in	O
Goal	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
be	O
indicted	O
for	O
an	O
Assault	O
the	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
Walter	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sharp	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Queenhith	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Moidores	O
,	O
three	O
half	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Money	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
February	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Samuel	B-pers
Burrard	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Charteris	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
's	I-place
Hanover-Square	I-place
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
not	O
having	O
the	O
Fear	O
of	O
God	O
before	O
his	O
Eyes	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
moved	O
by	O
the	O
Instigation	O
of	O
the	O
Devil	O
,	O
did	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
Ravish	O
,	O
and	O
Carnally	O
know	O
Anne	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
Will	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Anne	O
Bond	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
Peace	O
of	O
our	O
Sovereign	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
his	O
Crown	O
and	O
Dignity	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
the	O
Statute	O
in	O
that	O
Case	O
made	O
and	O
provided	O
.	O
To	O
this	O
Indictment	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pleaded	O
not	O
Guilty	O
;	O
and	O
for	O
his	O
Trial	O
,	O
put	O
himself	O
upon	O
God	O
and	O
his	O
Country	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
After	O
a	O
long	O
Hearing	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
N.B	O
.	O
So	O
great	O
a	O
Variety	O
of	O
uncommon	O
Circumstances	O
occuring	O
in	O
the	O
Course	O
of	O
this	O
Trial	O
,	O
the	O
Publisher	O
is	O
oblig	O
'd	O
to	O
suspend	O
Publishing	O
them	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
Assizes	O
in	O
the	O
several	O
Counties	O
are	O
ended	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Judges	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
Town	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
printed	O
in	O
a	O
true	O
and	O
impartial	O
Manner	O
.	O
Ferdinando	B-pers
Shrimpton	I-pers
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Drummond	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Godfrey	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Hackney	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Simon	B-pers
Pechant	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Pistol-Bullet	O
in	O
the	O
Arm	O
,	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
3	O
Inches	O
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
;	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Drummond	I-pers
being	O
present	O
,	O
aiding	O
and	O
abetting	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
also	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Samuel	B-pers
Tyson	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Shrimpton	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
on	O
Sunday	O
,	O
about	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
in	O
Kingstand	O
Road	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
seeing	O
a	O
Light	O
,	O
rode	O
towards	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
being	O
on	O
Horse-back	O
,	O
and	O
himself	O
on	O
Foot	O
,	O
that	O
between	O
Kingstand	B-place
Road	I-place
and	O
the	O
Cock	B-place
,	O
Shrimpton	O
rode	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Chariot	O
and	O
fir	O
'd	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
and	O
Drummond	O
rode	O
to	O
the	O
Chariot	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Money	O
;	O
but	O
his	O
Horse	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
near	O
enough	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
Shrimpton	O
rode	O
up	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
your	O
Money	O
,	O
your	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
your	O
Rings	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
himself	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
Cause-way	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
bid	O
him	O
Dismount	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Lad	O
tumbled	O
off	O
the	O
Horse	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
rode	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
took	O
off	O
the	O
Saddle	O
,	O
and	O
turn	O
'd	O
the	O
Horse	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
Drummond	O
's	O
House	O
a	O
pretty	O
way	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
shar	O
'd	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
Drummond	O
valuing	O
the	O
Watch	O
at	O
45	O
s.	O
allowing	O
them	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Drummond	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
must	O
pay	O
their	O
share	O
of	O
a	O
Quarters	O
Rent	O
of	O
his	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
then	O
Drummond	O
kept	O
the	O
Watch	O
himself	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Tyson	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
Home	O
in	O
his	O
Chariot	O
with	O
a	O
Light	O
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
he	O
hearing	O
a	O
Pistol	O
go	O
off	O
,	O
let	O
down	O
the	O
Window	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Men	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
your	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
your	O
Rings	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
observ	O
'd	O
two	O
Men	O
on	O
Horse-back	O
and	O
one	O
on	O
Foot	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
them	O
his	O
Watch	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
they	O
demanding	O
his	O
Rings	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Chariot	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
wore	O
none	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
more	O
;	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
,	O
damn	O
you	O
,	O
come	O
away	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
came	O
Home	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
;	O
that	O
his	O
Servant	O
was	O
shot	O
in	O
the	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
died	O
8	O
Days	O
after	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Parry	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
County	O
Goal	O
of	O
Surry	O
,	O
the	O
Watch	O
Mr.	O
Tyson	O
own	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
,	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
Drummond	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
at	O
a	O
Publick-House	O
in	O
the	O
City	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Robinson	O
,	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
before	O
his	O
receiving	O
that	O
Wound	O
,	O
was	O
in	O
perfect	O
Health	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
the	O
Fever	O
was	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
former	O
Evidence	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
Anthony	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
some	O
Persons	O
to	O
their	O
Character	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
availing	O
not	O
,	O
against	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Ferdinando	O
Shrimpton	O
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Drummond	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
,	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Robert	B-pers
Furnel	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Gelding	O
,	O
Value	O
12	O
l.	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Whip	O
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
riding	O
from	O
Hammersmith	B-place
to	O
Turnham-Green	B-place
,	O
three	O
Men	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
stand	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Whip	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
thinks	O
it	O
was	O
William	B-pers
Shrimpton	I-pers
took	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Shrimpton	O
his	O
Whip	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
third	O
Man	O
,	O
was	O
of	O
the	O
size	O
of	O
Drummond	O
.	O
That	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
yours	O
is	O
a	O
good	O
Horse	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
desiring	O
them	O
not	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
Horse	O
;	O
they	O
reply	O
'd	B-pers
,	I-pers
D	I-pers
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
Horse	O
for	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Horse	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
bigger	O
than	O
a	O
Jack	B-pers
Ass	I-pers
;	O
that	O
there	O
having	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
Waggons	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
3	O
Men	O
were	O
taken	O
at	O
Weybridge	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
going	O
thither	O
,	O
found	O
his	O
Watch	O
at	O
Esquire	O
Hapton	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Horse	O
at	O
the	O
Inn	O
in	O
Weybridge	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Prison	O
in	O
Southwark	O
,	O
Shrimpton	O
said	O
,	O
we	O
gave	O
you	O
a	O
little	O
Horse	O
,	O
that	O
we	O
had	O
taken	O
from	O
a	O
Drover	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Shrimpton	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
being	O
between	O
Acton	O
and	O
Turnham-Green	O
,	O
Ferdinando	O
Shrimpton	O
hearing	O
2	O
Men	O
riding	O
along	O
,	O
they	O
rode	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
Ferdinando	O
Shrimpton	O
attack	O
'd	O
Furnel	O
,	O
and	O
Drummond	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
taking	O
their	O
Horses	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
they	O
rode	O
towards	O
Brentford	O
,	O
but	O
gave	O
him	O
no	O
share	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
likewise	O
.	O
Ferdinando	O
Shrimpton	O
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Drummond	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
a	O
4th	O
time	O
,	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Cockup	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Bay	O
Gelding	O
,	O
Value	O
10	O
l.	O
2	O
Hampers	O
,	O
5	O
rosting	O
Pigs	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Joints	O
of	O
Pork	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
in	O
Hampstead-Road	B-place
,	O
near	O
the	O
Halfway-house	O
,	O
about	O
6	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
3	O
Men	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
positive	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
2	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Shrimpton	I-pers
the	O
third	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
3	O
on	O
Horse-back	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
London	O
with	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
desiring	O
them	O
not	O
to	O
rob	O
a	O
poor	O
Man	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
take	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
he	O
had	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
not	O
letting	O
go	O
his	O
Horse	O
's	O
Bridle	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
struck	O
him	O
a	O
Blow	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Eye	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
the	O
Fire	O
fly	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
drove	O
away	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
Panniers	O
,	O
with	O
Pigs	O
,	O
Spare-ribs	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
before	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
afterwards	O
hearing	O
at	O
Cheshunt	O
,	O
that	O
3	O
Men	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Weybridge	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
found	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Shrimpton	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
Morning	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
committed	O
the	O
Robbery	O
on	O
Justice	O
Tyson	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
together	O
to	O
Hampsteads	O
,	O
and	O
meeting	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
near	O
the	O
Half-way-house	O
,	O
they	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
before	O
sworn	O
;	O
that	O
Ferdinando	O
Shrimpton	O
,	O
drove	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Horse	O
so	O
fast	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Panniers	O
turn	O
'd	O
round	O
under	O
the	O
Horse	O
's	O
Belly	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Pigs	O
,	O
and	O
Pork	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Panniers	O
in	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
and	O
Drummond	O
rode	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Horse	O
,	O
till	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
at	O
Weybridge	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Simonds	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
about	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
inform	O
'd	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
3	O
suspicious	O
Persons	O
at	O
the	O
Anchor-Inn	O
at	O
Weybridge	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
acquainted	O
some	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
them	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
furnishing	O
himself	O
with	O
Fire-Arms	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Weapons	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Anchor-Inn	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Inn-yard	O
