TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
For	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
AND	O
ON	O
The	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
,	O
Monday	O
,	O
and	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
16th	O
,	O
17th	O
,	O
19th	O
,	O
and	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
1730	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Third	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	O
BROCAS	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Lord	O
Chief	B-pers
Baron	I-pers
Pengelly	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Reynolds	O
,	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Fortescue	O
,	O
the	O
Worshipful	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
Raby	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
:	O
John	B-pers
Chillingworth	I-pers
.	O
James	B-pers
Welsh	I-pers
.	O
James	B-pers
Wellder	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Stokes	I-pers
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Driver	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Allery	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Winston	I-pers
.	O
Erasmus	B-pers
Dangerfield	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Prater	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Goodge	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Gillmore	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Fortescue	I-pers
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Fairchild	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Bilson	I-pers
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Wrenn	I-pers
John	B-pers
Powers	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
Pound	O
of	O
Bees-Wax	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Alice	B-pers
Innis	I-pers
,	O
December	O
9	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Innis	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
December	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
Shop	O
about	O
Eight	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
them	O
call	O
out	O
,	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
;	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
Cake	O
of	O
Bees-Wax	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
knew	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
,	O
by	O
some	O
Soil	O
it	O
had	O
received	O
from	O
the	O
Carts	O
passing	O
by	O
,	O
it	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
Window	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Legg	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
House	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
my	O
Wife	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
loitering	O
about	O
,	O
called	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
get	O
upon	O
the	O
Groove	O
of	O
the	O
Shutters	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
something	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
something	O
,	O
seized	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
take	O
up	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
drop	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
hearing	O
a	O
cry	O
of	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
he	O
run	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
two	O
Yards	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
stumbled	O
on	O
the	O
Cake	O
of	O
Bees-Wax	O
;	O
which	O
Wax	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Rudruff	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
coming	O
by	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Legg	O
running	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drop	O
the	O
Wax	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
Coat	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
no	O
Defence	O
worth	O
repeating	O
,	O
nor	O
had	O
any	O
Person	O
to	O
call	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Chadwick	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Queenhithe	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
7	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
from	O
Richard	B-pers
Peers	I-pers
,	O
December	O
15	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Peers	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
having	O
lost	O
Money	O
several	O
times	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Drawer	O
,	O
notwithstanding	O
it	O
was	O
always	O
kept	O
Lock	O
'd	O
;	O
he	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
marked	O
several	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
watching	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
a	O
Key	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
open	O
the	O
Drawer	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
order	O
'd	O
a	O
Person	O
to	O
borrow	O
some	O
Money	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lent	O
him	O
3	O
s.	O
amongst	O
which	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
that	O
was	O
mark	O
'd	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
charged	O
a	O
Constable	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
searching	O
him	O
,	O
found	O
seven	O
mark	O
'd	O
Shillings	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Neal	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
upon	O
searching	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Pockets	O
and	O
his	O
Box	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
Key	O
and	O
seven	O
mark	O
'd	O
Shillings	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Drawer	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
Fault	O
he	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
;	O
and	O
his	O
Master	O
said	O
he	O
believed	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
his	O
first	O
Offence	O
,	O
having	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
of	O
him	O
from	O
whence	O
he	O
came	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bennett	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Lacey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Ware	I-pers
,	O
(	O
three	O
Boy	O
s	O
)	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary-At-Hill	I-place
,	I-place
Billinsgate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
56	O
Pound	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
Nov.	O
25	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
were	O
such	O
as	O
they	O
call	O
Feezers	O
,	O
that	O
lurk	O
about	O
the	O
Keys	O
,	O
and	O
lie	O
at	O
the	O
Glass-Houses	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
got	O
into	O
a	O
Warehouse	O
at	O
Smarts-Key	O
,	O
by	O
means	O
of	O
the	O
Crane	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
off	O
the	O
Goods	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
in	O
their	O
Aprons	O
;	O
the	O
Aprons	O
,	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Andrew	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary-At-Hill	I-place
,	I-place
Billinsgate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
112	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
value	O
28	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
Nov.	O
24	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Oliver	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
Boy	O
and	O
Confederate	O
)	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
stealing	O
the	O
112	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Sugar	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
none	O
but	O
Boys	O
could	O
get	O
in	O
,	O
a	O
board	O
being	O
broken	O
down	O
,	O
one	O
Gilbert	O
,	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
got	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
handed	O
out	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Sugar	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
in	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
about	O
30	O
lb	O
.	O
which	O
she	O
sold	O
at	O
an	O
Apple-Shop	O
in	O
New	O
Ragg-Fair	O
-	O
Jane	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
was	O
with	O
Martin	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
meddle	O
with	O
the	O
Sugar	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
she	O
carry	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Cornish	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
Boy	O
that	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
Bridewell	O
)	O
got	O
the	O
Sugar	O
out	O
for	O
Andrew	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
,	O
I	O
see	O
it	O
handed	O
out	O
through	O
the	O
Crane	O
:	O
Scott	O
stood	O
upon	O
the	O
Ladder	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
long	O
Baggs	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
hundred	O
Pound	O
Weight	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
't	O
was	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
Night	O
25th	O
of	O
Nov	O
.	O
Atkins	O
Moore	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
took	O
Scott	O
at	O
Bea-Key	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
him	O
in	O
Custody	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Rapson	O
;	O
that	O
Scott	O
got	O
away	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
Oliver	O
's	O
Direction	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
December	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Scott	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Glass-house	O
in	O
Rosemary-Lane	O
.	O
Scott	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
body	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
said	O
,	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Oliver	O
had	O
been	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
his	O
own	O
Brother	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
Scott	O
and	O
Martin	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
Fowles	O
,	O
alias	O
Fowler	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Hutchins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Mary-At-Hill	I-place
,	I-place
Billinsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
ten	O
Pound	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
Nov.	O
23	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
Sugar	O
was	O
all	O
out	O
of	O
one	O
Warehouse	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
Boy	B-pers
)	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary-At-Hill	I-place
,	I-place
Billinsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
fifty-six	O
Pound	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
value	O
fifteen	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
Nov.	O
25	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Oliver	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stole	O
the	O
Sugar	O
.	O
Atkins	O
Moore	O
(	O
the	O
Constable	O
)	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Hugh	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Thomas	I-place
Apostles	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
12	O
Pound	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
a	O
wooden	O
Box	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Horton	I-pers
,	O
September	O
8	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Horton	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
About	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
November	O
I	O
was	O
inform	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
my	O
Man	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
had	O
sold	O
a	O
Box	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Asplin	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Ship	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
Tower-street	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
charged	O
a	O
Constable	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
Tobacco	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Darrant	O
in	O
Thames-street	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Darrant	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
Tobacco	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
three	O
Boxes	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
since	O
May	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
last	O
he	O
bought	O
of	O
him	O
was	O
Saffron	O
cut	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
which	O
he	O
sold	O
Mr.	O
Asplin	O
was	O
Square	O
cut	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
four	O
Days	O
,	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
Tobacco	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Asplin	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
On	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
September	O
I	O
bought	O
a	O
Box	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
him	O
14	O
s.	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
desired	O
a	O
Receipt	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
one	O
,	O
though	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Name	O
:	O
On	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
's	O
Day	O
he	O
called	O
on	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
wanted	O
any	O
more	O
-	O
I	O
generally	O
buy	O
my	O
Tobacco	O
of	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Harrison	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
why	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
sell	O
as	O
cheap	O
as	O
another	O
,	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
buy	O
as	O
good	O
for	O
14	O
d.	O
as	O
she	O
made	O
me	O
pay	O
18	O
d.	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
her	O
know	O
who	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Horton	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
never	O
sold	O
me	O
any	O
,	O
otherwise	O
Mr.	O
Horton	O
had	O
known	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
Anthony	O
Newman	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
asked	O
pardon	O
when	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ceely	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
when	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
owned	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Tobacco	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
wronged	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
Masters	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
intended	O
to	O
give	O
his	O
Master	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
forgot	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
two	O
Months	O
time	O
between	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
being	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
receiving	O
the	O
Money	O
for	O
the	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Katharine	B-pers
Pember	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
one	O
Moidore	O
,	O
one	O
broad	O
Piece	O
,	O
value	O
23	O
s.	O
three	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
Pounds	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
,	O
November	O
1	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
Coming	O
down	O
Cornhill	O
with	O
a	O
Friend	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
another	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
afraid	O
of	O
Street-Robbers	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
Friend	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
accepted	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
,	O
as	O
we	O
thought	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
Danger	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
for	O
returning	O
back	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
we	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
Sisters	O
in	O
Chick-Lane	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
treat	O
us	O
with	O
a	O
Fowl	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Black	B-place
Boy	I-place
in	I-place
Black	I-place
Boy-Alley	I-place
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Tiff	O
of	O
Punch	O
,	O
(	O
it	O
being	O
a	O
publick	O
House	O
,	O
)	O
but	O
after	O
staying	O
there	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
not	O
very	O
well	O
liking	O
the	O
Place	O
,	O
called	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
I	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
my	O
Purse	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
it	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
kissed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
picked	O
my	O
Pocket	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Moidore	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
in	O
Trade	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
something	O
dubious	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
them	O
to	O
change	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
,	O
so	O
paid	O
them	O
in	O
other	O
Money	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
Money	O
not	O
two	O
Minutes	O
before	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
kiss	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
but	O
just	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
before	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
very	O
same	O
Effect	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
their	O
manner	O
of	O
coming	O
there	O
,	O
adding	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
his	O
Friend	O
complain	O
to	O
the	O
Landlord	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
Money	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
upwards	O
of	O
Nine	O
Pounds	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
kiss	O
him	O
,	O
or	O
take	O
his	O
Money	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
this	O
Effect	O
;	O
Sometime	O
ago	O
being	O
in	O
Wood-street	O
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
spoke	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
Matter	O
made	O
up	O
with	O
Bailey	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
six	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
Moidore	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
-	O
The	O
next	O
Day	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
five	O
Guineas	O
and	O
the	O
Moidore	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
Bailey	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
for	O
my	O
self	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
Mr.	O
Bailey	O
was	O
averse	O
to	O
making	O
of	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
Wright	O
said	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
Pember	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
that	O
goes	O
for	O
her	O
Husband	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Weller	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Pember	O
and	O
Wright	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
made	O
up	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
declared	O
the	O
Cole	O
was	O
sunk	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
had	O
five	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
Moidore	O
left	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
a	O
Note	O
for	O
the	O
rest	O
-	O
said	O
that	O
his	O
Wife	O
was	O
Drunk	O
in	O
Bed	O
-	O
this	O
Deponent	O
faith	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sent	O
several	O
times	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
desiring	O
him	O
to	O
prevail	O
with	O
Bailey	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
offer	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
for	O
Ten	O
Guineas	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
refus	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
Denby	O
Pierce	O
(	O
who	O
keeps	O
the	O
House	O
)	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
two	O
Men	O
and	O
two	O
Women	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
the	O
Men	O
were	O
fuddled	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
merry	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Tiff	O
of	O
Punch	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
three	O
Bowls	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
him	O
Ten	O
Shillings	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
Bailey	O
went	O
out	O
several	O
times	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
Twelve	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
Bailey	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Friend	O
asked	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
Lodging	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
told	O
them	O
his	O
Beds	O
were	O
full	O
-	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
with	O
some	O
others	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
this	O
Deponent	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
Ten	O
Pounds	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
no	O
Warrant	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
nor	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
it	O
-	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
did	O
offer	O
him	O
a	O
Moidore	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
Change	O
it	O
-	O
And	O
that	O
Pember	O
goes	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Husband	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
drink	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
them	O
together	O
in	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
Russel-Street	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bailey	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
up	O
with	O
a	O
Warrant	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
she	O
used	O
Mr.	O
Warwick	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Warrant	O
against	O
her	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
another	O
Woman	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
touched	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
swear	O
her	O
Life	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
away	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Harry	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Warwick	O
's	O
House	O
when	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
Barnic	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
say	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Bailey	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
had	O
Cloaths	O
that	O
she	O
might	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
raise	O
Money	O
upon	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
refus	O
'd	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Poor	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Pierce	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
Gentlemen	O
disguiz	O
'd	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
thanked	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
treated	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
called	O
for	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Bowls	O
of	O
Punch	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Bailey	O
was	O
sick	O
,	O
and	O
cast	O
up	O
his	O
Accompts	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
see	O
him	O
offer	O
a	O
Moidore	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
good	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Curtis	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
heard	O
James	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
say	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
up	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
if	O
he	O
waited	O
,	O
(	O
or	O
Watched	O
)	O
the	O
whole	O
Winter	O
.	O
N.	O
B.	O
Lewis	O
,	O
is	O
one	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
accuses	O
with	O
pushing	O
on	O
this	O
Prosecution	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Pierce	I-pers
(	O
Wife	O
of	O
Denby	O
Pierce	O
)	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
my	O
Sister	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
kept	O
her	O
this	O
two	O
Years	O
;	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
before	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
but	O
since	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
Married	O
she	O
has	O
lived	O
very	O
honestly	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
not	O
wanted	O
for	O
Victuals	O
and	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
for	O
Cloaths	O
she	O
had	O
enough	O
before	O
.	O
Bailey	O
says	O
further	O
,	O
That	O
upon	O
offering	O
to	O
take	O
Anne	B-pers
Pierce	I-pers
's	O
Husband	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
D	O
-	O
the	O
B	O
-	O
ch	O
,	O
my	O
Husband	O
shall	O
not	O
come	O
into	O
trouble	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
have	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
,	I-place
without	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Hannabell	I-pers
,	O
December	O
30	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hannabell	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
Coming	O
home	O
between	O
2	O
and	O
3	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
crossed	O
the	O
Way	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
see	O
me	O
home	O
;	O
and	O
immediately	O
put	O
her	O
Hand	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
Money	O
;	O
am	O
certain	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
just	O
before	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
two	O
half	O
Crowns	O
:	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
it	O
soon	O
after	O
she	O
left	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
inquired	O
of	O
the	O
Watchman	O
a	O
fter	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
Stocks-Market	O
,	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
two	O
Soldiers	O
,	O
go	O
into	O
an	O
Ale-House	O
cross	O
the	O
Market	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
be	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Same	O
Person	O
before	O
I	O
charged	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
is	O
the	O
Woman	O
that	O
came	O
cross	O
the	O
Way	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
Money	O
in	O
a	O
Minute	O
's	O
time	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Westminster	O
with	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Stocks-Market	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
sitting	O
between	O
two	O
Chimney-Sweepers	O
,	O
that	O
soon	O
afterwards	O
she	O
had	O
an	O
occasion	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
to	O
do	O
what	O
no	O
body	O
could	O
do	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
her	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Rods	O
to	O
whip	O
him	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
she	O
whipt	O
no	O
Body	O
besides	O
her	O
Children	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
one	O
Person	O
to	O
call	O
to	O
her	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Alice	B-pers
Strutt	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Stephen	I-place
's	I-place
Coleman-Street	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
for	O
stealing	O
twenty	O
five	O
Yards	O
of	O
Linen	O
Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
a	O
Damask	O
table	O
Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Clouds	I-pers
,	O
January	O
3	O
.	O
and	O
Alice	B-pers
Strutt	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
;	O
the	O
Facts	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Body	O
being	O
called	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Jones	O
:	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Strutt	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Phips	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Allaway	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Fairbrother	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Phips	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Allaway	I-pers
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Barrel	O
of	O
Small-Beer	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
s.	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Fairbrother	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Browning	I-pers
,	O
November	O
14	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
Richard	B-pers
Phips	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Allaway	I-pers
were	O
Servant	O
s	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Browning	O
,	O
and	O
intrusted	O
by	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
his	O
Dray	O
;	O
and	O
lay	O
down	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
the	O
laying	O
down	O
a	O
barrel	O
of	O
Beer	O
at	O
a	O
wrong	O
Place	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
amount	O
to	O
Felony	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bennett	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
's	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Cheeses	O
value	O
,	O
8s	O
.	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Solomon	B-pers
Fosset	I-pers
,	O
January	O
3	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Dalton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
in	O
assaulting	O
Dr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Mead	I-pers
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
rob	O
him	O
of	O
his	O
Money	O
and	O
Goods	O
,	O
December	O
1	O
.	O
Dr.	O
Mead	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
driving	O
through	O
Holbourn	O
on	O
Monday	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
near	O
Leather-Lane	B-place
,	O
a	O
Person	O
much	O
like	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
his	O
Chariot	O
side	O
,	O
in	O
great	O
haste	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
his	O
Watch	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Footman	O
jumpt	O
down	O
from	O
behind	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Person	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
my	O
Footman	O
run	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
Edmund	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Coachman	O
,	O
bid	O
him	O
stop	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
would	O
shoot	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
comes	O
to	O
the	O
Chariot	O
side	O
,	O
presented	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
stir	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
,	O
demanded	O
my	O
Watch	O
and	O
Money	O
;	O
I	O
jumpt	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
a	O
Shopkeeper	O
run	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
flash	O
'd	O
a	O
Pistol	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
grazed	O
on	O
his	O
Face	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
never	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
sight	O
,	O
while	O
taken	O
;	O
the	O
Pistol	O
he	O
dropt	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
when	O
pursued	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
making	O
towards	O
Leather-Lane	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
we	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Black	O
Bull-Inn	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
shot	O
and	O
powder	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Dr.	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
Charge	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
Penknife	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
large	O
shot	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
could	O
not	O
hang	O
him	O
for	O
this	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
wished	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
Murther	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
rather	O
be	O
hanged	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Brearcliff	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
shutting	O
up	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
them	O
cry	O
,	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
I	O
stopt	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
shoot	O
me	O
,	O
flashed	O
his	O
Pistol	O
in	O
the	O
Pan	O
,	O
which	O
grazed	O
on	O
my	O
Face	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
going	O
up	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
near	O
Leather-Lane	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
Person	O
call	O
,	O
Hold	O
-	O
Coachman	O
,	O
stop	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
thought	O
some	O
Body	O
had	O
wanted	O
his	O
Master	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
stopt	O
,	O
then	O
a	O
little	O
Man	O
,	O
much	O
like	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
presented	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
stop	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
shoot	O
him	O
through	O
the	O
Body	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Fine	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Provide	O
sureties	O
for	O
good	O
behaviour	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Katharine	B-pers
Carrol	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Silver	O
Snuff-Boxes	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
thirty-six	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Seal	O
,	O
value	O
35	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Dunant	I-pers
;	O
and	O
Patrick	B-pers
Macromack	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Cragg	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Tees	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
,	O
Nov.	O
19	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Dunant	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
November	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
too	O
much	O
Liquor	O
,	O
that	O
in	O
his	O
return	O
Home	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
some	O
Liquor	O
that	O
would	O
set	O
him	O
to	O
rights	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
Girl	O
brought	O
him	O
some	O
Brandy	O
about	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
;	O
he	O
fell	O
fast	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
waked	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
Money	O
and	O
Goods	O
,	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
surprized	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Woman	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Mitchell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
seven	O
Sacks	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
28	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Oats	O
,	O
value	O
46	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hammack	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
21	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
Sacks	O
,	O
and	O
twenty-four	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Wheat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
November	O
28	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
lost	O
three	O
Quarters	O
of	O
Wheat	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Boat	O
over-against	O
Deptford	B-place
,	O
with	O
the	O
Sacks	O
,	O
his	O
Name	O
was	O
five	O
of	O
the	O
Sacks	O
MWW	O
the	O
other	O
Sack	O
was	O
not	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Wheat	O
at	O
Creek-menti-House	O
near	O
Barkin	O
in	O
Essex	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
brought	O
it	O
for	O
Sale	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
charged	O
in	O
Custody	O
of	O
an	O
Officer	O
,	O
he	O
pretended	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
adrift	O
in	O
a	O
Boat	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Ralph	B-pers
Mitchell	I-pers
came	O
with	O
Paul	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
that	O
is	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
the	O
Wheat	O
to	O
Sale	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
an	O
Officer	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
found	O
it	O
adrift	O
,	O
the	O
Sacks	O
marked	O
,	O
excepting	O
one	O
MWW	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
intrusted	O
by	O
the	O
deceased	O
Paul	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
,	O
had	O
so	O
much	O
a	O
Week	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hammack	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
seven	O
Sacks	O
of	O
Oats	O
from	O
Westminster	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
Sacks	O
at	O
Creek's-Mouth	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
marked	O
T.	O
Hammack	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Langfield	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Paul	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
brought	O
the	O
Oats	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
them	O
for	O
Sale	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
per	O
Quarter	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
help	O
'd	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
Sacks	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Boat	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Deceased	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Second	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nosely	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
Boy	O
)	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
fifty	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Manning	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Rich	O
.	O
Manning	O
,	O
Jan.	O
10	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Manning	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
tied	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Black	O
Stockings	O
for	O
a	O
Customer	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
Eight	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
or	O
hear	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
them	O
till	O
Monday	O
Night	O
;	O
John	B-pers
May	I-pers
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
Boy	O
creeping	O
into	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Boy	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
confessed	O
,	O
that	O
himself	O
,	O
with	O
two	O
others	O
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
stole	O
the	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
King	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
9	O
d.	O
for	O
his	O
Share	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
sensible	O
then	O
of	O
his	O
Loss	O
,	O
notwithstanding	O
he	O
was	O
told	O
the	O
Boy	O
had	O
new	O
Stockings	O
on	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
none	O
of	O
mine	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
missing	O
four	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
he	O
examin	O
'd	O
the	O
Boy	O
further	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confessed	O
that	O
one	O
Booth	O
and	O
himself	O
stole	O
the	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
at	O
three	O
different	O
Places	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
7	O
s.	O
for	O
his	O
Share	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Stockings	O
he	O
had	O
on	O
;	O
which	O
Stockings	O
being	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
,	O
they	O
having	O
his	O
Mark	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pawlins	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
creep	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
on	O
his	O
Hands	O
and	O
Knees	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
behind	O
the	O
Compter	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
there	O
?	O
and	O
he	O
answered	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
tie	O
his	O
Garters	O
.	O
John	B-pers
May	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lightinhouse	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
have	O
the	O
Stockings	O
on	O
that	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
;	O
his	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
was	O
read	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4s	O
.	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
and	O
Martha	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
of	O
Enfield	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
15s	O
.	O
twenty-five	O
pound	O
of	O
Mutton	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
forty-five	O
pound	O
of	O
Beef	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Elsom	I-pers
,	O
December	O
6	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Elsom	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
stole	O
them	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hancock	I-pers
(	O
a	O
Boy	O
of	O
about	O
twelve	O
Years	O
old	O
)	O
was	O
the	O
chief	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
an	O
Errand	O
Boy	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Elsom	O
,	O
was	O
used	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Richard	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
asked	O
him	O
,	O
how	O
he	O
might	O
get	O
in	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Elsom	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
shook	O
the	O
Door	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
it	O
would	O
open	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
got	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
out	O
a	O
Lap-full	O
of	O
Meat	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
Home	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
promised	O
him	O
Two	O
Pence	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
having	O
no	O
Half-pence	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
had	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hancock	I-pers
(	O
the	O
Boy	O
's	O
Mother	O
)	O
and	O
Lucy	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
who	O
nursed	O
her	O
,	O
flatly	O
contradicted	O
his	O
Evidence	O
,	O
for	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
Boy	O
had	O
depos	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
them	O
commit	O
this	O
Robbery	O
,	O
they	O
both	O
swore	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
Home	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Bed	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Slighter	I-pers
,	O
Deputy-Constable	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
being	O
sent	O
by	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
the	O
High	O
Constable	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
them	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
;	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
so	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Boy	O
had	O
swore	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
got	O
but	O
a	O
very	O
little	O
distance	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Boy	O
,	O
Hancock	O
,	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
If	O
kissing	O
the	O
Book	O
was	O
Swearing	O
?	O
He	O
was	O
told	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
the	O
Boy	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
thought	O
Swearing	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
have	O
swore	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
they	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
could	O
have	O
out-swore	O
them	O
all	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
material	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Boy	O
having	O
but	O
an	O
ill	O
Character	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bridle	O
and	O
Saddle	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Benton	I-pers
,	O
October	O
31	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brown	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Benton	I-pers
,	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
October	O
31	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
Richard	B-pers
Benton	I-pers
kept	O
Horses	O
to	O
Lett	O
out	O
for	O
Hire	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
hired	O
this	O
Horse	O
,	O
Bridle	O
and	O
Saddle	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Edgworth	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
return	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
went	O
farther	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
brought	O
the	O
Horse	O
again	O
:	O
But	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Opinion	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Person	O
who	O
hired	O
a	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
deliver	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
notwithstanding	O
he	O
kept	O
him	O
longer	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
return	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
appointed	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
chang	O
'd	O
his	O
Horse	O
away	O
for	O
a	O
less	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
Guinea	O
with	O
the	O
little	O
Horse	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Sulivan	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Wall	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Stanley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Isabella	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
26	O
l.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Burroughs	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
October	O
16	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
two	O
Guineas	O
from	O
Henry	B-pers
Crew	I-pers
,	O
October	O
25	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Burroughs	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Standard	B-place
Tavern	I-place
in	I-place
Leicester-Fields	I-place
with	O
some	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
separate	O
Room	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
Mr.	O
Burroughs	O
's	O
Company	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
asked	O
,	O
what	O
Room	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
?	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Burroughs	O
being	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
off	O
his	O
Finger	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Sullivan	I-pers
owned	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
Eaton	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
came	O
when	O
sober	O
and	O
described	O
Sullivan	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
search	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
at	O
a	O
Brandy	O
shop	O
in	O
Shugg-Lane	O
,	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
was	O
at	O
our	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
promised	O
to	O
bring	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
came	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
West	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Drawer	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
one	O
Morning	O
to	O
ask	O
after	O
the	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Sullivan	O
who	O
was	O
then	O
her	O
Mistress	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
the	O
Crown	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Sherrard-Street	O
,	O
ordered	O
her	O
not	O
to	O
own	O
her	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Wilkins	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
Mrs.	O
Eaton	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
cut	O
out	O
some	O
Shifts	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
with	O
Eaton	O
all	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Eaton	O
was	O
not	O
Abroad	O
that	O
Evening	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Robbery	O
being	O
committed	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
her	O
Evidence	O
was	O
of	O
no	O
weight	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
had	O
mistaken	O
the	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
Month	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Harvey	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
accused	O
her	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
thereupon	O
she	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
Prison	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Crew	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
Last	O
Saturday	O
night	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
from	O
Leicester-Fields	O
towards	O
Bolton-Street	O
,	O
a	O
Woman	O
met	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
begged	O
of	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
turning	O
about	O
,	O
she	O
walked	O
close	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asking	O
me	O
again	O
for	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
we	O
agreed	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Crown	B-place
Tavern	I-place
in	I-place
Sherrard-Street	I-place
,	O
and	O
there	O
an	O
old	O
Man	O
lighted	O
us	O
up	O
Stairs	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
brought	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
we	O
had	O
drank	O
it	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Sullivan	I-pers
comes	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
says	O
to	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
hussy	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
here	O
?	O
get	O
you	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Woman	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
Sullivan	O
stayed	O
;	O
when	O
that	O
Pint	O
was	O
out	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
Sullivan	O
went	O
and	O
fetched	O
it	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
for	O
the	O
last	O
Pint	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
my	O
Money	O
;	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
brought	O
up	O
the	O
Wine	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
little	O
Conversation	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
fell	O
to	O
playing	O
at	O
'my	O
Cod-piece	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
second	O
time	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
heard	O
my	O
Money	O
chink	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
If	O
she	O
was	O
Mistress	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
,	O
instead	O
of	O
a	O
better	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
upon	O
that	O
she	O
swore	O
G	O
-	O
D	O
-	O
you	O
,	O
pay	O
your	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
and	O
get	O
you	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
pay	O
my	O
reckoning	O
then	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
my	O
Money	O
;	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
Pen	O
and	O
Ink	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
none	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
called	O
a	O
Watchman	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
hurry	O
,	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
instead	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
Round-House	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
were	O
none	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
till	O
after	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
shut	O
up	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
told	O
by	O
Eaton	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
I	O
came	O
some	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
chance	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
;	O
Anne	B-pers
Cragg	I-pers
was	O
the	O
Woman	O
that	O
first	O
pick	O
'd	O
me	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
touched	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
Warrant	O
against	O
Eaton	O
and	O
Sullivan	O
,	O
but	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
Sullivan	O
,	O
is	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
her	O
dress	O
hath	O
made	O
such	O
an	O
Alteration	O
.	O
Swiney	O
(	O
the	O
old	O
Fellow	O
,	O
that	O
conducted	O
them	O
up	O
Stairs	O
)	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
Nan	B-pers
Crago	I-pers
,	O
and	O
she	O
has	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
Whore	O
and	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
there	O
in	O
Company	O
till	O
she	O
had	O
drank	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
second	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Cragg	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
smoked	O
a	O
Pipe	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
believe	O
Cragg	O
,	O
(	O
who	O
is	O
since	O
run	O
away	O
)	O
had	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
West	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
Servant	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
only	O
see	O
it	O
shar	O
'd	O
between	O
Anne	B-pers
Cragg	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Sullivan	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Isabella	O
Eaton	O
,	O
they	O
shar	O
'd	O
the	O
two	O
Guineas	O
amongst	O
them	O
,	O
allowing	O
for	O
the	O
two	O
Pints	O
of	O
Wine	O
;	O
before	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
shar	O
'd	O
,	O
Cragg	O
made	O
a	O
great	O
Noise	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
leave	O
the	O
House	O
till	O
she	O
had	O
her	O
Part	O
.	O
Being	O
asked	O
(	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
)	O
how	O
they	O
shar	O
'd	O
the	O
Money	O
?	O
she	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
when	O
Money	O
was	O
taken	O
-	O
asked	O
,	O
how	O
taken	O
?	O
-	O
she	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
pick	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
Gentlemen	O
's	O
Pockets	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
share	O
ten	O
Guineas	O
of	O
a	O
Night	O
on	O
that	O
Account	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Harvey	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
West	O
was	O
a	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
long	O
harangue	O
about	O
two	O
Plates	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
her	O
having	O
Money	O
for	O
being	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
of	O
both	O
the	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Gatehouse	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Pinners	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Copper-Pot	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
two	O
Napkins	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
two	O
Musling	O
Caps	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pewter-dish	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Edmunds	I-pers
,	O
November	O
5	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Poole	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Burroughs	I-pers
,	O
November	O
5	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Recognizance	O
was	O
order	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
Estreated	O
.	O
Matth.ew	B-pers
Greenaway	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cotton	O
Apron	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Copper	O
Pot	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cape	I-pers
,	O
November	O
22	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Lionell	B-pers
Lias	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver-hilted	O
Sword	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Shotan	I-pers
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Rudd	I-pers
,	O
January	O
13	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Shotan	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
last	O
,	O
my	O
Sword	O
was	O
stole	O
out	O
of	O
Rudd	B-place
's	I-place
Coffee-House	I-place
,	O
a	O
Jew	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
Buttons	O
,	O
Buckles	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
down	O
from	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
hung	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Boy	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
Jew	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
something	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
after	O
him	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Streets	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
with	O
the	O
Sword	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Sword	O
;	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
why	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Wife	O
and	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
must	O
pay	O
his	O
Rent	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Barrow	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Coffee	O
Room	O
when	O
the	O
Jew	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
Buttons	O
,	O
Buckles	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Buckles	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
called	O
upon	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
after	O
that	O
for	O
some	O
bitter	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Entry	O
putting	O
something	O
in	O
his	O
Bosom	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
drop	O
'd	O
his	O
Glove	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
readily	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
turned	O
himself	O
side-way	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
;	O
presently	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
if	O
the	O
Jew	O
has	O
not	O
taken	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
run	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
overtook	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Hedge-Lane	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Sword	O
between	O
his	O
Coat	O
and	O
Wastcoat	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Collar	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
begg	O
'd	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Sword	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
(	O
if	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
called	O
a	O
Defence	O
)	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Sword	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
Entry	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
stayed	O
a	O
little	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
any	O
Body	O
would	O
own	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Arnold	I-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twenty	O
three	O
Deal	O
Boards	O
,	O
value	O
23	O
s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Haydon	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
27	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
plain	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Hanson	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Daniel	B-pers
Beauforth	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Beaver	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
19	O
s.	O
a	O
Rose	O
Hatband	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
Dec.	O
19	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
a	O
Defect	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Obadiah	B-pers
Hanshaw	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Magnus	I-place
the	I-place
Martyr	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Leaden	O
Image	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Beachcroft	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
January	O
2	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Peter	I-place
's	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
14	O
lb	O
.	O
Leaden	O
Weight	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
,	O
January	O
5	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
appearing	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Peacock	I-pers
,	O
of	O
White	B-place
Fryers	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
,	O
December	O
20	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
keeps	O
a	O
publick	O
House	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
George	B-place
in	I-place
Water-Lane	I-place
,	O
)	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Drinking	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
about	O
three	O
Hours	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Person	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
paid	O
his	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
went	O
into	O
other	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
alone	O
with	O
the	O
Tankard	O
;	O
that	O
while	O
his	O
Wife	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Bar	O
for	O
Change	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
without	O
paying	O
his	O
Reckoning	O
;	O
his	O
Tankard	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
)	O
he	O
found	O
at	O
a	O
Pawn-brokers	O
,	O
who	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
appear	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Vickeris	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
George	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
sate	O
and	O
drank	O
together	O
at	O
one	O
Table	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
having	O
some	O
Friends	O
come	O
,	O
paid	O
his	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Tankard	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stayed	O
longer	O
,	O
and	O
moved	O
to	O
a	O
Table	O
next	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
,	O
the	O
Tankard	O
and	O
Prisoner	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
Mr	O
.	O
Waters	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
after	O
the	O
other	O
Person	O
left	O
his	O
Company	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stay	O
'd	O
near	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
have	O
the	O
Tankard	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
the	O
Minute	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
dark	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
which	O
way	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
left	O
the	O
Tankard	O
behind	O
him	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Peacock	I-pers
,	O
Anne	B-pers
Yeats	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
spoke	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
to	O
contradict	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Evidence	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
and	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Keys	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hackney	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Samuel	B-pers
Tyson	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Seal	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
January	O
12	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Tyson	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
this	O
Effect	O
,	O
On	O
Monday	O
was	O
seven	O
Night	O
,	O
about	O
Twelve	O
or	O
One	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
between	O
Kingsland	B-place
and	O
the	O
Cock	B-place
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Pistol	O
go	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
comes	O
a	O
Fellow	O
with	O
a	O
long	O
Horse	O
Pistol	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
you	O
,	O
your	O
Money	O
;	O
I	O
delivered	O
them	O
my	O
Watch	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
I	O
must	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Coach	O
,	O
they	O
wanted	O
my	O
Rings	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
had	O
given	O
them	O
all	O
-	O
My	O
Servant	O
had	O
a	O
large	O
Lanthorn	O
,	O
with	O
two	O
Candles	O
in	O
it	O
-	O
There	O
was	O
two	O
on	O
Horseback	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
on	O
Foot	O
upon	O
the	O
Causeway	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
to	O
my	O
Servant	B-pers
,	I-pers
D	I-pers
-	O
you	O
,	O
Dismount	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
will	O
shoot	O
you	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
both	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
but	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
Persons	O
;	O
Johnson	O
was	O
in	O
Business	O
till	O
within	O
this	O
five	O
Months	O
,	O
how	O
he	O
hath	O
lived	O
since	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
of	O
very	O
good	O
Friends	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
accused	O
of	O
this	O
,	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
before	O
Justice	O
Cook	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
meet	O
me	O
there	O
:	O
The	O
other	O
's	O
Father	O
was	O
a	O
Bricklayer	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
idle	O
young	O
Fellow	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
sorry	O
to	O
see	O
it	O
;	O
my	O
Coachman	O
was	O
shot	O
in	O
the	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
died	O
of	O
the	O
Wound	O
this	O
Morning	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Gibbins	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
Coming	O
from	O
Hackney	O
between	O
Kingsland	O
and	O
the	O
Cok	O
,	O
I	O
bore	O
a	O
Lanthorn	O
before	O
my	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
some	O
Horsemen	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
thought	O
,	O
advance	O
towards	O
me	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
up	O
they	O
viewed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
hind	O
Wheel	O
of	O
the	O
Chariot	O
,	O
they	O
fir	O
'd	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
shot	O
the	O
Coachman	O
in	O
the	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
died	O
this	O
Morning	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
had	O
shot	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
them	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
your	O
Money	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
your	O
Watch	O
and	O
Rings	O
;	O
my	O
Master	O
said	O
nothing	O
,	O
I	O
stood	O
close	O
with	O
my	O
Lanthorn	O
,	O
and	O
Johnson	O
was	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
Horsemen	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
Johnson	O
held	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
Dismount	O
;	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
at	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
looked	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
let	O
off	O
the	O
Pistol	O
in	O
my	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
very	O
hard	O
indeed	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
got	O
,	O
or	O
rather	O
tumbled	O
off	O
my	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
Get	O
up	O
,	O
Get	O
up	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
got	O
upon	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
rid	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
him	O
up	O
at	O
the	O
Turnpike	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Saddle	O
and	O
Bridle	O
were	O
lost	O
-	O
Keys	O
came	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
Night	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
's	O
at	O
Stoke	O
Newington	O
,	O
and	O
confessed	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
going	O
home	O
that	O
Night	O
with	O
Mother	O
Mare	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
-	O
It	O
put	O
me	O
into	O
a	O
Tremble	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
Home	O
for	O
a	O
Stick	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
might	O
fright	O
my	O
Wife	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
goes	O
without	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Keys	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
that	O
Robb	O
'd	O
my	O
Master	O
-	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
believe	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
Blunderbuss	O
I	O
had	O
Died	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
view	O
'd	O
me	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
more	O
then	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
kill	O
my	O
Master	O
;	O
and	O
since	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
great	O
a	O
Man	O
with	O
a	O
Blunderbuss	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
kill	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
wish	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
Johnson	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Johnson	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
held	O
the	O
Pistol	O
to	O
my	O
Head	O
,	O
the	O
Man	O
on	O
Foot	O
was	O
a	O
civil	O
Fellow	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
't	O
was	O
pity	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
-	O
I	O
see	O
Johnson	O
afterwards	O
in	O
Newington	O
Town	O
when	O
't	O
was	O
almost	O
Dusk	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
but	O
just	O
turn	O
'd	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
confin	O
'd	O
Keys	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
my	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
before	O
Justice	O
Cook	O
,	O
who	O
committed	O
him	O
to	O
Newgate	O
.	O
Keys	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
this	O
Evidence	O
in	O
Red-Lyon-Street	O
,	O
London	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
Circumstances	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
running	O
in	O
his	O
Head	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
Drunk	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
.	O
Gibbins	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
his	O
giving	O
Keys	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
him	O
the	O
Circumstances	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
Gibbins	O
was	O
ask	O
'd	O
some	O
plain	O
Questions	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
prevaricated	O
;	O
which	O
did	O
not	O
much	O
advance	O
the	O
Credit	O
of	O
his	O
Evidence	O
.	O
John	O
Brown	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
Keys	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Coach	O
and	O
Horses	O
at	O
Newington	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
shot	O
John	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
troubled	O
his	O
Conscience	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
rest	O
Night	O
nor	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
owed	O
him	O
a	O
Spleen	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
hindred	O
him	O
of	O
Business	O
-	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
that	O
Robbed	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
11	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
would	O
shoot	O
him	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
he	O
went	O
abroad	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
by	O
Sunday	O
-	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
called	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Gardener	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
-	O
indeed	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
Keys	O
to	O
have	O
gone	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
mad	O
;	O
he	O
held	O
in	O
this	O
strain	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
Company	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
denied	O
Part	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
denied	O
it	O
all	O
;	O
Keys	O
said	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
he	O
remember	O
'd	O
nothing	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
Brown	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
ever	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
other	O
times	O
?	O
Brown	O
answered	O
no	O
,	O
nor	O
was	O
ever	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
before	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
observed	O
that	O
what	O
Keys	O
said	O
at	O
the	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
was	O
not	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Johnson	O
.	O
Johnson	O
alledged	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
voluntarily	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
see	O
Johnson	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Se'night	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Captain	O
Howsons	B-pers
for	O
a	O
Walk	O
(	O
John	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
,	O
was	O
with	O
us	O
)	O
he	O
Rents	O
Part	O
of	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
Home	O
till	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
London	O
about	O
6	O
o'Clock	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
call	O
on	O
him	O
-	O
I	O
called	O
about	O
5	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
was	O
in	O
Bed	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Hackney	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
Mile	O
from	O
Shacklewell	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Hugget	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
Johnson	O
fourteen	O
or	O
fifteen	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
how	O
this	O
Story	O
came	O
of	O
his	O
Robbing	O
Mr.	O
Tyson	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
then	O
to	O
go	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Tyson	O
asked	O
how	O
such	O
a	O
Story	O
came	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Bed	O
with	O
his	O
Wife	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fastbrook	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
desired	O
Johnson	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
,	O
for	O
Guilty	O
,	O
or	O
not	O
Guilty	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
sent	O
to	O
Newgate	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
refused	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
before	O
the	O
Justices	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
discharg	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Warner	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
Johnson	O
from	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Father	O
and	O
Mother	O
were	O
honest	O
People	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
100	O
l.	O
worth	O
of	O
his	O
Goods	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
them	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
upon	O
his	O
leaving	O
off	O
Trade	O
he	O
paid	O
him	O
20	O
l.	O
William	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
Johnson	O
from	O
an	O
Infant	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
Cloth	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
he	O
work	O
'd	O
very	O
hard	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
received	O
Money	O
enough	O
to	O
support	O
him	O
without	O
taking	O
any	O
irregular	O
Methods	O
-	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
Johnson	O
for	O
about	O
16	O
Years	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
done	O
Business	O
for	O
him	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Reason	O
he	O
left	O
off	O
his	O
Business	O
was	O
,	O
because	O
his	O
Rent	O
was	O
too	O
dear	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
view	O
of	O
other	O
Business	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Grigg	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
Johnson	O
many	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
trusted	O
him	O
with	O
Business	O
,	O
and	O
since	O
he	O
left	O
off	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
paid	O
him	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
40	O
s.	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Collings	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Iles	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Pratt	I-pers
,	O
and	O
several	O
others	O
who	O
appear	O
'd	O
like	O
Persons	O
of	O
Credit	O
,	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Spurling	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
Keys	O
a	O
crazy	O
strange	O
Fellow	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
Swear	O
any	O
Lies	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
any	O
Money	O
he	O
would	O
get	O
drunk	O
.	O
Susanna	B-pers
Keys	I-pers
(	O
his	O
Mother	O
)	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
her	O
Son	O
was	O
at	O
Home	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
lies	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
being	O
Lame	O
,	O
he	O
assisted	O
her	O
in	O
getting	O
in	O
and	O
out	O
of	O
Bed	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
work	O
'd	O
with	O
Keys	O
about	O
a	O
Week	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
strange	O
crazy	O
Fellow	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
Keys	O
is	O
a	O
crazy	O
Fellow	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
Kinsman	O
that	O
keeps	O
a	O
publick	O
House	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
there	O
one	O
Evening	O
a	O
little	O
late	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
stay	O
all	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
refus	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
Keys	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
went	O
Home	O
that	O
Night	O
he	O
would	O
Rob	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
must	O
bring	O
some	O
Body	O
with	O
him	O
then	O
,	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
Brace	O
of	O
Pistols	O
in	O
his	O
Pockets	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
him	O
my	O
self	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
none	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Batmaker	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Keys	O
,	O
when	O
Sober	O
,	O
was	O
Crazy	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
Drunk	O
,	O
a	O
Madman	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
always	O
took	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
crazy	O
Fellow	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Crawford	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
knew	O
Keys	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
crazy	O
Lad	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
in	O
Drink	O
would	O
talk	O
Things	O
false	O
and	O
groundless	O
,	O
and	O
charge	O
himself	O
with	O
Crimes	O
he	O
never	O
did	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
Lodged	O
at	O
his	O
Mother	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
Drunk	O
he	O
would	O
talk	O
idly	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Haddock	I-pers
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
thirty-six	O
Guineas	O
,	O
one	O
Portugal	O
Piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
36	O
s.	O
one	O
Broad	O
Piece	O
,	O
value	O
23	O
s.	O
four	O
Moidores	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
Spanish	O
Pistoles	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Money	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Appleby	I-pers
,	O
October	O
5	O
.	O
1728	O
.	O
Mr.	O
King	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
On	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
October	O
was	O
Twelve-months	O
,	O
a	O
Man	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
Master	O
Applebec	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
a	O
small	O
Brass	O
Cock	O
for	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
Guinea	O
to	O
Change	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
Silver	O
enough	O
forwards	O
,	O
going	O
to	O
a	O
Draw	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
more	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Person	O
followed	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Drawer	O
,	O
not	O
knowing	O
then	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
Body	O
behind	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
whilst	O
I	O
was	O
looking	O
out	O
the	O
Change	O
,	O
a	O
Paper	O
,	O
wherein	O
the	O
Gold	O
was	O
,	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
his	O
Change	O
before	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
hastily	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
the	O
Gold	O
and	O
his	O
Change	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
of	O
a	O
Saturday	O
in	O
the	O
Forenoon	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
is	O
so	O
long	O
since	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
to	O
the	O
Man	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
middle	O
Aged	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
Haddock	O
's	O
Stature	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
I	O
stepp	O
'd	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
believ	O
'd	O
I	O
was	O
Robb	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
which	O
way	O
he	O
went	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Priest	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
On	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
October	O
was	O
Twelve-months	O
,	O
there	O
came	O
in	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
a	O
light-colour	O
'd	O
Wigg	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
a	O
small	O
Brass	O
Cock	O
,	O
't	O
was	O
about	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
wanted	O
Change	O
for	O
a	O
Guinea	O
;	O
Mr.	O
King	O
went	O
back	O
for	O
Change	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Person	O
followed	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
picking	O
Metal	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
;	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
his	O
Change	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
hastily	O
forward	O
,	O
and	O
almost	O
jumpt	O
over	O
my	O
Back	O
;	O
presently	O
Mr.	O
King	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
If	O
I	O
knew	O
which	O
way	O
the	O
Man	O
went	O
?	O
For	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
Robb	O
'd	O
him	O
of	O
some	O
Money	O
;	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Dowdell	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
About	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
October	O
was	O
Twelve-months	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Shop	O
,	O
Haddock	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
bought	O
a	O
Brass	O
Cock	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
stole	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
Pyke	O
,	O
with	O
that	O
we	O
all	O
run	O
over	O
Fleetditch-Bridge	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
to	O
Temple-Stairs	O
,	O
crossed	O
the	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
St.	O
George's-Fields	O
,	O
and	O
divided	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
my	O
part	O
was	O
18	O
l.	O
18	O
s.	O
there	O
was	O
thirty	O
six	O
Guineas	O
,	O
five	O
Moidores	O
,	O
two	O
Broads	O
,	O
four	O
half	O
Broads	O
,	O
four	O
Spanish	O
Pistoles	O
,	O
one	O
Portugal	O
Piece	O
,	O
value	O
36	O
s.	O
two	O
French	O
Pistoles	O
and	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
Quarter	O
Broads	O
;	O
we	O
divided	O
18	O
l.	O
18	O
s.	O
a-piece	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
about	O
12	O
d.	O
over	O
;	O
being	O
asked	O
,	O
what	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
House	O
it	O
was	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
Corner	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
remember	O
'd	O
it	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
often	O
gone	O
by	O
it	O
since	O
,	O
and	O
wished	O
he	O
had	O
as	O
much	O
Money	O
then	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
once	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
that	O
House	O
-	O
Haddock	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
what	O
colour	O
'd	O
Cloaths	O
he	O
had	O
on	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
light	O
colour	O
'd	O
Coat	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bedford	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Richard	B-pers
Haddock	I-pers
,	O
had	O
been	O
his	O
Tenant	O
about	O
twelve	O
Months	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
paid	O
him	O
his	O
Rent	O
very	O
well	O
-	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
came	O
to	O
upwards	O
of	O
a	O
100	O
l.	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
paid	O
him	O
50	O
l.	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Roberts	O
gave	O
his	O
Bond	O
for	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
heard	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
kept	O
any	O
disorderly	O
Hours	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Berry	O
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Haddock	O
came	O
to	O
lodge	O
with	O
me	O
Michaelmas	O
was	O
twelve	O
Months	O
;	O
and	O
was	O
so	O
Sick	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
for	O
three	O
Weeks	O
after	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
dizziness	O
in	O
his	O
Head	O
;	O
and	O
sometime	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
never	O
went	O
farther	O
than	O
into	O
the	O
Park	O
for	O
a	O
little	O
Air	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Roberts	O
recommended	O
him	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
lodged	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
till	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Bagnio	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Victualling	O
House	O
at	O
Charing-Cross	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Berry	O
Rents	O
an	O
Apartment	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
Richard	B-pers
Haddock	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
very	O
ill	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
Michaelmas	O
Day	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
recommended	O
him	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Berry	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
would	O
see	O
her	O
paid	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
troubled	O
with	O
Vapours	O
in	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
ill	O
near	O
three	O
Weeks	O
;	O
during	O
which	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
every	O
Day	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
bound	O
for	O
him	O
for	O
40	O
l.	O
and	O
lent	O
him	O
40	O
l.	O
more	O
;	O
being	O
asked	O
(	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
)	O
what	O
Business	O
Haddock	O
followed	O
heretofore	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Bailiff	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sometime	O
a	O
Box-keeper	O
at	O
the	O
Rose	O
near	O
Covent-Garden	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
never	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drest	O
For	O
three	O
Weeks	O
after	O
he	O
first	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Berry	O
's	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
he	O
ever	O
see	O
Dowdell	O
and	O
Haddock	O
together	O
but	O
at	O
Hazard	O
Tables	O
.	O
And	O
as	O
to	O
Rogers	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
Lodged	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
kept	O
a	O
Stall	O
at	O
his	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
Greens	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Porter	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
Wife	O
being	O
ill	O
,	O
Rogers	O
used	O
to	O
be	O
pretty	O
much	O
about	O
Home	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
her	O
Goods	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
believes	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
honest	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Elkerk	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
Lodges	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Robert	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
Haddock	O
came	O
there	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
every	O
Day	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
-	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
formerly	O
been	O
a	O
Marshal's-Court	O
Officer	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Deer	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Dowdell	O
several	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
that	O
several	O
Persons	O
were	O
committed	O
to	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
Dowdell	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
sorry	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
Dowdell	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
hang	O
a	O
Thousand	O
before	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
Hang	B-pers
'd	I-pers
himself	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
believed	O
that	O
one	O
Reason	O
for	O
his	O
Malice	O
against	O
Haddock	O
was	O
,	O
for	O
discovering	O
him	O
once	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
put	O
off	O
a	O
gilt	O
King	O
Edward	O
's	O
Shilling	O
for	O
a	O
Broad	O
Piece	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
(	O
a	O
former	O
Servant	O
of	O
Haddock	O
's	O
)	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Michaelmas	O
was	O
Twelve-months	O
,	O
Haddock	O
was	O
so	O
ill	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
Abroad	O
for	O
three	O
Weeks	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
call	O
and	O
see	O
him	O
every	O
Day	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Scoophorns	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
Sunday	O
to	O
ask	O
for	O
my	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Woman	O
say	O
to	O
Dowdell	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
here	O
;	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
sorry	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
would	O
save	O
his	O
own	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
Money	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
himself	O
an	O
Informer	O
;	O
ay	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
but	O
you	O
inform	O
against	O
honest	O
Men	O
;	O
Dowdell	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
hang	O
the	O
three	O
Regiments	O
of	O
Guards	O
before	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
Hanged	O
himself	O
.	O
Several	O
Persons	O
that	O
Haddock	O
had	O
dealt	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
,	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Richards	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
High	O
Constable	O
of	O
Westminster	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
heard	O
Dowdell	O
say	O
,	O
He	O
could	O
Impeach	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
more	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Everett	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
Hezekiah	O
Rawpeny	O
,	O
and	O
Anne	B-pers
German	I-pers
spoke	O
to	O
Rogers	O
's	O
Character	O
,	O
so	O
far	O
as	O
that	O
they	O
knew	O
no	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Williamson	B-pers
Goodman	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Goodbarn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Strand	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Henry	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Peeling	I-pers
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
9	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
Sept.	O
4	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
On	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
going	O
from	O
the	O
City	O
near	O
Chancery-Lane	O
end	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
Chancery-Lane	O
?	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
shew	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
wanting	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Hearn	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
shew	O
me	O
his	O
House	O
too	O
,	O
or	O
bring	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
he	O
used	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
Mr.	O
Hearn	O
's	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
carry	O
'd	O
me	O
above	O
his	O
House	O
a	O
pretty	O
way	O
,	O
however	O
,	O
upon	O
Enquiry	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
Mr.	O
Hearn	O
's	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
Home	O
;	O
afterwards	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
Mug	O
of	O
Ale	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
press	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
treat	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Wine	O
;	O
upon	O
his	O
being	O
so	O
importunate	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
One	O
Bell	O
Inn	O
behind	O
the	O
New	O
Church	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
half	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
but	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
,	O
I	O
paid	O
for	O
it	O
my	O
self	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Box	O
of	O
Lace	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
followed	O
me	O
Home	O
,	O
was	O
very	O
full	O
of	O
Talk	O
,	O
and	O
invited	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
his	O
Quarters	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
talk	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
Sodomitical	O
Practices	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
great	O
Persons	O
that	O
us	O
'd	O
that	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
so	O
far	O
as	O
to	O
undo	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
suffer	O
Death	O
before	O
I	O
would	O
admit	O
of	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
Gold	O
about	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
him	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
swear	O
Sodomy	O
against	O
me	O
;	O
then	O
seiz	O
'd	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
Collar	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
't	O
was	O
in	O
vain	O
to	O
resist	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
Money	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
9	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
)	O
from	O
me	O
by	O
Force	O
:	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
given	O
him	O
part	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
it	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
me	O
turn	O
my	O
Pocket	O
;	O
indeed	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
scarce	O
knew	O
what	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
glad	O
to	O
get	O
from	O
him	O
on	O
any	O
Terms	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
run	O
into	O
a	O
Baker	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
enquir	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
off	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Sunday	O
follo	O
wing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
with	O
a	O
pretended	O
Constable	O
to	O
take	O
me	O
up	O
for	O
Sodomy	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
Constable	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
ask	O
'd	O
some	O
trifling	O
Questions	O
,	O
as	O
,	O
who	O
spoke	O
first	O
?	O
whether	O
Mr.	O
Thompson	O
could	O
Read	O
or	O
Write	O
?	O
because	O
he	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
his	O
Directions	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
Mr.	O
Hearn	O
's	O
which	O
being	O
imperfect	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Thompson	O
said	O
was	O
the	O
Reason	O
of	O
his	O
shewing	O
it	O
,	O
not	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
read	O
it	O
himself	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
know	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
ever	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
from	O
Thursday	O
to	O
Saturday	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Thompson	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
;	O
because	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
hurry	O
'd	O
in	O
Business	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
time	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
fell	O
Apples	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
where	O
Mr.	O
Thompson	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Thompson	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
dogg	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
a	O
Constable	O
-	O
A	O
Constable	O
,	O
said	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
lift	O
up	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
struck	O
Mr.	O
Thompson	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
avoided	O
the	O
Blow	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Thompson	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
person	O
to	O
Aid	O
him	O
Home	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
Robb	O
'd	O
him	O
already	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
further	O
Designs	O
he	O
had	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Ray	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Thompson	O
come	O
in	O
very	O
much	O
affrighted	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
a	O
sorry	O
Fellow	O
had	O
dogg	O
'd	O
him	O
from	O
the	O
One	O
Bell	O
Inn	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Ballandine	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
Sunday	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
broke	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Round-House	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
re-taken	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
rather	O
have	O
lost	O
his	O
Right-hand	O
,	O
than	O
have	O
been	O
concern	O
'd	O
against	O
Mr.	O
Thompson	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Illeiff	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
how	O
he	O
could	O
use	O
Mr.	O
Thompson	O
so	O
?	O
And	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
was	O
sorry	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
nothing	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
,	O
adding	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
clear	O
Mr.	O
Thompson	O
in	O
all	O
Respects	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Pointz	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Thompson	O
had	O
Lodged	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
near	O
twenty	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
a	O
fair	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
deserved	O
well	O
from	O
every	O
Body	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
other	O
Gentlemen	O
and	O
Persons	O
of	O
Reputation	O
that	O
gave	O
Mr.	O
Thompson	O
an	O
extraordinary	O
Character	O
,	O
for	O
being	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
an	O
unblemish	O
'd	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
a	O
very	O
trifling	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
the	O
Boy	O
that	O
draws	O
Wine	O
at	O
the	O
Inn	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Lodg	O
'd	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Thompson	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
stay	O
'd	O
about	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
half	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Thompson	O
paid	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
see	O
any	O
Company	O
come	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
he	O
ever	O
see	O
him	O
suddled	O
but	O
knew	O
that	O
he	O
writ	O
sometimes	O
a	O
Day	O
or	O
two	O
together	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Room	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
no	O
Body	O
to	O
call	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Norman	I-pers
,	O
in	O
an	O
open	O
Field	O
near	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
3	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
November	O
27	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Norman	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Newington-Green	B-place
,	O
near	O
Rosemary-Branch	B-place
,	O
in	O
a	O
large	O
Field	O
by	O
Sir	O
George	B-pers
Whitmores	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
be	O
fore	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
;	O
two	O
Men	O
overtook	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
pass	O
'd	O
by	O
me	O
;	O
presently	O
afterwards	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
three	O
Men	O
;	O
soon	O
after	O
the	O
three	O
Men	O
were	O
gone	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
who	O
had	O
first	O
pass	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
turned	O
upon	O
me	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
puts	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
my	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
worth	O
taking	O
,	O
he	O
Swore	O
D	O
-	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
deliver	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
shoot	O
me	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
gave	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
some	O
Half	O
pence	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
how	O
many	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
towards	O
London	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
shoot	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
followed	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
run	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
run	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
turned	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Men	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Dexter	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
overtook	O
Norman	O
,	O
and	O
pass	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
you	O
,	O
why	O
wo	O
n't	O
you	O
Rob	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
we	O
did	O
we	O
should	O
be	O
took	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
we	O
met	O
three	O
Men	O
,	O
then	O
stay	O
'd	O
till	O
they	O
were	O
past	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
Norman	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
us	O
;	O
I	O
held	O
the	O
Pistol	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
search	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
8	O
d.	O
in	O
Half	O
pence	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
;	O
and	O
had	O
very	O
little	O
Acquaintance	O
with	O
Dexter	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
asked	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
conversed	O
together	O
?	O
to	O
which	O
Dexter	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
at	O
his	O
own	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
Potter	O
's	O
Shop	O
in	O
White-Cross	O
Street	O
;	O
Dexter	O
further	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
he	O
discover	O
'd	O
this	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
,	O
and	O
he	O
got	O
Thomas	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
to	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
and	O
Porter	O
in	O
Crowder's-well	O
Alley	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
them	O
both	O
taken	O
together	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Pistol	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
by	O
Willis	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
Pistol	O
they	O
Robb	O
'd	O
with	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Day	O
he	O
caused	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
made	O
an	O
Appointment	O
to	O
Rob	O
that	O
Evening	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Samuel	B-pers
Dexter	I-pers
sent	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
three	O
Mariners	O
in	O
For-Street	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
ill	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
make	O
a	O
Discovery	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
advised	O
Dexter	O
to	O
go	O
before	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
Thomas	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
and	O
Porter	O
in	O
Crowder	O
's	O
well-Ally	O
,	O
being	O
fix	O
'd	O
there	O
by	O
Dexter	O
,	O
while	O
they	O
waited	O
at	O
the	O
Weoll-Pack	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Day	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
Friend	O
;	O
and	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
meet	O
with	O
Dexter	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
and	O
Porter	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
his	O
Brother	O
came	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
called	O
him	O
in	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
Dexter	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
brought	O
in	O
three	O
Men	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
drove	O
a	O
Coach	O
for	O
his	O
Livelihood	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
for	O
the	O
Robbery	O
he	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Dexterhad	O
been	O
in	O
Newgate	O
eight	O
Years	O
ago	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
a	O
Coblers	O
Stall	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Persons	O
of	O
Credit	O
,	O
and	O
Reputation	O
;	O
who	O
spoke	O
to	O
their	O
Characters	O
,	O
they	O
being	O
both	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
from	O
their	O
Infancy	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
lived	O
a	O
reputable	O
Life	O
;	O
they	O
drove	O
Coaches	O
for	O
their	O
Livelihoods	O
.	O
and	O
that	O
Richard	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
had	O
kept	O
a	O
Coach	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
(	O
a	O
Hackney	O
Coach	O
)	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
always	O
were	O
accounted	O
honest	O
Fellows	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Henry	B-pers
Mann	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
them	O
fourteen	O
or	O
fifteen	O
Years	O
;	O
that	O
Thomas	O
had	O
been	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
always	O
bore	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hargrove	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
knew	O
Thomas	O
from	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
drove	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
Lodged	O
with	O
him	O
till	O
within	O
,	O
or	O
about	O
three	O
Months	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
knew	O
them	O
many	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
both	O
been	O
his	O
Servants	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
James	B-pers
Waller	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
the	O
young	O
Lad	O
many	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Bacon	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Capper	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Annis	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Byfield	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Blackley	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Bellrs	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Tudor	B-pers
Hughs	I-pers
,	O
spoke	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
,	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Caleb	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
in	O
an	O
open	O
Field	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Callimanco	O
Shoes	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
an	O
Iron	O
Punch	O
,	O
value	O
2d	O
.	O
and	O
18	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
November	O
29	O
.	O
Caleb	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
this	O
Effect	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Shoemaker	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
November	O
about	O
Seven	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
going	O
from	O
my	O
own	O
House	O
in	O
Hodgsdon-Market	O
into	O
the	O
Town	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
;	O
I	O
chose	O
to	O
go	O
the	O
back	O
way	O
,	O
as	O
being	O
much	O
the	O
cleanest	O
,	O
having	O
went	O
that	O
way	O
very	O
often	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
met	O
with	O
any	O
Damage	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
past	O
the	O
Haberdasher	O
's	O
Hospital	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
got	O
upon	O
the	O
Causeway	O
that	O
leads	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Fairchild	O
's	O
,	O
not	O
far	O
from	O
the	O
Red-Lyon	B-place
Alehouse	I-place
;	O
I	O
heard	O
some	O
Persons	O
advance	O
nearer	O
,	O
making	O
a	O
humming	O
Noise	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
under	O
the	O
less	O
Apprehension	O
of	O
Danger	O
;	O
immediately	O
comes	O
up	O
three	O
Men	O
,	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
clapt	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
one	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
Side	O
,	O
another	O
on	O
the	O
Left	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
me	O
till	O
the	O
third	O
took	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Women	O
's	O
Shoes	O
,	O
an	O
Iron	O
Punch	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Medal	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
took	O
a	O
Letter	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
he	O
knew	O
how	O
to	O
direct	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
following	O
I	O
receiv	O
'd	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
Dexter	O
-	O
the	O
Letter	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
and	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
as	O
follows	O
.	O
Sir	O
,	O
This	O
comes	O
to	O
acquaint	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
inform	O
you	O
,	O
who	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
Robb	O
'd	O
you	O
,	O
come	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
Bearer	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
will	O
oblige	O
your	O
Humble	O
Servant	O
,	O
Dec.	O
6	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Dexter	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Warwick	O
procceded	O
,	O
-	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
Dexter	O
into	O
the	O
Lodge	O
;	O
he	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
they	O
Robb	O
'd	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Place	O
,	O
then	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
the	O
Medal	O
;	O
the	O
Shoes	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
were	O
pawn	O
'd	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Wives	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
what	O
they	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
Shoes	O
?	O
but	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
own	O
they	O
had	O
them	O
,	O
or	O
were	O
the	O
Persons	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Dexter	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
On	O
Saturday	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
I	O
met	O
near	O
the	O
Bull-Head	O
in	O
Jewin-Street	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
Robb	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Warwick	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
18	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
;	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
held	O
the	O
Pistol	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Shoes	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Bosom	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
and	O
Porter	O
and	O
shar	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
four	O
half	O
Crowns	O
,	O
and	O
8	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
small	O
Silver	O
;	O
Richard	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
had	O
the	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
allow	O
'd	O
us	O
twelve	O
pence	O
a-piece	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
December	O
I	O
discover	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Willis	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
were	O
to	O
have	O
gone	O
out	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Dexter	O
said	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
was	O
never	O
concern	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
any	O
Robbery	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Dancing	O
Master	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
That	O
Dexter	O
caution	O
'd	O
them	O
about	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
having	O
Pen-Knives	O
in	O
their	O
Pockets	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
searching	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
no	O
Arms	O
about	O
them	O
,	O
neither	O
Powder	O
nor	O
Ball	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
(	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
)	O
said	O
,	O
his	O
Landlord	O
where	O
he	O
Lodg	O
'd	O
,	O
could	O
prove	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
that	O
Day	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hooker	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Pastry-Cook	O
's	O
Shop	O
near	O
Barbican	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
Home	O
till	O
between	O
Five	O
and	O
Six	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
November	O
29	O
;	O
his	O
Wife	O
being	O
a	O
Washing	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
fetch	O
'd	O
her	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
assisted	O
her	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
kept	O
good	O
Hours	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
or	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
notwithstanding	O
I	O
enquir	O
'd	O
strictly	O
into	O
his	O
Character	O
before	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
as	O
a	O
Lodger	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
Persons	O
of	O
Reputation	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
good	O
Characters	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
the	O
former	O
Trial	O
;	O
but	O
none	O
that	O
contradicted	O
the	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Nowland	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Westwood	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Molton	I-pers
,	O
in	O
an	O
open	O
Field	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
4	O
s.	O
2	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
November	O
23	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Mary	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
November	O
23	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
one	O
Shilling	O
,	O
November	O
23	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
fourth	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Anne	B-pers
Nailor	I-pers
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
Nov.	O
23	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Molton	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
Coming	O
from	O
Lime-House	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Butler	O
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
Anne	B-pers
Nailor	I-pers
;	O
Anne	B-pers
Nailor	I-pers
and	O
I	O
were	O
about	O
twenty	O
Yards	O
before	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Field	B-place
near	I-place
Stepney	I-place
Meeting-House	I-place
;	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
Men	O
come	O
running	O
towards	O
us	O
,	O
but	O
knew	O
not	O
how	O
to	O
escape	O
them	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
were	O
Thieves	O
;	O
presently	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Pistol	O
fir	O
'd	O
behind	O
me	O
,	O
then	O
Nowland	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
presented	O
Pistol	O
to	O
my	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
would	O
shoot	O
me	O
through	O
the	O
Body	O
that	O
Minute	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
him	O
off	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
heard	O
my	O
Friend	O
was	O
engag	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
fight	O
my	O
self	O
,	O
so	O
gave	O
him	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
Shillings	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Butler	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
shall	O
take	O
this	O
Fellow	O
,	O
upon	O
that	O
Nowland	O
quitted	O
me	O
to	O
save	O
his	O
Companion	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Butler	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
being	O
kill	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Crisp	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bowling-Green	O
House	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
some	O
Assistance	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
bound	O
;	O
't	O
was	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
I	O
got	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
Mr.	O
Butler	O
came	O
there	O
very	O
much	O
wounded	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Wounds	O
were	O
dress	O
'd	O
-	O
'T	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
Moon-light	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
Nowland	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
Coat	O
with	O
the	O
Cape	O
button	O
'd	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
very	O
same	O
Coat	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
on	O
now	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
Person	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
Robb	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Lime-House	O
with	O
my	O
Wife	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Molton	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Wife	O
's	O
Sister	O
;	O
't	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
Moon-light	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
Path	O
by	O
Reason	O
of	O
the	O
Water	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
low	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
Ditches	O
on	O
both	O
,	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
abreast	O
;	O
and	O
my	O
little	O
Boy	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
us	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
Men	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
believ	O
'd	O
they	O
were	O
Thieves	O
;	O
and	O
presently	O
Westwood	O
comes	O
up	O
,	O
presented	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
you	O
,	O
your	O
Money	O
,	O
Sir	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
my	O
self	O
a	O
short	O
turn	O
from	O
the	O
Pistol	O
,	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
;	O
the	O
Pistol	O
went	O
off	O
,	O
wounded	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
tore	O
my	O
Coat	O
Sleeve	O
all	O
to	O
Pieces	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
something	O
under	O
Westwood	O
's	O
Coat	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
apprehend	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Tuck	O
afterwards	O
;	O
Nowland	O
came	O
up	O
but	O
slowly	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
you	O
,	O
why	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
give	O
him	O
your	O
Money	O
,	O
then	O
both	O
came	O
upon	O
me	O
;	O
D	O
-	O
you	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
two	O
against	O
one	O
is	O
too	O
much	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
me	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Ditch	O
,	O
and	O
Westwood	O
kept	O
Stabbing	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
shifted	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Wife	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
do	O
n't	O
kill	O
my	O
Husband	O
;	O
Westwood	O
said	O
,	O
are	O
not	O
you	O
a	O
Barbarous	O
Dog	O
not	O
to	O
give	O
us	O
your	O
Money	O
?	O
so	O
I'gave	O
them	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
a	O
Shilling	O
-	O
Nowland	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
kill	O
him	O
Westwood	O
,	O
he	O
swore	O
D	O
-	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
;	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
Stab	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
desired	O
this	O
Evidence	O
might	O
be	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
up	O
others	O
on	O
Account	O
of	O
this	O
Robbery	O
?	O
-	O
Mr.	O
Butler	O
denied	O
it	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Nailor	I-pers
thus	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
my	O
Brother	O
,	O
Sister	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Molton	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
